<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10107853</Id><Name>Hotel Koenigshof Garmisch-Partenkirchen</Name><Region><Id>116538</Id><Name>Garmisch-Partenkirchen</Name><CityId>16640</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>St. Martin-Strasse 4</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Garmisch-Partenkirchen</City><State /><Zip>82467</Zip><Country>Germany</Country><Tel>0049 (0)88219140</Tel><Fax>0049 (0)8821914400</Fax><Email>info@hotel-koenigshof-garmisch.de</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/Q7Ufront.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/Q7Uthumbfront.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2668</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/Q7Ubed.JPG</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/Q7Uthumbbed.JPG</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1661</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/Q7Umap.JPG</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/Q7Uthumbmap.JPG</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2154</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/Q7Ufront.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/Q7Uthumbfront.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2668</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/Q7Ubed.JPG</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/Q7Uthumbbed.JPG</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1661</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/Q7Umap.JPG</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/Q7Uthumbmap.JPG</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2154</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Hotel Königshof places you in the heart of Garmisch-Partenkirchen, convenient to Casino Garmisch-Partenkirchen and Garmisch-Partenkirchen Ski Resort. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Richard Strauss Institute and Werdenfels Museum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of 91 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and complimentary newspapers, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;After a day on the slopes, enjoy recreational amenities including a health club and a sauna. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and babysitting/childcare. You'll be on the slopes in no time with the complimentary ski shuttle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hotel Königshof. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, express check-out, and complimentary newspapers in the lobby. Planning an event in Garmisch-Partenkirchen? This hotel has facilities measuring 1615 square feet (150 square meters), including meeting rooms. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hotel Königshof. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; After a day on the slopes, enjoy recreational amenities including a health club and a sauna. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and babysitting/childcare. You'll be on the slopes in no time with the complimentary ski shuttle. &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of 91 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and complimentary newspapers, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Hotel Königshof places you in the heart of Garmisch-Partenkirchen, convenient to Casino Garmisch-Partenkirchen and Garmisch-Partenkirchen Ski Resort. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Richard Strauss Institute and Werdenfels Museum. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Casino Garmisch-Partenkirchen - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Richard Strauss Institute - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Werdenfels Museum - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum Aschenbrenner - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Garmisch-Partenkirchen Ski Resort - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Olympic Hill - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Werdenfels Castle Ruins - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kramerplateauweg Hiking Trail - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Partnach Gorge - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;King's House on Schachen - 8.2 km / 5.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ettal Abbey - 8.5 km / 5.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Zugspitze - 11.7 km / 7.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kranzberg Cable Car - 13 km / 8.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Leutaschklamm Gorge - 13.2 km / 8.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Linderhof Palace - 13.6 km / 8.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Königshof is Munich (MUC-Franz Josef Strauss Intl.) - 108.7 km / 67.6 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Quality Hotel Koenigshof is Munich (MUC-Franz Josef Strauss Intl.) - 109 km / 67.7 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseDining</Code><Text>Hotel restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HotelSafe</Code><Text>Central hotel safe</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>