<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10107845</Id><Name>InterCityHotel Leipzig</Name><Region><Id>16597</Id><Name>Leipzig</Name><CityId>16597</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Troendlinring 2</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Leipzig</City><State /><Zip>04105</Zip><Country>Germany</Country><Tel>0049 (0)341308661707</Tel><Fax>0049 (0)341308661900</Fax><Email>leipzig@intercityhotel.de</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/L9Ifront.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/L9Ithumbfront.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1918</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/L9Ibed.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/L9Ithumbbed.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2294</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/L9Imap.JPG</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/L9Ithumbmap.JPG</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2270</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;InterCityHotel Leipzig is in the heart of Leipzig, walking distance from Museum of Fine Arts and Leipzig City History Museum - Neubau. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Naschmarkt and Barfussgasse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 166 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities, which include wireless Internet access (surcharge) and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of InterCityHotel Leipzig, or stop in at a snack bar/deli. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Full breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, express check-in, and express check-out. Planning an event in Leipzig? This hotel has 2270 square feet (211 square meters) of space consisting of conference space and meeting rooms. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of InterCityHotel Leipzig, or stop in at a snack bar/deli. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Full breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities, which include wireless Internet access (surcharge) and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 166 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>InterCityHotel Leipzig is in the heart of Leipzig, walking distance from Museum of Fine Arts and Leipzig City History Museum - Neubau. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Naschmarkt and Barfussgasse. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Museum of Fine Arts - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Leipzig City History Museum - Neubau - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Naschmarkt - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Barfussgasse - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Leipzig's Old Town Hall - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum Zum Arabischen Coffe Baum - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Leipzig Market Square - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Leipzig Zoo - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maedler Passage - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Runde Ecke Memorial Museum - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Nicholas Church - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stadtisches Kaufhaus - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Leipzig University - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Thomas Church - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bach Museum - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for InterCityHotel Leipzig is Leipzig (LEJ-Leipzig - Halle) - 13.3 km / 8.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseDining</Code><Text>Hotel restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HandicapAccessible</Code><Text>Handicap accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditionedRooms</Code><Text>Air-conditioned rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>