<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10113859</Id><Name>Kristall</Name><Region><Id>20997</Id><Name>Central</Name><CityId>17117</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Via General Cantore 6/8</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Milan</City><State /><Zip>20094</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel>0039 0245100270</Tel><Fax>0039 0245100212</Fax><Email>info@hotelkristallcorsico.it</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/K35front.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/K35thumbfront.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1944</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/K35bed.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/K35thumbbed.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1858</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/K35map.JPG</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/K35thumbmap.JPG</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1548</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Kristall in Corsico, you'll be close to Parrocchia Sant'Ambrogio Trezzano and Domus Academy. This hotel is within close proximity of Chiesa di San Cristoforo Sul Naviglio and San Carlo Borromeo Hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 45 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare. Additional amenities include a television in the lobby and tour/ticket assistance. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite from a snack bar/deli, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, dry cleaning/laundry services, and multilingual staff. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite from a snack bar/deli, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare. Additional amenities include a television in the lobby and tour/ticket assistance. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 45 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Kristall in Corsico, you'll be close to Parrocchia Sant'Ambrogio Trezzano and Domus Academy. This hotel is within close proximity of Chiesa di San Cristoforo Sul Naviglio and San Carlo Borromeo Hospital. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Parrocchia Sant'Ambrogio Trezzano - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Domus Academy - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chiesa di San Cristoforo Sul Naviglio - 4.1 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Carlo Borromeo Hospital - 4.1 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Assago Forum - 4.6 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;IULM University - 4.6 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Teatro Della Luna - 4.6 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Centro Commerciale MilanoFiori - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Siro Stadium - 5.2 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Teatro Ventaglio Nazionale - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Siro Race Course - 5.7 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Boscoincitta - 5.7 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Giuseppe Hospital - 6 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Leonardo da Vinci Museum of Science and Technology - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Porta Ticinese - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Kristall is Milan (LIN-Linate) - 13.8 km / 8.6 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CoffeeTeaMaker</Code><Text>Tea and Coffee maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseDining</Code><Text>Hotel restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HandicapAccessible</Code><Text>Handicap accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditionedRooms</Code><Text>Air-conditioned rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HotelSafe</Code><Text>Central hotel safe</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>