<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10113461</Id><Name>San Giuseppe</Name><Region><Id>20974</Id><Name>Otranto</Name><CityId>17105</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Via Ottocento Martiri 60</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Otranto</City><State /><Zip>73028</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel>0039 0836806029</Tel><Fax>0039 0836806335</Fax><Email>info@hotelsangiuseppeotranto.it</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/6GOfront.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/6GOthumbfront.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1587</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/6GObed.JPG</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/6GOthumbbed.JPG</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1417</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/6GOmap.JPG</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/6GOthumbmap.JPG</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1446</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The 4-star San Giuseppe hotel is a located in the historical city of Otranto with the picturesque surroundings of the Adriatic sea. The hotel is set in an ideal location for exploring the beautiful beaches of the Adriatic Sea and a great starting point to discover the historical folk traditions, Italian cuisine and the ancient villages of the surrounding region. The renovated hotel is ready to receive visitors after the extraordinary refurbishment which has transformed the 16-century farmhouse into the contemporary and elegant hotel it is now. The hotel has 19 rooms furnished to a high standard. Many have retained some original features such as barrel vaults. Standard rooms are, however, situated in the modern part of the hotel. All rooms come with a double bed and a spacious bathroom. Modern amenities include a 32-inch LCD TV with SKY Gold satellite channels and high speed internet connection. The hotelâs spa includes a Jacuzzi, Turkish bath, relaxation area, massage rooms and gym. Breakfast is served in the historical part of the building, in a breakfast room with original vaulted ceilings. There is no restaurant in the hotel, however, there are numerous restaurants within walking distance. The town centre is situated at a short distance from the hotel and shuttle service is provided to and from the main airports of Puglia, Brindisi and Bari or to the railway stations.
Otranto, Italy - for all arrivals from 01/07/2011 - the local Government has introduced a new city tax which will be levied on all visitors (except for children under 12 years old).
The fees are as follows:
- €2.00 PER PERSON PER NIGHT for stays in 4 star hotels (charged up to 7 nights)
Please note: Travco rates are EXCLUSIVE of this tax so the tax has to be paid by the PASSENGER DIRECTLY at the hotel before the end of the stay. Agents must advise their clients of this fact.
The tax is also payable even if the accommodation was booked and paid for before 1 July 2011.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FitnessFacility</Code><Text>Fitness facility</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HandicapAccessible</Code><Text>Handicap accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditionedRooms</Code><Text>Air-conditioned rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HotelSafe</Code><Text>Central hotel safe</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>