<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>101178</Id><Name>Acta Splendid</Name><Region><Id>21149</Id><Name>Eixample - Financial District</Name><CityId>18350</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>MUNTANER 2 08011 BARCELONA</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Barcelona SPAIN</City><State /><Zip /><Country>Spain</Country><Tel>34-93-4512142</Tel><Fax>34-93-3231684</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>41.3839924</Latitude><Longitude>2.1631583</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/BCN-ACT1hotel_Exterior_1.jpg</Url><Width>287</Width><Height>288</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/BCN-ACT1hotel_Exterior_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>60</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>80</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Barcelona (El Raval), Acta Splendid is minutes from Placa Universitat and Barcelona Museum of Contemporary Art.  This hotel is close to Casa Batllo and Palau de la Musica Catalana.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 40 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and gift shops/newsstands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour front desk, multilingual staff, and luggage storage.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2:00 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and gift shops/newsstands. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 40 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Barcelona (El Raval), Acta Splendid is minutes from Placa Universitat and Barcelona Museum of Contemporary Art.  This hotel is close to Casa Batllo and Palau de la Musica Catalana. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Placa Universitat - 0.2 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Barcelona Museum of Contemporary Art - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Centre de Cultura Contemporania de Barcelona - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Barcelona - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sant Antoni Market - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cafe-Teatre Llantiol - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Francisco Godia Foundation - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Placa de Catalunya - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Boqueria Market - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hospital de la Santa Creu de Barcelona - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Teatre Romea - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Virreina Palace - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Casa Golferichs - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rambla del Raval - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Roman Tombs - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Acta Splendid is Barcelona (BCN-Barcelona Intl.) - 11.5 km / 7.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>