<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10124486</Id><Name>Assambleya Nikitskaya</Name><Region><Id>18146</Id><Name>Moscow</Name><CityId>18146</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Bolshaya Nikitskaya 12/2</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Moscow</City><State /><Zip>125009</Zip><Country>Russia</Country><Tel>007 4959335001</Tel><Fax>007 4952215410</Fax><Email>nikitskaya@assambleya-hotels.ru</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1136/15/54/71/155471_1001120943002373095.jpg</Url><Width>312</Width><Height>235</Height><Bytes>10474</Bytes><Caption>Guest Room</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1136/15/54/71/155471_1001120943002373095thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>92</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2117</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1136/15/54/71/155471_1001120946002373169.jpg</Url><Width>312</Width><Height>235</Height><Bytes>11185</Bytes><Caption>Guest Room</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1136/15/54/71/155471_1001120946002373169thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>92</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2027</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1136/15/54/71/155471_1005211705003049534.jpg</Url><Width>312</Width><Height>235</Height><Bytes>11779</Bytes><Caption>Meeting Room</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1136/15/54/71/155471_1005211705003049534thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>92</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2238</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1136/15/54/71/155471_1201152356005832546.jpg</Url><Width>312</Width><Height>233</Height><Bytes>10353</Bytes><Caption>155471_1201152356005832546</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1136/15/54/71/155471_1201152356005832546thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2036</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1136/15/54/71/155471_14042814320019226156.jpg</Url><Width>312</Width><Height>233</Height><Bytes>15163</Bytes><Caption>155471_14042814320019226156</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1136/15/54/71/155471_14042814320019226156thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2664</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Assambleya Nikitskaya Hotel, you'll be centrally located in Moscow, steps from Moscow Conservatory and minutes from St Andrew's Anglican Church.  This 4-star hotel is close to Moscow Kremlin and Red Square.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 29 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Your room comes with a Tempur-Pedic bed. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have rainfall showerheads and complimentary toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and gift shops/newsstands. This hotel also features a television in the lobby, tour/ticket assistance, and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility. Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the area shuttle (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include high-speed (wired) Internet access (surcharge), a business center, and limo/town car service. Planning an event in Moscow? This hotel has facilities measuring 12 square feet (1 square meters), including meeting rooms. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and gift shops/newsstands. This hotel also features a television in the lobby, tour/ticket assistance, and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility. Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the area shuttle (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 29 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Your room comes with a Tempur-Pedic bed. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have rainfall showerheads and complimentary toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Assambleya Nikitskaya Hotel, you'll be centrally located in Moscow, steps from Moscow Conservatory and minutes from St Andrew's Anglican Church.  This 4-star hotel is close to Moscow Kremlin and Red Square. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Moscow Conservatory - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Andrew's Anglican Church - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vernadsky State Geological Museum - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Manege - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Moscow Arts Theatre - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gogol House - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Manezh Square - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Alexander Gardens - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Yury Dolgoruky Monument - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tomb of the Unknown Soldier - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Theatre on Malaya Bronnaya - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gorky House Museum - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Greater Church of the Ascension - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;War of 1812 Museum - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Resurrection Gate - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Assambleya Nikitskaya Hotel is Moscow (SVO-Sheremetyevo) - 26.3 km / 16.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HandicapAccessible</Code><Text>Handicap accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditionedRooms</Code><Text>Air-conditioned rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HotelSafe</Code><Text>Central hotel safe</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>19</Rank></HotelElement>