<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10124704</Id><Name>The St. Regis Moscow Nikolskaya</Name><Region><Id>18146</Id><Name>Moscow</Name><CityId>18146</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>St. Nikolskaya 12</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Moscow</City><State /><Zip>109012</Zip><Country>Russia</Country><Tel>007 4959677776</Tel><Fax>007 4952872720</Fax><Email>reservations.moscow1@stregis.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/MOW-99hotel_Lobby_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>239</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/MOW-99hotel_Lobby_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/MOW-99hotel_Restaurant_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/MOW-99hotel_Restaurant_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/MOW-99hotel_Lobby_2.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/MOW-99hotel_Lobby_2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/MOW-99hotel_Guest_Room_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>243</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/MOW-99hotel_Guest_Room_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The St. Regis Moscow Nikolskaya Hotel is in the heart of Moscow, walking distance from Polytechnical Museum and FSB Museum.  This 5-star hotel is close to Red Square and St. Basil's Cathedral.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 210 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take time to pamper yourself with a visit to the full-service spa. If you're looking for recreational opportunities, you'll find a health club, an indoor pool, and a 24-hour fitness center. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and wedding services. Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the area shuttle (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Relax with a refreshing drink at one of the 2 bars/lounges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour business center, express check-out, and complimentary newspapers in the lobby. Planning an event in Moscow? This hotel has 4304 square feet (400 square meters) of space consisting of a conference center, conference space, and meeting rooms. For a surcharge, guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle (available on request) and a train station pick-up service.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is Noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Relax with a refreshing drink at one of the 2 bars/lounges. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take time to pamper yourself with a visit to the full-service spa. If you're looking for recreational opportunities, you'll find a health club, an indoor pool, and a 24-hour fitness center. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and wedding services. Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the area shuttle (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 210 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The St. Regis Moscow Nikolskaya Hotel is in the heart of Moscow, walking distance from Polytechnical Museum and FSB Museum.  This 5-star hotel is close to Red Square and St. Basil's Cathedral. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Polytechnical Museum - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;FSB Museum - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maly Theatre - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;TSUM Department Store - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bolshoi Theatre - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Revolution Square - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;War of 1812 Museum - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sanduny Bath House - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kazan Cathedral - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;GUM Department Store - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Resurrection Gate - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gulag History Museum - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place of Skulls - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;State Historical Museum - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gostiny Dvor Arcade - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The St. Regis Moscow Nikolskaya Hotel is Moscow (SVO-Sheremetyevo) - 26.5 km / 16.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CoffeeTeaMaker</Code><Text>Tea and Coffee maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FitnessFacility</Code><Text>Fitness facility</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseDining</Code><Text>Hotel restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HandicapAccessible</Code><Text>Handicap accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditionedRooms</Code><Text>Air-conditioned rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HotelSafe</Code><Text>Central hotel safe</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>