<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>102483</Id><Name>Carlemany</Name><Region><Id>21182</Id><Name>Girona Area</Name><CityId>18373</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>PZ. MIGUEL SANTALO</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>GIRONA</City><State /><Zip>17002</Zip><Country>SPAIN</Country><Tel>972211212</Tel><Fax>972214994</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>41.9780945</Latitude><Longitude>2.8190749</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1040703-hotelcarlmeny_ext_Thumbnailed.jpg</Url><Width>70</Width><Height>70</Height><Bytes>1925</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1040703-hotelcarlmeny_ext_Thumbnailed.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1923</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Carlemany places you in the heart of Girona, convenient to Museum of Cinema and Girona Cathedral.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Eiffel Bridge and Rafael Maso Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 89 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature designer toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include safes and desks, and you can also request irons/ironing boards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at one of the hotel's dining establishments, which include 2 restaurants and a coffee shop/café. From your room, you can also access room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour business center, express check-in, and express check-out. Planning an event in Girona? This hotel has 6458 square feet (600 square meters) of space consisting of conference space, meeting rooms, and a meeting room.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at one of the hotel's dining establishments, which include 2 restaurants and a coffee shop/café. From your room, you can also access room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 89 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature designer toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include safes and desks, and you can also request irons/ironing boards.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Carlemany places you in the heart of Girona, convenient to Museum of Cinema and Girona Cathedral.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Eiffel Bridge and Rafael Maso Foundation. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Museum of Cinema - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eiffel Bridge - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rafael Maso Foundation - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jewish History Museum - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Walls of Girona - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;City History Museum - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Girona's Museum of Art - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Girona Cathedral - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fira de Girona Convention Center - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of Sant Feliu - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Arab Baths - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Monestir de Sant Pere de Galligants - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Archaeology Museum of Catalonia - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Castle of Montjuic - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Espai Girona Shopping Center - 3.5 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Carlemany is Gerona (GRO-Costa Brava) - 10 km / 6.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Carlemany is Gerona (GRO-Costa Brava) - 10 km / 6.2 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HandicapAccessible</Code><Text>Handicap accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Pub</Code><Text>Pub</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantAirconditioned</Code><Text>Restaurant Air-Conditioned</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WLANAccessPoint</Code><Text>WLAN Access Point</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Cafe(s)</Code><Text>Cafe(s)</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>