<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>103145</Id><Name>Campanario de Calahonda</Name><Region><Id>21199</Id><Name>Mijas</Name><CityId>18378</CityId></Region><Type>Apartments</Type><Address><Address1>ESPAÑA 22</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>MIJAS</City><State /><Zip>29650</Zip><Country>SPAIN</Country><Tel>952933263</Tel><Fax>952933461</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>36.4929052</Latitude><Longitude>-4.7189484</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/MIJC-VIMhotel_Exterior_1.jpg</Url><Width>300</Width><Height>200</Height><Bytes>21131</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/MIJC-VIMhotel_Exterior_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2992</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/MIJC-VIMhotel_Guest_Room_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>214</Height><Bytes>16747</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/MIJC-VIMhotel_Guest_Room_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2136</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/MIJC-VIMhotel_Swimming_Pool_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>195</Height><Bytes>18656</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/MIJC-VIMhotel_Swimming_Pool_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2309</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>SwimmingPool</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/MIJC-VIMhotel_Swimming_Pool_2.jpg</Url><Width>300</Width><Height>200</Height><Bytes>23998</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/MIJC-VIMhotel_Swimming_Pool_2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>3347</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>SwimmingPool</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Mijas (Calahonda), Ona Campanario is convenient to La Siesta Golf Club and Cabopino Golf Marbella.  This hotel is within the vicinity of Miraflores Golf Club and El Chaparral Golf Club.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 52 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and microwaves. Rooms have private balconies. Satellite television is provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include safes and separate sitting areas, and you can also request irons/ironing boards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Dip into one of the 3 outdoor swimming pools or enjoy other recreational amenities including a sauna and a fitness center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Ona Campanario, or find a snack in a coffee shop/café. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour front desk, multilingual staff, and luggage storage. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 5 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Ona Campanario, or find a snack in a coffee shop/café. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Dip into one of the 3 outdoor swimming pools or enjoy other recreational amenities including a sauna and a fitness center. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 52 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and microwaves. Rooms have private balconies. Satellite television is provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include safes and separate sitting areas, and you can also request irons/ironing boards.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Mijas (Calahonda), Ona Campanario is convenient to La Siesta Golf Club and Cabopino Golf Marbella.  This hotel is within the vicinity of Miraflores Golf Club and El Chaparral Golf Club. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;La Siesta Golf Club - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cabopino Golf Marbella - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Miraflores Golf Club - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;El Chaparral Golf Club - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Santana Golf and Country Club - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marbella Beach - 7.1 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mijas Golf Course - 7.8 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marbella Golf and Country Club - 8.3 km / 5.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Santa Clara Golf Course - 8.7 km / 5.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sohail Castle - 8.9 km / 5.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fuengirola Adventure Golf - 9.2 km / 5.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bioparc Fuengirola - 9.7 km / 6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fuengirola Beach - 10.1 km / 6.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Funny Beach - 12.1 km / 7.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Las Gaviotas Beach - 12.3 km / 7.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Ona Campanario is Malaga (AGP) - 28.8 km / 17.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Vime Campanario de Calahonda is Malaga (AGP) - 29.2 km / 18.1 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Sauna</Code><Text>Sauna</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Garage</Code><Text>Garage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreshWaterPool</Code><Text>Fresh Water Pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Balcony</Code><Text>Balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>