<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>103133</Id><Name>Itaca Fuengirola  (Formerly Acuarium)</Name><Region><Id>21202</Id><Name>Fuengirola</Name><CityId>18378</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>SANTA AMALIA 2</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>FUENGIROLA</City><State /><Zip>29640</Zip><Country>SPAIN</Country><Tel>952460150</Tel><Fax>952460154</Fax><Email>reservasacuarium@galahoteles.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>36.5325735</Latitude><Longitude>-4.6270289</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/FUEG-AQUhotel_Exterior_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>341</Height><Bytes>30518</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/FUEG-AQUhotel_Exterior_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2635</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/FUEG-AQUhotel_Guest_Room_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>291</Height><Bytes>26852</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/FUEG-AQUhotel_Guest_Room_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2632</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/FUEG-AQUhotel_Swimming_Pool_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>270</Height><Bytes>33772</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/FUEG-AQUhotel_Swimming_Pool_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>3517</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>SwimmingPool</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Itaca Fuengirola places you in the heart of Fuengirola, walking distance from Bioparc Fuengirola and Fuengirola Beach.  This hotel is within close proximity of Fuengirola Adventure Golf and Sohail Castle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 58 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have bathtubs or showers and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Itaca Fuengirola, or stop in at a snack bar/deli. Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar. Breakfast is available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Itaca Fuengirola, or stop in at a snack bar/deli. Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar. Breakfast is available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 58 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have bathtubs or showers and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Itaca Fuengirola places you in the heart of Fuengirola, walking distance from Bioparc Fuengirola and Fuengirola Beach.  This hotel is within close proximity of Fuengirola Adventure Golf and Sohail Castle. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Bioparc Fuengirola - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fuengirola Beach - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fuengirola Adventure Golf - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sohail Castle - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Las Gaviotas Beach - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Torreblanca Beach - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;El Chaparral Golf Club - 3.8 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mijas Golf Course - 4.1 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Santana Golf and Country Club - 6 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mijas Plaza de Toros - 6.7 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stupa de la Iluminacion - 7.2 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Colomares Castle - 7.9 km / 4.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Miraflores Golf Club - 7.9 km / 4.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Plaza de Espana - 8.2 km / 5.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Viborilla Beach - 8.3 km / 5.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Itaca Fuengirola is Malaga (AGP) - 19.8 km / 12.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Hotel Acuarium is Malaga (AGP) - 20 km / 12.4 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreshWaterPool</Code><Text>Fresh Water Pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SunBathingTerrace</Code><Text>Sun Bathing Terrace</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Balcony</Code><Text>Balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>