<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10364117</Id><Name>Domina Home Les Jumeaux</Name><Region><Id>20893</Id><Name>Courmayeur</Name><CityId>17053</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Strada Regionale 35</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Courmayeur</City><State /><Zip>11013</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel>0039 0165846796</Tel><Fax>0039 0165844122</Fax><Email>lesjumeaux@dominahome.it</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/D9Ffront.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/D9Fthumbfront.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2266</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/D9Fbed.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/D9Fthumbbed.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1919</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/D9Fmap.JPG</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/D9Fthumbmap.JPG</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1538</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Courmayeur, Domina Home Les Jumeaux is in the mountains and minutes from The Duke of Abruzzi Alpine Museum and Courmayeur Cable Car. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Abbe Henry Park and Fun Park Dolonne.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 85 guestrooms featuring minibars. Rooms have private balconies. Cable television is provided for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature bidets and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Spend the day on the slopes, or enjoy other recreational amenities, which include ski-in/ski-out access. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at one of the hotel's 2 restaurants. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary buffet breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, a 24-hour front desk, and luggage storage. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 5 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at one of the hotel's 2 restaurants. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary buffet breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Spend the day on the slopes, or enjoy other recreational amenities, which include ski-in/ski-out access. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 85 guestrooms featuring minibars. Rooms have private balconies. Cable television is provided for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature bidets and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Courmayeur, Domina Home Les Jumeaux is in the mountains and minutes from The Duke of Abruzzi Alpine Museum and Courmayeur Cable Car. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Abbe Henry Park and Fun Park Dolonne. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;The Duke of Abruzzi Alpine Museum - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Courmayeur Cable Car - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Abbe Henry Park - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fun Park Dolonne - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dolonne Cable Car - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Courmayeur Forum Sport Center - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dzeleuna Ski Lift - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Val Veny Cable Car - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pre-Saint-Didier Spa - 3.1 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Notre Dame de Guerison Sanctuary - 3.3 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mont Blanc Cable Car - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Arpy Lake - 7.5 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Miage Lake - 8.2 km / 5.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Il Dente del Gigante - 8.2 km / 5.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marais Natural Reserve - 8.3 km / 5.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Domina Home Les Jumeaux is Turin (TRN-Turin Intl.) - 84.5 km / 52.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Domina Home Les Jumeaux is Turin (TRN-Turin Intl.) - 84.3 km / 52.4 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseDining</Code><Text>Hotel restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditionedRooms</Code><Text>Air-conditioned rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HotelSafe</Code><Text>Central hotel safe</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>