<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10436215</Id><Name>Residence Villa Frejus</Name><Region><Id>5031922</Id><Name>Bardonecchia</Name><CityId>5031922</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Viale Della Vittoria, 12</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Bardonecchia</City><State>Italy</State><Zip>10052</Zip><Country>It</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>11</CountRooms><CountFloors>3</CountFloors></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Residence villa Frejus, you'll be centrally located in Bardonecchia, walking distance from Forte di Bramafam Museum and close to Bardonecchia - Fregiusia Ski Lift. This residence is within close proximity of Smith 4 Ski Lift and Bardonecchia Ski Resort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Treat yourself to a stay in one of the 11 guestrooms, featuring fireplaces and LCD televisions. Rooms have private balconies. Kitchenettes are outfitted with refrigerators. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities including a sauna and a fitness center. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access and ski storage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include multilingual staff, luggage storage, and laundry facilities. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities including a sauna and a fitness center. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access and ski storage. &lt;br /&gt; Treat yourself to a stay in one of the 11 guestrooms, featuring fireplaces and LCD televisions. Rooms have private balconies. Kitchenettes are outfitted with refrigerators. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Residence villa Frejus, you'll be centrally located in Bardonecchia, walking distance from Forte di Bramafam Museum and close to Bardonecchia - Fregiusia Ski Lift. This residence is within close proximity of Smith 4 Ski Lift and Bardonecchia Ski Resort. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Forte di Bramafam Museum - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bardonecchia - Fregiusia Ski Lift - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Smith 4 Ski Lift - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bardonecchia Ski Resort - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bardonecchia Community Pool - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Les Arnauds Ski Lift - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Melezet - Chesal Ski Lift - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Colle Del Sommelier - 12.6 km / 7.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fenils Ethnographic Museum - 12.6 km / 7.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mont Chaberton - 12.7 km / 7.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fort Mont Chaberton - 12.7 km / 7.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sauze D'Oulx Ski Area - 13.2 km / 8.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Frejus Road Tunnel - 13.7 km / 8.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Little Secrets of the Universe - 13.8 km / 8.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Baby Sansicario Ski Lift - 14.6 km / 9.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Residence villa Frejus is Turin (TRN-Turin Intl.) - 74.6 km / 46.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;B&gt;Turin Airport (TRN):&lt;/B&gt; Approximate driving time to Residence Frejus&amp;#x0D;&amp;#x0A;is 1 hour 30 minutes and distance is 120 kilometres (75 miles).&lt;/p&gt;&amp;#x0D;&amp;#x0A;&lt;p&gt;&lt;B&gt;Getting there:&lt;/B&gt; A train links the airport with the central railway station in Turin (Dora Station). The airport train station is a few metres from the terminal and trains depart every 30 minutes. From Dora Station, services run to Bardonecchia train station, located 200 metres from Residence Frejus.&lt;/p&gt;&amp;#x0D;&amp;#x0A;&lt;p&gt;&lt;B&gt;Getting around:&lt;/B&gt; Bardonecchia is easily explored on foot. A car is recommended to explore nearby towns and villages.&lt;/p&gt; &amp;#x0D;&amp;#x0A;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>