<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10437891</Id><Name>Parco Torre Chia</Name><Region><Id>20904</Id><Name>Cagliari</Name><CityId>17064</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Viale Mediterraneo S/n, Località Chia, Domus De Maria</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Cagliari</City><State /><Zip>09010</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Club Valtur Parco Torre Chia in Domus de Maria (Chia), you'll be minutes from Su Portu Beach and Chia Tower.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Sa Colonia Beach and Monte Cogoni Beach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 210 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Rooms have private furnished balconies or patios. Satellite television is provided for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. After dipping into one of the 2 outdoor swimming pools, you can spend some time at the private beach. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, where you can take in a garden view, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar. A complimentary buffet breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a computer station, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, where you can take in a garden view, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar. A complimentary buffet breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. After dipping into one of the 2 outdoor swimming pools, you can spend some time at the private beach. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 210 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Rooms have private furnished balconies or patios. Satellite television is provided for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Club Valtur Parco Torre Chia in Domus de Maria (Chia), you'll be minutes from Su Portu Beach and Chia Tower.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Sa Colonia Beach and Monte Cogoni Beach. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Su Portu Beach - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chia Tower - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sa Colonia Beach - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Monte Cogoni Beach - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cala del Morto Beach - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Campana Dune Beach - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chia Golf Sporting Club - 2 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Baia Chia Beach - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Su Giudeu Beach - 3.3 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cala Cipolla Beach - 3.8 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tuerredda Beach - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Laguna di Nora Aquarium - 14 km / 8.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Nora Beach - 14.5 km / 9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Archaeological Area of Nora - 14.6 km / 9.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of Sant'Efisio - 14.6 km / 9.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Club Valtur Parco Torre Chia is Cagliari (CAG-Elmas) - 41.9 km / 26 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Chia Laguna Resort - Hotel Torre Chia is Cagliari (CAG-Elmas) - 41.9 km / 26 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Sauna</Code><Text>Sauna</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarRentDesk</Code><Text>Car rental desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Playground</Code><Text>Playground</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MultilingualStaff</Code><Text>Multilingual Staff</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>