<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10436614</Id><Name>Cosmopolitan</Name><Region><Id>20898</Id><Name>Bologna</Name><CityId>17061</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Via Del Commercio Associato, 9</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip>40127</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Cosmopolitan Bologna in Bologna (Exhibition Center), you'll be close to Centro Agroalimentare di Bologna and BolognaFiere. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Parco Nord Arena and EuropAuditorium Theater.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 139 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and minibars. Flat-screen televisions with digital programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, shopping on site, and a television in the lobby. Guests can get around on the shuttle (surcharge), which operates within 5 km.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include limo/town car service, a computer station, and complimentary newspapers in the lobby. Event facilities at this hotel consist of a conference center, conference space, and meeting rooms. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 1 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, shopping on site, and a television in the lobby. Guests can get around on the shuttle (surcharge), which operates within 5 km. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 139 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and minibars. Flat-screen televisions with digital programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Cosmopolitan Bologna in Bologna (Exhibition Center), you'll be close to Centro Agroalimentare di Bologna and BolognaFiere. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Parco Nord Arena and EuropAuditorium Theater. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Centro Agroalimentare di Bologna - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Parco Nord Arena - 3 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;BolognaFiere - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;EuropAuditorium Theater - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Caserme Rosse - 3.9 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museo di Anatomia Patologica - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aldini Valeriani Sirani - 4.3 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sant'Orsola Malpighi Hospital - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bologna Botanical Gardens - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Art Gallery of Bologna - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museo di Antropologia - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Parish of St. Maria Lacrimosa of the Alemanni - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museo Aldovrandi - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museo della Specola - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of Military Architechture - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Cosmopolitan Bologna is Bologna (BLQ-Guglielmo Marconi) - 8.7 km / 5.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Hotel Cosmopolitan Bologna is Bologna (BLQ-Guglielmo Marconi) - 8.7 km / 5.4 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MultilingualStaff</Code><Text>Multilingual Staff</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>