<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10436212</Id><Name>San Luca</Name><Region><Id>20896</Id><Name>Cortona</Name><CityId>17054</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>PIAZZA GARIBALDI, 2</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Cortona 52044</City><State /><Zip /><Country>Italy</Country><Tel>39-0575-630460</Tel><Fax>39-0575-630105</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/CORO-SANhotel_Lobby_1.jpg</Url><Width>310</Width><Height>288</Height><Bytes>33183</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/CORO-SANhotel_Lobby_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2850</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/CORO-SANhotel_Guest_Room_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>239</Height><Bytes>22843</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/CORO-SANhotel_Guest_Room_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2755</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/CORO-SANhotel_Other_1.jpg</Url><Width>239</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>20882</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/CORO-SANhotel_Other_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>60</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>80</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2216</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/CORO-SANhotel_Restaurant_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>239</Height><Bytes>24114</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/CORO-SANhotel_Restaurant_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2479</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/CORO-SANhotel_Health_Club_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>213</Height><Bytes>22653</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/CORO-SANhotel_Health_Club_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2659</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Hotel San Luca places you in the heart of Cortona, walking distance from Piazza della Repubblica and Museo dell'Accademia Etrusca. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Palazzo Comunale and Santa Maria delle Grazie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 54 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have bathtubs or showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and babysitting/childcare (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour business center, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at noon  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 54 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have bathtubs or showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Hotel San Luca places you in the heart of Cortona, walking distance from Piazza della Repubblica and Museo dell'Accademia Etrusca. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Palazzo Comunale and Santa Maria delle Grazie. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Piazza della Repubblica - 0.2 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museo dell'Accademia Etrusca - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palazzo Comunale - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Santa Maria delle Grazie - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cathedral of Cortona - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museo Diocesano - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Santa Maria Nuova - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eremo Le Celle - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tennis Club Castiglionese - 8.9 km / 5.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Agricola Buccelletti Winery - 8.9 km / 5.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Municipal Art Gallery - 9.1 km / 5.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vasari Loggia - 9.1 km / 5.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Archaeological Museum - 9.2 km / 5.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cassero Tower - 9.2 km / 5.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Guglielmi Castle - 13.8 km / 8.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel San Luca is Perugia (PEG-Sant Egidio) - 46.4 km / 28.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>