<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10455654</Id><Name>Locanda Dell'angelo Paracucchi</Name><Region><Id>17098</Id><Name>La Spezia</Name><CityId>17098</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Viale Xxv Aprile, 60</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip>19031</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Locanda Dell'Angelo in Ameglia, you'll be next to a golf course and close to Sarzana Church and Sarzanello Fortress.  This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of Lerici Beach and Golf Club Marigola.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 31 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature bidets and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Head down to the water and enjoy a day at the private beach, or take advantage of other recreational amenities including an outdoor pool and a spa tub. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves lunch and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff. Guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle for a surcharge, and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves lunch and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Head down to the water and enjoy a day at the private beach, or take advantage of other recreational amenities including an outdoor pool and a spa tub. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 31 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature bidets and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Locanda Dell'Angelo in Ameglia, you'll be next to a golf course and close to Sarzana Church and Sarzanello Fortress.  This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of Lerici Beach and Golf Club Marigola. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Sarzana Church - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sarzanello Fortress - 4.8 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lerici Beach - 5.2 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Golf Club Marigola - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Carrara Convention Center - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Castello Malaspina di Fosdinovo - 8.2 km / 5.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Civic Marble Museum - 8.3 km / 5.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palazzo delle Logge - 10.2 km / 6.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Carrara Cathedral - 10.3 km / 6.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sporting Beach - 10.5 km / 6.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of St. Peter - 11.2 km / 7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Doria Castle - 11.3 km / 7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marmo di Carrara - 11.7 km / 7.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ferry Terminal - 11.8 km / 7.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cattedrale di Cristo Re - 12 km / 7.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Locanda Dell'Angelo is Pisa (PSA-Galileo Galilei) - 54 km / 33.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Locanda Dell'Angelo is Pisa (PSA-Galileo Galilei) - 54 km / 33.5 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>