<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10455010</Id><Name>Major</Name><Region><Id>4464776</Id><Name>Gorizia</Name><CityId>4464776</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Via Pietro Micca 19 C</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip>34077</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Major in Ronchi dei Legionari, you'll be within the vicinity of Marco Felluga and Vie di Romans. This 4-star hotel is within the region of Aquileia National Archaeological Museum and Cathedral of Aquileia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 96 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have shower/tub combinations and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour business center, a computer station, and express check-in. Event facilities at this hotel consist of a conference center and meeting rooms. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 96 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have shower/tub combinations and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Major in Ronchi dei Legionari, you'll be within the vicinity of Marco Felluga and Vie di Romans. This 4-star hotel is within the region of Aquileia National Archaeological Museum and Cathedral of Aquileia. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Marco Felluga - 6.8 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vie di Romans - 8.2 km / 5.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aquileia National Archaeological Museum - 11.5 km / 7.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cathedral of Aquileia - 12 km / 7.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Archaeological Area and the Patriarchal Basilica of Aquileia - 12 km / 7.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Villa Russiz - 12.4 km / 7.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palmanova Outlet Village - 12.4 km / 7.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Baia di Sistiana - 13 km / 8.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Trieste Adventure Park - 13.2 km / 8.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza Grande - 15.7 km / 9.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Castle of Gorizia - 15.9 km / 9.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of St Ignatius of Loyola - 15.9 km / 9.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kostanjevica Monastery - 17.1 km / 10.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eugenio Collavini Vini and Spumanti - 17.8 km / 11 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lupinc Farm - 18 km / 11.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Major is Trieste (TRS-Friuli Venezia Giulia) - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Best Western Hotel Major is Trieste (TRS-Friuli Venezia Giulia) - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarRentDesk</Code><Text>Car rental desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Garage</Code><Text>Garage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MultilingualStaff</Code><Text>Multilingual Staff</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>