<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10462212</Id><Name>Cave Del Sole Resort &amp; Beauty</Name><Region><Id>144484</Id><Name>Matera</Name><CityId>144484</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Contrada La Vaglia S.n.c.</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip>75100</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Hotel Cave del Sole in Matera, you'll be in a regional park and convenient to Convent of Sant'Agostino and San Giovanni Battista Church.  This residence is within close proximity of Tramontano Castle and Cathedral of Matera.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 16 guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes. LCD televisions with digital programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and minibars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. This residence also features a television in the lobby and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at a coffee shop/café serving guests of Hotel Cave del Sole.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, express check-out, and complimentary newspapers in the lobby. A train station pick-up service is provided at no charge (available on request), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10:30 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at a coffee shop/café serving guests of Hotel Cave del Sole. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. This residence also features a television in the lobby and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 16 guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes. LCD televisions with digital programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and minibars.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Hotel Cave del Sole in Matera, you'll be in a regional park and convenient to Convent of Sant'Agostino and San Giovanni Battista Church.  This residence is within close proximity of Tramontano Castle and Cathedral of Matera. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Convent of Sant'Agostino - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Giovanni Battista Church - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tramontano Castle - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cathedral of Matera - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Domenico Ridola National Archaeological Museum - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Altamura Cathedral - 16.3 km / 10.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Plebescito Plaza - 31.7 km / 19.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bernalda Castle - 32.2 km / 20 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of St. Peter and St. Paul - 32.8 km / 20.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tavole Palatine - 35.4 km / 22 mi &lt;br /&gt;Acquazzurra Water Park - 37.6 km / 23.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Metaponto Archaeological Site - 38.6 km / 24 mi &lt;br /&gt;Metaponto Beach - 41.5 km / 25.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Flight of the Angel - 48.9 km / 30.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Scanzano Jonico Park - 49 km / 30.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Cave del Sole is Bari (BRI-Karol Wojtyla) - 52.2 km / 32.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Garage</Code><Text>Garage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MultilingualStaff</Code><Text>Multilingual Staff</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>