<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10469069</Id><Name>City Parma</Name><Region><Id>21016</Id><Name>Parma</Name><CityId>17129</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Strada Cornocchio, 55</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Parma</City><State /><Zip>43126</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Hotel City Parma in Parma, you'll be near the airport and convenient to Hospital of Parma and Parma Exhibition Center. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Ducale Park and Palazzo della Pilotta.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 50 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Your room comes with a memory foam bed. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have rainfall showerheads and complimentary toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as wireless Internet access (surcharge) and an arcade/game room. Additional features include a television in the lobby and a picnic area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk. This hotel has 2 meeting rooms available for events. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as wireless Internet access (surcharge) and an arcade/game room. Additional features include a television in the lobby and a picnic area. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 50 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Your room comes with a memory foam bed. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have rainfall showerheads and complimentary toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Hotel City Parma in Parma, you'll be near the airport and convenient to Hospital of Parma and Parma Exhibition Center. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Ducale Park and Palazzo della Pilotta. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Hospital of Parma - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Parma Exhibition Center - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ducale Park - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palazzo della Pilotta - 2.8 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Teatro Regio di Parma - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shrine of Santa Maria della Steccata - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Parma - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bishop's Palace - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Baptistery of Parma - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cathedral of Parma - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza Garibaldi - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Auditorium Niccolo Paganini - 4.1 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eridania Park - 4.1 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Barilla Center - 4.1 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ennio Tardini Stadium - 4.1 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel City Parma is Parma (PMF) - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Ora Hotels City Parma is Parma (PMF) - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MultilingualStaff</Code><Text>Multilingual Staff</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>