<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10462125</Id><Name>Ca' Vendramin Di Santa Fosca</Name><Region><Id>21076</Id><Name>Venice</Name><CityId>17175</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Cannaregio 2400</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip>30121</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Hotel Ca' Vendramin di Santa Fosca places you in the heart of Venice, walking distance from Ca' d'Oro and Galleria Giorgio Franchetti alla Ca' d'Oro. This 4-star hotel is close to Rialto Bridge and St. Mark's Basilica.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare, and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a computer station, and dry cleaning/laundry services.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM   &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare, and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Hotel Ca' Vendramin di Santa Fosca places you in the heart of Venice, walking distance from Ca' d'Oro and Galleria Giorgio Franchetti alla Ca' d'Oro. This 4-star hotel is close to Rialto Bridge and St. Mark's Basilica. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Ca' d'Oro - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Galleria Giorgio Franchetti alla Ca' d'Oro - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Casino of Venice - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ca'Pesaro - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Stae - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Casino Vendramin-Calergi - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fondamenta Nuove Marina - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ca' D'Oro Waterbus - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Marcuola Waterbus Stop - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fondaco of Turks - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Venetian Museum of Natural History - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pescaria - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Madonna dell'Orto - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Venetian Ghetto - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sant Alvise - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Ca' Vendramin di Santa Fosca is Venice (VCE-Marco Polo) - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Hotel Ca'Vendramin di Santa Fosca is Venice (VCE-Marco Polo) - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MultilingualStaff</Code><Text>Multilingual Staff</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>