<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10485668</Id><Name>Ovolo 2 Arbuthnot Road, Central</Name><Region><Id>20856</Id><Name>Central</Name><CityId>16772</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>2 Arbuthnot Road Central</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Hong Kong</City><State /><Zip /><Country>Hong Kong</Country><Tel>852 2165 1000</Tel><Fax>-</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/HKG-9Lhotel_Exterior_1.jpg</Url><Width>239</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/HKG-9Lhotel_Exterior_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>60</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>80</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Ovolo Central places you in the heart of Hong Kong, steps from Grotto Fine Art and Lan Kwai Fong.  This 4-star hotel is close to Soho and Victoria Peak Tram.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 42 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and LCD televisions. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while DVD players and cable programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature designer toiletries and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a 24-hour fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or grab a snack at a coffee shop/café. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and dry cleaning/laundry services.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is Noon &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or grab a snack at a coffee shop/café. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a 24-hour fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 42 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and LCD televisions. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while DVD players and cable programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature designer toiletries and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Ovolo Central places you in the heart of Hong Kong, steps from Grotto Fine Art and Lan Kwai Fong.  This 4-star hotel is close to Soho and Victoria Peak Tram. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Grotto Fine Art - 0.1 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;10 Chancery Lane Gallery - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lan Kwai Fong - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hong Kong Immaculate Conception Cathedral - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hong Kong Fringe Club - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hong Kong Central Hospital - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mid-levels Escalators - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hong Kong Zoological and Botanical Gardens - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Government House - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Soho - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Landmark Shopping Area - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Former French Mission Building - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dr. Sun Yat-sen Museum - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;HSBC Hong Kong Headquarter Building - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Statue Square - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Ovolo Central is Hong Kong (HKG-Hong Kong Intl.) - 22.8 km / 14.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>