<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10485292</Id><Name>Butterfly on Victoria Boutique Hotel</Name><Region><Id>20861</Id><Name>North Point</Name><CityId>16772</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>33 King'S Road, Causeway Bay</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Hong Kong</City><State /><Zip /><Country>Hong Kong</Country><Tel>+852 2132 6000</Tel><Fax>+852 2132 6100</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Butterfly on Victoria, you'll be centrally located in Hong Kong, steps from Tin Hau Temple and minutes from Victoria Park. This hotel is close to Times Square Shopping Mall and Happy Valley Race Course.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of 132 guestrooms featuring LCD televisions. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a computer station, and dry cleaning/laundry services.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of 132 guestrooms featuring LCD televisions. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Butterfly on Victoria, you'll be centrally located in Hong Kong, steps from Tin Hau Temple and minutes from Victoria Park. This hotel is close to Times Square Shopping Mall and Happy Valley Race Course. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Tin Hau Temple - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Victoria Park - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hong Kong Shue Yan University - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hong Kong Central Library - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Windsor House - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Causeway Bay Typhoon Shelter - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Noon Day Gun - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;World Trade Centre - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lee Gardens - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hong Kong Sogo - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hysan Place - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tung Wah Eastern Hospital - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sunbeam Theatre - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Edge Gallery - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hong Kong Stadium - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Butterfly on Victoria is Hong Kong (HKG-Hong Kong Intl.) - 26.6 km / 16.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CurrencyExchangeService</Code><Text>Currency Exchange Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Doctoroncall</Code><Text>Doctor on call</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>