<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10529329</Id><Name>Hotel Commonwealth</Name><Region><Id>21440</Id><Name>Back Bay</Name><CityId>19402</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>500 Commonwealth Avenue</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Boston</City><State /><Zip>02215</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>617-933-5000</Tel><Fax>+1 (617) 2662530</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Commonwealth in Boston, you'll be minutes from Kenmore Square and Fenway Park. This 4.5-star hotel is close to Hynes Convention Center and Boston Museum of Fine Arts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 150 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and tablet computers. Your pillowtop bed comes with down comforters and Egyptian cotton sheets. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while 48-inch flat-screen televisions with digital programming provide entertainment. Bathrooms feature shower/tub combinations, designer toiletries, and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a health club, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. Additional amenities include gift shops/newsstands, shopping on site, and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant or in a coffee shop/café. Or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a 24-hour business center, and express check-in. Planning an event in Boston? This hotel has facilities measuring 6000 square feet (557 square meters), including a meeting room.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is Noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant or in a coffee shop/café. Or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a health club, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. Additional amenities include gift shops/newsstands, shopping on site, and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 150 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and tablet computers. Your pillowtop bed comes with down comforters and Egyptian cotton sheets. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while 48-inch flat-screen televisions with digital programming provide entertainment. Bathrooms feature shower/tub combinations, designer toiletries, and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Commonwealth in Boston, you'll be minutes from Kenmore Square and Fenway Park. This 4.5-star hotel is close to Hynes Convention Center and Boston Museum of Fine Arts. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Kenmore Square - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;House of Blues Boston - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fenway Park - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Back Bay Fens - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Berklee College of Music - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mapparium - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mary Baker Eddy Library - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hynes Convention Center - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Christian Science Plaza - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Boston Symphony Hall - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Shops at Prudential Center - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Prudential Tower - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;New England Conservatory of Music - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Northeastern University - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Boston Museum of Fine Arts - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Commonwealth is Boston, MA (BOS-Logan Intl.) - 6.6 km / 4.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Hotel Commonwealth is Boston, MA (BOS-Logan Intl.) - 6.6 km / 4.1 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property’s location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CurrencyExchangeService</Code><Text>Currency Exchange Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>