<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10523092</Id><Name>Residence Inn by Marriott Atlanta Midtown/Historic</Name><Region><Id>21409</Id><Name>Midtown/Piedmont</Name><CityId>19342</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1041 W Peachtree Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Atlanta</City><State /><Zip>30309</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>+1 (404) 872-8885</Tel><Fax>+1 (404) 724-9218</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Residence Inn by Marriott Atlanta Midtown/Georgia Tech places you in the heart of Atlanta, minutes from Margaret Mitchell House and Museum and close to Centennial Olympic Park. This hotel is within close proximity of Whole World Theater and Atlanta Symphony Hall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 90 guestrooms, featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and microwaves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and a hair salon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Residence Inn by Marriott Atlanta Midtown/Georgia Tech. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, express check-out, and complimentary newspapers in the lobby. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 4 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Residence Inn by Marriott Atlanta Midtown/Georgia Tech. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and a hair salon. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 90 guestrooms, featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and microwaves.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Residence Inn by Marriott Atlanta Midtown/Georgia Tech places you in the heart of Atlanta, minutes from Margaret Mitchell House and Museum and close to Centennial Olympic Park. This hotel is within close proximity of Whole World Theater and Atlanta Symphony Hall. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Margaret Mitchell House and Museum - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Whole World Theater - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Atlanta Symphony Hall - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;High Museum of Art - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Woodruff Arts Center - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Georgia Institute of Technology - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Museum of Patriotism - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Center for Puppetry Arts - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fox Theatre - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rhodes Memorial Hall - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Atlantic Station - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;William Breman Jewish Heritage Museum - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Institute of Paper and Science Technology - 1.5 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Atlanta Botanical Garden - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piedmont Park - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Atlanta, GA (PDK-DeKalb-Peachtree) - 13.4 km / 8.3 mi&lt;br /&gt;Atlanta, GA (ATL-Hartsfield-Jackson Atlanta Intl.) - 16.7 km / 10.4 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Residence Inn by Marriott Atlanta Midtown/Georgia Tech is Atlanta, GA (ATL-Hartsfield-Jackson Atlanta Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Residence Inn by Marriott Atlanta Midtown/Historic is Atlanta, GA (ATL-Hartsfield-Jackson Atlanta Intl.) - 16.7 km / 10.4 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ContinentalBreakfast</Code><Text>Contintenal breakfast</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InRoomMovies</Code><Text>In-room movies</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WakeUpService</Code><Text>Wake up service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarRentDesk</Code><Text>Car rental desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Kitchen</Code><Text>Kitchen</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Freenewspaper</Code><Text>Free Newspaper</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Icemachine</Code><Text>Ice Machine</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TV</Code><Text>TeleVision</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Medical centre</Code><Text>Medical centre</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>24HourFrontDesk</Code><Text>24 Hour Front Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BeautyShop</Code><Text>Beauty Shop</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ATMMachine</Code><Text>ATM Machine</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>