<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10522460</Id><Name>Hotel Pepper Tree Kitchen Suites</Name><Region><Id>21400</Id><Name>Knotts Berry Farm Area</Name><CityId>19324</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>2375 West Lincoln Ave</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Anaheim</City><State /><Zip>92801</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>1-714-774-7370</Tel><Fax>1-714-774-8068</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Hotel Pepper Tree Anaheim, All Suites Hotel places you in the heart of Anaheim, minutes from Dad Miller Golf Course and close to Knott's Berry Farm. This family-friendly aparthotel is within close proximity of Southern California Institute of Technology and Buena Park Mall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 80 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private furnished balconies or patios. 40-inch flat-screen televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include microwaves and coffee/tea makers, as well as phones with free local calls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hotel Pepper Tree Anaheim, All Suites Hotel. A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a computer station, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hotel Pepper Tree Anaheim, All Suites Hotel. A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 80 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private furnished balconies or patios. 40-inch flat-screen televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include microwaves and coffee/tea makers, as well as phones with free local calls.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Hotel Pepper Tree Anaheim, All Suites Hotel places you in the heart of Anaheim, minutes from Dad Miller Golf Course and close to Knott's Berry Farm. This family-friendly aparthotel is within close proximity of Southern California Institute of Technology and Buena Park Mall. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Dad Miller Golf Course - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Southern California Institute of Technology - 1.7 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Buena Park Mall - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Independence Hall - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hobby City Doll and Toy Museum - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Adventure City - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Knott's Marketplace - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Knott's Berry Farm - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Knott's Soak City Water Park - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bodies the Exhibition - 3.5 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Medieval Times - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Titanic the Experience - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Anaheim Central Library - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Rinks Anaheim Ice - 4.6 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Disneyland&lt;/b&gt;® - 4.8 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Long Beach, CA (LGB-Long Beach Municipal) - 16.4 km / 10.2 mi&lt;br /&gt;Orange County, CA (SNA-John Wayne) - 19.6 km / 12.2 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Pepper Tree Anaheim, All Suites Hotel is Orange County, CA (SNA-John Wayne). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The closest major airports to Hotel Pepper Tree Anaheim, All Suites Hotel are:&lt;br /&gt;Long Beach, CA (LGB-Long Beach Municipal) - 16.5 km / 10.2 mi&lt;br /&gt;Orange County, CA (SNA-John Wayne) - 19.6 km / 12.2 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Pepper Tree Anaheim, All Suites Hotel is Orange County, CA (SNA-John Wayne). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>