<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10536915</Id><Name>Sands of Kahana</Name><Region><Id>21632</Id><Name>Lahaina</Name><CityId>19726</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>4299 Lower Honoapiilani Hwy</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Lahaina</City><State /><Zip>96761</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>702-367-4010</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Sands of Kahana in Lahaina (Kaanapali), you'll be close to Napili Bay and Kapalua Beach.  This beach condominium resort is within close proximity of Kapalua Golf Resort Bay Course and Oneloa Beach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in of the guestrooms, featuring kitchens with refrigerators and microwaves. Rooms have private lanais. Cable programming and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and separate sitting areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including an outdoor pool, an outdoor tennis court, and a sauna. Additional amenities include concierge services, shopping on site, and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Sands of Kahana. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a 24-hour front desk, and laundry facilities. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 4 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Sands of Kahana. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including an outdoor pool, an outdoor tennis court, and a sauna. Additional amenities include concierge services, shopping on site, and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in of the guestrooms, featuring kitchens with refrigerators and microwaves. Rooms have private lanais. Cable programming and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and separate sitting areas.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Sands of Kahana in Lahaina (Kaanapali), you'll be close to Napili Bay and Kapalua Beach.  This beach condominium resort is within close proximity of Kapalua Golf Resort Bay Course and Oneloa Beach. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Napili Bay - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kapalua Beach - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kapalua Golf Resort Bay Course - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Oneloa Beach - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;D.T. Fleming Beach Park - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Black Rock - 5.2 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kaanapali Beach - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Whalers Village - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Whalers Village Museum - 5.7 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kapalua Golf Club Plantation Course - 5.8 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kaanapali Golf Courses - 6 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Honolua Bay - 6.4 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Costantino Art Gallery - 10 km / 6.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Outlets of Maui - 10.2 km / 6.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maui Theater - 10.4 km / 6.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Sands of Kahana is Kapalua, HI (JHM-West Maui) - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The closest major airports to Sands of Kahana are:&lt;br /&gt;Kapalua, HI (JHM-West Maui) - 1 km / 0.6 mi&lt;br /&gt;Kahului, HI (OGG) - 26.4 km / 16.4 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Sands of Kahana is Kapalua, HI (JHM-West Maui). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>