<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10534044</Id><Name>River Hotel</Name><Region><Id>21467</Id><Name>The Loop</Name><CityId>19455</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>75a East Wacker Drive</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Chicago</City><State /><Zip>60601</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>312.777.0990</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at River Hotel, you'll be centrally located in Chicago, steps from Bridgehouse and Chicago River Museum and Vietnam Veterans Memorial.  This 4-star hotel is close to Millennium Park and Art Institute of Chicago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and complimentary newspapers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a health club, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner. Dining is also available at a coffee shop/café, and room service (during limited hours) is provided. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a business center, and express check-in. Event facilities at this hotel consist of conference space and meeting rooms.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner. Dining is also available at a coffee shop/café, and room service (during limited hours) is provided. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a health club, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and complimentary newspapers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at River Hotel, you'll be centrally located in Chicago, steps from Bridgehouse and Chicago River Museum and Vietnam Veterans Memorial.  This 4-star hotel is close to Millennium Park and Art Institute of Chicago. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Bridgehouse and Chicago River Museum - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vietnam Veterans Memorial - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Michigan Avenue Bridge - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wrigley Building - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chicago Theater - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;House of Blues Chicago - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tribune Tower - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;American Medical Association Headquarters - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Goodman Theater - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ford Center for the Performing Arts Oriental Theatre - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Harris Theater - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aon Center - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chicago Cultural Center - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Picasso Statue - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Millennium Park - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Chicago, IL (MDW-Midway Intl.) - 14.6 km / 9.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;Chicago, IL (ORD-O'Hare Intl.) - 25.1 km / 15.6 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for River Hotel is Chicago, IL (ORD-O'Hare Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The closest major airports to River Hotel are:&lt;br /&gt;Chicago, IL (MDW-Midway Intl.) - 14.6 km / 9.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;Chicago, IL (ORD-O'Hare Intl.) - 25.1 km / 15.6 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for River Hotel is Chicago, IL (ORD-O'Hare Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>