<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10534662</Id><Name>HYATT house Dallas/Uptown</Name><Region><Id>21488</Id><Name>Infomart/World Trade Centre</Name><CityId>19485</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>2914 Harry Hines Boulevard</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Dallas</City><State /><Zip>75201</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>+1 (214) 965-9990</Tel><Fax>+214 (965) 9996</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at HYATT house Dallas/Uptown in Dallas (Uptown - Oak Lawn), you'll be minutes from American Airlines Center and close to Morton H. Meyerson Symphony Center. This aparthotel is close to Dallas World Aquarium and Dallas Convention Center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 141 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and premium TV channels provides entertainment. Conveniences include complimentary weekday newspapers and separate sitting areas, as well as phones with free local calls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including an outdoor pool, a spa tub, and a fitness center. This aparthotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a television in the lobby. Guests can get around on the complimentary shuttle, which operates within 3 mi.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Mingle with other guests at a complimentary reception, held on select days. A complimentary buffet breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a 24-hour business center, and complimentary newspapers in the lobby. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Mingle with other guests at a complimentary reception, held on select days. A complimentary buffet breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including an outdoor pool, a spa tub, and a fitness center. This aparthotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a television in the lobby. Guests can get around on the complimentary shuttle, which operates within 3 mi. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 141 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and premium TV channels provides entertainment. Conveniences include complimentary weekday newspapers and separate sitting areas, as well as phones with free local calls.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at HYATT house Dallas/Uptown in Dallas (Uptown - Oak Lawn), you'll be minutes from American Airlines Center and close to Morton H. Meyerson Symphony Center. This aparthotel is close to Dallas World Aquarium and Dallas Convention Center. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;American Airlines Center - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Perot Museum of Nature and Science - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Klyde Warren Park - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Nasher Sculpture Center - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Trammell and Margaret Crow Collection of Asian Art - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;American Museum of the Miniature Arts - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Morton H. Meyerson Symphony Center - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;ATT Performing Arts Center - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dallas Museum of Art - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;I.M. Pei's Fountain Place - 1.4 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dallas World Aquarium - 1.4 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cathedral Santuario de Guadalupe - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dallas JPMorgan Chase Tower - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dallas Market Center - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dallas Holocaust Museum - 1.7 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Dallas, TX (DAL-Love Field) - 6.6 km / 4.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;Dallas, TX (DFW-Dallas-Fort Worth Intl.) - 24.4 km / 15.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for HYATT house Dallas/Uptown is Dallas, TX (DFW-Dallas-Fort Worth Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The closest major airports to Hyatt Summerfield Suites Dallas/Uptown are:&lt;br /&gt;Dallas, TX (DAL-Love Field) - 6.6 km / 4.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;Dallas, TX (DFW-Dallas-Fort Worth Intl.) - 24.4 km / 15.2 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hyatt Summerfield Suites Dallas/Uptown is Dallas, TX (DFW-Dallas-Fort Worth Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WakeUpService</Code><Text>Wake up service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FamilyRooms</Code><Text>Family rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Kitchen</Code><Text>Kitchen</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lounge</Code><Text>Lounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomCentralHeating</Code><Text>Central heating in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Freenewspaper</Code><Text>Free Newspaper</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Golf</Code><Text>Golf</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TV</Code><Text>TeleVision</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>24HourFrontDesk</Code><Text>24 Hour Front Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>JoggingTrack</Code><Text>Jogging Track</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ATMMachine</Code><Text>ATM Machine</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>