<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10536923</Id><Name>Lahaina Shores - A CRH Property</Name><Region><Id>21632</Id><Name>Lahaina</Name><CityId>19726</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>475 Front Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Lahaina, Maui</City><State /><Zip>96761</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>808-879-2778</Tel><Fax>808-879-7825</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Lahaina Shores Beach Resort in Lahaina, you'll be on the beach and minutes from Lahaina Harbor and Banyan Tree Park.  This beach condo is within close proximity of Baldwin Home Museum and Maui Theater.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 199 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Rooms have private lanais. Cable programming and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as complimentary newspapers and microwaves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss out on recreational opportunities including an outdoor pool and a spa tub. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Don’t miss out on recreational opportunities including an outdoor pool and a spa tub. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 199 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Rooms have private lanais. Cable programming and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as complimentary newspapers and microwaves.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Lahaina Shores Beach Resort in Lahaina, you'll be on the beach and minutes from Lahaina Harbor and Banyan Tree Park.  This beach condo is within close proximity of Baldwin Home Museum and Maui Theater. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Lahaina Harbor - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Banyan Tree Park - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Baldwin Home Museum - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maui Theater - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Outlets of Maui - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Costantino Art Gallery - 1.7 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kaanapali Golf Courses - 5.8 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Whalers Village - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Whalers Village Museum - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kaanapali Beach - 6.7 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Black Rock - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Iao Valley State Park - 13.6 km / 8.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Napili Bay - 14.2 km / 8.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kapalua Golf Resort Bay Course - 14.6 km / 9.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kapalua Beach - 14.7 km / 9.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Kapalua, HI (JHM-West Maui) - 10.5 km / 6.5 mi&lt;br /&gt;Kahului, HI (OGG) - 24.9 km / 15.5 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Lahaina Shores Beach Resort is Kahului, HI (OGG). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The closest major airports to Lahaina Shores Beach Resort are:&lt;br /&gt;Kapalua, HI (JHM-West Maui) - 10.7 km / 6.6 mi&lt;br /&gt;Kahului, HI (OGG) - 24.8 km / 15.4 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Lahaina Shores Beach Resort is Kahului, HI (OGG). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property’s location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>