<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10536898</Id><Name>Sugar Beach Resort - A CRH Property</Name><Region><Id>21635</Id><Name>Kihei</Name><CityId>19726</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>145 N. Kihei Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Kihei</City><State /><Zip>96753</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>(808) 879-2778</Tel><Fax>808-879-7825</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Sugar Beach Resort - Maui Condo &amp; Home in Kihei, you'll be on the beach and close to Kealia Pond National Wildlife Refuge and Maui Ocean Center.  This beach condo is within close proximity of Kalepolepo and Waipuilani Park.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 216 air-conditioned guestrooms. Rooms have private patios. Complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers and sofa beds, and you can also request cribs/infant beds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a garden. This condo also features concierge services, babysitting/childcare, and a picnic area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at a coffee shop/café serving guests of Sugar Beach Resort - Maui Condo &amp; Home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at a coffee shop/café serving guests of Sugar Beach Resort - Maui Condo &amp; Home. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a garden. This condo also features concierge services, babysitting/childcare, and a picnic area. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 216 air-conditioned guestrooms. Rooms have private patios. Complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers and sofa beds, and you can also request cribs/infant beds.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Sugar Beach Resort - Maui Condo &amp; Home in Kihei, you'll be on the beach and close to Kealia Pond National Wildlife Refuge and Maui Ocean Center.  This beach condo is within close proximity of Kalepolepo and Waipuilani Park. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Kealia Pond National Wildlife Refuge - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kalepolepo - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Waipuilani Park - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maui Ocean Center - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maui Nui Golf Club - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maalaea Harbor - 4.9 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kihei Regional Park - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kalama Beach Park - 6.2 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kamaole Beach Park - 7.4 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kamaole Beach Park 2 - 8 km / 5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kamaole Beach Park 3 - 8.4 km / 5.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Dunes at Maui Lani - 8.9 km / 5.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Alexander and Baldwin Sugar Museum - 9.4 km / 5.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Keawakapu Beach - 10.3 km / 6.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mokapu Beach - 10.7 km / 6.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Sugar Beach Resort - Maui Condo &amp; Home is Kahului, HI (OGG) - 12.5 km / 7.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The closest major airports to Sugar Beach Resort - Maui Condo &amp; Home are:&lt;br /&gt;Kahului, HI (OGG) - 12.5 km / 7.7 mi&lt;br /&gt;Kapalua, HI (JHM-West Maui) - 29.1 km / 18.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Sugar Beach Resort - Maui Condo &amp; Home is Kahului, HI (OGG). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property’s location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>