<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10537245</Id><Name>Aston at the Executive Centre Hotel</Name><Region><Id>21697</Id><Name>Honolulu (Downtown)</Name><CityId>19807</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1088 Bishop Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Honolulu</City><State /><Zip>96813</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>1-808-539-3000</Tel><Fax>1-808-523-1088</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Aston at the Executive Centre Hotel, you'll be centrally located in Honolulu, steps from Hawaii State Art Museum and Hawaii Theater. This hotel is close to Aloha Tower and University of Hawaii at Manoa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access is available. Private bathrooms have jetted bathtubs and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include safes and complimentary newspapers, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. Additional features include babysitting/childcare (surcharge), babysitting/childcare, and gift shops/newsstands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Aston at the Executive Centre Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, limo/town car service, and dry cleaning/laundry services. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Aston at the Executive Centre Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. Additional features include babysitting/childcare (surcharge), babysitting/childcare, and gift shops/newsstands. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access is available. Private bathrooms have jetted bathtubs and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include safes and complimentary newspapers, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Aston at the Executive Centre Hotel, you'll be centrally located in Honolulu, steps from Hawaii State Art Museum and Hawaii Theater. This hotel is close to Aloha Tower and University of Hawaii at Manoa. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Hawaii State Art Museum - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hawaii Theater - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Iolani Palace - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;King Kamehameha Statue - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hawaii State Capitol - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aloha Tower Marketplace - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aloha Tower - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Foster Botanical Gardens - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Honolulu Academy of Arts - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Neal S. Blaisdell Center - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hawaii Opera Theater - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Memorial Cemetery of the Pacific - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kaka'ako Waterfront Park - 1.7 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ala Moana Center - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ala Moana Beach Park - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Aston at the Executive Centre Hotel is Honolulu, HI (HNL-Honolulu Intl.) - 6.6 km / 4.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>