<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10537975</Id><Name>Staybridge Suites HOUSTON IAH - BELTWAY 8</Name><Region><Id>21574</Id><Name>George Bush Intercont'al Airport (IAH)</Name><CityId>19612</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1910 North Sam Houston Parkway East</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Houston</City><State /><Zip>77032</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>+1 (281) 6617700</Tel><Fax>+1 (281) 6617701</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Staybridge Suites Houston IAH - Beltway 8 in Houston, you'll be in the business district and close to Houston Police Department Museum.  This family-friendly aparthotel is within the vicinity of Greenspoint Mall and Houston Grand Prix.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 90 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with stovetops and microwaves. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while DVD players and cable programming provide entertainment. Conveniences include desks and sofa beds, and housekeeping is provided weekly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreational amenities such as an outdoor pool and a 24-hour fitness center. This aparthotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, a fireplace in the lobby, and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Mingle with other guests at a complimentary reception, held on select days. A complimentary buffet breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a 24-hour business center, and a computer station. Planning an event in Houston? This aparthotel has facilities measuring 800 square feet (74 square meters), including a meeting room. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Mingle with other guests at a complimentary reception, held on select days. A complimentary buffet breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreational amenities such as an outdoor pool and a 24-hour fitness center. This aparthotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, a fireplace in the lobby, and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 90 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with stovetops and microwaves. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while DVD players and cable programming provide entertainment. Conveniences include desks and sofa beds, and housekeeping is provided weekly.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Staybridge Suites Houston IAH - Beltway 8 in Houston, you'll be in the business district and close to Houston Police Department Museum.  This family-friendly aparthotel is within the vicinity of Greenspoint Mall and Houston Grand Prix. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Houston Police Department Museum - 3.3 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Greenspoint Mall - 5.4 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Houston Grand Prix - 5.5 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Redstone Golf Club - 9.9 km / 6.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Humble Civic Center - 10.7 km / 6.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cypresswood Golf Club - 10.9 km / 6.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mercer Arboretum and Botanic Gardens - 11.2 km / 6.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Deerbrook Mall - 11.7 km / 7.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Humble Oil Patch Golf Center - 13.3 km / 8.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Houston Motorsports Park - 13.3 km / 8.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tour 18 Golf Course - 14.4 km / 8.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old MacDonald's Farm - 14.6 km / 9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kingwood Cove Golf Club - 15 km / 9.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Heron Lakes Golf Course - 16.6 km / 10.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Splashtown - 16.6 km / 10.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Staybridge Suites Houston IAH - Beltway 8 is Houston, TX (IAH-George Bush Intercontinental) - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Kitchen</Code><Text>Kitchen</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Icemachine</Code><Text>Ice Machine</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TV</Code><Text>TeleVision</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>