<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10536838</Id><Name>Hale Pau Hana Resort LLC</Name><Region><Id>21635</Id><Name>Kihei</Name><CityId>19726</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>2480 S. Kihei Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Kihei</City><State /><Zip>96753</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>1-800-367-6036</Tel><Fax>1-808-875-0238</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Hale Pau Hana Resort in Kihei, you'll be on the beach and minutes from Kamaole Beach Park 2 and Kamaole Beach Park. This beach condo is within close proximity of Kamaole Beach Park 3 and Kalama Beach Park.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 64 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private furnished balconies or patios. Cable programming and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include safes and microwaves, as well as phones with free local calls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a garden. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a computer station, laundry facilities, and an elevator (lift). Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a garden. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 64 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private furnished balconies or patios. Cable programming and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include safes and microwaves, as well as phones with free local calls.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Hale Pau Hana Resort in Kihei, you'll be on the beach and minutes from Kamaole Beach Park 2 and Kamaole Beach Park. This beach condo is within close proximity of Kamaole Beach Park 3 and Kalama Beach Park. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Kamaole Beach Park 2 - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kamaole Beach Park - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kamaole Beach Park 3 - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kalama Beach Park - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kihei Regional Park - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Keawakapu Beach - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mokapu Beach - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ulua Beach - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ulua Beach Park - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maui Nui Golf Club - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shops at Wailea - 3.5 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wailea Beach - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Waipuilani Park - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Polo Beach - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wailea Blue Golf Course - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hale Pau Hana Resort is Kahului, HI (OGG) - 19.6 km / 12.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The closest major airports to Hale Pau Hana Resort are:&lt;br /&gt;Kahului, HI (OGG) - 19.6 km / 12.2 mi&lt;br /&gt;Kapalua, HI (JHM-West Maui) - 36.1 km / 22.4 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hale Pau Hana Resort is Kahului, HI (OGG). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property’s location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>