<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10546385</Id><Name>Boulan South Beach</Name><Region><Id>21648</Id><Name>Miami Beach - South Beach</Name><CityId>19741</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>2000 Collins Avenue</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Miami</City><State /><Zip>33139</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>(305) 878-6176</Tel><Fax>+1 (305) 7638836</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Miami Beach (Miami Beach Boardwalk), Boulan South Beach is minutes from Miami City Ballet and Bass Museum of Art.  This 4.5-star condo is within close proximity of Miami Beach Convention Center and The Fillmore Miami.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 52 air-conditioned rooms featuring microwaves and flat-screen televisions. Your pillowtop bed comes with down comforters and Egyptian cotton sheets, and all rooms are furnished with queen sofa beds. Cable programming and iPod docking stations are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature rainfall showerheads and designer toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Head down to the water and enjoy a day at the private beach, or take advantage of other recreational amenities including a health club and an outdoor pool. This Art Deco condo also features complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and shopping on site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite at one of the condo's 2 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). While enjoying a refreshing dip in the condo pool, you can order your favorite drink at the poolside bar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 4 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite at one of the condo's 2 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). While enjoying a refreshing dip in the condo pool, you can order your favorite drink at the poolside bar. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Head down to the water and enjoy a day at the private beach, or take advantage of other recreational amenities including a health club and an outdoor pool. This Art Deco condo also features complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and shopping on site. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 52 air-conditioned rooms featuring microwaves and flat-screen televisions. Your pillowtop bed comes with down comforters and Egyptian cotton sheets, and all rooms are furnished with queen sofa beds. Cable programming and iPod docking stations are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature rainfall showerheads and designer toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Miami Beach (Miami Beach Boardwalk), Boulan South Beach is minutes from Miami City Ballet and Bass Museum of Art.  This 4.5-star condo is within close proximity of Miami Beach Convention Center and The Fillmore Miami. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Miami City Ballet - 0.2 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bass Museum of Art - 0.2 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Miami Beach Convention Center - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Fillmore Miami - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;New World Symphony Park - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;New World Symphony Campus - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;New World Center - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Miami Beach Botanical Garden - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Anchor Shops - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bayshore Municipal Golf Course - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Holocaust Memorial - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Scott Rakow Youth Center - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lincoln Road Mall - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Miami Beach Golf Club - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Colony Theater - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Boulan South Beach is Miami, FL (MIA-Miami Intl.) - 15 km / 9.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>