<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10545498</Id><Name>Hollywood Historic Hotel</Name><Region><Id>21626</Id><Name>Hollywood/Beverly Hills</Name><CityId>19704</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>5162 Melrose Ave.</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Los Angeles</City><State /><Zip>90038</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>323-378-6312</Tel><Fax>323-378-6329</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hollywood Historic Hotel in Los Angeles, you'll be convenient to Paramount Studios and Hollywood Walk of Fame. This hotel is close to Dolby Theater and TCL Chinese Theatre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 62 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and LCD televisions. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You can find a meal at a coffee shop/café serving guests of Hollywood Historic Hotel, or stop in at a snack bar/deli.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour front desk, luggage storage, and an elevator (lift). Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is Noon &lt;br/&gt; You can find a meal at a coffee shop/café serving guests of Hollywood Historic Hotel, or stop in at a snack bar/deli. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 21 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 62 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and LCD televisions. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hollywood Historic Hotel in Los Angeles, you'll be convenient to Paramount Studios and Hollywood Walk of Fame. This hotel is close to Dolby Theater and TCL Chinese Theatre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Paramount Studios - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hollywood Palladium - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pantages Theatre - 2.3 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hollywood Walk of Fame - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hollywood and Vine - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wiltern Theatre - 2.5 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Capitol Records Tower - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Barnsdall Art Park - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Grauman's Egyptian Theatre - 3 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hollywood Wax Museum - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ripley's Believe It or Not - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hollywood and Highland Center - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;El Capitan Theatre - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dolby Theater - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;TCL Chinese Theatre - 3.3 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Burbank, CA (BUR-Bob Hope) - 13.1 km / 8.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;Los Angeles, CA (LAX-Los Angeles Intl.) - 17.6 km / 10.9 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hollywood Historic Hotel is Los Angeles, CA (LAX-Los Angeles Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 21 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>