<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10543704</Id><Name>The Resort on Mount Charleston</Name><Region><Id>21613</Id><Name>Others</Name><CityId>19680</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>2275 Kyle Canyon Road,</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Las Vegas</City><State /><Zip>89124</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>1-702-872-5500</Tel><Fax>1-702-872-5685</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-THEBhotel_Exterior_1.jpg</Url><Width>288</Width><Height>288</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-THEBhotel_Exterior_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>60</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>80</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/LAS-THEBhotel_Bar_Lounge_1.jpg</Url><Width>300</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/LAS-THEBhotel_Bar_Lounge_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>60</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>80</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at The Resort on Mount Charleston in Las Vegas (Mount Charleston), you'll be convenient to Toiyabe National Forest.  This family-friendly resort is within the vicinity of Mount Charleston Wilderness Area and Las Vegas Ski and Snowboard Resort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 62 guestrooms featuring iPod docking stations and DVD players. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Flat-screen televisions are provided for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and an arcade/game room. This resort also features wedding services, a fireplace in the lobby, and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the resort's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner. Dining is also available at a coffee shop/café, and room service (during limited hours) is provided. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-out, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff. Event facilities at this resort consist of a conference center, conference space, and meeting rooms. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 4 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the resort's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner. Dining is also available at a coffee shop/café, and room service (during limited hours) is provided. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and an arcade/game room. This resort also features wedding services, a fireplace in the lobby, and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 62 guestrooms featuring iPod docking stations and DVD players. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Flat-screen televisions are provided for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at The Resort on Mount Charleston in Las Vegas (Mount Charleston), you'll be convenient to Toiyabe National Forest.  This family-friendly resort is within the vicinity of Mount Charleston Wilderness Area and Las Vegas Ski and Snowboard Resort. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Toiyabe National Forest - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mount Charleston Wilderness Area - 7 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Las Vegas Ski and Snowboard Resort - 8.5 km / 5.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Spring Mountains National Recreation Area - 9.2 km / 5.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Red Rock Canyon - 15.7 km / 9.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Spring Mountain Ranch State Park - 25.3 km / 15.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Highland Falls Golf Club - 25.5 km / 15.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Las Vegas Paiute Golf Club Resort - 26.2 km / 16.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tournament Players Club - 27.5 km / 17.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bear's Best Golf Club - 28.4 km / 17.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Durango Hills Golf Club - 28.6 km / 17.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bruce Trent Park - 29.1 km / 18.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Badlands Golf Club - 29.2 km / 18.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Angel Park Golf Club - 29.5 km / 18.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Floyd Lamb State Park - 29.6 km / 18.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Resort on Mount Charleston is Las Vegas, NV (LAS-McCarran Intl.) - 44.8 km / 27.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for The Resort on Mount Charleston is Las Vegas, NV (LAS-McCarran Intl.) - 44.8 km / 27.8 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>