<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10543962</Id><Name>Club de Soleil All-Suite Resort</Name><Region><Id>21613</Id><Name>Others</Name><CityId>19680</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>5499 Tropicana Avenue</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Las Vegas</City><State /><Zip>89103</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>702-221-0400</Tel><Fax>1-702-252-0518</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Las Vegas (West of The Strip), Club De Soleil All-Suite Resort is close to Orleans Arena and Crystals at City Center. This condo is within close proximity of Bali Hai Golf Club and The Linq.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 282 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and microwaves. Cable television is provided for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and coffee/tea makers, and you can also request cribs/infant beds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including a health club, an outdoor pool, and a spa tub. Additional features include wedding services, tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills. Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the complimentary area shuttle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-out, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk. Event facilities at this condo consist of a conference center and conference space. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 4 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including a health club, an outdoor pool, and a spa tub. Additional features include wedding services, tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills. Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the complimentary area shuttle. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 282 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and microwaves. Cable television is provided for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and coffee/tea makers, and you can also request cribs/infant beds.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Las Vegas (West of The Strip), Club De Soleil All-Suite Resort is close to Orleans Arena and Crystals at City Center. This condo is within close proximity of Bali Hai Golf Club and The Linq. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Orleans Arena - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Crystals at City Center - 4.1 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bali Hai Golf Club - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Linq - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;High Roller - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Auto Collections - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Welcome to Fabulous Las Vegas Sign - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Town Square Las Vegas - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sands Expo Convention Center - 5.4 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fashion Show Mall - 5.4 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Desert Breeze Park - 5.7 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Atomic Testing Museum - 6.4 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Desert Research Institute - 6.5 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Thomas and Mack Center - 6.5 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Las Vegas Convention Center - 6.8 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Club De Soleil All-Suite Resort is Las Vegas, NV (LAS-McCarran Intl.) - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Club De Soleil All-Suite Resort is Las Vegas, NV (LAS-McCarran Intl.) - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property’s location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>