<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10547179</Id><Name>Sense Beach House</Name><Region><Id>21648</Id><Name>Miami Beach - South Beach</Name><CityId>19741</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>400 Ocean Drive</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Miami Beach</City><State /><Zip>33139</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>305-538-5529</Tel><Fax>305-590-5495</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Sense Beach House in Miami Beach (Ocean Drive), you'll be minutes from Jewish Museum of Florida and close to Port of Miami. This romantic hotel is within close proximity of Lummus Park Beach and Miami Beach Marina.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 18 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Sense Beach House, or find a snack in a coffee shop/café. Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, express check-in, and express check-out.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Sense Beach House, or find a snack in a coffee shop/café. Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 18 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Sense Beach House in Miami Beach (Ocean Drive), you'll be minutes from Jewish Museum of Florida and close to Port of Miami. This romantic hotel is within close proximity of Lummus Park Beach and Miami Beach Marina. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Jewish Museum of Florida - 0.2 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lummus Park Beach - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Miami Beach Marina - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Art Deco Welcome Center - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Art Deco Museum - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;South Pointe Park - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Wolfsonian Museum - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fifth and Alton Shopping Center - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Miami Beach Cinematheque - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Flamingo Park - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Anchor Shops - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lincoln Road Mall - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;New World Symphony Campus - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;New World Center - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Colony Theater - 2 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Sense Beach House is Miami, FL (MIA-Miami Intl.) - 14.8 km / 9.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Sense South Beach Hotel is Miami, FL (MIA-Miami Intl.) - 14.8 km / 9.2 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>