<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10543695</Id><Name>Eastside Cannery Casino Hotel</Name><Region><Id>21613</Id><Name>Others</Name><CityId>19680</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>5255 Boulder Highway</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Las Vegas</City><State /><Zip>89122</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>1 702 8565300</Tel><Fax>1-702-856-5588</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Eastside Cannery Casino &amp; Hotel in Las Vegas (East Las Vegas), you'll be close to Royal Links Golf Club and Ethel M Botanical Cactus Gardens. This casino hotel is within close proximity of Ethel M Chocolates Factory and Sam Boyd Stadium.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and irons/ironing boards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Head straight for the casino, or wait for that lucky feeling while you enjoy one of the other recreational opportunities, such as a nightclub and an outdoor pool. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at one of the hotel's dining establishments, which include 5 restaurants and a coffee shop/café. From your room, you can also access room service (during limited hours). Relax with a refreshing drink at one of the 3 bars/lounges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-out, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk. Event facilities at this hotel consist of a conference center, conference space, and a meeting room. Free valet parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is Noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at one of the hotel's dining establishments, which include 5 restaurants and a coffee shop/café. From your room, you can also access room service (during limited hours). Relax with a refreshing drink at one of the 3 bars/lounges. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Head straight for the casino, or wait for that lucky feeling while you enjoy one of the other recreational opportunities, such as a nightclub and an outdoor pool. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and irons/ironing boards.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Eastside Cannery Casino &amp; Hotel in Las Vegas (East Las Vegas), you'll be close to Royal Links Golf Club and Ethel M Botanical Cactus Gardens. This casino hotel is within close proximity of Ethel M Chocolates Factory and Sam Boyd Stadium. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Royal Links Golf Club - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ethel M Botanical Cactus Gardens - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ethel M Chocolates Factory - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sam Boyd Stadium - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Galleria at Sunset - 4.9 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wildhorse Golf Club - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Henderson Bird Viewing Preserve - 6.2 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Las Vegas National Golf Club - 6.4 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sunset Park - 6.7 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Clark County Library - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Boulevard Mall - 7.3 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marjorie Barrick Museum - 7.4 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Nevada-Las Vegas - 7.5 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Thomas and Mack Center - 7.8 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Touro University Nevada - 8 km / 4.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Eastside Cannery Casino &amp; Hotel is Las Vegas, NV (LAS-McCarran Intl.) - 8.6 km / 5.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Casino</Code><Text>Casino</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Giftshop</Code><Text>Gift Shop</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CurrencyExchangeService</Code><Text>Currency Exchange Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>NightClub</Code><Text>Night Club</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>