<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10545808</Id><Name>Garden Suite Hotel &amp; Resort</Name><Region><Id>21626</Id><Name>Hollywood/Beverly Hills</Name><CityId>19704</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>681 S Western Avenue</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Los Angeles</City><State /><Zip>90005</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>213-383-0000</Tel><Fax>213-383-3882</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You'll be centrally located in Los Angeles with a stay at Garden Suite Hotel, steps from Wiltern Theatre and close to University of Southern California.  This hotel is within close proximity of MacArthur Park and Paramount Studios.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and complimentary newspapers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or grab a snack at a coffee shop/café. Relax with a refreshing drink at one of the 2 bars/lounges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour business center, a computer station, and complimentary newspapers in the lobby. Event facilities at this hotel consist of conference space and meeting rooms. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or grab a snack at a coffee shop/café. Relax with a refreshing drink at one of the 2 bars/lounges. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and complimentary newspapers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>You'll be centrally located in Los Angeles with a stay at Garden Suite Hotel, steps from Wiltern Theatre and close to University of Southern California.  This hotel is within close proximity of MacArthur Park and Paramount Studios. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Wiltern Theatre - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;MacArthur Park - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Paramount Studios - 2.8 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Loyola Law School - 3.8 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Good Samaritan Hospital - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;L.A. Live - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;La Brea Tar Pits - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Craft and Folk Art Museum - 4.3 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Staples Center - 4.3 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Microsoft Theater - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Los Angeles Convention Center - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Grammy Museum - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hollywood Palladium - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Groundlings - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Los Angeles County Museum of Art - 4.6 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Los Angeles, CA (LAX-Los Angeles Intl.) - 15.6 km / 9.7 mi&lt;br /&gt;Burbank, CA (BUR-Bob Hope) - 15.7 km / 9.7 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Garden Suite Hotel is Los Angeles, CA (LAX-Los Angeles Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>