<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10546820</Id><Name>Posh South Beach Hotel &amp; Hostel</Name><Region><Id>21648</Id><Name>Miami Beach - South Beach</Name><CityId>19741</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>820 Collins Avenue</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Miami Beach</City><State /><Zip>33139</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>305-398-7000</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Posh South Beach Hostel in Miami Beach (Art Deco Historic District), you'll be minutes from Lummus Park Beach and Art Deco Welcome Center. This hostel is within close proximity of Art Deco Museum and The Wolfsonian Museum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 58 air-conditioned rooms featuring microwaves and plasma televisions. Your memory foam bed comes with Egyptian cotton sheets. Prepare your meals in the shared/communal kitchen. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms feature showers, designer toiletries, and complimentary toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a rooftop terrace and a terrace. Additional amenities at this Art Deco hostel include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Posh South Beach Hostel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include limo/town car service, express check-in, and complimentary newspapers in the lobby. A roundtrip airport shuttle is complimentary at scheduled times.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Posh South Beach Hostel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a rooftop terrace and a terrace. Additional amenities at this Art Deco hostel include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 58 air-conditioned rooms featuring microwaves and plasma televisions. Your memory foam bed comes with Egyptian cotton sheets. Prepare your meals in the shared/communal kitchen. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms feature showers, designer toiletries, and complimentary toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Posh South Beach Hostel in Miami Beach (Art Deco Historic District), you'll be minutes from Lummus Park Beach and Art Deco Welcome Center. This hostel is within close proximity of Art Deco Museum and The Wolfsonian Museum. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Lummus Park Beach - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Art Deco Welcome Center - 0.2 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Art Deco Museum - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Wolfsonian Museum - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Miami Beach Cinematheque - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jewish Museum of Florida - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Flamingo Park - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fifth and Alton Shopping Center - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Miami Beach Marina - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Anchor Shops - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lincoln Road Mall - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;New World Symphony Campus - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;New World Center - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;South Pointe Park - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Colony Theater - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Posh South Beach Hostel is Miami, FL (MIA-Miami Intl.) - 14.8 km / 9.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>