<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10551968</Id><Name>Melrose Mansion</Name><Region><Id>21680</Id><Name>French Quarter</Name><CityId>19791</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>937 Esplanade Avenue</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>New Orleans</City><State /><Zip>70116</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>504-944-2255</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in New Orleans (French Quarter), Melrose Mansion is minutes from Saint Augustine Church and Louisiana Museum of African American History. This romantic hotel is within close proximity of Backstreet Cultural Museum and Gallier House.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 21 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring iPod docking stations and LCD televisions. Your pillowtop bed comes with down comforters. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss out on recreational opportunities including an outdoor pool and a 24-hour fitness center. Additional features at this Art Deco hotel include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Mingle with other guests at a complimentary reception, held daily. For your convenience, a complimentary breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour front desk, luggage storage, and coffee/tea in the lobby. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 4 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Mingle with other guests at a complimentary reception, held daily. For your convenience, a complimentary breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 18 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Don’t miss out on recreational opportunities including an outdoor pool and a 24-hour fitness center. Additional features at this Art Deco hotel include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 21 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring iPod docking stations and LCD televisions. Your pillowtop bed comes with down comforters. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in New Orleans (French Quarter), Melrose Mansion is minutes from Saint Augustine Church and Louisiana Museum of African American History. This romantic hotel is within close proximity of Backstreet Cultural Museum and Gallier House. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Saint Augustine Church - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Louisiana Museum of African American History - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Backstreet Cultural Museum - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gallier House - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Frenchmen Street Jazz Clubs - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Beauregard-Keyes House - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Ursuline Convent - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;New Orleans Jazz Park - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Historic Voodoo Museum - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;New Orleans Mint - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Louis Armstrong Park - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Congo Square - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;French Market - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;New Orleans Jazz National Historical Park - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mahalia Jackson Theater - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;New Orleans, LA (NEW-Lakefront) - 8.6 km / 5.4 mi&lt;br /&gt;New Orleans, LA (MSY-Louis Armstrong New Orleans Intl.) - 19 km / 11.8 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Melrose Mansion is New Orleans, LA (MSY-Louis Armstrong New Orleans Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 18 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>