<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10551443</Id><Name>Frenchmen Orleans at 519</Name><Region><Id>21680</Id><Name>French Quarter</Name><CityId>19791</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>519 Frenchmen Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>New Orleans</City><State /><Zip>70116</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>+1 (504) 9433100</Tel><Fax>+1 (504) 3240863</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Frenchmen Orleans at 519, you'll be centrally located in New Orleans, steps from Frenchmen Street Jazz Clubs and minutes from New Orleans Mint. This condominium resort is within close proximity of Beauregard-Keyes House and Old Ursuline Convent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 19 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private patios. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers and sofa beds, and housekeeping is provided weekly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include luggage storage and laundry facilities. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 4 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 19 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private patios. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers and sofa beds, and housekeeping is provided weekly.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Frenchmen Orleans at 519, you'll be centrally located in New Orleans, steps from Frenchmen Street Jazz Clubs and minutes from New Orleans Mint. This condominium resort is within close proximity of Beauregard-Keyes House and Old Ursuline Convent. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Frenchmen Street Jazz Clubs - 0 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;New Orleans Mint - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Beauregard-Keyes House - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Ursuline Convent - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gallier House - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;French Market - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;New Orleans Jazz National Historical Park - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Historic Voodoo Museum - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pontalba Buildings - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Presbytere - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Louisiana State Museum - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Saint Louis Cathedral - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Washington Artillery Park - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Saint Augustine Church - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Backstreet Cultural Museum - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;New Orleans, LA (NEW-Lakefront) - 8.7 km / 5.4 mi&lt;br /&gt;New Orleans, LA (MSY-Louis Armstrong New Orleans Intl.) - 19.4 km / 12.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Frenchmen Orleans at 519 is New Orleans, LA (MSY-Louis Armstrong New Orleans Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Frenchmen Orleans at 519 is New Orleans, LA (MSY-Louis Armstrong New Orleans Intl.) - 19.6 km / 12.2 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Kitchen</Code><Text>Kitchen</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TV</Code><Text>TeleVision</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>