<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10559879</Id><Name>Flatiron Hotel</Name><Region><Id>64379</Id><Name>Midtown Manhattan</Name><CityId>19793</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>9 West 26th Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>New York</City><State /><Zip>10010</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>+1 (212) 8398000</Tel><Fax>+1 (516) 2556831</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Flatiron Hotel in New York (Chelsea), you'll be minutes from Madison Square Park and The Institute of Culinary Education.  This 4-star hotel is close to Empire State Building and Macy's.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 64 air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and minibars. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while 37-inch flat-screen televisions with cable programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms have designer toiletries and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include laptop-compatible safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, a television in the lobby, and complimentary use of a nearby fitness facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Flatiron Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour business center, limo/town car service, and a computer station. Event facilities at this hotel consist of a conference center and a meeting room.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 4 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Flatiron Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, a television in the lobby, and complimentary use of a nearby fitness facility. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 64 air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and minibars. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while 37-inch flat-screen televisions with cable programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms have designer toiletries and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include laptop-compatible safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Flatiron Hotel in New York (Chelsea), you'll be minutes from Madison Square Park and The Institute of Culinary Education.  This 4-star hotel is close to Empire State Building and Macy's. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Madison Square Park - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Institute of Culinary Education - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Flatiron Building - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Manhattan Mall - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fashion Institute of Technology - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Empire State Building - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Madison Square Garden - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Metropolitan Pavilion - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Penn Plaza Pavilion - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gramercy Park - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Herald Square - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Macy's - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Center for Jewish History - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rubin Museum of Himalayan Art - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Morgan Library and Museum - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;New York, NY (JRB-Downtown Manhattan Heliport) - 5 km / 3.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;New York, NY (LGA-LaGuardia) - 10.4 km / 6.5 mi&lt;br /&gt;Newark, NJ (EWR-Liberty Intl.) - 16.9 km / 10.5 mi&lt;br /&gt;New York, NY (JFK-John F. Kennedy Intl.) - 20.7 km / 12.8 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Flatiron Hotel is New York, NY (JFK-John F. Kennedy Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ContinentalBreakfast</Code><Text>Contintenal breakfast</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WakeUpService</Code><Text>Wake up service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FamilyRooms</Code><Text>Family rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>24HourFrontDesk</Code><Text>24 Hour Front Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Porters</Code><Text>Porters</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>