<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10551072</Id><Name>Hotel Preston</Name><Region><Id>21676</Id><Name>Nashville</Name><CityId>19784</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>733 Briley Parkway</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Nashville</City><State /><Zip>37217</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>615-361-5900</Tel><Fax>1-615-367-4468</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel8799-1227503249.jpg</Url><Width>100</Width><Height>100</Height><Bytes>3402</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel8799-1227503249.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2056</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel8799-269968782.jpg</Url><Width>200</Width><Height>200</Height><Bytes>4316</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel8799-269968782.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1967</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Preston Nashville Airport, A Provenance Hotel in Nashville, you'll be near the airport and close to Lane Motor Museum and Larry Keeton Theater.  This hotel is within the vicinity of Shelby Park and Tennessee Central Railway Museum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 196  air-conditioned guestrooms. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Premium TV channels and video-game consoles are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Bathrooms have designer toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreational amenities such as an outdoor pool and a fitness center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include high-speed (wired) Internet access (surcharge), a business center, and dry cleaning/laundry services. Planning an event in Nashville? This hotel has 8,800 square feet (1 square meters) of space consisting of conference space and a meeting room. A roundtrip airport shuttle is complimentary (available 24 hours).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreational amenities such as an outdoor pool and a fitness center. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 196  air-conditioned guestrooms. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Premium TV channels and video-game consoles are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Bathrooms have designer toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Preston Nashville Airport, A Provenance Hotel in Nashville, you'll be near the airport and close to Lane Motor Museum and Larry Keeton Theater.  This hotel is within the vicinity of Shelby Park and Tennessee Central Railway Museum. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Lane Motor Museum - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Larry Keeton Theater - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shelby Park - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tennessee Central Railway Museum - 5.1 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wave Country - 5.2 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tennessee State Fairgrounds - 5.4 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Two Rivers Golf Course - 5.7 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Escape Game Nashville - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Nashville Zoo - 6.4 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Greer Stadium - 6.4 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cumberland Park - 6.7 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fort Negley Park - 6.8 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Adventure Science Center - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Nissan Stadium - 7 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Riverfront Park - 7.1 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Preston Nashville Airport, A Provenance Hotel is Nashville, TN (BNA-Nashville Intl.) - 3 km / 1.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Hotel Preston is Nashville, TN (BNA-Nashville Intl.) - 3 km / 1.8 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property’s location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>21</Rank></HotelElement>