<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10557647</Id><Name>City Club Hotel</Name><Region><Id>64379</Id><Name>Midtown Manhattan</Name><CityId>19793</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>55 W 44th Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>New York City</City><State /><Zip>10036</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>2129215500</Tel><Fax>212.944.5544</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at City Club Hotel, you'll be centrally located in New York, steps from International Center of Photography and minutes from Broadway. This 4-star hotel is close to Times Square and Rockefeller Center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 65  air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and iPod docking stations. Your pillowtop bed comes with down comforters and Frette Italian sheets. Plasma televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature designer toiletries and complimentary toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). Additional features include tour/ticket assistance and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Breakfast is available for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour business center, limo/town car service, and a computer station. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Breakfast is available for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). Additional features include tour/ticket assistance and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 65  air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and iPod docking stations. Your pillowtop bed comes with down comforters and Frette Italian sheets. Plasma televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature designer toiletries and complimentary toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at City Club Hotel, you'll be centrally located in New York, steps from International Center of Photography and minutes from Broadway. This 4-star hotel is close to Times Square and Rockefeller Center. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;International Center of Photography - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bryant Park - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;New York Public Library - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Broadway - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Toys 'R' Us Times Square - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Times Square - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;NBC Studios - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Minskoff Theater - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;New Amsterdam Theater - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Top of the Rock Observation Deck - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rockefeller Center - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Madame Tussauds Wax Museum - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Radio City Music Hall - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Grand Central Terminal - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Patrick's Cathedral - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;New York, NY (JRB-Downtown Manhattan Heliport) - 6.4 km / 4 mi&lt;br /&gt;New York, NY (LGA-LaGuardia) - 9.5 km / 5.9 mi&lt;br /&gt;Newark, NJ (EWR-Liberty Intl.) - 18 km / 11.2 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for City Club Hotel is New York, NY (LGA-LaGuardia). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>