<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10552165</Id><Name>Hotel on Rivington</Name><Region><Id>21687</Id><Name>Lower Manhattan</Name><CityId>19793</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>107 Rivington Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>New York City</City><State /><Zip>10002</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>1-212-475-2600</Tel><Fax>+1 (212) 4480811</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Hotel On Rivington places you in the heart of New York, minutes from Lower East Side Tenement Museum and close to New York University.  This 4-star hotel is close to Brooklyn Bridge and Empire State Building.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 110 air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and minibars. Your Tempur-Pedic bed comes with Frette Italian sheets. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, and flat-screen televisions with cable programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms have designer toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss out on recreational opportunities including a nightclub and a fitness center. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Relax with a refreshing drink at one of the 2 bars/lounges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a 24-hour business center, and limo/town car service.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 4 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Relax with a refreshing drink at one of the 2 bars/lounges. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Don’t miss out on recreational opportunities including a nightclub and a fitness center. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 110 air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and minibars. Your Tempur-Pedic bed comes with Frette Italian sheets. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, and flat-screen televisions with cable programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms have designer toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Hotel On Rivington places you in the heart of New York, minutes from Lower East Side Tenement Museum and close to New York University.  This 4-star hotel is close to Brooklyn Bridge and Empire State Building. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Lower East Side Tenement Museum - 0.2 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;New Museum - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mott Street - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eldridge Street Synagogue - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Children's Museum of the Arts - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Merchant's House Museum - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Peter Cooper Park - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Orpheum Theater - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of Chinese in Americas - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Manhattan Bridge - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;New York University - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Collect Pond Park - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Washington Square Park - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Williamsburg Bridge - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;African Burial Ground National Monument - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;New York, NY (JRB-Downtown Manhattan Heliport) - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi&lt;br /&gt;New York, NY (LGA-LaGuardia) - 11.5 km / 7.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;Newark, NJ (EWR-Liberty Intl.) - 16.3 km / 10.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;New York, NY (JFK-John F. Kennedy Intl.) - 19.3 km / 12 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel On Rivington is New York, NY (JFK-John F. Kennedy Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BeautyShop</Code><Text>Beauty Shop</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Doctoroncall</Code><Text>Doctor on call</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>NightClub</Code><Text>Night Club</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>