<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10552599</Id><Name>World Center Hotel</Name><Region><Id>21687</Id><Name>Lower Manhattan</Name><CityId>19793</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>144 Washington Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>New York</City><State /><Zip>10006</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>212-577-2933</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at World Center Hotel in New York (Wall Street - Financial District), you'll be minutes from The National September 11 Memorial and New York Stock Exchange. This 4-star hotel is close to Brooklyn Bridge and Ellis Island.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and LCD televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms have designer toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of World Center Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, express check-in, and dry cleaning/laundry services. Event facilities at this hotel consist of conference space, meeting rooms, and a meeting room.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of World Center Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and LCD televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms have designer toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at World Center Hotel in New York (Wall Street - Financial District), you'll be minutes from The National September 11 Memorial and New York Stock Exchange. This 4-star hotel is close to Brooklyn Bridge and Ellis Island. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;The National September 11 Memorial - 0 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;FDNY Memorial - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Trinity Church - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;National September 11 Memorial Museum - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;World Financial Center - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;New York Stock Exchange - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;One World Trade Center - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Federal Hall - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Federal Reserve Bank of New York - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Paul's Chapel - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of American Finance - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Museum of the American Indian - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Skyscraper Museum - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of Jewish Heritage - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Woolworth Building - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;New York, NY (JRB-Downtown Manhattan Heliport) - 1 km / 0.6 mi&lt;br /&gt;Newark, NJ (EWR-Liberty Intl.) - 13.9 km / 8.7 mi&lt;br /&gt;New York, NY (LGA-LaGuardia) - 14 km / 8.7 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for World Center Hotel is New York, NY (LGA-LaGuardia). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>