<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10557650</Id><Name>Library Hotel</Name><Region><Id>64379</Id><Name>Midtown Manhattan</Name><CityId>19793</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>299 Madison Avenue</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>New York City</City><State /><Zip>10017</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>1-212-983-4500</Tel><Fax>+1 (212) 4999099</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at The Library Hotel in New York (Midtown East - Grand Central), you'll be minutes from Grand Central Terminal and Chrysler Building. This 4-star hotel is close to Empire State Building and Macy's.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 60 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and flat-screen televisions. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while iPod docking stations and cable programming provide entertainment. Bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. Additional features include concierge services and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves lunch, dinner, and brunch, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Meet other guests and eat at a complimentary reception. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a 24-hour business center, and complimentary newspapers in the lobby. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 1 PM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves lunch, dinner, and brunch, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Meet other guests and eat at a complimentary reception. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. Additional features include concierge services and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 60 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and flat-screen televisions. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while iPod docking stations and cable programming provide entertainment. Bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at The Library Hotel in New York (Midtown East - Grand Central), you'll be minutes from Grand Central Terminal and Chrysler Building. This 4-star hotel is close to Empire State Building and Macy's. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Grand Central Terminal - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;New York Public Library - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chrysler Building - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Morgan Library and Museum - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bryant Park - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;International Center of Photography - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Empire State Building - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Macy's - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Herald Square - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;NBC Studios - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Times Square - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Toys 'R' Us Times Square - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Patrick's Cathedral - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rockefeller Center - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Top of the Rock Observation Deck - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;New York, NY (JRB-Downtown Manhattan Heliport) - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi&lt;br /&gt;New York, NY (LGA-LaGuardia) - 9.4 km / 5.8 mi&lt;br /&gt;Newark, NJ (EWR-Liberty Intl.) - 18 km / 11.2 mi&lt;br /&gt;New York, NY (JFK-John F. Kennedy Intl.) - 20.5 km / 12.7 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Library Hotel is New York, NY (JFK-John F. Kennedy Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>