<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10567724</Id><Name>Four Points by Sheraton San Antonio Airport</Name><Region><Id>19916</Id><Name>San Antonio, TX</Name><CityId>19916</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>8818 Jones Maltsberger</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>San Antonio</City><State /><Zip>78216</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>+1 (210) 348-9960</Tel><Fax>+1 (210) 524-0095</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/SKF-FOU1hotel_Exterior_1.jpg</Url><Width>343</Width><Height>230</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/SKF-FOU1hotel_Exterior_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Four Points by Sheraton San Antonio Airport, you'll be centrally located in San Antonio, convenient to North Star Mall and Marion Koogler McNay Art Museum.  This family-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Quarry Golf Club and Alamo Quarry Market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 120 guestrooms featuring refrigerators and microwaves. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while 37-inch LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment. Bathrooms have shower/tub combinations and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities including an outdoor pool and a fitness center. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, a fireplace in the lobby, and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Four Points by Sheraton San Antonio Airport. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Breakfast is available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour business center, express check-in, and express check-out. Planning an event in San Antonio? This hotel has facilities measuring 987 square feet (92 square meters), including a meeting room. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided at no charge.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Four Points by Sheraton San Antonio Airport. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Breakfast is available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 21 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities including an outdoor pool and a fitness center. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, a fireplace in the lobby, and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 120 guestrooms featuring refrigerators and microwaves. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while 37-inch LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment. Bathrooms have shower/tub combinations and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Four Points by Sheraton San Antonio Airport, you'll be centrally located in San Antonio, convenient to North Star Mall and Marion Koogler McNay Art Museum.  This family-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Quarry Golf Club and Alamo Quarry Market. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;North Star Mall - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Quarry Golf Club - 2.8 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Alamo Quarry Market - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marion Koogler McNay Art Museum - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Texas Transportation Museum - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;McAllister Park - 5.7 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Silverhorn Golf Club of Texas - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Malibu Castle - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Trinity University - 6.6 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Antonio Zoo and Aquarium - 6.7 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Japanese Tea Gardens - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Witte Museum - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wonderland of the Americas Mall - 7.2 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brackenridge Park - 7.3 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;United States Army Medical Department Museum - 7.3 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Four Points by Sheraton San Antonio Airport is San Antonio, TX (SAT-San Antonio Intl.) - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Best Western Casa Linda Inn is San Antonio, TX (SAT-San Antonio Intl.) - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property’s location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0. 1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 21 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ATMMachine</Code><Text>ATM Machine</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>