<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10562940</Id><Name>Four Points by Sheraton Philadelphia City Center</Name><Region><Id>21769</Id><Name>Philadelphia</Name><CityId>19857</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1201 Race Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Philadelphia</City><State /><Zip>19107</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>+1 (215) 496-2700</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Four Points by Sheraton Philadelphia City Center places you in the heart of Philadelphia, walking distance from Pennsylvania Convention Center and Reading Terminal Market. This hotel is close to Liberty Bell Center and Independence Hall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 92 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature designer toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and gift shops/newsstands. Additional features include shopping on site, wedding services, and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a business center, and express check-out. Event facilities at this hotel consist of conference space and meeting rooms. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and gift shops/newsstands. Additional features include shopping on site, wedding services, and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 92 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature designer toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Four Points by Sheraton Philadelphia City Center places you in the heart of Philadelphia, walking distance from Pennsylvania Convention Center and Reading Terminal Market. This hotel is close to Liberty Bell Center and Independence Hall. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Pennsylvania Convention Center - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Reading Terminal Market - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of American Art - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Masonic Temple - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;City Hall - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Free Library of Philadelphia - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jefferson University Hospital - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;African American Museum - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Franklin Square - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Declaration House - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;United States Mint - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Atwater Kent Museum of Philadelphia - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cathedral Basilica of Saints Peter and Paul - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Constitution Center - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Four Points by Sheraton Philadelphia City Center is Philadelphia, PA (PHL-Philadelphia Intl.) - 11.2 km / 6.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Four Points by Sheraton Philadelphia City Center is Philadelphia, PA (PHL-Philadelphia Intl.) - 11.2 km / 6.9 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ValetParking</Code><Text>Valet parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lounge</Code><Text>Lounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>24HourFrontDesk</Code><Text>24 Hour Front Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>