<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10562919</Id><Name>Le Meridien Philadelphia</Name><Region><Id>21769</Id><Name>Philadelphia</Name><CityId>19857</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1421 Arch Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Philadelphia</City><State /><Zip>19102</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>+1 (215) 422-8200</Tel><Fax>+1 (215) 422-8277</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/69Afront.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/69Athumbfront.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2877</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/69Abed.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/69Athumbbed.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1855</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/69Amap.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/69Athumbmap.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2377</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Le Meridien Philadelphia, you'll be centrally located in Philadelphia, steps from Museum of American Art and Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts.  This 4-star hotel is close to Liberty Bell Center and Independence Hall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 202 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Your pillowtop bed comes with down comforters. Cable programming provides entertainment, and wired and wireless Internet access is available for a surcharge. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. Additional features include wedding services, a television in the lobby, and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a 24-hour business center, and express check-in. Planning an event in Philadelphia? This hotel has facilities measuring 7000 square feet (650 square meters), including a meeting room.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is Noon &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. Additional features include wedding services, a television in the lobby, and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 202 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Your pillowtop bed comes with down comforters. Cable programming provides entertainment, and wired and wireless Internet access is available for a surcharge. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Le Meridien Philadelphia, you'll be centrally located in Philadelphia, steps from Museum of American Art and Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts.  This 4-star hotel is close to Liberty Bell Center and Independence Hall. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Museum of American Art - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Masonic Temple - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;City Hall - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Free Library of Philadelphia - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Reading Terminal Market - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pennsylvania Convention Center - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Art Institute of Philadelphia - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cathedral Basilica of Saints Peter and Paul - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Academy of Natural Sciences - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Academy of Music - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jefferson University Hospital - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Historical Society of Pennsylvania - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ben Franklin National Memorial - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kimmel Center for the Performing Arts - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Le Meridien Philadelphia is Philadelphia, PA (PHL-Philadelphia Intl.) - 10.8 km / 6.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ValetParking</Code><Text>Valet parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Security24Hour</Code><Text>24-hour security</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shops</Code><Text>Shops</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>24HourFrontDesk</Code><Text>24 Hour Front Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Porters</Code><Text>Porters</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ATMMachine</Code><Text>ATM Machine</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>