<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>105665605</Id><Name>Joy Beach</Name><Region><Id>20837</Id><Name>Perissa</Name><CityId>16716</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Perivolos, Thira 847 03</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>SANTORINI</City><State /><Zip /><Country>GREECE</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>12</CountRooms><CountFloors>1</CountFloors><CheckInTime>14:00</CheckInTime><CheckOutTime>12:00</CheckOutTime></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1033/16/25/56/8/iBGd2kKV_5db35ad912b72bb1ac90f000e1a742e4.jpg</Url><Width>840</Width><Height>460</Height><Bytes>39708</Bytes><Caption>iBGd2kKV_5db35ad912b72bb1ac90f000e1a742e4</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1033/16/25/56/8/iBGd2kKV_5db35ad912b72bb1ac90f000e1a742e4thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>127</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2279</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1033/16/25/56/8/2uy7Ik5X_2e7e2819542561b0aa814dbec048a4b2.jpg</Url><Width>840</Width><Height>460</Height><Bytes>43350</Bytes><Caption>2uy7Ik5X_2e7e2819542561b0aa814dbec048a4b2</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1033/16/25/56/8/2uy7Ik5X_2e7e2819542561b0aa814dbec048a4b2thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>127</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2521</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1033/16/25/56/8/HRpOmk5S_6f538dfec45e41e3fc8e2cff7de6ff99.jpg</Url><Width>840</Width><Height>460</Height><Bytes>65320</Bytes><Caption>HRpOmk5S_6f538dfec45e41e3fc8e2cff7de6ff99</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1033/16/25/56/8/HRpOmk5S_6f538dfec45e41e3fc8e2cff7de6ff99thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>127</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2898</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1033/16/25/56/8/zVvDXsZW_b1eba442554c2b2a2ccf9c2cd23bfe5b.jpg</Url><Width>840</Width><Height>460</Height><Bytes>34652</Bytes><Caption>zVvDXsZW_b1eba442554c2b2a2ccf9c2cd23bfe5b</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1033/16/25/56/8/zVvDXsZW_b1eba442554c2b2a2ccf9c2cd23bfe5bthumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>127</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2121</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Joy Beach Hotel in Santorini (Perivolos), you'll be convenient to Perivolos Beach and Waterpark Santorini.  This beach apartment is within close proximity of Perissa Beach and Museum of Minerals and Fossils.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 12 air-conditioned rooms featuring fireplaces and private pools. Rooms have private furnished balconies. Kitchenettes are outfitted with refrigerators and stovetops. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, and LCD televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Relax and unwind with body treatments and facials. After a day at the private beach, you can enjoy other recreational amenities, which include a seasonal outdoor pool. This apartment also features complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and gift shops/newsstands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the apartment's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a computer station, and express check-in. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the apartment's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on property policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Relax and unwind with body treatments and facials. After a day at the private beach, you can enjoy other recreational amenities, which include a seasonal outdoor pool. This apartment also features complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and gift shops/newsstands. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 12 air-conditioned rooms featuring fireplaces and private pools. Rooms have private furnished balconies. Kitchenettes are outfitted with refrigerators and stovetops. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, and LCD televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Joy Beach Hotel in Santorini (Perivolos), you'll be convenient to Perivolos Beach and Waterpark Santorini.  This beach apartment is within close proximity of Perissa Beach and Museum of Minerals and Fossils. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Perivolos Beach - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Waterpark Santorini - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Perissa Beach - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of Minerals and Fossils - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vlychada Beach - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ancient Thira - 2.8 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Panagia Episkopi - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Prophet Elias Monastery - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eros Beach - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wine Museum - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Open Air Cinema Kamari - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Boutari Winery - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gavalas Vineyard - 4.6 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Antoniou Winery - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Osho Santorini - 4.8 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Joy Beach Hotel is Thira (JTR-Santorini National) - 6.8 km / 4.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on property policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>CarRentDesk</Code><Text>Car rental desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MultilingualStaff</Code><Text>Multilingual Staff</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OnSiteBeach</Code><Text>On-Site Beach</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Doctoroncall</Code><Text>Doctor on call</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>