<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10562935</Id><Name>Club Quarters at Philadelphia</Name><Region><Id>21769</Id><Name>Philadelphia</Name><CityId>19857</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1628 Chestnut Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Philadelphia</City><State /><Zip>19103</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>215-282-5000</Tel><Fax>+1 (215) 2825001</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Club Quarters in Philadelphia, you'll be centrally located in Philadelphia, steps from Art Institute of Philadelphia and minutes from Rittenhouse Square. This 4-star hotel is close to Liberty Bell Center and Independence Hall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 275 air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, express check-in, and express check-out. Planning an event in Philadelphia? This hotel has 1430 square feet (133 square meters) of space consisting of conference space and meeting rooms. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 275 air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Club Quarters in Philadelphia, you'll be centrally located in Philadelphia, steps from Art Institute of Philadelphia and minutes from Rittenhouse Square. This 4-star hotel is close to Liberty Bell Center and Independence Hall. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Art Institute of Philadelphia - 0 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rittenhouse Square - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Academy of Music - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;City Hall - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Masonic Temple - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Free Library of Philadelphia - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kimmel Center for the Performing Arts - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of American Art - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Historical Society of Pennsylvania - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cathedral Basilica of Saints Peter and Paul - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rosenbach Museum and Library - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Academy of Natural Sciences - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mutter Museum - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ben Franklin National Memorial - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Club Quarters in Philadelphia is Philadelphia, PA (PHL-Philadelphia Intl.) - 10.3 km / 6.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>