<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10561319</Id><Name>Residence Inn by Marriott Orlando East/UCF</Name><Region><Id>21736</Id><Name>Others</Name><CityId>19827</CityId></Region><Type>Apartments</Type><Address><Address1>11651 University Blvd.</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Orlando</City><State /><Zip>32817</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>+1 (407) 513-9000</Tel><Fax>+1 (407) 513-9001</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Residence Inn by Marriott Orlando East/UCF Area in Orlando, you'll be convenient to St. Matthews University and University of Central Florida Art Gallery. This hotel is within close proximity of University of Central Florida and University of Central Florida Arena.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 99 individually furnished guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed, and all rooms are furnished with sofa beds. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming provides entertainment. Conveniences include safes and desks, as well as phones with free local calls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreational amenities such as an outdoor pool and a spa tub. Additional features include a fireplace in the lobby, a television in the lobby, and a picnic area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite from a snack bar/deli serving guests of Residence Inn by Marriott Orlando East/UCF Area. Meet other guests and eat at a complimentary reception. A complimentary hot/cold buffet breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour business center, express check-in, and express check-out.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite from a snack bar/deli serving guests of Residence Inn by Marriott Orlando East/UCF Area. Meet other guests and eat at a complimentary reception. A complimentary hot/cold buffet breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreational amenities such as an outdoor pool and a spa tub. Additional features include a fireplace in the lobby, a television in the lobby, and a picnic area. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 99 individually furnished guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed, and all rooms are furnished with sofa beds. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming provides entertainment. Conveniences include safes and desks, as well as phones with free local calls.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Residence Inn by Marriott Orlando East/UCF Area in Orlando, you'll be convenient to St. Matthews University and University of Central Florida Art Gallery. This hotel is within close proximity of University of Central Florida and University of Central Florida Arena. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;St. Matthews University - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Central Florida Art Gallery - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Central Florida - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Central Florida Arena - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bright House Networks Stadium - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Florida Technical College - 3.3 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Congo River Golf - East Orlando - 3.9 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Waterford Lakes Town Center - 5.1 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Twin Rivers Golf Course - 6.7 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Full Sail University - 8.4 km / 5.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Winter Pines Golf Club - 9.2 km / 5.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albin Polasek Museum and Sculpture Gardens - 12.2 km / 7.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ventura Country Club - 12.5 km / 7.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cornell Fine Arts Museum - 12.5 km / 7.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Winter Park Country Club - 12.7 km / 7.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Orlando, FL (SFB-Orlando Sanford Intl.) - 19.9 km / 12.4 mi&lt;br /&gt;Orlando, FL (MCO-Orlando Intl.) - 20.5 km / 12.7 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Residence Inn by Marriott Orlando East/UCF Area is Orlando, FL (MCO-Orlando Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ContinentalBreakfast</Code><Text>Contintenal breakfast</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WakeUpService</Code><Text>Wake up service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarRentDesk</Code><Text>Car rental desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Kitchen</Code><Text>Kitchen</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Freenewspaper</Code><Text>Free Newspaper</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TV</Code><Text>TeleVision</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Medical centre</Code><Text>Medical centre</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>24HourFrontDesk</Code><Text>24 Hour Front Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BeautyShop</Code><Text>Beauty Shop</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>