<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10571571</Id><Name>Courtyard by Marriott San Diego Airport/Liberty Station</Name><Region><Id>21822</Id><Name>Downtown/Airport (SAN)</Name><CityId>19918</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>2592 Laning Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>San Diego</City><State /><Zip>92106</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>+1 (619) 221-1900</Tel><Fax>+1 (619) 221-0900</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Courtyard by Marriott San Diego Airport/Liberty Station in San Diego (Beach Cities), you'll be close to Rock Church and Seaworld. This family-friendly hotel is within close proximity of NTC Promenade and Marine Corps Recruit Depot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 197 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and premium TV channels provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss out on recreational opportunities including an outdoor pool and a fitness center. This hotel also features concierge services, wedding services, and a fireplace in the lobby. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the complimentary area shuttle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant or in a coffee shop/café. Or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, express check-in, and express check-out. Event facilities at this hotel consist of conference space and meeting rooms. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided at no charge.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 4 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant or in a coffee shop/café. Or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Don’t miss out on recreational opportunities including an outdoor pool and a fitness center. This hotel also features concierge services, wedding services, and a fireplace in the lobby. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the complimentary area shuttle. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 197 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and premium TV channels provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Courtyard by Marriott San Diego Airport/Liberty Station in San Diego (Beach Cities), you'll be close to Rock Church and Seaworld. This family-friendly hotel is within close proximity of NTC Promenade and Marine Corps Recruit Depot. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Rock Church - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;NTC Promenade - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marine Corps Recruit Depot - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Town Trolley Tours - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Town San Diego State Park - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Heritage Park - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Point Loma Nazarene University - 3.5 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Presidio Park - 3.5 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ocean Beach Athletic Area - 3.6 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Seaworld - 3.7 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Junipero Serra Museum - 3.7 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ocean Beach Park - 4.1 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;B Street Cruise Ship Terminal - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maritime Museum of San Diego - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Port of San Diego - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Courtyard by Marriott San Diego Airport/Liberty Station is San Diego, CA (SAN-San Diego Intl.) - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Courtyard by Marriott San Diego Airport is San Diego, CA (SAN-San Diego Intl.) - 2 km / 1.3 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ContinentalBreakfast</Code><Text>Contintenal breakfast</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InRoomMovies</Code><Text>In-room movies</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WakeUpService</Code><Text>Wake up service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarRentDesk</Code><Text>Car rental desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CoffeeShop</Code><Text>Coffee shop</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lounge</Code><Text>Lounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Freenewspaper</Code><Text>Free Newspaper</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Icemachine</Code><Text>Ice Machine</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TV</Code><Text>TeleVision</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CurrencyExchangeService</Code><Text>Currency Exchange Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Medical centre</Code><Text>Medical centre</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Scuba Diving</Code><Text>Scuba Diving</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>24HourFrontDesk</Code><Text>24 Hour Front Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BeautyShop</Code><Text>Beauty Shop</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ATMMachine</Code><Text>ATM Machine</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>