<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10572309</Id><Name>White Swan Inn</Name><Region><Id>21827</Id><Name>Union Square - Nob Hill</Name><CityId>19919</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>845 Bush St.</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>San Francisco</City><State /><Zip>94108</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>415-775-1755</Tel><Fax>+1 (415) 7755717</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at White Swan Inn, you'll be centrally located in San Francisco, steps from Marines Memorial Theater and Un-Scripted Theater Company.  This family-friendly hotel is close to Union Square and Lombard Street.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Treat yourself to a stay in one of the 26 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring fireplaces and LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include refrigerators and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and an arcade/game room. Additional amenities include tour/ticket assistance and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A complimentary hot/cold buffet breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour business center, limo/town car service, and a computer station. Planning an event in San Francisco? This hotel has facilities measuring 360 square feet (33 square meters), including a meeting room.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM   &lt;br/&gt; A complimentary hot/cold buffet breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and an arcade/game room. Additional amenities include tour/ticket assistance and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility. &lt;br /&gt; Treat yourself to a stay in one of the 26 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring fireplaces and LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include refrigerators and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at White Swan Inn, you'll be centrally located in San Francisco, steps from Marines Memorial Theater and Un-Scripted Theater Company.  This family-friendly hotel is close to Union Square and Lombard Street. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Marines Memorial Theater - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Un-Scripted Theater Company - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;SF Playhouse - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Grace Cathedral - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lorraine Hansberry Theatre - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Francisco Magic Parlor - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Alcove Theater - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;SHN Curran Theatre - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;American Conservatory Theater - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Union Square - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marrakech Magic Theater - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chinese Historical Society of America - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Xanadu Gallery - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kong Chow Temple - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cable Car Museum - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Oakland, CA (OAK-Oakland Intl.) - 19.4 km / 12.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;San Francisco, CA (SFO-San Francisco Intl.) - 19.5 km / 12.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for White Swan Inn is San Francisco, CA (SFO-San Francisco Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for White Swan Inn, a Joie de Vivre Boutique Hotel is San Francisco, CA (SFO-San Francisco Intl.) - 19.5 km / 12.1 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property’s location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>