<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10574234</Id><Name>The Hay-Adams</Name><Region><Id>21948</Id><Name>Capitol Hill - Dupont Circle</Name><CityId>20071</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>800 16th Street Nw</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Washington</City><State /><Zip>20006</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>202.638.6600</Tel><Fax>1-202-293-2396</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at The Hay-Adams, you'll be centrally located in Washington, steps from Lafayette Park and Lafayette Square. This 5-star hotel is close to White House and George Washington University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 145  air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Your pillowtop bed comes with down comforters and Egyptian cotton sheets. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature designer toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and babysitting/childcare. Additional features include tour/ticket assistance and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour business center, limo/town car service, and express check-out. Event facilities at this hotel consist of conference space, meeting rooms, and a meeting room.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and babysitting/childcare. Additional features include tour/ticket assistance and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 145  air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Your pillowtop bed comes with down comforters and Egyptian cotton sheets. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature designer toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at The Hay-Adams, you'll be centrally located in Washington, steps from Lafayette Park and Lafayette Square. This 5-star hotel is close to White House and George Washington University. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Lafayette Park - 0 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lafayette Square - 0 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. John's Church - 0 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;Decatur House - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ellipse - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Treasury Building - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;White House - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Blair House - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Renwick Gallery - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;McPherson Square - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Farragut Square - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eisenhower Executive Office Building - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Corcoran Gallery of Art - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Franklin Square - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Geographic Society - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Hay-Adams is Washington, DC (DCA-Ronald Reagan Washington National) - 5.7 km / 3.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The closest major airports to The Hay-Adams are:&lt;br /&gt;Washington, DC (DCA-Ronald Reagan Washington National) - 5.7 km / 3.5 mi&lt;br /&gt;Washington, DC (IAD-Washington Dulles Intl.) - 36.1 km / 22.4 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Hay-Adams is Washington, DC (DCA-Ronald Reagan Washington National). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property’s location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>