<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10571697</Id><Name>Andrews Hotel</Name><Region><Id>21827</Id><Name>Union Square - Nob Hill</Name><CityId>19919</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>624 Post St.</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>San Francisco</City><State /><Zip>94109</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>1-415-563-6877</Tel><Fax>1-415-928-6919</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at The Andrews Hotel, you'll be centrally located in San Francisco, steps from Lorraine Hansberry Theatre and SHN Curran Theatre. This hotel is close to Union Square and Lombard Street.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of 48 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and complimentary newspapers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of The Andrews Hotel. Meet other guests and eat at a complimentary reception. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of The Andrews Hotel. Meet other guests and eat at a complimentary reception. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of 48 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and complimentary newspapers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at The Andrews Hotel, you'll be centrally located in San Francisco, steps from Lorraine Hansberry Theatre and SHN Curran Theatre. This hotel is close to Union Square and Lombard Street. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Lorraine Hansberry Theatre - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;SHN Curran Theatre - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marines Memorial Theater - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;American Conservatory Theater - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marrakech Magic Theater - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Alcove Theater - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Un-Scripted Theater Company - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;SF Playhouse - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Glide Memorial United Methodist Church - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Francisco Magic Parlor - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Union Square - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Grace Cathedral - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Powell and Market Cable Car Turnaround - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Westfield San Francisco Center Shopping Mall - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Francisco Visitor's Center - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;San Francisco, CA (SFO-San Francisco Intl.) - 19.2 km / 12 mi&lt;br /&gt;Oakland, CA (OAK-Oakland Intl.) - 19.4 km / 12.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Andrews Hotel is San Francisco, CA (SFO-San Francisco Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>