<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10573892</Id><Name>The Quincy</Name><Region><Id>21948</Id><Name>Capitol Hill - Dupont Circle</Name><CityId>20071</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1823 L Street Nw</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Washington</City><State /><Zip>20036</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>202-223-4320</Tel><Fax>1-202-293-4977</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/QUINfront.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/QUINthumbfront.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2862</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/QUINbed.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/QUINthumbbed.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2222</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/QUINmap.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/QUINthumbmap.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2194</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The Quincy is in the heart of Washington, walking distance from Farragut Square and Cathedral of St. Matthew the Apostle.  This hotel is close to George Washington University and White House.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 99 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and microwaves. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access is available. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and complimentary use of a nearby fitness facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and dry cleaning/laundry services. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and complimentary use of a nearby fitness facility. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 99 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and microwaves. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access is available. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The Quincy is in the heart of Washington, walking distance from Farragut Square and Cathedral of St. Matthew the Apostle.  This hotel is close to George Washington University and White House. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Farragut Square - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cathedral of St. Matthew the Apostle - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Charles Sumner School Museum and Archives - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Foundry Gallery - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Christian Heurich House - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Geographic Society - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Decatur House - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Blair House - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Renwick Gallery - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Embassy of Australia - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;George Washington University - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. John's Church - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lafayette Park - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lafayette Square - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Alexander Pushkin Statue - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Quincy is Washington, DC (DCA-Ronald Reagan Washington National) - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The closest major airports to The Quincy are:&lt;br /&gt;Washington, DC (DCA-Ronald Reagan Washington National) - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi&lt;br /&gt;Washington, DC (IAD-Washington Dulles Intl.) - 35.5 km / 22.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Quincy is Washington, DC (DCA-Ronald Reagan Washington National). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property’s location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>