<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10570513</Id><Name>Residence Inn by Marriott San Diego Central</Name><Region><Id>21825</Id><Name>Northern Region</Name><CityId>19918</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>5400 Kearny Mesa Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>San Diego</City><State /><Zip>92111</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>+1 (858) 278-2100</Tel><Fax>+1 (858) 268-3926</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Residence Inn By Marriott San Diego Central in San Diego (Central San Diego), you'll be close to Marine Corps Air Station Miramar.  This family-friendly hotel is within the vicinity of University of San Diego and San Diego State University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 144 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including an outdoor pool, a spa tub, and a fitness center. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A complimentary full breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, express check-in, and express check-out. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 4 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; A complimentary full breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including an outdoor pool, a spa tub, and a fitness center. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 144 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Residence Inn By Marriott San Diego Central in San Diego (Central San Diego), you'll be close to Marine Corps Air Station Miramar.  This family-friendly hotel is within the vicinity of University of San Diego and San Diego State University. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Marine Corps Air Station Miramar - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Qualcomm Stadium - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mission Basilica San Diego de Alcala - 6.5 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mission Valley Mall - 7.1 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fashion Valley Mall - 7.5 km / 4.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of San Diego - 7.9 km / 4.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Riverwalk Golf Club - 8 km / 5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mission Trails Regional Park - 8.3 km / 5.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Diego State University - 9.1 km / 5.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Junipero Serra Museum - 9.5 km / 5.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Diego State University Art Gallery - 9.5 km / 5.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;VA Medical Center - 9.6 km / 6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Presidio Park - 9.7 km / 6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Heritage Park - 10 km / 6.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mount Soledad - 10.1 km / 6.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Residence Inn By Marriott San Diego Central is San Diego, CA (SAN-San Diego Intl.) - 12.4 km / 7.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Residence Inn By Marriott San Diego Central is San Diego, CA (SAN-San Diego Intl.) - 12.3 km / 7.7 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ContinentalBreakfast</Code><Text>Contintenal breakfast</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WakeUpService</Code><Text>Wake up service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarRentDesk</Code><Text>Car rental desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Kitchen</Code><Text>Kitchen</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CoffeeShop</Code><Text>Coffee shop</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Freenewspaper</Code><Text>Free Newspaper</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Icemachine</Code><Text>Ice Machine</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TV</Code><Text>TeleVision</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ChildrensClub</Code><Text>Childrens Club</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Medical centre</Code><Text>Medical centre</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>24HourFrontDesk</Code><Text>24 Hour Front Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BeautyShop</Code><Text>Beauty Shop</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ATMMachine</Code><Text>ATM Machine</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>