<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10572348</Id><Name>Talaris Conference Center</Name><Region><Id>58467</Id><Name>Lynnwood - Northside</Name><CityId>19943</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>4000 Ne 41st Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Seattle</City><State /><Zip /><Country>United States</Country><Tel>+1 (206) 268-7000</Tel><Fax>+1 (206) 268-7001</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Talaris Conference Center in Seattle (University District), you'll be convenient to Seattle Children's Hospital and University of Washington. This hotel is within close proximity of University Village and Husky Stadium.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 33 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and LCD televisions. Cable programming and iPod docking stations are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and complimentary newspapers, and housekeeping is provided weekly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. Additional amenities include a television in the lobby, a picnic area, and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A complimentary continental breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a business center, and limo/town car service. Planning an event in Seattle? This hotel has 1431 square feet (133 square meters) of space consisting of a conference center and conference space. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 4 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; A complimentary continental breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. Additional amenities include a television in the lobby, a picnic area, and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 33 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and LCD televisions. Cable programming and iPod docking stations are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and complimentary newspapers, and housekeeping is provided weekly.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Talaris Conference Center in Seattle (University District), you'll be convenient to Seattle Children's Hospital and University of Washington. This hotel is within close proximity of University Village and Husky Stadium. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Seattle Children's Hospital - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Washington - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;University Village - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Husky Stadium - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Drumheller Fountain - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Washington Medical Center - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Burke Museum of Natural History and Culture - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Henry Art Gallery - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ravenna Park - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Washington Park Arboretum - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Madison Park Beach - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Seattle Japanese Garden - 3.3 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lake View Cemetery - Bruce Lee's Grave - 3.5 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Volunteer Park - 3.6 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Volunteer Park Conservatory - 3.8 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Kenmore, WA (KEH-Kenmore Air Harbor) - 11.3 km / 7 mi&lt;br /&gt;Seattle, WA (SEA-Seattle - Tacoma Intl.) - 23.9 km / 14.9 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Talaris Conference Center is Seattle, WA (SEA-Seattle - Tacoma Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>ContinentalBreakfast</Code><Text>Contintenal breakfast</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WakeUpService</Code><Text>Wake up service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FamilyRooms</Code><Text>Family rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Kitchen</Code><Text>Kitchen</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TV</Code><Text>TeleVision</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>