<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10571704</Id><Name>Club Quarters, San Francisco</Name><Region><Id>21827</Id><Name>Union Square - Nob Hill</Name><CityId>19919</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>424 Clay Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>San Francisco</City><State /><Zip>94111</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>1-415-392-7400</Tel><Fax>1-415-392-7300</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Club Quarters in San Francisco, you'll be centrally located in San Francisco, steps from Embarcadero Center and TransAmerica Redwood Forest. This 4-star hotel is close to Union Square and Pier 39.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 346 air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and flat-screen televisions. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as a 24-hour fitness center or take in the view from a terrace. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a fireplace in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner. Dining is also available at a coffee shop/café, and room service (during limited hours) is provided. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a business center, and limo/town car service. Event facilities at this hotel consist of conference space and meeting rooms. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner. Dining is also available at a coffee shop/café, and room service (during limited hours) is provided. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as a 24-hour fitness center or take in the view from a terrace. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a fireplace in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 346 air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and flat-screen televisions. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Club Quarters in San Francisco, you'll be centrally located in San Francisco, steps from Embarcadero Center and TransAmerica Redwood Forest. This 4-star hotel is close to Union Square and Pier 39. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Embarcadero Center - 0.1 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;TransAmerica Redwood Forest - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;TransAmerica Pyramid - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pacific Heritage Museum of San Francisco - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wells Fargo History Museum - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chinese Culture Center - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;555 California Street - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Buddha's Universal Church - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mechanics Monument - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old St. Mary's Cathedral - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Mary Square - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Norras Temple - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tin How Temple - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Beat Museum - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ferry Building - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Oakland, CA (OAK-Oakland Intl.) - 18.9 km / 11.7 mi&lt;br /&gt;San Francisco, CA (SFO-San Francisco Intl.) - 19.9 km / 12.4 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Club Quarters in San Francisco is San Francisco, CA (SFO-San Francisco Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>