<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10572184</Id><Name>Courtyard by Marriott San Francisco Fisherman's Wharf</Name><Region><Id>21828</Id><Name>Fisherman's Wharf - Russian Hill</Name><CityId>19919</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>580 Beach Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>San Francisco</City><State /><Zip>94133</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>+1 (415) 775-3800</Tel><Fax>+1 (415) 441-7307</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Courtyard San Francisco Fisherman's Wharf, you'll be centrally located in San Francisco, steps from The Cannery at Del Monte Square and Winery Collective. This family-friendly hotel is close to Lombard Street and Fisherman's Wharf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 127  guestrooms. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and premium TV channels provides entertainment. Bathrooms feature shower/tub combinations, complimentary toiletries, and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and separate sitting areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the recreation opportunities such as a fitness center or make use of other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at a coffee shop/café serving guests of Courtyard San Francisco Fisherman's Wharf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-out, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and dry cleaning/laundry services.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at a coffee shop/café serving guests of Courtyard San Francisco Fisherman's Wharf. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy the recreation opportunities such as a fitness center or make use of other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 127  guestrooms. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and premium TV channels provides entertainment. Bathrooms feature shower/tub combinations, complimentary toiletries, and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and separate sitting areas.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Courtyard San Francisco Fisherman's Wharf, you'll be centrally located in San Francisco, steps from The Cannery at Del Monte Square and Winery Collective. This family-friendly hotel is close to Lombard Street and Fisherman's Wharf. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;The Cannery at Del Monte Square - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Winery Collective - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hyde Street Pier - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fishermans Wharf Cable Car Turnaround - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ride the Ducks San Francisco - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Francisco Maritime National Historical Park - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ripley's Believe It Or Not Museum - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ghirardelli Square - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Musee Mecanique - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ferryboat Eureka - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wax Museum at Fisherman's Wharf - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Balclutha - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;SS Jeremiah O'Brien - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;USS Pampanito - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Red and White Fleet at Pier 43 and a Half - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Courtyard San Francisco Fisherman's Wharf is San Francisco, CA (SFO-San Francisco Intl.) - 21.4 km / 13.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Courtyard by Marriott Fishermans Wharf is San Francisco, CA (SFO-San Francisco Intl.) - 21.4 km / 13.3 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ValetParking</Code><Text>Valet parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InRoomMovies</Code><Text>In-room movies</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WakeUpService</Code><Text>Wake up service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarRentDesk</Code><Text>Car rental desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CoffeeShop</Code><Text>Coffee shop</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Freenewspaper</Code><Text>Free Newspaper</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Icemachine</Code><Text>Ice Machine</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TV</Code><Text>TeleVision</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Medical centre</Code><Text>Medical centre</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>24HourFrontDesk</Code><Text>24 Hour Front Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BeautyShop</Code><Text>Beauty Shop</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>