<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10571550</Id><Name>Orchard Garden Hotel</Name><Region><Id>21827</Id><Name>Union Square - Nob Hill</Name><CityId>19919</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>466 Bush St.</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>San Francisco</City><State /><Zip>94108</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>1-415-399-9807</Tel><Fax>1-415-393-9917</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Orchard Garden Hotel, you'll be centrally located in San Francisco, steps from St. Mary Square and Old St. Mary's Cathedral. This 4-star hotel is close to Union Square and Lombard Street.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 86 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and DVD players. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, and LCD televisions with pay movies provide entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature designer toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as a fitness center or take in the view from a rooftop terrace. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Full breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, limo/town car service, and express check-out. Planning an event in San Francisco? This hotel has 0 square feet (0 square meters) of space consisting of meeting rooms and a meeting room.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Full breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as a fitness center or take in the view from a rooftop terrace. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 86 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and DVD players. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, and LCD televisions with pay movies provide entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature designer toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Orchard Garden Hotel, you'll be centrally located in San Francisco, steps from St. Mary Square and Old St. Mary's Cathedral. This 4-star hotel is close to Union Square and Lombard Street. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;St. Mary Square - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old St. Mary's Cathedral - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;555 California Street - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Crocker Galleria - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Xanadu Gallery - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;77 Geary Galleries - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wells Fargo History Museum - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lotta's Fountain - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Francisco Magic Parlor - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Union Square - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tin How Temple - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;SF Playhouse - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Un-Scripted Theater Company - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kong Chow Temple - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pacific Heritage Museum of San Francisco - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Oakland, CA (OAK-Oakland Intl.) - 19 km / 11.8 mi&lt;br /&gt;San Francisco, CA (SFO-San Francisco Intl.) - 19.5 km / 12.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Orchard Garden Hotel is San Francisco, CA (SFO-San Francisco Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Orchard Garden Hotel is San Francisco, CA (SFO-San Francisco Intl.) - 19.5 km / 12.1 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property’s location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>