<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10574230</Id><Name>One Washington Circle Hotel</Name><Region><Id>21949</Id><Name>Foggy Bottom</Name><CityId>20071</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>One Washington Circle Nw</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Washington</City><State /><Zip>20037</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>1-202-872-1680</Tel><Fax>1-202-785-6603</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/WAS-ONEhotel_Suite_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/WAS-ONEhotel_Suite_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/WAS-ONEhotel_Suite_2.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/WAS-ONEhotel_Suite_2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at One Washington Circle Hotel, you'll be centrally located in Washington, minutes from George Washington University Hospital and George Washington University.  This family-friendly hotel is close to White House and Lincoln Memorial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 151 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and flat-screen televisions. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Rooms have private balconies. Digital programming and iPod docking stations are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature designer toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including an outdoor pool, a fitness center, and a seasonal outdoor pool. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Breakfast is available for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, limo/town car service, and dry cleaning/laundry services. Planning an event in Washington? This hotel has 3500 square feet (315 square meters) of space consisting of conference space and meeting rooms.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Breakfast is available for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including an outdoor pool, a fitness center, and a seasonal outdoor pool. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 151 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and flat-screen televisions. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Rooms have private balconies. Digital programming and iPod docking stations are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature designer toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at One Washington Circle Hotel, you'll be centrally located in Washington, minutes from George Washington University Hospital and George Washington University.  This family-friendly hotel is close to White House and Lincoln Memorial. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;George Washington University Hospital - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Alexander Pushkin Statue - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;George Washington University - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Mary's Episcopal Church - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Francis Pool - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Watergate Complex - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Christian Heurich House - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Justice William O. Douglas Statue - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cathedral of St. Matthew the Apostle - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Farragut Square - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Foundry Gallery - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Anderson House - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Anderson House Museum - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Embassy of India - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Stone House - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for One Washington Circle Hotel is Washington, DC (DCA-Ronald Reagan Washington National) - 6 km / 3.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The closest major airports to One Washington Circle Hotel are:&lt;br /&gt;Washington, DC (DCA-Ronald Reagan Washington National) - 6 km / 3.7 mi&lt;br /&gt;Washington, DC (IAD-Washington Dulles Intl.) - 34.9 km / 21.7 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for One Washington Circle Hotel is Washington, DC (DCA-Ronald Reagan Washington National). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property’s location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>