<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10573875</Id><Name>The Jefferson Hotel, Washington DC</Name><Region><Id>21948</Id><Name>Capitol Hill - Dupont Circle</Name><CityId>20071</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1200 16th Street, Nw</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Washington Dc</City><State /><Zip>20036</Zip><Country>United States</Country><Tel>1-202-448-2300</Tel><Fax>202-448-3262</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Washington (Dupont Circle), The Jefferson is minutes from National Geographic Society and Charles Sumner School Museum and Archives. This 5-star hotel is close to White House and George Washington University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 95 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring iPod docking stations and flat-screen televisions. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while DVD players and pay movies are also offered to provide entertainment. Bathrooms have designer toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks, as well as phones with free local calls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a fireplace in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite at one of the hotel's 2 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a 24-hour business center, and a 24-hour front desk.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite at one of the hotel's 2 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a fireplace in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 95 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring iPod docking stations and flat-screen televisions. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while DVD players and pay movies are also offered to provide entertainment. Bathrooms have designer toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks, as well as phones with free local calls.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Washington (Dupont Circle), The Jefferson is minutes from National Geographic Society and Charles Sumner School Museum and Archives. This 5-star hotel is close to White House and George Washington University. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;National Geographic Society - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Charles Sumner School Museum and Archives - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Embassy of Australia - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;D.C. Chamber of Commerce - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cathedral of St. Matthew the Apostle - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;McPherson Square - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Farragut Square - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Foundry Gallery - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mary McLeod Bethune Council House - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Washington D.C. Jewish Community Center - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aaron and Cecile Goldman Theater - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Studio Theatre - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. John's Church - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lafayette Park - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lafayette Square - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Jefferson is Washington, DC (DCA-Ronald Reagan Washington National) - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The closest major airports to The Jefferson Hotel are:&lt;br /&gt;Washington, DC (DCA-Ronald Reagan Washington National) - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi&lt;br /&gt;Washington, DC (IAD-Washington Dulles Intl.) - 35.9 km / 22.3 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Jefferson Hotel is Washington, DC (DCA-Ronald Reagan Washington National). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property’s location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>