<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>106281</Id><Name>Jabeque</Name><Region><Id>21228</Id><Name>Playa den Bossa</Name><CityId>18395</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>CARLOS ROMAN FERRER 25</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>IBIZA</City><State /><Zip>07800</Zip><Country>SPAIN</Country><Tel>971304211</Tel><Fax>971305825</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>38.8995587</Latitude><Longitude>1.4185291</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1203982-JabequeApartHotel_ext_Thumbnailed.jpg</Url><Width>100</Width><Height>100</Height><Bytes>4701</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1203982-JabequeApartHotel_ext_Thumbnailed.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2439</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1203982-JabequeApartHotel_guest.jpg</Url><Width>200</Width><Height>200</Height><Bytes>8422</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1203982-JabequeApartHotel_guest.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1818</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1203982-JabequeApartHotel_ext.jpg</Url><Width>200</Width><Height>200</Height><Bytes>12872</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1203982-JabequeApartHotel_ext.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2334</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1203982-JabequeApartHotel_pool.jpg</Url><Width>200</Width><Height>200</Height><Bytes>13923</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1203982-JabequeApartHotel_pool.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2410</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>SwimmingPool</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Aparthotel Jabeque Soul in Ibiza (Playa d'en Bossa), you'll be convenient to Ibiza Cathedral and Ibiza Castle.  This aparthotel is within close proximity of Archaeological Museum of Ibiza and Teatro Pereyra.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 159 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchenettes. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include safes and separate sitting areas, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a terrace. This aparthotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, an arcade/game room, and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar. Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour front desk, multilingual staff, and luggage storage.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar. Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a terrace. This aparthotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, an arcade/game room, and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 159 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchenettes. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include safes and separate sitting areas, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Aparthotel Jabeque Soul in Ibiza (Playa d'en Bossa), you'll be convenient to Ibiza Cathedral and Ibiza Castle.  This aparthotel is within close proximity of Archaeological Museum of Ibiza and Teatro Pereyra. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Ibiza Cathedral - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ibiza Castle - 1.7 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Archaeological Museum of Ibiza - 1.7 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Teatro Pereyra - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ibiza Museum of Contemporary Art - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Port of Ibiza - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aguamar Water Park - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bossa Beach - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marina Botafoch - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Faro de Punta Grossa - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sacred Heart of Jesus Statue - 4.6 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sant Rafel Church - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Las Salinas Beach - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Golf Club Ibiza - 7.7 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Rafael Racetrack - 8.9 km / 5.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Aparthotel Jabeque Soul is Ibiza (IBZ) - 5.1 km / 3.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Apartamentos Jabeque is Ibiza (IBZ) - 5.1 km / 3.2 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Garage</Code><Text>Garage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreshWaterPool</Code><Text>Fresh Water Pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SunBathingTerrace</Code><Text>Sun Bathing Terrace</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Balcony</Code><Text>Balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>