<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10648337</Id><Name>Residence Inn Munich City East</Name><Region><Id>20685</Id><Name>Haidhausen</Name><CityId>16609</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Orleansstrasse 81-83 · Munich,</Address1><Address2>Bavaria</Address2><Address3 /><City>Munich</City><State /><Zip>81667</Zip><Country>Germany</Country><Tel>49-89-558925-0</Tel><Fax>49-89-558925-1000</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>48.131096</Latitude><Longitude>11.607506</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Residence Inn by Marriott Munich City East in Munich (Au-Haidhausen), you'll be convenient to Prinzregententheater and English Garden. This aparthotel is within close proximity of Maximilianeum and Gasteig.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 125 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. 32-inch flat-screen televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including a sauna, a steam room, and a 24-hour fitness center. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and gift shops/newsstands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Residence Inn by Marriott Munich City East, or stop in at a snack bar/deli. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a 24-hour business center, and a computer station. Planning an event in Munich? This aparthotel has facilities measuring 183 square feet (17 square meters), including a meeting room. Extended parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Residence Inn by Marriott Munich City East, or stop in at a snack bar/deli. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including a sauna, a steam room, and a 24-hour fitness center. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and gift shops/newsstands. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 125 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. 32-inch flat-screen televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Residence Inn by Marriott Munich City East in Munich (Au-Haidhausen), you'll be convenient to Prinzregententheater and English Garden. This aparthotel is within close proximity of Maximilianeum and Gasteig. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Prinzregententheater - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maximilianeum - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gasteig - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Praterinsel - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Alpines Museum - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Schackgalerie - 1.7 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Siemens Headquarters - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bavarian National Museum - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;State Museum of Ethnology - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Deutsches Museum - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;European Patent Office - 2 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eisbach Surfing - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Isar Tor - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Munich Kammerspiele Schauspielhaus - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;House of Art - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Residence Inn by Marriott Munich City East is Munich (MUC-Franz Josef Strauss Intl.) - 28 km / 17.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>