<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10707810</Id><Name>Rimondi Estate</Name><Region><Id>20761</Id><Name>Rethymno</Name><CityId>16664</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>21, Xanthoudidou - 16, Har. Trikoupi Str, Old Town</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Rethymno - Rethymno City</City><State /><Zip /><Country>Greece - Islands</Country><Tel>28310 51001</Tel><Fax>2831051013</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/B8Lfront.jpg</Url><Width>840</Width><Height>460</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/B8Lthumbfront.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>127</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>3429</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/B8Lbed.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/B8Lthumbbed.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2080</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/B8Lmap.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/B8Lthumbmap.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1237</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Rimondi Boutique Hotels is a luxury 4-star property offering elegant accommodation in Rethymno, on the northwest coast of Crete. Highlights include an outdoor swimming pool, free Wi-Fi and a good location near the beachfront. Rethymno is a picturesque city with beautiful coastal views. It boasts a well-preserved Venetian old town with 16th-century architecture and Byzantine and Hellenic-Roman remains. Nearby places of interest include the Old Venetian Port, the Archaeological Museum of Rethymno and the Historical and Folklore Museum of Rethymno. The hotel is housed in a collection of traditional mid-rise buildings. Facilities include an outdoor swimming pool and private massage treatment rooms. Free Wi-Fi is available throughout the premises. Superior rooms, housed in the Palazzo Collection are 20-40sqm and decorated in a comfortable style with neutral tones and dark wood furniture. They feature a comfortable sitting area. Amenities include air-conditioning, a flat-screen satellite TV, a mini-bar, a safe, a telephone and an en-suite bathroom featuring a bathtub with integrated shower and a hairdryer. The hotel restaurant serves Mediterranean and international cuisine in an elegant setting. Guests can also enjoy a range of drinks at the hotel bar, and a buffet breakfast is provided every morning. Free parking is possible nearby. The hotel has a 24-hour reception.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>