<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10724980</Id><Name>Pietra E Mare Suites</Name><Region><Id>20804</Id><Name>Others</Name><CityId>16699</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Kalo Livadi</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Mykonos - Kalo Livadi</City><State /><Zip /><Country>Greece - Islands</Country><Tel>2289071152 - 71156</Tel><Fax>2289071441</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1224645-main001_Thumbnailed.jpg</Url><Width>100</Width><Height>100</Height><Bytes>4028</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1224645-main001_Thumbnailed.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2190</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Pietra e Mare Mykonos Hotel in Mykonos (Kalo Livadi), you'll be minutes from Kalo Livadi Beach and close to Super Paradise Beach. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Elia Beach and Kalafatis Beach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 31 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring iPod docking stations and minibars. Your pillowtop bed comes with down comforters. Rooms have private furnished balconies or patios. 32-inch LCD televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature designer toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with onsite massages, body treatments, and facials. Additional features at this Art Deco hotel include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner. Dining is also available at a coffee shop/café, and 24-hour room service is provided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include limo/town car service, a computer station, and express check-in. For a surcharge, guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle (available 24 hours) and a cruise ship terminal shuttle.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner. Dining is also available at a coffee shop/café, and 24-hour room service is provided. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on property policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 18 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with onsite massages, body treatments, and facials. Additional features at this Art Deco hotel include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 31 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring iPod docking stations and minibars. Your pillowtop bed comes with down comforters. Rooms have private furnished balconies or patios. 32-inch LCD televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature designer toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Pietra e Mare Mykonos Hotel in Mykonos (Kalo Livadi), you'll be minutes from Kalo Livadi Beach and close to Super Paradise Beach. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Elia Beach and Kalafatis Beach. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Kalo Livadi Beach - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Elia Beach - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kalafatis Beach - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Monastery of Panagia Tourliani - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Paranga Beach - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Agrari Beach - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Monastery of Paleokastro - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lia Beach - 3.3 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Super Paradise Beach - 3.5 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ftelia Archeological Site - 3.9 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ftelia Beach - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Paradise Beach - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Agia Anna Beach - 5.5 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Paranga Beach - 5.5 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Platis Gialos Beach - 5.7 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Mykonos (JMK-Mykonos Island National) - 5 km / 3.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;Naxos (JNX-Naxos Island National) - 39.2 km / 24.3 mi&lt;br /&gt;Ermoupolis (JSY-Syros Island National) - 40.2 km / 25 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Pietra e Mare Mykonos Hotel is Mykonos (JMK-Mykonos Island National). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on property policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 18 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>