<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10734802</Id><Name>Sweet Tweet</Name><Region><Id>20837</Id><Name>Perissa</Name><CityId>16716</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Perissa</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Santorini - Perissa</City><State /><Zip /><Country>Greece - Islands</Country><Tel>6908344520</Tel><Fax>2286081960</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1130/49/15/20/9982580_1_b.jpg</Url><Width>350</Width><Height>262</Height><Bytes>11160</Bytes><Caption>9982580_1_b</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1130/49/15/20/9982580_1_bthumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1847</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1130/49/15/20/9982580_2_b.jpg</Url><Width>350</Width><Height>262</Height><Bytes>11866</Bytes><Caption>9982580_2_b</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1130/49/15/20/9982580_2_bthumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2097</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1130/49/15/20/9982580_3_b.jpg</Url><Width>350</Width><Height>262</Height><Bytes>13257</Bytes><Caption>9982580_3_b</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1130/49/15/20/9982580_3_bthumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1958</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Sweet Tweet in Santorini (Perissa), you'll be minutes from Museum of Minerals and Fossils and close to Ancient Thira.  This bed &amp; breakfast is within close proximity of Perissa Beach and Waterpark Santorini.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 6 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool or make use of other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;While enjoying a refreshing dip in the bed &amp; breakfast pool, you can order your favorite drink at the poolside bar. A complimentary continental breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2:00 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; While enjoying a refreshing dip in the bed &amp; breakfast pool, you can order your favorite drink at the poolside bar. A complimentary continental breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on property policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy the recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool or make use of other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 6 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Sweet Tweet in Santorini (Perissa), you'll be minutes from Museum of Minerals and Fossils and close to Ancient Thira.  This bed &amp; breakfast is within close proximity of Perissa Beach and Waterpark Santorini. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Museum of Minerals and Fossils - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ancient Thira - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Perissa Beach - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Waterpark Santorini - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Prophet Elias Monastery - 1.5 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Panagia Episkopi - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Open Air Cinema Kamari - 2.3 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wine Museum - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Perivolos Beach - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Art Space Santorini - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Boutari Winery - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gavalas Vineyard - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vlychada Beach - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Osho Santorini - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Antoniou Winery - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Sweet Tweet is Thira (JTR-Santorini National) - 4.9 km / 3.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on property policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>