<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10818255</Id><Name>Queens Drive</Name><Region><Id>52890</Id><Name>Kings Cross &amp; Camden</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>169 Queens Drive</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>N4 2AP</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 207 224 4405</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Queens Drive in London (North London), you'll be convenient to Finsbury Park and Emirates Stadium. This hotel is within close proximity of Almeida Theatre and Alexandra Palace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of the guestrooms featuring LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms with bathtubs or showers are provided. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of the guestrooms featuring LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms with bathtubs or showers are provided. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Queens Drive in London (North London), you'll be convenient to Finsbury Park and Emirates Stadium. This hotel is within close proximity of Almeida Theatre and Alexandra Palace. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Finsbury Park - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Emirates Stadium - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Almeida Theatre - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Alexandra Palace - 3.7 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;London Canal Museum - 3.8 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Highgate Ponds - 3.8 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Angel Building - 3.8 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hackney Empire - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sadler's Wells Theatre - 4.1 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Geffrye Museum - 4.1 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;London Fields - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;British Library - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hoxton Square - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kenwood House - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cartwright Gardens - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Queens Drive is London (LCY-London City) - 12.5 km / 7.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>