<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10817203</Id><Name>The Windermere Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52923</Id><Name>Southbank</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>142/144 Warwick Way</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>SW1V 4JE</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 207 834 5163</Tel><Fax>+44 (207) 6308831</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at The Windermere Hotel in London (Victoria), you'll be convenient to Apollo Victoria Theatre and Buckingham Palace. This 4-star guesthouse is close to Harrods and Big Ben.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 20 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring iPod docking stations and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have designer toiletries and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the guesthouse's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a computer station, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and dry cleaning/laundry services. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available 24 hours), and self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the guesthouse's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 20 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring iPod docking stations and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have designer toiletries and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at The Windermere Hotel in London (Victoria), you'll be convenient to Apollo Victoria Theatre and Buckingham Palace. This 4-star guesthouse is close to Harrods and Big Ben. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Apollo Victoria Theatre - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chelsea Bridge - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Victoria Palace Theatre - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Westminster Cathedral - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sloane Square - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Saatchi Gallery - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Hospital Chelsea - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Mews - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queen's Gallery - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. James Park - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Battersea Park - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Buckingham Palace - 1.4 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Green Park - 1.4 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tate Britain - 1.4 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vauxhall Bridge - 1.4 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;London (LCY-London City) - 13.6 km / 8.5 mi&lt;br /&gt;London (LHR-Heathrow) - 21.1 km / 13.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Windermere Hotel is London (LHR-Heathrow). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The closest major airports to Windermere Hotel are:&lt;br /&gt;London (LCY-London City) - 13.6 km / 8.5 mi&lt;br /&gt;London (LHR-Heathrow) - 21.2 km / 13.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;London (LGW-Gatwick) - 37.2 km / 23.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Windermere Hotel is London (LHR-Heathrow). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Doctoroncall</Code><Text>Doctor on call</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>