<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10816645</Id><Name>Presidential Marylebone</Name><Region><Id>52927</Id><Name>West End &amp; Marble Arch</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Apartments</Type><Address><Address1>102 George Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>W1U 8NT</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 (0)20 7486 0097</Tel><Fax>+44 2074873624</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Presidential Serviced Apartments Marylebone, you'll be centrally located in London, steps from Portman Square and minutes from Selfridges. This aparthotel is close to Harrods and Buckingham Palace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 33 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Flat-screen televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include desks and separate sitting areas, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and shopping on site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include multilingual staff, laundry facilities, and a safe deposit box at the front desk. A roundtrip airport shuttle is available for a surcharge.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and shopping on site. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 33 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Flat-screen televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include desks and separate sitting areas, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Presidential Serviced Apartments Marylebone, you'll be centrally located in London, steps from Portman Square and minutes from Selfridges. This aparthotel is close to Harrods and Buckingham Palace. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Portman Square - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wallace Collection - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Selfridges - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marble Arch - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wigmore Hall - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Madame Tussaud's Wax Museum - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hyde Park Speakers' Corner - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Grosvenor Square - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Academy of Music - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Crescent Gardens - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Park Square Garden - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Oxford Circus - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queen Mary's Gardens - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;London Business School - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Regent's Park - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Presidential Serviced Apartments Marylebone is London (LCY-London City) - 14.4 km / 8.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The closest major airports to Presidential Apartments are:&lt;br /&gt;London (LCY-London City) - 14.4 km / 8.9 mi&lt;br /&gt;London (LHR-Heathrow) - 20.9 km / 13 mi&lt;br /&gt;London (LGW-Gatwick) - 40.2 km / 25 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Presidential Apartments is London (LCY-London City). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Security24Hour</Code><Text>24-hour security</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WakeUpService</Code><Text>Wake up service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Kitchen</Code><Text>Kitchen</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CoffeeShop</Code><Text>Coffee shop</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TV</Code><Text>TeleVision</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shops</Code><Text>Shops</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Doctoroncall</Code><Text>Doctor on call</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>