<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10816910</Id><Name>Park View Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52890</Id><Name>Kings Cross &amp; Camden</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>18 &amp;amp; 25 Wilberforce Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>N4 2SN</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>00442072244405</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Park View in London (North London), you'll be close to Finsbury Park and London Zoo.  This hotel is within close proximity of Emirates Stadium and Almeida Theatre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 18 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Bathrooms with showers are provided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 18 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Bathrooms with showers are provided.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Park View in London (North London), you'll be close to Finsbury Park and London Zoo.  This hotel is within close proximity of Emirates Stadium and Almeida Theatre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Finsbury Park - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Emirates Stadium - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Almeida Theatre - 2.8 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;London Canal Museum - 3.6 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Angel Building - 3.7 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Alexandra Palace - 3.7 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Highgate Ponds - 3.8 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hackney Empire - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sadler's Wells Theatre - 3.9 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Geffrye Museum - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;London Fields - 4.1 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;British Library - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hoxton Square - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kenwood House - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cartwright Gardens - 4.6 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Park View is London (LCY-London City) - 12.5 km / 7.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>