<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10817171</Id><Name>The Windmill</Name><Region><Id>52917</Id><Name>Paddington &amp; Bayswater</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>57 Cricklewood Broadway</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>NW2 3JX</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>0044-20722-444-05</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at The Windmill in London (Camden), you'll be close to The Tricycle Theatre and London Zoo.  This guesthouse is within close proximity of Everyman Cinemas - Hampstead and Hampstead Heath.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of 20 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers, housekeeping is provided daily, and irons/ironing boards can be requested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour front desk and luggage storage. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 1 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of 20 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers, housekeeping is provided daily, and irons/ironing boards can be requested.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at The Windmill in London (Camden), you'll be close to The Tricycle Theatre and London Zoo.  This guesthouse is within close proximity of Everyman Cinemas - Hampstead and Hampstead Heath. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;The Tricycle Theatre - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Everyman Cinemas - Hampstead - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hampstead Heath - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Freud Museum - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brent Cross Shopping Centre - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Burgh House - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hampstead Theatre - 2.8 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Swiss Cottage Farmers' Market - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Keats House - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Swaminarayan Hindu Temple - 3.5 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kenwood House - 3.8 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Primrose Hill - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lord's Cricket Ground - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Highgate Ponds - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Middlesex University Hendon Campus - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;London (LHR-Heathrow) - 18.9 km / 11.7 mi&lt;br /&gt;London (LCY-London City) - 18.9 km / 11.8 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Windmill is London (LCY-London City). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>