<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10828294</Id><Name>Exhibition Court Hotel 4</Name><Region><Id>52887</Id><Name>Kensington &amp; Earls Court</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>25 Collingham Place, Earl'S Court</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>SW5 00F</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>44-207-370-2414</Tel><Fax>011-44 207 373 4391</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Exhibition Court Hotel 4, you'll be centrally located in London, convenient to Kensington Roof Gardens and Imperial College London.  This hotel is close to Royal Albert Hall and Harrods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 20 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Your memory foam bed comes with Egyptian cotton sheets. Prepare your meals in the shared/communal kitchen. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature rainfall showerheads and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, express check-out, and a 24-hour front desk.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 1:00 PM  Check-out time is 11:00 AM &lt;br/&gt; A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 20 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Your memory foam bed comes with Egyptian cotton sheets. Prepare your meals in the shared/communal kitchen. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature rainfall showerheads and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Exhibition Court Hotel 4, you'll be centrally located in London, convenient to Kensington Roof Gardens and Imperial College London.  This hotel is close to Royal Albert Hall and Harrods. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Kensington Roof Gardens - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;London Natural History Museum - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Imperial College London - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Albert Hall - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;London Science Museum - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albert Memorial - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kensington Palace - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Victoria and Albert Museum - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Olympia Conference and Exhibition Centre - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brompton Oratory - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stamford Bridge Stadium - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Holland Park - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kensington Gardens - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Beauchamp Place - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Harrods - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;London (LCY-London City) - 16.6 km / 10.3 mi&lt;br /&gt;London (LHR-Heathrow) - 18.2 km / 11.3 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Exhibition Court Hotel 4 is London (LHR-Heathrow). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>