<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10821339</Id><Name>The William IV</Name><Region><Id>52917</Id><Name>Paddington &amp; Bayswater</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>786 Harrow Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>NW10 5JX</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>2089695955</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at The William IV in London (North London), you'll be close to Portobello Road Market and Royal Albert Hall. This inn is close to Imperial College London and London Zoo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 9 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Bathrooms with showers are provided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services. Additional features include a fireplace in the lobby, tour/ticket assistance, and a picnic area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of The William IV. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 1 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of The William IV. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services. Additional features include a fireplace in the lobby, tour/ticket assistance, and a picnic area. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 9 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Bathrooms with showers are provided.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at The William IV in London (North London), you'll be close to Portobello Road Market and Royal Albert Hall. This inn is close to Imperial College London and London Zoo. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Portobello Road Market - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Electric Cinema - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Tricycle Theatre - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Westfield London Shopping Centre - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Loftus Road Stadium - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Whiteleys Shopping Centre - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shepherd's Bush Empire - 2.8 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Holland Park - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lord's Cricket Ground - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kensington Palace - 3.3 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hampstead Theatre - 3.5 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Freud Museum - 3.5 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Swiss Cottage Farmers' Market - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kensington Roof Gardens - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kensington Gardens - 3.7 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;London (LHR-Heathrow) - 17.3 km / 10.7 mi&lt;br /&gt;London (LCY-London City) - 18.8 km / 11.7 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The William IV is London (LHR-Heathrow). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>