<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10821590</Id><Name>The Rookery Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52856</Id><Name>City of London &amp; Barbican</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>12 Peter'S Lane</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>EC1M 6DS</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>0044 (0) 20 7336 0931</Tel><Fax>+44 (20) 7336 0932</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at The Rookery Hotel, you'll be centrally located in London, steps from Smithfield Market and minutes from St. Etheldreda's. This 4-star hotel is close to St. Paul's Cathedral and King's College London.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 33 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while DVD players and satellite programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms have designer toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and a fireplace in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk. This hotel has 2 meeting rooms available for events.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and a fireplace in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 33 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while DVD players and satellite programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms have designer toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at The Rookery Hotel, you'll be centrally located in London, steps from Smithfield Market and minutes from St. Etheldreda's. This 4-star hotel is close to St. Paul's Cathedral and King's College London. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Smithfield Market - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Etheldreda's - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of London - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Bailey - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;London Stock Exchange - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Giles Cripplegate - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Barbican Arts Centre - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dr. Johnsons' House - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Paul's Cathedral - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Brides' Church - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;London Temple Church - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;London Guildhall - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Unilever PLC - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Courts of Justice - Law Courts - 1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dickens House - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;London (LCY-London City) - 10.7 km / 6.6 mi&lt;br /&gt;London (LHR-Heathrow) - 24.7 km / 15.3 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Rookery Hotel is London (LHR-Heathrow). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The closest major airports to The Rookery are:&lt;br /&gt;London (LCY-London City) - 10.7 km / 6.6 mi&lt;br /&gt;London (LHR-Heathrow) - 24.7 km / 15.3 mi&lt;br /&gt;London (LGW-Gatwick) - 40.7 km / 25.3 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Rookery is London (LHR-Heathrow). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property’s location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>