<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10828768</Id><Name>Comfotel Blu Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52877</Id><Name>Hammersmith &amp; Fulham</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>114 Shepherds Bush Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>W6 7PD</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>00442072244405</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Comfotel Blu in London (Hammersmith and Fulham), you'll be close to Shepherd's Bush Empire and Royal Albert Hall. This hotel is close to Imperial College London and Harrods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of 16 guestrooms featuring LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks, housekeeping is provided daily, and irons/ironing boards can be requested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour front desk and coffee/tea in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of 16 guestrooms featuring LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks, housekeeping is provided daily, and irons/ironing boards can be requested.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Comfotel Blu in London (Hammersmith and Fulham), you'll be close to Shepherd's Bush Empire and Royal Albert Hall. This hotel is close to Imperial College London and Harrods. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Shepherd's Bush Empire - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Broadway Shopping Centre - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hammersmith Apollo - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Olympia Conference and Exhibition Centre - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Westfield London Shopping Centre - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Riverside Studios - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Holland Park - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Loftus Road Stadium - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kensington Roof Gardens - 2.2 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Electric Cinema - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Portobello Road Market - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kensington Palace - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Craven Cottage Stadium - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stamford Bridge Stadium - 2.8 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Whiteleys Shopping Centre - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;London (LHR-Heathrow) - 16.1 km / 10 mi&lt;br /&gt;London (LCY-London City) - 18.8 km / 11.7 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Comfotel Blu is London (LHR-Heathrow). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>