<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10821158</Id><Name>Studios 2 Let</Name><Region><Id>52890</Id><Name>Kings Cross &amp; Camden</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Apartments</Type><Address><Address1>36-37 Cartwright Gardens</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>WC1H 9EH</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 (0) 20 7380 8450</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Studios 2 Let Serviced Apartments - Cartwright Gardens, you'll be centrally located in London, steps from Cartwright Gardens and minutes from British Library. This apartment is close to King's College London and Trafalgar Square.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 144 guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and microwaves. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while 27-inch LCD televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment. Conveniences include phones and safes, and housekeeping is provided weekly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as outdoor tennis courts or take in the view from a terrace and a garden. Additional features at this Victorian apartment include complimentary wireless Internet access, tour/ticket assistance, and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, express check-in, and express check-out.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as outdoor tennis courts or take in the view from a terrace and a garden. Additional features at this Victorian apartment include complimentary wireless Internet access, tour/ticket assistance, and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 144 guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and microwaves. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while 27-inch LCD televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment. Conveniences include phones and safes, and housekeeping is provided weekly.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Studios 2 Let Serviced Apartments - Cartwright Gardens, you'll be centrally located in London, steps from Cartwright Gardens and minutes from British Library. This apartment is close to King's College London and Trafalgar Square. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Cartwright Gardens - 0 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;British Library - 0.2 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bloomsbury Theatre - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of London - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;University College London - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;University College Hospital - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Russell Square - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;London Senate House Library - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Great Ormond Street Hospital - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dickens House - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;The British Museum - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bedford Square - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bloomsbury Square - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;London Canal Museum - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;BT Tower - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;London (LCY-London City) - 12.5 km / 7.8 mi&lt;br /&gt;London (LHR-Heathrow) - 23.2 km / 14.4 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Studios 2 Let Serviced Apartments - Cartwright Gardens is London (LHR-Heathrow). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>