<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10839309</Id><Name>Homewood Park</Name><Region><Id>52374</Id><Name>Bath</Name><CityId>52374</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1 Hinton Charterhouse</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Bath</City><State /><Zip>BA27TB</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 (1225) 723731</Tel><Fax>+44 (1225) 723820</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Homewood Park Hotel &amp; Spa - Bath in Bath (Limpley Stoke), you'll be close to Iford Manor and the Peto Garden and American Museum in Britain. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Westwood Manor and Prior Park Landscape Garden.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 21 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring DVD players and LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature designer toiletries and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include complimentary bottled water and a turndown service, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Relax at the full-service spa, where you can enjoy massages, body treatments, and facials. You're sure to appreciate the recreational amenities, including an outdoor pool, a sauna, and a steam room. Additional amenities at this Victorian hotel include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, where you can enjoy drinks at a bar, take in a garden view, and even dine alfresco (weather permitting). You can also stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. English breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff. This hotel has 3 meeting rooms available for events. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2:30 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, where you can enjoy drinks at a bar, take in a garden view, and even dine alfresco (weather permitting). You can also stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. English breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Relax at the full-service spa, where you can enjoy massages, body treatments, and facials. You're sure to appreciate the recreational amenities, including an outdoor pool, a sauna, and a steam room. Additional amenities at this Victorian hotel include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 21 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring DVD players and LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature designer toiletries and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include complimentary bottled water and a turndown service, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Homewood Park Hotel &amp; Spa - Bath in Bath (Limpley Stoke), you'll be close to Iford Manor and the Peto Garden and American Museum in Britain. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Westwood Manor and Prior Park Landscape Garden. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Iford Manor and the Peto Garden - 2 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Westwood Manor - 3.3 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;American Museum in Britain - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Prior Park Landscape Garden - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Claverton Pumping Station - 4.6 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Bath - 5.1 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Alexandra Park - 5.4 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bath Golf Club - 5.7 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bath's Original Theatre Royal and Masonic Museum - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bath Mission Theater - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Parade Gardens - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bath Rugby Stadium - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chapel Arts Centre - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sally Lunn's - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Roman Baths - 6 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Homewood Park Hotel &amp; Spa - Bath is Bristol (BRS-Bristol Intl.) - 27.6 km / 17.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Homewood Park is London (LHR-Heathrow) - 130.5 km / 81.1 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TV</Code><Text>TeleVision</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ComplimentaryBreakfast</Code><Text>Complimentary Breakfast</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>