<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10839794</Id><Name>The Green House</Name><Region><Id>52402</Id><Name>Bournemouth - Poole</Name><CityId>52402</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>4 Grove Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Bournemouth</City><State /><Zip>BH1 3AX</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>01202498900</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The Green House is centrally located in Bournemouth, walking distance from Russell-Cotes Art Gallery and Museum and close to Bournemouth Pavillion Theater. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of St. Peter's Church and Oceanarium.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 32 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring iPod docking stations and DVD players. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while 32-inch flat-screen televisions with digital programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature designer toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Relax and unwind with massages and facials. This Victorian hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, where you can enjoy drinks at a bar, take in a garden view, and even dine alfresco (weather permitting). You can also stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. For your convenience, a complimentary breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk. Planning an event in Bournemouth? This hotel has facilities measuring 431 square feet (40 square meters), including meeting rooms. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, where you can enjoy drinks at a bar, take in a garden view, and even dine alfresco (weather permitting). You can also stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. For your convenience, a complimentary breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Relax and unwind with massages and facials. This Victorian hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 32 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring iPod docking stations and DVD players. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while 32-inch flat-screen televisions with digital programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature designer toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The Green House is centrally located in Bournemouth, walking distance from Russell-Cotes Art Gallery and Museum and close to Bournemouth Pavillion Theater. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of St. Peter's Church and Oceanarium. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Russell-Cotes Art Gallery and Museum - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bournemouth Pavillion Theater - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Peter's Church - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Oceanarium - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bournemouth Pier - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bournemouth Lower Gardens - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Genting Casino Bournemouth - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bournemouth Beach - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bournemouth International Centre - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Square - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bournemouth Natural Science Society - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bournemouth Town Hall - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Knyveton Gardens - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Boscombe Chine Gardens Mini Golf Course - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Meyrick Park Golf Course - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Green House is Bournemouth (BOH-Bournemouth Intl.) - 7 km / 4.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for The Green House is Bournemouth (BOH-Bournemouth Intl.) - 7 km / 4.3 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>