<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10833565</Id><Name>Club Quarters Lincoln's Inn Fields</Name><Region><Id>52848</Id><Name>Bloomsbury &amp; Holborn</Name><CityId>52612</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>61 Lincoln'S Inn Fields</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>London</City><State /><Zip>WC2A 3JW</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>2039052080</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Club Quarters Lincoln's Inn Fields, you'll be centrally located in London, minutes from London School of Economics and Political Science and King's College London. This 4-star hotel is close to Trafalgar Square and St. Paul's Cathedral.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 157 air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and LCD televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as a fitness center or take in the view from a terrace. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Breakfast is available for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a 24-hour business center, and a computer station. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Breakfast is available for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as a fitness center or take in the view from a terrace. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 157 air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and LCD televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Club Quarters Lincoln's Inn Fields, you'll be centrally located in London, minutes from London School of Economics and Political Science and King's College London. This 4-star hotel is close to Trafalgar Square and St. Paul's Cathedral. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;London School of Economics and Political Science - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Opera House - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Theatre Royal Drury Lane - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bloomsbury Square - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;London Transport Museum - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Courts of Justice - Law Courts - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;King's College London - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Covent Garden - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lyceum Theatre - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Covent Garden Market - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;London Temple Church - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;London St. Paul's Church - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Somerset House - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Two Temple Place - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Great Ormond Street Hospital - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;London (LCY-London City) - 11.7 km / 7.3 mi&lt;br /&gt;London (LHR-Heathrow) - 23.5 km / 14.6 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Club Quarters Lincoln's Inn Fields is London (LHR-Heathrow). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>