<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10840966</Id><Name>Rhinefield House Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52418</Id><Name>Brockenhurst</Name><CityId>52418</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Rhinefield Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Brockenhurst</City><State /><Zip>S042 7QB</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 (845) 727516</Tel><Fax>+44 (845) 727517</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Rhinefield House Hotel in Brockenhurst (New Forest), you'll be close to New Forest and Brockenhurst College. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Brockenhurst Manor Golf Club and St. Nicholas Church.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 50 individually furnished guestrooms, featuring refrigerators and DVD players. Flat-screen televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Relax at the full-service spa, where you can enjoy massages, body treatments, and facials. You can take advantage of recreational amenities such as a health club, an indoor pool, and a sauna. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and a picnic area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite at one of the hotel's 2 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-out, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and a 24-hour front desk. Event facilities at this hotel consist of conference space and meeting rooms. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite at one of the hotel's 2 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Relax at the full-service spa, where you can enjoy massages, body treatments, and facials. You can take advantage of recreational amenities such as a health club, an indoor pool, and a sauna. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and a picnic area. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 50 individually furnished guestrooms, featuring refrigerators and DVD players. Flat-screen televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Rhinefield House Hotel in Brockenhurst (New Forest), you'll be close to New Forest and Brockenhurst College. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Brockenhurst Manor Golf Club and St. Nicholas Church. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;New Forest - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brockenhurst College - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brockenhurst Manor Golf Club - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Nicholas Church - 4.6 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Burley Golf Club - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bolderwood Deer Sanctuary - 5.2 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Burley Park - 5.4 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;New Forest Museum - 5.4 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;New Forest Golf Club - 6.4 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sammy Miller Museum - 8.4 km / 5.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rufus Stone - 8.5 km / 5.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bramshaw Golf Club - 10.1 km / 6.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Liberty's Owl Raptor and Reptile Centre - 10.2 km / 6.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Barbe Museum and Art Gallery - 10.2 km / 6.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;New Forest Wildlife Park - 10.5 km / 6.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Bournemouth (BOH-Bournemouth Intl.) - 15.9 km / 9.9 mi&lt;br /&gt;Southampton (SOU) - 22.6 km / 14 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Rhinefield House Hotel is Southampton (SOU). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Rhinefield House Hotel is Southampton (SOU) - 22.5 km / 14 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ValetParking</Code><Text>Valet parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Sauna</Code><Text>Sauna</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndoorPool</Code><Text>Indoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WakeUpService</Code><Text>Wake up service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FamilyRooms</Code><Text>Family rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SteamBath</Code><Text>Steam Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Freenewspaper</Code><Text>Free Newspaper</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Golf</Code><Text>Golf</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TV</Code><Text>TeleVision</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>24HourFrontDesk</Code><Text>24 Hour Front Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Fishing</Code><Text>Fishing</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>