<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10846641</Id><Name>Park Inn By Radisson Thurrock</Name><Region><Id>52543</Id><Name>Grays</Name><CityId>52543</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>High Road, North Stifford</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Grays</City><State /><Zip>RM16 5UE</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 (1708) 719988</Tel><Fax>+44 (1708) 719980</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Park Inn by Radisson Thurrock in Grays (Thurrock), you'll be convenient to Arena Essex Raceway and Lakeside Shopping Centre. This eco-friendly hotel is within the vicinity of Tilbury Fort and Bluewater Shopping Centre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 97 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. Additional features include wedding services, a fireplace in the lobby, and a picnic area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, express check-in, and express check-out. This hotel has 11 meeting rooms available for events. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. Additional features include wedding services, a fireplace in the lobby, and a picnic area. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 97 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Park Inn by Radisson Thurrock in Grays (Thurrock), you'll be convenient to Arena Essex Raceway and Lakeside Shopping Centre. This eco-friendly hotel is within the vicinity of Tilbury Fort and Bluewater Shopping Centre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Arena Essex Raceway - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lakeside Shopping Centre - 2.3 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tilbury Fort - 6.6 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bluewater Shopping Centre - 7.1 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gravesend Town Pier - 7.3 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pocahontas Statue - 7.3 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gravesend Gurdwara - 7.9 km / 4.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cold War Bunker - 8.5 km / 5.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Orchard Theatre - 8.9 km / 5.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Coalhouse Fort - 9 km / 5.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dartford Borough Museum - 9 km / 5.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kent Cyclopark - 9.7 km / 6 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. John's Jerusalem - 11.4 km / 7.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Victoria Road Stadium - 11.7 km / 7.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eastgate Shopping Centre - 13.1 km / 8.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;London (LCY-London City) - 18.2 km / 11.3 mi&lt;br /&gt;London (STN-Stansted) - 43.5 km / 27 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Park Inn by Radisson Thurrock is London (STN-Stansted). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Park Inn Thurrock is London (STN-Stansted) - 43.5 km / 27 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ContinentalBreakfast</Code><Text>Contintenal breakfast</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InRoomMovies</Code><Text>In-room movies</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shops</Code><Text>Shops</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ATMMachine</Code><Text>ATM Machine</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>