<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10840976</Id><Name>BEST WESTERN Old Mill Hotel &amp; Leisure Club</Name><Region><Id>52427</Id><Name>Bury</Name><CityId>52427</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Springwood</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Bury</City><State /><Zip>BL0 9DS</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 +44 1706 822991</Tel><Fax>+44 +44 1706 822291</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Bury (Ramsbottom), Best Western Old Mill Hotel&amp; Leisure Club is convenient to Peel Monument and Cronkshaw Fold Farm. This eco-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Helmshore Mills Textile Museum and Burrs Activity Centre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 30 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include complimentary weekday newspapers and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities, including an indoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Breakfast is available for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour business center, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk. Event facilities at this hotel consist of a conference center, conference space, and meeting rooms. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Breakfast is available for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities, including an indoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 30 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include complimentary weekday newspapers and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Bury (Ramsbottom), Best Western Old Mill Hotel&amp; Leisure Club is convenient to Peel Monument and Cronkshaw Fold Farm. This eco-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Helmshore Mills Textile Museum and Burrs Activity Centre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Peel Monument - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cronkshaw Fold Farm - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Helmshore Mills Textile Museum - 4.4 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Burrs Activity Centre - 4.6 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mather Gallery - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jumbles Country Park - 6 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Turton Tower - 6 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bury Transport Museum - 6.4 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Rock - 6.5 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Haslingden Halo - 6.5 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Met - 6.6 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fusilier Museum - 6.7 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bury Art Gallery and Museum - 6.7 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bury Market - 6.7 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Greenbooth Reservoir - 6.8 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Best Western Old Mill Hotel&amp; Leisure Club is Manchester (MAN) - 32.1 km / 20 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndoorPool</Code><Text>Indoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WakeUpService</Code><Text>Wake up service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lounge</Code><Text>Lounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CurrencyExchangeService</Code><Text>Currency Exchange Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>24HourFrontDesk</Code><Text>24 Hour Front Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>