<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10842386</Id><Name>The Ickworth Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52428</Id><Name>Bury St Edmunds</Name><CityId>52428</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Horringer 1</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Bury St. Edmunds</City><State /><Zip>IP29 5QE</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 (1284) 735350</Tel><Fax>+44 (1284) 736300</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at The Ickworth Hotel in Bury St Edmunds, you'll be close to Bury St Edmunds Art Gallery and Theatre Royal. This 4.5-star hotel is within close proximity of Athenaeum and St Edmundsbury Cathedral.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 38 air-conditioned rooms featuring DVD players and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access is available. Bathrooms have bathtubs or showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as coffee/tea makers and irons/ironing boards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. You're sure to appreciate the recreational amenities, including an indoor pool and an outdoor tennis court. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of The Ickworth Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary English breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, dry cleaning/laundry services, and an elevator (lift).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of The Ickworth Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary English breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. You're sure to appreciate the recreational amenities, including an indoor pool and an outdoor tennis court. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 38 air-conditioned rooms featuring DVD players and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access is available. Bathrooms have bathtubs or showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as coffee/tea makers and irons/ironing boards.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at The Ickworth Hotel in Bury St Edmunds, you'll be close to Bury St Edmunds Art Gallery and Theatre Royal. This 4.5-star hotel is within close proximity of Athenaeum and St Edmundsbury Cathedral. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Bury St Edmunds Art Gallery - 4.6 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Theatre Royal - 4.6 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Athenaeum - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Edmundsbury Cathedral - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Abbeygate - 4.8 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bury St Edmunds Abbey - 4.9 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Corpus Christi Guildhall - 15.6 km / 9.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Horseracing Museum - 17.4 km / 10.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Newmarket Racecourse - 19 km / 11.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Stud - 19.9 km / 12.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gainsborough's House - 20.9 km / 13 mi &lt;br /&gt;Portman Road - 38 km / 23.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cornhill - 38.3 km / 23.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Christchurch Mansion - 38.5 km / 23.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ipswich Regent Theatre - 38.8 km / 24.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Ickworth Hotel is Norwich (NWI-Norwich Intl.) - 65.2 km / 40.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>InRoomMovies</Code><Text>In-room movies</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndoorPool</Code><Text>Indoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FamilyRooms</Code><Text>Family rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Playground</Code><Text>Playground</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TV</Code><Text>TeleVision</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ChildrensClub</Code><Text>Childrens Club</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>