<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10844788</Id><Name>Dartmouth Golf and Country Club</Name><Region><Id>52478</Id><Name>Dartmouth</Name><CityId>52478</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Blackawton</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Dartmouth</City><State /><Zip>TQ9 7DE</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>44 1803 712686</Tel><Fax>44 1803 712 628</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Best Western The Dartmouth Hotel Golf &amp; Spa in Totnes (English Riviera), you'll be minutes from Woodlands Leisure Park. This golf hotel is within the vicinity of Blackpool Sands and Royal Naval College.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of 42 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Your pillowtop bed comes with down comforters and Egyptian cotton sheets. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;While the golfer in the family is out on the course, try one of the other recreational amenities offered, such as a health club or an indoor pool. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, multilingual staff, and laundry facilities. Event facilities at this hotel consist of conference space and meeting rooms. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; While the golfer in the family is out on the course, try one of the other recreational amenities offered, such as a health club or an indoor pool. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of 42 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Your pillowtop bed comes with down comforters and Egyptian cotton sheets. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Best Western The Dartmouth Hotel Golf &amp; Spa in Totnes (English Riviera), you'll be minutes from Woodlands Leisure Park. This golf hotel is within the vicinity of Blackpool Sands and Royal Naval College. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Woodlands Leisure Park - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Blackpool Sands - 5.8 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Naval College - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dartmouth Museum - 6.2 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dartmouth Castle - 7.3 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Totnes Castle - 8.4 km / 5.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Paignton Zoo - 9.8 km / 6.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Goodrington Sands Beach - 10.8 km / 6.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Paignton Beach - 11.6 km / 7.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Golden Hind - 11.7 km / 7.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Berry Head - 13.6 km / 8.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Torre Abbey - 14.8 km / 9.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Abbey Sands - 14.9 km / 9.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Riviera International Conference Centre - 14.9 km / 9.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Living Coasts - 15 km / 9.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Best Western The Dartmouth Hotel Golf &amp; Spa is Newquay (NQY-Newquay Cornwall) - 94.8 km / 58.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndoorPool</Code><Text>Indoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>GameRoom</Code><Text>GameRoom</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Golf</Code><Text>Golf</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>