<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10844141</Id><Name>Cobham Lodge</Name><Region><Id>52462</Id><Name>Cobham</Name><CityId>52462</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>46 Portsmouth Rd</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Cobham</City><State /><Zip>KT11 1HY</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>44-193-286-2015</Tel><Fax>011-44-193-258-9948</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Cobham Lodge in Cobham, you'll be in the business district and close to Painshill Park and Brooklands Museum. This hotel is within close proximity of The Medicine Garden and Burhill Golf Club.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 39 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and blackout drapes/curtains, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at a coffee shop/café serving guests of Cobham Lodge. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at a coffee shop/café serving guests of Cobham Lodge. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 39 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and blackout drapes/curtains, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Cobham Lodge in Cobham, you'll be in the business district and close to Painshill Park and Brooklands Museum. This hotel is within close proximity of The Medicine Garden and Burhill Golf Club. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Painshill Park - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Medicine Garden - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Burhill Golf Club - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Silvermere Golf Complex - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cobham Training Centre - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Claremont Landscape Garden - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brooklands Museum - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;London Bus Museum - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mercedes-Benz World - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Horticultural Society Garden Wisley - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;RHS Garden Wisley - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Drift Golf Club - 5.1 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Elmbridge Museum - 5.4 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sandown Park - 6 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;KBR Headquarters - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Cobham Lodge is London (LHR-Heathrow) - 15.6 km / 9.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>