<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10846862</Id><Name>Fox Country Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52568</Id><Name>High Wycombe</Name><CityId>52568</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Main Road, Ibstone</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>High Wycombe</City><State /><Zip>HP14 3XT</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>44-149-163-9333</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Fox Country Inn in High Wycombe (Ibstone), you'll be within the vicinity of West Wycombe Park. This hotel is within the region of Leander Club and Henley Bridge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the guestrooms featuring refrigerators and minibars. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones and irons/ironing boards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as concierge services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Event facilities at this hotel consist of meeting rooms and a meeting room. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed      Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as concierge services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the guestrooms featuring refrigerators and minibars. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones and irons/ironing boards.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Fox Country Inn in High Wycombe (Ibstone), you'll be within the vicinity of West Wycombe Park. This hotel is within the region of Leander Club and Henley Bridge. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;West Wycombe Park - 7.9 km / 4.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Leander Club - 11.1 km / 6.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Henley Bridge - 11.2 km / 6.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;River and Rowing Museum - 11.8 km / 7.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bisham Abbey - 13 km / 8.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Longridge Activity Centre - 13.4 km / 8.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Helen's Church - 13.8 km / 8.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Thames Path - 14.8 km / 9.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Roald Dahl Museum and Story Centre - 16.1 km / 10 mi &lt;br /&gt;Waterstock Golf Club - 16.6 km / 10.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stanley Spencer Art Gallery - 16.7 km / 10.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dorchester Abbey - 17.3 km / 10.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Caversham Golf Club - 17.6 km / 11 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cliveden House - 17.9 km / 11.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;All Saints' Church - 18 km / 11.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Fox Country Inn is London (LHR-Heathrow) - 37.1 km / 23.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Fox Country Inn is London (LHR-Heathrow) - 37.1 km / 23.1 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>