<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10849990</Id><Name>Thurnham hall</Name><Region><Id>52598</Id><Name>Lancaster</Name><CityId>52598</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Thurnham</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Nr Lancaster</City><State /><Zip>LA2 0DT</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>01524 751766</Tel><Fax>0044 1524 843 305</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Thurnham Hall in Lancaster (Thurnham), you'll be close to Lancaster University and Forrest Hills. This 4-star aparthotel is within the vicinity of Old Holly Farm and Williamson Park.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 60 guestrooms, featuring kitchens with refrigerators and microwaves. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and DVD players are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as coffee/tea makers and sofa beds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including an indoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna. Additional amenities include wireless Internet access (surcharge), wedding services, and a fireplace in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Thurnham Hall. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour front desk, laundry facilities, and a library. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 4 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Thurnham Hall. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including an indoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna. Additional amenities include wireless Internet access (surcharge), wedding services, and a fireplace in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 60 guestrooms, featuring kitchens with refrigerators and microwaves. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and DVD players are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as coffee/tea makers and sofa beds.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Thurnham Hall in Lancaster (Thurnham), you'll be close to Lancaster University and Forrest Hills. This 4-star aparthotel is within the vicinity of Old Holly Farm and Williamson Park. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Lancaster University - 3.7 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Forrest Hills - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Holly Farm - 5.8 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Williamson Park - 7.2 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ashton Memorial - 7.3 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lancaster City Museum - 7.3 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cottage Museum - 7.4 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Dukes - 7.4 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lancaster Castle - 7.4 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Judges' Lodgings - 7.5 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of St Mary - 7.5 km / 4.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;St John's Historic Church - 7.6 km / 4.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Grand Theater - 7.6 km / 4.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lancaster Maritime Museum - 7.9 km / 4.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Peter's Church - 8.9 km / 5.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Thurnham Hall is Manchester (MAN) - 77.9 km / 48.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Thurnham Hall is Manchester (MAN-Manchester Intl.) - 77.9 km / 48.4 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>