<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10846849</Id><Name>Beales Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52558</Id><Name>Hatfield</Name><CityId>52558</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Comet Way</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Hatfield</City><State /><Zip>AL 10 9NG</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>44-170-728-8500</Tel><Fax>011-44-170-725-6282</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Beales Hotel in Hatfield, you'll be in the business district and convenient to Hatfield House. This 4-star hotel is within the region of Verulamium Museum and Elstree Film Studios.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 53 air-conditioned rooms featuring LCD televisions. Your bed comes with down comforters and Egyptian cotton sheets. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. This hotel also features wedding services, a television in the lobby, and complimentary use of a nearby fitness facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, where you can enjoy drinks at a bar and dine alfresco (weather permitting). Or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. English breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a business center, and express check-in. Event facilities at this hotel consist of a conference center, conference space, and meeting rooms. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, where you can enjoy drinks at a bar and dine alfresco (weather permitting). Or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. English breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. This hotel also features wedding services, a television in the lobby, and complimentary use of a nearby fitness facility. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 53 air-conditioned rooms featuring LCD televisions. Your bed comes with down comforters and Egyptian cotton sheets. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Beales Hotel in Hatfield, you'll be in the business district and convenient to Hatfield House. This 4-star hotel is within the region of Verulamium Museum and Elstree Film Studios. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Hatfield House - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Verulamium Museum - 7.9 km / 4.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Elstree Film Studios - 11.8 km / 7.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Knebworth House - 12.5 km / 7.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Paradise Wildlife Park - 12.5 km / 7.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hertfordshire County Showground - 12.8 km / 7.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Trent Park - 13.6 km / 8.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aldenham Country Park - 13.6 km / 8.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Warner Bros. Studio Tour London - 14.6 km / 9 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Snow Centre - 15.1 km / 9.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bushey Museum and Art Gallery - 15.5 km / 9.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Watford Market - 15.8 km / 9.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vicarage Road - 16.6 km / 10.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Finchley Golf Club - 17 km / 10.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Artsdepot - 17.1 km / 10.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Beales Hotel is London (LTN-Luton) - 16 km / 9.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>