<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10846500</Id><Name>Corse Lawn House Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52539</Id><Name>Gloucester</Name><CityId>52539</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Corse Lawn House Hotel</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Gloucester</City><State /><Zip>GL19 4LZ</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>01482 780771</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Corse Lawn House Hotel in Gloucester (Corse Lawn), you'll be within the vicinity of Tewkesbury Abbey and Roses Theatre. This hotel is within the region of Kingsholm Stadium and Gloucester Cathedral.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the guestrooms featuring refrigerators. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and separate sitting areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as an indoor pool or take in the view from a garden.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Corse Lawn House Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This hotel has 2 meeting rooms available for events. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is Noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Corse Lawn House Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as an indoor pool or take in the view from a garden. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the guestrooms featuring refrigerators. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and separate sitting areas.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Corse Lawn House Hotel in Gloucester (Corse Lawn), you'll be within the vicinity of Tewkesbury Abbey and Roses Theatre. This hotel is within the region of Kingsholm Stadium and Gloucester Cathedral. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Tewkesbury Abbey - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Roses Theatre - 6.8 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kingsholm Stadium - 11.4 km / 7.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gloucester Cathedral - 11.9 km / 7.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gloucester Folk Museum - 11.9 km / 7.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Waterways Museum - 12.2 km / 7.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Regiments of Gloucestershire Museum - 12.2 km / 7.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Merchants' Quay - 12.3 km / 7.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;City Museum - 12.4 km / 7.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cheltenham Racecourse - 13.7 km / 8.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cheltenham Art Gallery and Museum - 13.7 km / 8.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pitville Pump Room - 14.1 km / 8.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Holst Birthplace Museum - 14.4 km / 8.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cheltenham General Hospital - 15 km / 9.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Gloucestershire - 15 km / 9.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Corse Lawn House Hotel is Bristol (BRS-Bristol Intl.) - 72.6 km / 45.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>DRIVING DIRECTIONS TO THE PROPERTY&amp;#x0D;FROM BIRMINGHAM AIRPORT HEAD FOR M6/M5 SOUTH  FOLLOW M5 TO&amp;#x0D;J8  M50 . GET OFF M50 IMMEDIATELY   J1. TAKE A38 TO&amp;#x0D;TEWKESBURY. JUST BEFORE TEWKESBURY  3 MILES  TURN RIGHT ONTO&amp;#x0D;A438 TOWARDS LEDBURY. GO 3 MILES AND TURN LEFT ON B4211.&amp;#x0D;AMONGST OTHERS THERE IS A FINGER POST THAT SAYS CORSE LAWN 1&amp;#x0D;MILES. WE ARE ON THE RIGHT HAND SIDE.&amp;#x0D;COME UP M50. GET OFF AT J2 AND FOLLOW SIGNS FOR GLOUCESTER&amp;#x0D;ON A417.&amp;#x0D;FROM BRISTOL AIRPORT HEAD TO M5 NORTHFOLLOW M5 TO J8  M50 .&amp;#x0D;GET OFF M50 IMMEDIATELY   J1. TAKE A38 TO TEWKESBURY. JUST&amp;#x0D;BEFORE TEWKESBURY  3 MILES  TURN RIGHT ONTO A438 TOWARDS&amp;#x0D;LEDBURY. GO 3 MILES AND TURN LEFT ON B4211. AMONGST OTHERS&amp;#x0D;THERE IS A FINGER POST THAT SAYS CORSE LAWN 1  MILES</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>