<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10840554</Id><Name>Sea Breeze Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52414</Id><Name>Brighton</Name><CityId>52414</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>13 Upper Rock Gardens</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Brighton</City><State /><Zip>BN2 1QE</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>0844 736 1847</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Sea Breeze Brighton places you in the heart of Brighton, walking distance from Brighton Wheel and Brighton Sea Life Centre. This 4-star guesthouse is within close proximity of Brighton Pier and Victoria Gardens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of 7 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and complimentary toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;For your convenience, a complimentary breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, express check-out, and luggage storage.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; For your convenience, a complimentary breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of 7 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and complimentary toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Sea Breeze Brighton places you in the heart of Brighton, walking distance from Brighton Wheel and Brighton Sea Life Centre. This 4-star guesthouse is within close proximity of Brighton Pier and Victoria Gardens. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Brighton Wheel - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brighton Sea Life Centre - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brighton Pier - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Victoria Gardens - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brighton Royal Pavilion - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Corn Exchange - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brighton Dome - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brighton Museum and Art Gallery - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Police Cells Museum - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chapel Royal - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brighton Theatre Royal - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pavilion Theatre - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brighton Lanes - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Komedia Brighton - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Friends Meeting House - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Sea Breeze Brighton is London (LGW-Gatwick) - 37.3 km / 23.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>