<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10840984</Id><Name>The Regency Bristol Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52850</Id><Name>Bristol</Name><CityId>52416</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>40 - 44 St Pauls Road,</Address1><Address2>Clifton</Address2><Address3 /><City>Bristol</City><State /><Zip>BS8 1LR</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>0117 9238788</Tel><Fax>0117 3295501</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at The Regency Bristol Hotel, you'll be centrally located in Bristol, steps from Victoria Rooms and minutes from BBC Bristol. This hotel is within close proximity of Royal West of England Academy and Clifton Cathedral.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of the guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Your room comes with a Select Comfort bed. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have designer toiletries and complimentary toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour front desk and luggage storage. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of the guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Your room comes with a Select Comfort bed. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have designer toiletries and complimentary toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at The Regency Bristol Hotel, you'll be centrally located in Bristol, steps from Victoria Rooms and minutes from BBC Bristol. This hotel is within close proximity of Royal West of England Academy and Clifton Cathedral. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Victoria Rooms - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;BBC Bristol - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal West of England Academy - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Clifton Cathedral - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bristol City Museum and Art Gallery - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Bristol - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brandon Hill - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cabot Tower - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Georgian House - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Red Lodge - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bristol Ice Rink - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bristol Council House - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Clifton Downs and Observatory - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Colston Hall - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bristol Cathedral - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Regency Bristol Hotel is Bristol (BRS-Bristol Intl.) - 10.4 km / 6.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>