<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10844784</Id><Name>Rowhill Grange Hotel and Utopia Spa</Name><Region><Id>52477</Id><Name>Dartford</Name><CityId>52477</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Wilmington</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Dartford</City><State /><Zip>DA2 7QH</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>44-124-625-2397</Tel><Fax>011-44-1342-859-759</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Dartford (Wilmington), Rowhill Grange Hotel &amp; Utopia Spa is close to Birchwood Park Golf Centre and St. John's Jerusalem. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Dartford Borough Museum and Orchard Theatre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of 38 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Your Select Comfort bed comes with Egyptian cotton sheets. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature designer toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. You can take advantage of recreational amenities such as a health club, an indoor pool, and a spa tub. Additional features at this Victorian hotel include complimentary wireless Internet access, a hair salon, and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at one of the hotel's dining establishments, which include 2 restaurants and a coffee shop/café. From your room, you can also access 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, express check-in, and express check-out. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at one of the hotel's dining establishments, which include 2 restaurants and a coffee shop/café. From your room, you can also access 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. You can take advantage of recreational amenities such as a health club, an indoor pool, and a spa tub. Additional features at this Victorian hotel include complimentary wireless Internet access, a hair salon, and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of 38 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Your Select Comfort bed comes with Egyptian cotton sheets. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature designer toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Dartford (Wilmington), Rowhill Grange Hotel &amp; Utopia Spa is close to Birchwood Park Golf Centre and St. John's Jerusalem. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Dartford Borough Museum and Orchard Theatre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Birchwood Park Golf Centre - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. John's Jerusalem - 3.5 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dartford Borough Museum - 3.8 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Orchard Theatre - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eagle Heights Wildlife Park - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lullingstone Roman Villa - 5.7 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Red House - 6 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lullingstone Castle - 6.4 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bluewater Shopping Centre - 6.5 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Danson House - 6.7 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brands Hatch Circuit - 7.9 km / 4.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chislehurst Caves - 9.1 km / 5.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Elmstead Wood - 9.7 km / 6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eltham Palace - 10.3 km / 6.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;London Golf Club - 10.5 km / 6.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;London (LCY-London City) - 13.7 km / 8.5 mi&lt;br /&gt;London (LGW-Gatwick) - 37.8 km / 23.5 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Rowhill Grange Hotel &amp; Utopia Spa is London (LGW-Gatwick). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Rowhill Grange Hotel &amp; Utopia Spa is London (LGW-Gatwick) - 37.8 km / 23.5 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>