<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10846471</Id><Name>Falmouth Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52946</Id><Name>Falmouth</Name><CityId>52946</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Castle Beach</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Falmout</City><State /><Zip>TR11 4NZ</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 (013) 26312671</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at The Falmouth Hotel places you in the heart of Falmouth, steps from Gyllyngvase Beach and close to National Maritime Museum. This hotel is within close proximity of Swanpool Beach and Pendinnis Castle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 71 guestrooms. Private bathrooms with bathtubs feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones and coffee/tea makers, and you can also request irons/ironing boards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Treat yourself with massages and facials. You're sure to appreciate the recreational amenities, including an indoor pool, a sauna, and a fitness center. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of The Falmouth Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. For your convenience, a complimentary breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a safe deposit box at the front desk and an elevator (lift). This hotel has 6 meeting rooms available for events. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of The Falmouth Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. For your convenience, a complimentary breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Treat yourself with massages and facials. You're sure to appreciate the recreational amenities, including an indoor pool, a sauna, and a fitness center. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 71 guestrooms. Private bathrooms with bathtubs feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones and coffee/tea makers, and you can also request irons/ironing boards.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at The Falmouth Hotel places you in the heart of Falmouth, steps from Gyllyngvase Beach and close to National Maritime Museum. This hotel is within close proximity of Swanpool Beach and Pendinnis Castle. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Gyllyngvase Beach - 0 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Maritime Museum - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Swanpool Beach - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pendinnis Castle - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maenporth Beach - 2.8 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Mawes Castle - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gweek Seal Sanctuary - 11.3 km / 7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Cornwall Museum - 13.2 km / 8.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Truro Cathedral - 13.3 km / 8.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Loe Bar Beach - 18.1 km / 11.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Poldhu Cove - 18.6 km / 11.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Porthleven Beach - 19 km / 11.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Polurrian Beach - 19 km / 11.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Caerhays Castle - 19 km / 11.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Porthluney Cove - 19.1 km / 11.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Falmouth Hotel is Newquay (NQY-Newquay Cornwall) - 33 km / 20.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TV</Code><Text>TeleVision</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>