<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10850492</Id><Name>Amblehurst Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52720</Id><Name>Sale</Name><CityId>52720</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>44 Washway Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Manchester</City><State /><Zip>M33 7QZ</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>0161-973-8800</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Amblehurst Hotel in Sale, you'll be in the suburbs and close to Chorlton Ees Nature Reserve and Wythenshawe Hall. This hotel is within close proximity of Old Trafford Cricket Ground and EventCity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 50 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, a 24-hour front desk, and luggage storage. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 50 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Amblehurst Hotel in Sale, you'll be in the suburbs and close to Chorlton Ees Nature Reserve and Wythenshawe Hall. This hotel is within close proximity of Old Trafford Cricket Ground and EventCity. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Chorlton Ees Nature Reserve - 2.7 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wythenshawe Hall - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Trafford Cricket Ground - 4.6 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;EventCity - 4.8 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Legoland Discovery Centre - 4.8 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Trafford Centre - 4.9 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Northenden Golf Course - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Manchester United Museum - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Trafford - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Withington Golf Course - 5.2 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Imperial War Museum North - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chill FactorE - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Airkix Indoor Skydiving - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Lowry Art and Entertainment - 5.7 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Didsbury Golf Course - 5.7 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Amblehurst Hotel is Manchester (MAN) - 7.7 km / 4.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>