<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10855945</Id><Name>Ilsington Country House Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52661</Id><Name>Newton Abbot</Name><CityId>52661</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Ilsington Village</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Newton Abbot</City><State /><Zip>TQ13 9RR</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 (1364) 44-1364-661452</Tel><Fax>+44 (1364) 661307</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Ilsington Country House Hotel in Newton Abbot (Dartmoor), you'll be within the vicinity of Grimspound and Buckfast Abbey. This hotel is within the region of Bellever Tor and Castle Drogo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of 25 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Relax and unwind with massages and body treatments. If you're looking for recreational opportunities, you'll find a health club, an indoor pool, and a spa tub.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, where you can take in a garden view, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, multilingual staff, and laundry facilities. Event facilities at this hotel consist of a conference center, conference space, and meeting rooms. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, where you can take in a garden view, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Relax and unwind with massages and body treatments. If you're looking for recreational opportunities, you'll find a health club, an indoor pool, and a spa tub. &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of 25 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Ilsington Country House Hotel in Newton Abbot (Dartmoor), you'll be within the vicinity of Grimspound and Buckfast Abbey. This hotel is within the region of Bellever Tor and Castle Drogo. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Grimspound - 8.9 km / 5.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Buckfast Abbey - 9.3 km / 5.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bellever Tor - 13.1 km / 8.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Castle Drogo - 15 km / 9.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Totnes Castle - 15.8 km / 9.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dartmoor Forest - 16.6 km / 10.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dartmoor National Park - 16.8 km / 10.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Babbacombe Model Village and Gardens - 17.7 km / 11 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bygones Victorian Museum - 17.8 km / 11.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Torre Abbey - 17.9 km / 11.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Riviera International Conference Centre - 17.9 km / 11.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Babbacombe Beach - 18 km / 11.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Abbey Sands - 18.3 km / 11.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Princess Theatre - 18.7 km / 11.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Paignton Zoo - 19 km / 11.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Ilsington Country House Hotel is Exeter (EXT-Exeter Intl.) - 28.3 km / 17.6 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Sauna</Code><Text>Sauna</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndoorPool</Code><Text>Indoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WakeUpService</Code><Text>Wake up service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarRentDesk</Code><Text>Car rental desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CoffeeShop</Code><Text>Coffee shop</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SteamBath</Code><Text>Steam Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Golf</Code><Text>Golf</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TV</Code><Text>TeleVision</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shops</Code><Text>Shops</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Doctoroncall</Code><Text>Doctor on call</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>