<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10859059</Id><Name>George in Rye</Name><Region><Id>153616</Id><Name>Rye</Name><CityId>153616</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>98 High Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Rye</City><State /><Zip>TN31 7JT</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>01797222114</Tel><Fax>+44 (1797) 224065</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at The George in Rye in Rye, you'll be minutes from Rye Castle Museum and Lamb House. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Rye Art Gallery and Rye St. Mary's Parish Church.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 34 guestrooms featuring DVD players. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Bathrooms have designer toiletries and bathrobes. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant or in a coffee shop/café. Or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant or in a coffee shop/café. Or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 34 guestrooms featuring DVD players. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Bathrooms have designer toiletries and bathrobes. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at The George in Rye in Rye, you'll be minutes from Rye Castle Museum and Lamb House. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Rye Art Gallery and Rye St. Mary's Parish Church. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Rye Castle Museum - 0.1 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lamb House - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rye Art Gallery - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rye St. Mary's Parish Church - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rye Heritage Centre - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Camber Castle - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rye Harbour Nature Reserve - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of St Thomas a Becket - 3.5 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Camber Sands - 4.8 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rye Farm World - 8.6 km / 5.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Smallythe Place - 10 km / 6.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Chapel Down Winery - 10.3 km / 6.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Great Dixter House and Gardens - 11 km / 6.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hastings Country Park - 11.3 km / 7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tenterden Museum - 13.5 km / 8.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The George in Rye is London (LCY-London City) - 77.7 km / 48.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for The George in Rye is London (LCY-London City) - 77.7 km / 48.3 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ContinentalBreakfast</Code><Text>Contintenal breakfast</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WakeUpService</Code><Text>Wake up service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CoffeeShop</Code><Text>Coffee shop</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TrouserPress</Code><Text>Trouser press</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TV</Code><Text>TeleVision</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>