<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10856459</Id><Name>Imperial Plymouth Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52683</Id><Name>Plymouth</Name><CityId>52683</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Lockyer Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Plymouth</City><State /><Zip>PL1 2QD</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>01752 227311</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at The Imperial Plymouth in Plymouth, you'll be near the beach and minutes from Smeatons Tower and Plymouth Dome. This 4-star guesthouse is within close proximity of Royal Citadel and Elizabethan House.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 20 guestrooms featuring DVD players and flat-screen televisions. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at a coffee shop/café serving guests of The Imperial Plymouth. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access and multilingual staff. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at a coffee shop/café serving guests of The Imperial Plymouth. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 20 guestrooms featuring DVD players and flat-screen televisions. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at The Imperial Plymouth in Plymouth, you'll be near the beach and minutes from Smeatons Tower and Plymouth Dome. This 4-star guesthouse is within close proximity of Royal Citadel and Elizabethan House. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Smeatons Tower - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Plymouth Dome - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Citadel - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Elizabethan House - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Charles Church - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mayflower Steps - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Plymouth - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Maritime Aquarium - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Marine Aquarium - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Home Park - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mt. Edgcumbe - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Saltram House - 4.6 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Whitsand Bay Beach - 8.2 km / 5.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Buckland Abbey - 12.7 km / 7.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Garden House - 14.1 km / 8.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Plymouth (PLH-Plymouth City) - 6.5 km / 4 mi&lt;br /&gt;Exeter (EXT-Exeter Intl.) - 65.4 km / 40.6 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Imperial Plymouth is Exeter (EXT-Exeter Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>