<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10859576</Id><Name>The Coniston Hotel- A Recommended Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52735</Id><Name>Skipton</Name><CityId>52735</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Coniston Cold</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Skipton, North Yorkshire</City><State /><Zip>BD23 4EA</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>017-567-480-80</Tel><Fax>+44 (1756) 749487</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Skipton (Coniston Cold), The Coniston Hotel and Country Estate is within the vicinity of Yorkshire Dales Mining Museum and The Mart Theatre. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of Gordale Scar and Malham Cove.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 71 individually decorated guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have separate bathtubs and showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as bicycles to rent or take in the view from a garden. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and a picnic area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, where you can take in a garden view, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, express check-out, and dry cleaning/laundry services. Planning an event in Skipton? This hotel has facilities measuring 100 square feet (9 square meters), including conference space. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2:30 PM  Check-out time is 10:30 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, where you can take in a garden view, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as bicycles to rent or take in the view from a garden. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and a picnic area. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 71 individually decorated guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have separate bathtubs and showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Skipton (Coniston Cold), The Coniston Hotel and Country Estate is within the vicinity of Yorkshire Dales Mining Museum and The Mart Theatre. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of Gordale Scar and Malham Cove. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Yorkshire Dales Mining Museum - 8.5 km / 5.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Mart Theatre - 8.7 km / 5.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gordale Scar - 8.8 km / 5.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Malham Cove - 8.8 km / 5.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Craven Museum and Gallery - 10.3 km / 6.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Skipton Castle - 10.3 km / 6.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Settle Victoria Hall - 11.2 km / 7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kilnsey Park Estate - 14.8 km / 9.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Muni Theater - 15.3 km / 9.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lund's Tower - 15.7 km / 9.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Yorkshire Dales Falconry and Conservation Centre - 16.2 km / 10.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wycoller Country Park - 16.4 km / 10.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pendle Hill - 16.4 km / 10.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Atom - 16.6 km / 10.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hesketh Farm Park - 16.6 km / 10.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Coniston Hotel and Country Estate is Leeds (LBA-Leeds Bradford) - 35.8 km / 22.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Doctoroncall</Code><Text>Doctor on call</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>