<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10850477</Id><Name>Thames Riviera Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52628</Id><Name>Maidenhead</Name><CityId>52628</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Bridge Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Maidenhead</City><State /><Zip>SL6 8DW</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 (1628) 44-1628-674057</Tel><Fax>+44 (1628) 776586</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Maidenhead, Thames Riviera Hotel is minutes from Maidenhead Railway Bridge and close to All Saints' Church. This hotel is within close proximity of Bray Marina and Stanley Spencer Art Gallery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of 52 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include laptop-compatible safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Thames Riviera Hotel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Thames Riviera Hotel. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of 52 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include laptop-compatible safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Maidenhead, Thames Riviera Hotel is minutes from Maidenhead Railway Bridge and close to All Saints' Church. This hotel is within close proximity of Bray Marina and Stanley Spencer Art Gallery. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Maidenhead Railway Bridge - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;All Saints' Church - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bray Marina - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stanley Spencer Art Gallery - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cliveden House - 4.1 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dorney Lake - 5.4 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Longridge Activity Centre - 6 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bisham Abbey - 6.4 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Windsor Racecourse - 6.4 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Windsor Leisure Centre - 7 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bird Hills Golf Centre - 7.1 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eton College - 7.4 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eton High Street Shopping - 7.6 km / 4.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Mary's Church - 7.7 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Windsor Bridge - 7.8 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Thames Riviera Hotel is London (LHR-Heathrow) - 18.5 km / 11.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WakeUpService</Code><Text>Wake up service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FamilyRooms</Code><Text>Family rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CoffeeShop</Code><Text>Coffee shop</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Freenewspaper</Code><Text>Free Newspaper</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Golf</Code><Text>Golf</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TV</Code><Text>TeleVision</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>24HourFrontDesk</Code><Text>24 Hour Front Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>