<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10855516</Id><Name>Hare &amp; Hounds Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52656</Id><Name>Newbury</Name><CityId>52656</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Bath Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Newbury</City><State /><Zip>RG14 1QY</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>01635 521152</Tel><Fax>+44 (01635) 47708</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Newbury, Hare &amp; Hounds Hotel is in a rural location and convenient to Deanwood Park Golf Course and Donnington Castle. This hotel is within close proximity of Watermill Theatre and Newbury Town Hall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 30 guestrooms featuring DVD players. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and babysitting/childcare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hare &amp; Hounds Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-out, dry cleaning/laundry services, and laundry facilities. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed       &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hare &amp; Hounds Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and babysitting/childcare. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 30 guestrooms featuring DVD players. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Newbury, Hare &amp; Hounds Hotel is in a rural location and convenient to Deanwood Park Golf Course and Donnington Castle. This hotel is within close proximity of Watermill Theatre and Newbury Town Hall. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Deanwood Park Golf Course - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Donnington Castle - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Watermill Theatre - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Newbury Town Hall - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;West Berkshire Museum - 2 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shaw House - 2 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Newbury Racecourse - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Newbury and Crookham Golf Club - 4.9 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Thatcham Nature Discovery Centre - 5.1 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Greenham Common - 5.2 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Mary's Church - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Welford Park - 6.8 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;4 Kingdoms Adventure Park - 7.1 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sandham Memorial Chapel - 7.4 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Highclere Castle - 9.2 km / 5.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hare &amp; Hounds Hotel is London (LHR-Heathrow) - 62.5 km / 38.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>