<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10859555</Id><Name>Prince Rupert Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52733</Id><Name>Shrewsbury</Name><CityId>52733</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Butcher Row</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Shrewsbury</City><State /><Zip>SY1 1UQ</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 (1743) 44-1743-499955</Tel><Fax>+44 (1743) 357306</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Prince Rupert Hotel, you'll be centrally located in Shrewsbury, steps from St. Mary's Church and minutes from Shrewsbury Castle. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Shrewsbury Abbey and Greenhous Meadow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of 50 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) is available to keep you connected. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Relax at the full-service spa, where you can enjoy body treatments and facials. You can take advantage of recreational amenities such as a health club, a spa tub, and a sauna. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, an arcade/game room, and a hair salon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at one of the hotel's dining establishments, which include 2 restaurants and a coffee shop/café. From your room, you can also access 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary full breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, a 24-hour front desk, and luggage storage. Planning an event in Shrewsbury? This hotel has facilities measuring 301 square feet (28 square meters), including meeting rooms.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at one of the hotel's dining establishments, which include 2 restaurants and a coffee shop/café. From your room, you can also access 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary full breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Relax at the full-service spa, where you can enjoy body treatments and facials. You can take advantage of recreational amenities such as a health club, a spa tub, and a sauna. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, an arcade/game room, and a hair salon. &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of 50 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) is available to keep you connected. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Prince Rupert Hotel, you'll be centrally located in Shrewsbury, steps from St. Mary's Church and minutes from Shrewsbury Castle. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Shrewsbury Abbey and Greenhous Meadow. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;St. Mary's Church - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shrewsbury Castle - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shrewsbury Abbey - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Greenhous Meadow - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ironbridge Museum - 19.1 km / 11.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Iron Bridge - 21 km / 13 mi &lt;br /&gt;Blists Hill - 22.1 km / 13.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maws Craft Centre - 22.2 km / 13.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Coalport China Museum - 22.7 km / 14.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Julilee Park - 29.3 km / 18.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;JB Joyce and Company - 29.4 km / 18.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Whitechurch Heritage Centre - 29.5 km / 18.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Weston Park - 31.4 km / 19.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Titterstone Clee Hill - 36.7 km / 22.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ludlow Castle - 38 km / 23.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Prince Rupert Hotel is Birmingham (BHX) - 74.6 km / 46.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Prince Rupert Classic Hotel is Birmingham (BHX) - 74.6 km / 46.3 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Sauna</Code><Text>Sauna</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WakeUpService</Code><Text>Wake up service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CoffeeShop</Code><Text>Coffee shop</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>GameRoom</Code><Text>GameRoom</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SteamBath</Code><Text>Steam Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Golf</Code><Text>Golf</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TV</Code><Text>TeleVision</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shops</Code><Text>Shops</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CurrencyExchangeService</Code><Text>Currency Exchange Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>24HourFrontDesk</Code><Text>24 Hour Front Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Doctoroncall</Code><Text>Doctor on call</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>