<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10859571</Id><Name>BEST WESTERN The Grange at Oborne</Name><Region><Id>52731</Id><Name>Sherborne</Name><CityId>52731</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Oborne</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Sherborne</City><State /><Zip>DT9 4LA</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 +44 1935 813463</Tel><Fax>+44 44 1935 817464</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/SHER-BEShotel_Exterior_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>239</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/SHER-BEShotel_Exterior_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Sherborne, Best Western The Grange at Oborne is convenient to Sherborne Steam and Waterwheel Centre and Sherborne Old Castle.  This romantic hotel is within close proximity of Sherborne Castle and Global Images Gallery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 18 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones and coffee/tea makers, and you can also request irons/ironing boards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). A complimentary full breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This hotel has 2 meeting rooms available for events. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). A complimentary full breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 18 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones and coffee/tea makers, and you can also request irons/ironing boards.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Sherborne, Best Western The Grange at Oborne is convenient to Sherborne Steam and Waterwheel Centre and Sherborne Old Castle.  This romantic hotel is within close proximity of Sherborne Castle and Global Images Gallery. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Sherborne Steam and Waterwheel Centre - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sherborne Old Castle - 2 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sherborne Castle - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Global Images Gallery - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sherborne Museum - 2.7 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sherborne Abbey - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cadbury Castle - 7.1 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Haynes International Motor Museum - 9.4 km / 5.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fleet Air Arm Museum - 11.9 km / 7.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sturminster Newton Mill - 13.7 km / 8.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lytes Cary Manor - 14.8 km / 9.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tintinhull House Garden - 15.3 km / 9.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Montacute House - 15.7 km / 9.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cerne Abbas Giant - 17 km / 10.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stourhead - 19.5 km / 12.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Best Western The Grange at Oborne is Bristol (BRS-Bristol Intl.) - 48.9 km / 30.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WakeUpService</Code><Text>Wake up service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Playground</Code><Text>Playground</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lounge</Code><Text>Lounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>24HourFrontDesk</Code><Text>24 Hour Front Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>