<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10855505</Id><Name>Windsor Hotel Newcastle</Name><Region><Id>52657</Id><Name>Newcastle Upon Tyne</Name><CityId>52657</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>South Parade Whitley Bay</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Newcastle Upon Tyne</City><State /><Zip>NE26 2RF</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>44-191-251-8888</Tel><Fax>011-44-191-297-0272</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Windsor Hotel in Whitley Bay, you'll be near the beach and close to Blue Reef Aquarium and St. Mary's Lighthouse. This hotel is within close proximity of Tynemouth Castle and Arbeia Roman Fort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 67 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have separate bathtubs and showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers, as well as phones with free local calls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Windsor Hotel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk. Planning an event in Whitley Bay? This hotel has 5380 square feet (500 square meters) of space consisting of a conference center and meeting rooms. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Windsor Hotel. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 67 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have separate bathtubs and showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers, as well as phones with free local calls.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Windsor Hotel in Whitley Bay, you'll be near the beach and close to Blue Reef Aquarium and St. Mary's Lighthouse. This hotel is within close proximity of Tynemouth Castle and Arbeia Roman Fort. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Blue Reef Aquarium - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Mary's Lighthouse - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tynemouth Castle - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Arbeia Roman Fort - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Seaton Sluice Beach - 5.4 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Port Of Tyne - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Seaton Delaval Hall - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Seaton Delaval Arts Centre - 6.2 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bede's World - 7.1 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Paul's Monastery - 7.3 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marsden Rock Bird Reserve - 7.4 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Blyth Battery - 8.1 km / 5.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Segedunum Roman Fort - 8.4 km / 5.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ridley Park - 9.6 km / 5.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Souter Point Lighthouse - 9.6 km / 6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Windsor Hotel is Newcastle (NCL-Newcastle Intl.) - 17.1 km / 10.6 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>