<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10858379</Id><Name>Swan at Streatley</Name><Region><Id>52699</Id><Name>Reading</Name><CityId>52699</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Streatley On Thames</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Reading</City><State /><Zip>RG8 9HR</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 (1491) 44-1491-878800</Tel><Fax>+44 (871) 2636820</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at The Swan at Streatley in Reading (Streatley), you'll be convenient to Lardon Chase - the Holies and Lough Down and Basildon Park. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of Beale Park and Living Rainforest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 39 guestrooms. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as complimentary newspapers and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers body treatments and facials. You're sure to appreciate the recreational amenities, including a health club, an indoor pool, and a spa tub. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite at one of the hotel's 2 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and dry cleaning/laundry services. This hotel has 5 meeting rooms available for events. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite at one of the hotel's 2 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers body treatments and facials. You're sure to appreciate the recreational amenities, including a health club, an indoor pool, and a spa tub. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 39 guestrooms. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as complimentary newspapers and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at The Swan at Streatley in Reading (Streatley), you'll be convenient to Lardon Chase - the Holies and Lough Down and Basildon Park. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of Beale Park and Living Rainforest. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Lardon Chase - the Holies and Lough Down - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Basildon Park - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Beale Park - 3.8 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Living Rainforest - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mapledurham House and Watermill - 8.5 km / 5.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Thames Path - 8.8 km / 5.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Caversham Golf Club - 10.3 km / 6.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Helen's Church - 11 km / 6.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bucklebury Farm Park - 11.5 km / 7.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;UK Wolf Centre - 12 km / 7.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Prospect Park - 12.3 km / 7.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dorchester Abbey - 13.5 km / 8.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Broad Street Mall - 13.9 km / 8.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hexagon - 13.9 km / 8.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Reading Civic Centre - 13.9 km / 8.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Swan at Streatley is London (LHR-Heathrow) - 48.4 km / 30.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Sauna</Code><Text>Sauna</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WakeUpService</Code><Text>Wake up service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TV</Code><Text>TeleVision</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shops</Code><Text>Shops</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Sun roof solarium</Code><Text>Sun roof solarium</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>24HourFrontDesk</Code><Text>24 Hour Front Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Doctoroncall</Code><Text>Doctor on call</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>