<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10850196</Id><Name>Staycity Serviced Apartments Duke St, Lever Court</Name><Region><Id>52609</Id><Name>Liverpool</Name><CityId>52609</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>37-41 Duke Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Liverpool</City><State /><Zip>L15AP</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 151 707 2302</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Staycity Serviced Apartments - Duke St, Lever Court, you'll be centrally located in Liverpool, steps from Neptune Theatre and minutes from Liverpool ONE. This 4-star apartment is within close proximity of Concert Square and Clayton Square Shopping Centre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 52 guestrooms, featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed, and all rooms are furnished with sofa beds. LCD televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include desks and separate sitting areas, and housekeeping is provided weekly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a computer station, a 24-hour front desk, and an elevator (lift). Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 52 guestrooms, featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed, and all rooms are furnished with sofa beds. LCD televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include desks and separate sitting areas, and housekeeping is provided weekly.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Staycity Serviced Apartments - Duke St, Lever Court, you'll be centrally located in Liverpool, steps from Neptune Theatre and minutes from Liverpool ONE. This 4-star apartment is within close proximity of Concert Square and Clayton Square Shopping Centre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Neptune Theatre - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Concert Square - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Liverpool ONE - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Clayton Square Shopping Centre - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;FACT - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;St John's Beacon - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Liverpool Playhouse - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cavern Club - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Merseyside Maritime Museum - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;International Slavery Museum - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Court Theatre - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Static Gallery - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Beatles Story - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Liverpool Wheel - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Liverpool National Conservation Centre - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Staycity Serviced Apartments - Duke St, Lever Court is Liverpool (LPL-John Lennon) - 11.2 km / 6.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>