<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10850305</Id><Name>The  Crown Manor House Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52626</Id><Name>Lyndhurst</Name><CityId>52626</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>High Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Lyndhurst</City><State /><Zip>SO43 7NF</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>02380 28 29 22</Tel><Fax>+44 (2380) 282751</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at The Crown Manor House Hotel in Lyndhurst (New Forest), you'll be minutes from New Forest Museum and close to New Forest Golf Club. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of New Forest and Rufus Stone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of 50 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Bathrooms feature shower/tub combinations, complimentary toiletries, and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary English breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour front desk, a safe deposit box at the front desk, and an elevator (lift). This hotel has 5 meeting rooms available for events. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary English breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of 50 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Bathrooms feature shower/tub combinations, complimentary toiletries, and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at The Crown Manor House Hotel in Lyndhurst (New Forest), you'll be minutes from New Forest Museum and close to New Forest Golf Club. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of New Forest and Rufus Stone. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;New Forest Museum - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;New Forest Golf Club - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;New Forest - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rufus Stone - 5.1 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bolderwood Deer Sanctuary - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brockenhurst College - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;New Forest Wildlife Park - 5.8 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bramshaw Golf Club - 6.4 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Nicholas Church - 6.5 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brockenhurst Manor Golf Club - 7.3 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eling Tide Mill - 8 km / 5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Peppa Pig World - 8.6 km / 5.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Paultons Family Theme Park - 8.6 km / 5.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Burley Golf Club - 9.7 km / 6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Burley Park - 10 km / 6.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Crown Manor House Hotel is Southampton (SOU) - 17.6 km / 10.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>