<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10859073</Id><Name>The Hope Anchor</Name><Region><Id>153616</Id><Name>Rye</Name><CityId>153616</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Watchbell Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Rye, East Sussex</City><State /><Zip>TN31 7HA</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>01797 222216</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Rye, The Hope Anchor Hotel and Restaurant is minutes from Lamb House and Rye Heritage Centre. This hotel is within close proximity of Rye St. Mary's Parish Church and Rye Castle Museum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 16 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and complimentary newspapers, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (complimentary).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of The Hope Anchor Hotel and Restaurant. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, dry cleaning/laundry services, and luggage storage. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of The Hope Anchor Hotel and Restaurant. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 16 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and complimentary newspapers, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (complimentary).</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Rye, The Hope Anchor Hotel and Restaurant is minutes from Lamb House and Rye Heritage Centre. This hotel is within close proximity of Rye St. Mary's Parish Church and Rye Castle Museum. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Lamb House - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rye Heritage Centre - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rye St. Mary's Parish Church - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rye Castle Museum - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rye Art Gallery - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Camber Castle - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rye Harbour Nature Reserve - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of St Thomas a Becket - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Camber Sands - 4.8 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rye Farm World - 8.7 km / 5.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Smallythe Place - 10.2 km / 6.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Chapel Down Winery - 10.5 km / 6.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Great Dixter House and Gardens - 11 km / 6.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hastings Country Park - 11.1 km / 6.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Morgan Museum - 13.6 km / 8.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Hope Anchor Hotel and Restaurant is London (LGW-Gatwick) - 66.8 km / 41.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>