<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10856228</Id><Name>The Old Bank Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52674</Id><Name>Oxford</Name><CityId>52674</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>92-94 High Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Oxford</City><State /><Zip>OX1 4BJ</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>0014-418-657-995-99</Tel><Fax>+44 (0) 1865 799598</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Old Bank Hotel in Oxford (Oxford City Centre), you'll be minutes from All Souls College and University Church of St Mary the Virgin.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Radcliffe Camera and University College.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 42 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have designer toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Treat yourself with massages and facials. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Old Bank Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and dry cleaning/laundry services. This hotel has 4 meeting rooms available for events. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Old Bank Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Treat yourself with massages and facials. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 42 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have designer toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Old Bank Hotel in Oxford (Oxford City Centre), you'll be minutes from All Souls College and University Church of St Mary the Virgin.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Radcliffe Camera and University College. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;All Souls College - 0 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;University Church of St Mary the Virgin - 0.1 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;Radcliffe Camera - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;University College - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brasenose College - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Queen's College - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Divinity School - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hertford College - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Merton College - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bodleian Library - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bridge of Sighs - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;New College - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sheldonian Theatre - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Exeter College - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Covered Market - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Old Bank Hotel is London (LHR-Heathrow) - 63.7 km / 39.6 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>