<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10855441</Id><Name>Rookery Hall</Name><Region><Id>52652</Id><Name>Nantwich</Name><CityId>52652</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Worleston</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Nantwich</City><State /><Zip /><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>44-1270-610016</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Rookery Hall Hotel in Nantwich (Worleston), you'll be within the vicinity of Alexandra Stadium and Wychwood Park Conference Centre. This 4-star hotel is within the region of JB Joyce and Company and Whitechurch Heritage Centre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 70 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring minibars and plasma televisions. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while DVD players and satellite programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and complimentary newspapers, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. If you're looking for recreational opportunities, you'll find an indoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and a fireplace in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at one of the hotel's dining establishments, which include 3 restaurants and a coffee shop/café. From your room, you can also access 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, limo/town car service, and a computer station. Planning an event in Nantwich? This hotel has 5552 square feet (516 square meters) of space consisting of conference space and meeting rooms. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at one of the hotel's dining establishments, which include 3 restaurants and a coffee shop/café. From your room, you can also access 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. If you're looking for recreational opportunities, you'll find an indoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and a fireplace in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 70 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring minibars and plasma televisions. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while DVD players and satellite programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and complimentary newspapers, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Rookery Hall Hotel in Nantwich (Worleston), you'll be within the vicinity of Alexandra Stadium and Wychwood Park Conference Centre. This 4-star hotel is within the region of JB Joyce and Company and Whitechurch Heritage Centre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Alexandra Stadium - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wychwood Park Conference Centre - 9.7 km / 6 mi &lt;br /&gt;JB Joyce and Company - 18.2 km / 11.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Whitechurch Heritage Centre - 18.4 km / 11.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Julilee Park - 18.6 km / 11.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Loomer Road Stadium - 18.7 km / 11.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Delamere Forest - 19.6 km / 12.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jodrell Bank Discovery Centre - 20.6 km / 12.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Capesthorne Hall - 24.8 km / 15.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Arley Hall - 25 km / 15.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Paul's Church - 26.1 km / 16.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Mary's Church - Handbridge - 26.8 km / 16.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Grosvenor Park - 26.8 km / 16.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Dee Bridge - 26.9 km / 16.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Roman Amphitheatre - 26.9 km / 16.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Rookery Hall Hotel is Manchester (MAN) - 33.4 km / 20.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Rookery Hall Hotel is Manchester (MAN-Manchester Intl.) - 33.4 km / 20.7 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Porters</Code><Text>Porters</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>