<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10856247</Id><Name>Barnsdale Lodge Hotel A Recommended Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52669</Id><Name>Oakham</Name><CityId>52669</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>The Avenue</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Oakham</City><State /><Zip>LE15 8AH</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>01572 724678</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Barnsdale Lodge Hotel and Restaurant in Oakham (Rutland Water), you'll be close to Oakham Castle. This historic hotel is within the region of Stamford Meadows and Burghley House.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of 45 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature designer toiletries and complimentary toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Relax and unwind with massages and facials. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, where you can enjoy drinks at a bar, take in a garden view, and even dine alfresco (weather permitting). You can also stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). A complimentary English breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff. Event facilities at this hotel consist of conference space and meeting rooms. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, where you can enjoy drinks at a bar, take in a garden view, and even dine alfresco (weather permitting). You can also stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). A complimentary English breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Relax and unwind with massages and facials. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of 45 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature designer toiletries and complimentary toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Barnsdale Lodge Hotel and Restaurant in Oakham (Rutland Water), you'll be close to Oakham Castle. This historic hotel is within the region of Stamford Meadows and Burghley House. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Oakham Castle - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stamford Meadows - 12.3 km / 7.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Burghley House - 14.3 km / 8.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Woolsthorpe Manor - 15.1 km / 9.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Barnsdale Lodge Hotel and Restaurant is East Midlands (EMA) - 48.2 km / 30 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>