<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10869175</Id><Name>Crathorne Hall Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52838</Id><Name>Yarm</Name><CityId>52838</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Crathorne Village</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Yarm</City><State /><Zip>TS15 0AR</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 (845) 44-845-727440</Tel><Fax>+44 (1642) 700814</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Crathorne Hall Hotel in Yarm (Crathorne), you'll be within the vicinity of Butterfly World and Preston Park. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of St Mary's Cathedral and Middlesbrough Municipal Golf Centre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 37 guestrooms featuring DVD players. Complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature designer toiletries and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include safes and desks, and you can also request refrigerators.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. This hotel also features concierge services, babysitting/childcare, and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, where you can enjoy drinks at a bar, take in a garden view, and even dine alfresco (weather permitting). You can also stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and dry cleaning/laundry services. This hotel has 3 meeting rooms available for events. Free valet parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, where you can enjoy drinks at a bar, take in a garden view, and even dine alfresco (weather permitting). You can also stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. This hotel also features concierge services, babysitting/childcare, and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 37 guestrooms featuring DVD players. Complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature designer toiletries and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include safes and desks, and you can also request refrigerators.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Crathorne Hall Hotel in Yarm (Crathorne), you'll be within the vicinity of Butterfly World and Preston Park. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of St Mary's Cathedral and Middlesbrough Municipal Golf Centre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Butterfly World - 7.3 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Preston Park - 7.4 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Mary's Cathedral - 8.8 km / 5.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Middlesbrough Municipal Golf Centre - 9.2 km / 5.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ropner Park - 9.5 km / 5.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Middlesbrough Golf Club - 9.5 km / 5.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mount Grace Priory - 10.1 km / 6.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stewart Park - 10.3 km / 6.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Middlesbrough Theatre - 10.5 km / 6.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wild Animal Adventures - 11.3 km / 7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dorman Museum - 11.5 km / 7.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albert Park - 11.7 km / 7.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ormesby Hall - 12 km / 7.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Middlesbrough Institute of Modern Art - 12.7 km / 7.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Riverside Stadium - 13.5 km / 8.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Crathorne Hall Hotel is Durham (MME-Tees Valley) - 8.8 km / 5.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Crathorne Hall Hotel is Durham (MME-Tees Valley) - 8.7 km / 5.4 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ValetParking</Code><Text>Valet parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WakeUpService</Code><Text>Wake up service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FamilyRooms</Code><Text>Family rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CoffeeShop</Code><Text>Coffee shop</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Freenewspaper</Code><Text>Free Newspaper</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TrouserPress</Code><Text>Trouser press</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TV</Code><Text>TeleVision</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>24HourFrontDesk</Code><Text>24 Hour Front Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>