<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10868974</Id><Name>Hotel Mon Ami</Name><Region><Id>52818</Id><Name>Weymouth</Name><CityId>52818</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>143/145 The Esplanade</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Weymouth</City><State /><Zip>DT4 7NN</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>00442072244002</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Mon Ami in Weymouth, you'll be near the beach and minutes from Weymouth Marina and Weymouth Beach. This hotel is within close proximity of Radipole Lake Nature Reserve and Sea Life Tower.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 42 guestrooms. Bathrooms with showers are provided. Conveniences include phones and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and a fireplace in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hotel Mon Ami. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a library and an elevator (lift). Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hotel Mon Ami. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and a fireplace in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 42 guestrooms. Bathrooms with showers are provided. Conveniences include phones and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Mon Ami in Weymouth, you'll be near the beach and minutes from Weymouth Marina and Weymouth Beach. This hotel is within close proximity of Radipole Lake Nature Reserve and Sea Life Tower. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Weymouth Marina - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Weymouth Beach - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Radipole Lake Nature Reserve - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sea Life Tower - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Weymouth Pavilion - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Weymouth Ferry Terminal - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sandworld - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sea Life Park - 1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Deep Sea Adventure - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Nothe Fort - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Leighton Art Gallery - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pirate Adventure Mini Golf - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tudor House - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Weymouth D-Day Museum - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Discovery Weymouth - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Mon Ami is Bournemouth (BOH-Bournemouth Intl.) - 47.1 km / 29.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>