<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10867985</Id><Name>Grosvenor Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52783</Id><Name>Torquay</Name><CityId>52783</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Belgrave Road,</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Torquay</City><State /><Zip>TQ2 5HG</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>0800 005 2244</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Torquay (English Riviera), The Grosvenor Hotel is minutes from Abbey Sands and Riviera International Conference Centre. This hotel is within close proximity of Princess Theatre and Torre Abbey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 47 individually decorated guestrooms. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including a health club, an outdoor pool, and an indoor pool. This Victorian hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, an arcade/game room, and a hair salon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar. A complimentary English breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk. Event facilities at this hotel consist of conference space and meeting rooms. Guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle for a surcharge, and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar. A complimentary English breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including a health club, an outdoor pool, and an indoor pool. This Victorian hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, an arcade/game room, and a hair salon. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 47 individually decorated guestrooms. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Torquay (English Riviera), The Grosvenor Hotel is minutes from Abbey Sands and Riviera International Conference Centre. This hotel is within close proximity of Princess Theatre and Torre Abbey. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Abbey Sands - 0.1 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;Riviera International Conference Centre - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Princess Theatre - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Torre Abbey - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Living Coasts - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Torquay Museum - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Meadfoot Beach - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bygones Victorian Museum - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kents Cavern Prehistoric Caves - 2.3 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Babbacombe Model Village and Gardens - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Babbacombe Beach - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Paignton Beach - 3.3 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Goodrington Sands Beach - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Paignton Zoo - 5.2 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Golden Hind - 7.6 km / 4.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Grosvenor Hotel is Exeter (EXT-Exeter Intl.) - 31 km / 19.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Grosvenor Hotel is Exeter (EXT-Exeter Intl.) - 31 km / 19.3 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>