<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10860472</Id><Name>Silks Hotels - The White Horse</Name><Region><Id>52741</Id><Name>Southampton</Name><CityId>52741</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Market Place</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Southampton</City><State /><Zip>SO51 8ZJ</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>44-075-2529-8006</Tel><Fax>44-017-9451-7485</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at The White Horse Inn in Norwich, you'll be convenient to Banham Zoo. This inn is within the region of Bressingham Steam and Gardens and St. Martin Cathedral.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 6 individually decorated guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers and irons/ironing boards, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the inn's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services and luggage storage. This inn has 2 meeting rooms available for events. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 5 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the inn's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 6 individually decorated guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers and irons/ironing boards, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (surcharge).</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at The White Horse Inn in Norwich, you'll be convenient to Banham Zoo. This inn is within the region of Bressingham Steam and Gardens and St. Martin Cathedral. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Banham Zoo - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bressingham Steam and Gardens - 6.8 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Martin Cathedral - 15.3 km / 9.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wayland Wood - 17.7 km / 11 mi &lt;br /&gt;Watton Clock Tower - 19.1 km / 11.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Go Ape Thetford - 22.6 km / 14.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sainsbury Centre for the Visual Arts - 26.2 km / 16.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of East Anglia - 26.6 km / 16.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dereham Windmill - 27.1 km / 16.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Scarning Parish - 27.4 km / 17 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Forum - 29.3 km / 18.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Peter Mancroft - 29.3 km / 18.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Norwich City Hall - 29.4 km / 18.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Market Place - 29.4 km / 18.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Strangers Hall Garden - 29.5 km / 18.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The White Horse Inn is Norwich (NWI-Norwich Intl.) - 32.2 km / 20 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>