<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10872576</Id><Name>Twelve Picardy Place</Name><Region><Id>52867</Id><Name>Edinburgh City</Name><CityId>52507</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>12 Picardy Place</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Edinburgh</City><State /><Zip>EH1 3JT</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44 (0)131 556 1289</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Twelve Picardy Place, you'll be centrally located in Edinburgh, steps from Edinburgh Playhouse Theatre and Omni Centre Edinburgh. This 4-star hotel is close to St. Giles' Cathedral and Princes Street Gardens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 10 guestrooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. This hotel also features concierge services, wedding services, and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at one of the hotel's 2 restaurants. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include limo/town car service, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at one of the hotel's 2 restaurants. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. This hotel also features concierge services, wedding services, and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 10 guestrooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Twelve Picardy Place, you'll be centrally located in Edinburgh, steps from Edinburgh Playhouse Theatre and Omni Centre Edinburgh. This 4-star hotel is close to St. Giles' Cathedral and Princes Street Gardens. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Edinburgh Playhouse Theatre - 0 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;Omni Centre Edinburgh - 0 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;Nelson Monument - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Calton Hill - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Waterloo Place - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Andrew Square - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Princes Mall - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;City Art Centre - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fruitmarket Gallery - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Scott Monument - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Edinburgh Dungeon - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;John Knox House - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of Childhood - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brass Rubbing Centre - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;People's Story Museum - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Twelve Picardy Place is Edinburgh (EDI) - 11.1 km / 6.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>