<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10873265</Id><Name>Hot-el-apartments Glasgow Central</Name><Region><Id>52875</Id><Name>Glasgow City</Name><CityId>52536</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>15/3 Oswald Street,</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Glasgow</City><State /><Zip>G1 4PD</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44(141)2432094</Tel><Fax>+44(141)2222635</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Glasgow (City Centre Glasgow), Hot-el-apartments Glasgow Central is minutes from Arches Theatre and St. Enoch Centre. This apartment is within close proximity of Argyll Arcade and Lighthouse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 27 guestrooms, featuring kitchens with refrigerators and microwaves. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and DVD players are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include safes and separate sitting areas, and you can also request cribs/infant beds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include limo/town car service, dry cleaning/laundry services, and multilingual staff. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 27 guestrooms, featuring kitchens with refrigerators and microwaves. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and DVD players are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include safes and separate sitting areas, and you can also request cribs/infant beds.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Glasgow (City Centre Glasgow), Hot-el-apartments Glasgow Central is minutes from Arches Theatre and St. Enoch Centre. This apartment is within close proximity of Argyll Arcade and Lighthouse. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Arches Theatre - 0.1 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Enoch Centre - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Argyll Arcade - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lighthouse - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Princes Square - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Buchanan Street - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gallery of Modern Art - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Vincent Street Church - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;George Square - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Merchants' House - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Citizens Theatre - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Italian Centre - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;City Chambers - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hutchesons' Hall - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Buchanan Galleries - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hot-el-apartments Glasgow Central is Glasgow (GLA-Glasgow Intl.) - 10.9 km / 6.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Hot-el-apartments Glasgow Central is Glasgow (GLA-Glasgow Intl.) - 10.9 km / 6.8 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>