<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10871927</Id><Name>City Wharf Apartments</Name><Region><Id>52841</Id><Name>Aberdeen City</Name><CityId>52342</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>47 Regent Quay</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Aberdeen</City><State /><Zip>AB11 5BE</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>44-012-245-892-82</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at City Wharf Apartments places you in the heart of Aberdeen, walking distance from Aberdeen Maritime Museum and Provost Ross's House. This apartment is within close proximity of St. Andrew's Episcopal Cathedral and Aberdeen Arts Centre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 8 guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and microwaves. Your bed comes with down comforters and Egyptian cotton sheets. 32-inch flat-screen televisions with digital programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms have deep soaking bathtubs and complimentary toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with onsite body treatments or make use of the other amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and complimentary use of a nearby fitness facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, express check-in, and express check-out.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with onsite body treatments or make use of the other amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and complimentary use of a nearby fitness facility. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 8 guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and microwaves. Your bed comes with down comforters and Egyptian cotton sheets. 32-inch flat-screen televisions with digital programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms have deep soaking bathtubs and complimentary toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at City Wharf Apartments places you in the heart of Aberdeen, walking distance from Aberdeen Maritime Museum and Provost Ross's House. This apartment is within close proximity of St. Andrew's Episcopal Cathedral and Aberdeen Arts Centre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Aberdeen Maritime Museum - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Provost Ross's House - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Andrew's Episcopal Cathedral - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aberdeen Arts Centre - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Union Square Shopping Centre - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Provost Skene's House - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marischal Museum - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Nicholas Centre - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aberdeen Art Gallery - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Carby Art Gallery - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Academy - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Codonas Amusement Park - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mall Trinity - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bon-Accord Centre - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Belmont Picturehouse - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for City Wharf Apartments is Aberdeen (ABZ) - 9.1 km / 5.6 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for City Wharf Apartments is Aberdeen (ABZ) - 9.1 km / 5.6 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>