<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10872236</Id><Name>Richmond Place Apartments</Name><Region><Id>52867</Id><Name>Edinburgh City</Name><CityId>52507</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>5-9 Richmond Place</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Edinburgh</City><State /><Zip>EH8 9VE</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>+44(0)131 651 2119</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Richmond Place Apartments, you'll be centrally located in Edinburgh, steps from Surgeon's Hall and minutes from Festival Theatre. This apartment is close to Greyfriars Kirk and St. Giles' Cathedral.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 32 guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, and LCD televisions with digital programming provide entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and microwaves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Full breakfasts are available for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a 24-hour front desk, and laundry facilities.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10:30 AM &lt;br/&gt; Full breakfasts are available for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 32 guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, and LCD televisions with digital programming provide entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and microwaves.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Richmond Place Apartments, you'll be centrally located in Edinburgh, steps from Surgeon's Hall and minutes from Festival Theatre. This apartment is close to Greyfriars Kirk and St. Giles' Cathedral. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Surgeon's Hall - 0.1 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;Festival Theatre - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Potterrow Student Centre - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Talbot Rice Gallery - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;George Square - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Edinburgh - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Museum of Scotland - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brass Rubbing Centre - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Greyfriar's Bobby - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of Childhood - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;John Knox House - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Greyfriars Kirk - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queen's Hall - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Parliament House - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;City Chambers - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Richmond Place Apartments is Edinburgh (EDI) - 11.3 km / 7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>