<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>109081</Id><Name>Costa Portals</Name><Region><Id>99732</Id><Name>Portals Nous</Name><CityId>18419</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>VAQUER, 16</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>PORTALS NOUS</City><State /><Zip>07181</Zip><Country>SPAIN</Country><Tel>971677311</Tel><Fax>971676533</Fax><Email>INFO@HOTELCOSTAPORTALS.COM</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>39.5357764</Latitude><Longitude>2.5762415</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/PNOU-VIVhotel_Exterior_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>270</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/PNOU-VIVhotel_Exterior_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/PNOU-VIVhotel_Guest_Room_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>268</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/PNOU-VIVhotel_Guest_Room_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/PNOU-VIVhotel_Swimming_Pool_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>268</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/PNOU-VIVhotel_Swimming_Pool_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>SwimmingPool</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Costa Portals - Adults Only in Calvia (Portals Nous), you'll be close to Puerto Portals Marina and Bellver Castle.  This hotel is within close proximity of Marineland Mallorca and Real Golf Bendinat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 94 air-conditioned guestrooms. Rooms have private balconies. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include safes, and rollaway/extra beds can be requested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including wireless Internet access (surcharge) and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;All-inclusive rates are available at this hotel. Meals and beverages at onsite dining establishments are included in all-inclusive rates. Charges may be applied for dining at some restaurants, special dinners and dishes, some beverages, and other amenities. &lt;p&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hotel Costa Portals - Adults Only. Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff. A shuttle from the hotel to the airport is provided for a surcharge (available on request).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is Noon &lt;br/&gt; All-inclusive rates are available at this hotel. Meals and beverages at onsite dining establishments are included in all-inclusive rates. Charges may be applied for dining at some restaurants, special dinners and dishes, some beverages, and other amenities. &lt;p&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hotel Costa Portals - Adults Only. Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including wireless Internet access (surcharge) and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 94 air-conditioned guestrooms. Rooms have private balconies. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include safes, and rollaway/extra beds can be requested.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Costa Portals - Adults Only in Calvia (Portals Nous), you'll be close to Puerto Portals Marina and Bellver Castle.  This hotel is within close proximity of Marineland Mallorca and Real Golf Bendinat. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Puerto Portals Marina - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marineland Mallorca - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Real Golf Bendinat - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cala Mayor Beach - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marivent Palace - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Golf Fantasia - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palma Nova Beach - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Carlos Castle - 4.1 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mallorca Casino - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Porto Pi Centro Comercial - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Port of Palma de Mallorca - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bellver Castle - 4.8 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pirates Adventure Show - 5.5 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gomila Square - 5.9 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pueblo Espanol - 6 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Costa Portals - Adults Only is Palma de Mallorca (PMI) - 13.4 km / 8.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Hotel Costa Portals is Palma de Mallorca (PMI) - 13.4 km / 8.3 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MoneyExchange</Code><Text>Money exchange</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BicycleRental</Code><Text>Bicycle Rental</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Balcony</Code><Text>Balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Cafe(s)</Code><Text>Cafe(s)</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>