<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10910733</Id><Name>Glencoe House</Name><Region><Id>52871</Id><Name>Fort William</Name><CityId>52569</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Glencoe</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Glencoe</City><State /><Zip>PH49 4HT</Zip><Country>Scotland</Country><Tel>1855 811 179</Tel><Fax>0208 545 2604</Fax><Email>reservations@glencoe-house.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Glencoe House in Ballachulish (Glencoe), you'll be close to Glen Coe Visitor Centre. This 5-star guesthouse is within the vicinity of The Ice Factor and Atlas Brewery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Treat yourself to a stay in one of the 7 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring fireplaces and plasma televisions. Your bed comes with down comforters and Egyptian cotton sheets. Satellite programming and iPod docking stations are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature deep soaking bathtubs and rainfall showerheads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. Additional features at this Victorian guesthouse include concierge services, wedding services, and a fireplace in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of the guesthouse's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, a computer station, and express check-in. For a surcharge, guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle (available on request) and a train station pick-up service.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of the guesthouse's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. Additional features at this Victorian guesthouse include concierge services, wedding services, and a fireplace in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Treat yourself to a stay in one of the 7 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring fireplaces and plasma televisions. Your bed comes with down comforters and Egyptian cotton sheets. Satellite programming and iPod docking stations are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature deep soaking bathtubs and rainfall showerheads.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Glencoe House in Ballachulish (Glencoe), you'll be close to Glen Coe Visitor Centre. This 5-star guesthouse is within the vicinity of The Ice Factor and Atlas Brewery. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Glen Coe Visitor Centre - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Ice Factor - 8.7 km / 5.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Atlas Brewery - 9.1 km / 5.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Buchaille Etive Mor - 12.7 km / 7.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ben Nevis - 13.3 km / 8.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;West Highland Museum - 14.6 km / 9.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aonach Mor Ski Resort - 16 km / 10 mi &lt;br /&gt;Glen Coe Mountain Resort - 16.3 km / 10.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ben Nevis Distillery - 16.6 km / 10.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Neptune's Staircase - 17.7 km / 11 mi &lt;br /&gt;Leanachan Forest - 19.4 km / 12.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Grey Corries - 19.8 km / 12.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Commando Memorial - 25.3 km / 15.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Glenfinnan Monument - 29.2 km / 18.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Glenfinnan Museum - 29.4 km / 18.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Glencoe House is Glasgow (GLA-Glasgow Intl.) - 100.3 km / 62.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>