<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>10910630</Id><Name>Cotswold Water Park Four Pillars Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52458</Id><Name>Cirencester</Name><CityId>52458</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Lake 6, Spine Road East</Address1><Address2>South Cerney</Address2><Address3 /><City>Cirencester</City><State /><Zip>GL7 5FP</Zip><Country>England</Country><Tel>0044 0 1285 864000</Tel><Fax>004401285864001</Fax><Email>waterpark@four-pillars.co.uk</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Cotswold Water Park Four Pillars Hotel in Cirencester (South Cerney), you'll be close to Cotswold Country Park and Beach. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of Cirencester Roman Amphitheatre and Cirencester Church.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of 328 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have shower/tub combinations and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks, and you can also request cribs/infant beds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Relax at the full-service spa, where you can enjoy body treatments and facials. If you're looking for recreational opportunities, you'll find a health club, an indoor pool, and a spa tub. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Cotswold Water Park Four Pillars Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, express check-in, and express check-out. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Cotswold Water Park Four Pillars Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Relax at the full-service spa, where you can enjoy body treatments and facials. If you're looking for recreational opportunities, you'll find a health club, an indoor pool, and a spa tub. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of 328 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have shower/tub combinations and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks, and you can also request cribs/infant beds.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Cotswold Water Park Four Pillars Hotel in Cirencester (South Cerney), you'll be close to Cotswold Country Park and Beach. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of Cirencester Roman Amphitheatre and Cirencester Church. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Cotswold Country Park and Beach - 4.4 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cirencester Roman Amphitheatre - 6.6 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cirencester Church - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Corinium Museum - 7.1 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Swindon and Cricklade Railway - 8.3 km / 5.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cirencester Golf Club - 9.4 km / 5.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cirencester Park Polo Club - 9.6 km / 6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lydiard Park - 12.7 km / 7.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stanton Country Park - 13.1 km / 8.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Swindon Designer Outlet - 14 km / 8.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of the Great Western Railway - 14.1 km / 8.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chedworth Roman Villa - 16.6 km / 10.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Malmesbury Abbey - 16.6 km / 10.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Coate Water Country Park - 17.8 km / 11 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of St. Peter and St. Paul - 18.2 km / 11.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Cotswold Water Park Four Pillars Hotel is Bristol (BRS-Bristol Intl.) - 63.9 km / 39.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>