<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>109337</Id><Name>Isabel</Name><Region><Id>21269</Id><Name>Cala Millor</Name><CityId>18419</CityId></Region><Type>Apartments</Type><Address><Address1>Ronda D'es Prats S/N</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>CALA BONA</City><State /><Zip>07559</Zip><Country>SPAIN</Country><Tel>971585163</Tel><Fax>971585163</Fax><Email>isabel@olahotels.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>39.6218481</Latitude><Longitude>3.3901957</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/CLBO-OLAhotel_Exterior_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/CLBO-OLAhotel_Exterior_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/CLBO-OLAhotel_Restaurant_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/CLBO-OLAhotel_Restaurant_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/CLBO-OLAhotel_Recreational_Facilities_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/CLBO-OLAhotel_Recreational_Facilities_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Son Servera (Cala Millor), Ola Aparthotel Isabel - All Inclusive is close to Cala Millor Beach and Punta de N'Amer Watch Tower.  This all-inclusive aparthotel is within the vicinity of Torre de Canyamel and Cuevas de Artà.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 113 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchenettes. Rooms have private balconies or patios. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and separate sitting areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreational amenities such as an outdoor pool and a seasonal outdoor pool. Additional features include wireless Internet access (surcharge), concierge services, and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This aparthotel is all inclusive. Rates include meals and beverages at onsite dining establishments. Charges may be applied for dining at some restaurants, special dinners and dishes, some beverages, and other amenities. &lt;p&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Ola Aparthotel Isabel - All Inclusive. While enjoying a refreshing dip in the aparthotel pool, you can order your favorite drink at the poolside bar. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour front desk, multilingual staff, and luggage storage.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed    Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; This aparthotel is all inclusive. Rates include meals and beverages at onsite dining establishments. Charges may be applied for dining at some restaurants, special dinners and dishes, some beverages, and other amenities. &lt;p&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Ola Aparthotel Isabel - All Inclusive. While enjoying a refreshing dip in the aparthotel pool, you can order your favorite drink at the poolside bar. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreational amenities such as an outdoor pool and a seasonal outdoor pool. Additional features include wireless Internet access (surcharge), concierge services, and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 113 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchenettes. Rooms have private balconies or patios. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and separate sitting areas.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Son Servera (Cala Millor), Ola Aparthotel Isabel - All Inclusive is close to Cala Millor Beach and Punta de N'Amer Watch Tower.  This all-inclusive aparthotel is within the vicinity of Torre de Canyamel and Cuevas de Artà. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Cala Millor Beach - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Punta de N'Amer Watch Tower - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Torre de Canyamel - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cuevas de Artà - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Canyamel Golf - 6.4 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Caves of Drach - 10.9 km / 6.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cala Ratjada Port - 11.7 km / 7.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cala Gat Beach - 12.1 km / 7.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cala Agulla Beach - 12.3 km / 7.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cala Varques - 15.9 km / 9.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cala Antena Beach - 19.8 km / 12.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cala Domingo Beach - 20.7 km / 12.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vall d'Or Golf - 26 km / 16.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albufera Natural Park - 31 km / 19.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Alcudia Port - 32.9 km / 20.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Ola Aparthotel Isabel - All Inclusive is Palma de Mallorca (PMI) - 57.2 km / 35.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Ola Aparthotel Isabel is Palma de Mallorca (PMI) - 57.1 km / 35.5 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>IndoorPool</Code><Text>Indoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Kitchen</Code><Text>Kitchen</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MoneyExchange</Code><Text>Money exchange</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniClub</Code><Text>Mini Club</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Playground</Code><Text>Playground</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreshWaterPool</Code><Text>Fresh Water Pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ChildrenPool</Code><Text>Children's pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SunLounge</Code><Text>SunLounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parasol</Code><Text>Parasol</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SunBathingTerrace</Code><Text>Sun Bathing Terrace</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniFridge</Code><Text>MiniFridge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lounge</Code><Text>Lounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Balcony</Code><Text>Balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomTerraceBalcony</Code><Text>Terrace or balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>