<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>109566</Id><Name>Astures</Name><Region><Id>18433</Id><Name>Oviedo</Name><CityId>18433</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>CAMPO DE LOS PATOS 7</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>OVIEDO</City><State /><Zip>33010</Zip><Country>SPAIN</Country><Tel>985200908</Tel><Fax>985226746</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>43.3634723</Latitude><Longitude>-5.8390306</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CA/N6/22/80/0/CAN622800_0.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>36684</Bytes><Caption>Exterior view</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CA/N6/22/80/0/CAN622800_0thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>3428</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CA/N6/22/80/0/CAN622800_1.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>17738</Bytes><Caption>Bedroom</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CA/N6/22/80/0/CAN622800_1thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2001</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CA/N6/22/80/0/CAN622800_2.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>21428</Bytes><Caption>Conference room</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CA/N6/22/80/0/CAN622800_2thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2635</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Oviedo, Hotel Astures is minutes from Camara Santa de Oviedo and Oviedo Cathedral.  This hotel is within close proximity of Museum of Fine Arts and San Julian de los Prados.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 65 guestrooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have deep soaking bathtubs and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and irons/ironing boards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities including an indoor pool and a fitness center. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed    Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities including an indoor pool and a fitness center. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 65 guestrooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have deep soaking bathtubs and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and irons/ironing boards.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Oviedo, Hotel Astures is minutes from Camara Santa de Oviedo and Oviedo Cathedral.  This hotel is within close proximity of Museum of Fine Arts and San Julian de los Prados. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Camara Santa de Oviedo - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Oviedo Cathedral - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of Fine Arts - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Julian de los Prados - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Oviedo - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hospital Universitario Central de Asturias - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Central Asturias Hospital - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Carlos Tartiere Stadium - 2.5 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Santa Maria del Naranco - 2.8 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Miguel de Lillo - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Institute of Molecular and Oncological Medicine of Asturias - 3.7 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Trasona Reservoir Park - 19.4 km / 12.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Astures is Oviedo (OVD-Asturias) - 26.8 km / 16.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Hairdresser</Code><Text>Hairdresser</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MobilePhoneNetwork</Code><Text>Mobile Phone Network</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MedicalService</Code><Text>Medical Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BicycleStorage</Code><Text>Bicycle Storage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Garage</Code><Text>Garage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreshWaterPool</Code><Text>Fresh Water Pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HeatedPool</Code><Text>Heated Pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lounge</Code><Text>Lounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Fridge</Code><Text>Fridge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Cafe(s)</Code><Text>Cafe(s)</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>