<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>109589</Id><Name>Ciudad de Oviedo</Name><Region><Id>18433</Id><Name>Oviedo</Name><CityId>18433</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>GASCONA 21</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>OVIEDO</City><State /><Zip>33001</Zip><Country>SPAIN</Country><Tel>98.5222224</Tel><Fax>98.5221599</Fax><Email>reservas@hotelciudaddeoviedo.es</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>43.3648866</Latitude><Longitude>-5.845659</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1214360-photo-not-available-small.jpg</Url><Width>70</Width><Height>70</Height><Bytes>727</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1214360-photo-not-available-small.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>727</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Hotel Sercotel Ciudad de Oviedo is in the heart of Oviedo, walking distance from Oviedo Cathedral and University of Oviedo.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Camara Santa de Oviedo and Museum of Fine Arts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 57 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (complimentary).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast and dinner. Dining is also available at a coffee shop/café, and room service (during limited hours) is provided. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and a 24-hour front desk. Planning an event in Oviedo? This hotel features 968 square feet (90 square meters) of event facilities. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at noon  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast and dinner. Dining is also available at a coffee shop/café, and room service (during limited hours) is provided. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 57 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (complimentary).</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Hotel Sercotel Ciudad de Oviedo is in the heart of Oviedo, walking distance from Oviedo Cathedral and University of Oviedo.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Camara Santa de Oviedo and Museum of Fine Arts. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Oviedo Cathedral - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Oviedo - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Camara Santa de Oviedo - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of Fine Arts - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Julian de los Prados - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Central Asturias Hospital - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hospital Universitario Central de Asturias - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Carlos Tartiere Stadium - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Santa Maria del Naranco - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Miguel de Lillo - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Institute of Molecular and Oncological Medicine of Asturias - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Trasona Reservoir Park - 19.2 km / 11.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Sercotel Ciudad de Oviedo is Oviedo (OVD-Asturias) - 26.4 km / 16.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Sercotel Ciudad de Oviedo is Oviedo (OVD-Asturias) - 26.4 km / 16.4 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CloakRoom</Code><Text>Cloak Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVRoom</Code><Text>TV Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DiningRoom</Code><Text>Dining Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WLANAccessPoint</Code><Text>WLAN Access Point</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MedicalService</Code><Text>Medical Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Carpeted</Code><Text>Carpeted</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Launderette</Code><Text>Launderette</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Cafe(s)</Code><Text>Cafe(s)</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>