<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11174861</Id><Name>Shardana</Name><Region><Id>20924</Id><Name>Costa Esmeralda</Name><CityId>17078</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Località Baia Santa Reparata</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip>07028</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Club Esse Shardana in Santa Teresa di Gallura, you'll be near the beach and convenient to Longonsardo Tower and Lu Brandali.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Cala Spinosa Beach and Moon Valley.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 75 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Digital television is provided for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and day beds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreational amenities such as an outdoor pool and a seasonal outdoor pool. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Club Esse Shardana. Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour front desk, luggage storage, and laundry facilities. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 4 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Club Esse Shardana. Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreational amenities such as an outdoor pool and a seasonal outdoor pool. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 75 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Digital television is provided for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and day beds.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Club Esse Shardana in Santa Teresa di Gallura, you'll be near the beach and convenient to Longonsardo Tower and Lu Brandali.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Cala Spinosa Beach and Moon Valley. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Longonsardo Tower - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lu Brandali - 1.4 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cala Spinosa Beach - 3.5 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Moon Valley - 3.8 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Monti Russu Beach - 11.4 km / 7.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Porto Pollo Beach - 11.7 km / 7.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Monti Russu - 12 km / 7.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Talmone Beach - 13 km / 8.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Talmone Gun Battery - 13 km / 8.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lu Litarroni Beach - 13.4 km / 8.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Plage de Petit Sperone - 15 km / 9.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sperone Golf Club - 15.1 km / 9.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Monte Altura Fortress - 15.6 km / 9.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vignola Mare Beach - 16.3 km / 10.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;La Sciumara Beach - 16.4 km / 10.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Club Esse Shardana is Olbia (OLB-Costa Smeralda) - 46.2 km / 28.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>CarRentDesk</Code><Text>Car rental desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Entertainment</Code><Text>Entertainment</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MultilingualStaff</Code><Text>Multilingual Staff</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>