<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11174729</Id><Name>Arathena Rocks</Name><Region><Id>20911</Id><Name>Taormina</Name><CityId>17070</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Via Calcide Eubea, 55</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip>98035</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel>+39 0942 52088</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Arathena Rocks Hotel in Giardini Naxos, you'll be on the waterfront and minutes from Archaeological Museum and close to Greek Theatre. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Recanati Beach and San Marco Beach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 51 air-conditioned guestrooms. Rooms have private balconies. Dial-up Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and bidets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities including an outdoor pool and bicycles to rent. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, where you can take in a pool view, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary buffet breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed       &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, where you can take in a pool view, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary buffet breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities including an outdoor pool and bicycles to rent. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 51 air-conditioned guestrooms. Rooms have private balconies. Dial-up Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and bidets.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Arathena Rocks Hotel in Giardini Naxos, you'll be on the waterfront and minutes from Archaeological Museum and close to Greek Theatre. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Recanati Beach and San Marco Beach. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Archaeological Museum - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Recanati Beach - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Marco Beach - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fondazione Mazzullo - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of San Domenico - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of Sant'Antonio Abate - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palazzo dei Duchi di Santo Stefano - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cathedral of Taormina - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Baroque Fountain - 3.5 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza del Duomo - 3.5 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Torre dell'Orogio - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Badia Vecchia - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Taormina Archaeological Museum - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of San Giuseppe - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza IX April - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Arathena Rocks Hotel is Reggio di Calabria (REG-Strait of Messina) - 43.7 km / 27.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarRentDesk</Code><Text>Car rental desk</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>