<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11174864</Id><Name>Cristal Palace</Name><Region><Id>20934</Id><Name>Madonna Di Campiglio</Name><CityId>17084</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Via Cima Tosa, 104/a</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip>38086</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Madonna di Campiglio, Cristal Palace Hotel is minutes from Pradalago Gondola and close to 5 Laghi Express Gondola. This 4.5-star hotel is within close proximity of Groste 1 Express Gondola and Spinale Gondola.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 61 guestrooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take time to pamper yourself with a visit to the full-service spa. A spa tub and a sauna offer a relaxing way to wind down after a day on the slopes. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, supervised childcare/activities, and ski storage. You'll be on the slopes in no time with the complimentary ski shuttle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Cristal Palace Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary buffet breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff. Planning an event in Madonna di Campiglio? This hotel has facilities measuring 1399 square feet (130 square meters), including a meeting room. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Cristal Palace Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary buffet breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take time to pamper yourself with a visit to the full-service spa. A spa tub and a sauna offer a relaxing way to wind down after a day on the slopes. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, supervised childcare/activities, and ski storage. You'll be on the slopes in no time with the complimentary ski shuttle. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 61 guestrooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Madonna di Campiglio, Cristal Palace Hotel is minutes from Pradalago Gondola and close to 5 Laghi Express Gondola. This 4.5-star hotel is within close proximity of Groste 1 Express Gondola and Spinale Gondola. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Pradalago Gondola - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;5 Laghi Express Gondola - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Groste 1 Express Gondola - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Spinale Gondola - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Golf Club Campo Carlo Magno - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lake Ritorto - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Groste 2 Express Gondola - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Folgarida Ski Area - 6.4 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marilleva Ski Area - 7.3 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Copai-Panciana Gondola - 7.5 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Belvedere Gondola - 7.7 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Caprioli Lake - 7.8 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albare Gondola - 7.8 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Folgarida Gondola - 8 km / 5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Folgarida Ski Area - 8.1 km / 5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Cristal Palace Hotel is Verona (VRN-Valerio Catullo) - 92.8 km / 57.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Sauna</Code><Text>Sauna</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVRoom</Code><Text>TV Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniClub</Code><Text>Mini Club</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Playground</Code><Text>Playground</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>