<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>112343</Id><Name>Alfonso Hotel</Name><Region><Id>18479</Id><Name>Zaragoza</Name><CityId>18479</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Calle Coso 15-17-19,</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Zaragoza</City><State /><Zip>50003</Zip><Country>Spain</Country><Tel>+34 876 54 11 18</Tel><Fax>+34 876 54 11 19</Fax><Email>hotelalfonso@palafoxhoteles.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>117</CountRooms><CountFloors>8</CountFloors><Latitude>41.6533735</Latitude><Longitude>-0.8827736</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAF497200_0.jpg</Url><Width>361</Width><Height>480</Height><Bytes>46681</Bytes><Caption>Unknown</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAF497200_0.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>52</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>11436</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAF497200_1.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>312</Height><Bytes>28101</Bytes><Caption>Unknown</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAF497200_1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>107</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>21805</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Alfonso in Zaragoza, you'll be minutes from Pablo Gargallo Museum and Plaza de Espana.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Museo Ibercaja Camon Aznar and Roman Theatre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 120 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Conveniences include safes and desks, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (complimentary).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as a seasonal outdoor pool or take in the view from a rooftop terrace. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a bite to eat at a coffee shop/café, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff. Planning an event in Zaragoza? This hotel has 11 square feet (0 square meters) of space consisting of conference space and a meeting room. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2:00 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a bite to eat at a coffee shop/café, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as a seasonal outdoor pool or take in the view from a rooftop terrace. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 120 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Conveniences include safes and desks, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (complimentary).</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Alfonso in Zaragoza, you'll be minutes from Pablo Gargallo Museum and Plaza de Espana.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Museo Ibercaja Camon Aznar and Roman Theatre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Pablo Gargallo Museum - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Plaza de Espana - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museo Ibercaja Camon Aznar - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Roman Theatre - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Roman Wall - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Basilica de Nuestra Senora del Pilar - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Torreon de la Zuda - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Plaza del Pilar - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Goya Monument - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museo del Foro de Caesaraugusta - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Zaragoza Museum - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;La Seo Cathedral - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museo del Puerto Fluvial de Caesaraugusta - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pablo Serrano Museum - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Santa Maria Magdalena Church - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Alfonso is Zaragoza (ZAZ) - 10.5 km / 6.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>