<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>112733</Id><Name>PV Residence Cannes Villa Francia</Name><Region><Id>20435</Id><Name>Cannes</Name><CityId>16409</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>AVENUE WESTER WEMYSS 33</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>CANNES-LA BOCCA</City><State /><Zip>6150</Zip><Country>FRANCE</Country><Tel>0033158215821</Tel><Fax>0033158215049</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>43.553579</Latitude><Longitude>6.990159</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/27/94/7/27947-GEN-3.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>26132</Bytes><Caption>General</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/27/94/7/27947-GEN-3thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2639</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/27/94/7/27947-HAB-4.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>17206</Bytes><Caption>Room</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/27/94/7/27947-HAB-4thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2364</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/27/94/7/27947-PIS-1.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>19179</Bytes><Caption>Pool</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/27/94/7/27947-PIS-1thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2317</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>SwimmingPool</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/27/94/7/27947-PIS-7.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>19866</Bytes><Caption>Pool</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/27/94/7/27947-PIS-7thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2280</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>SwimmingPool</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Pierre &amp; Vacances Residence Cannes Villa Francia in Cannes (La Bocca), you'll be convenient to Midi Beach and Palace of Festivals and Congress Hall. This family-friendly residence is within close proximity of Cannes Hospital and Castre Museum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 360 guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and microwaves. Rooms have private furnished balconies or patios. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and flat-screen televisions are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Dip into one of the 2 outdoor swimming pools or enjoy other recreational amenities, which include an outdoor tennis court. Additional features include wireless Internet access (surcharge) and an arcade/game room. Getting to the surf and sand is a breeze with the complimentary beach shuttle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the residence's restaurant, where you can take in a pool view and dine alfresco (weather permitting). Snacks are also available at a coffee shop/café. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Breakfast is available for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include multilingual staff, luggage storage, and laundry facilities. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed      Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the residence's restaurant, where you can take in a pool view and dine alfresco (weather permitting). Snacks are also available at a coffee shop/café. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Breakfast is available for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Dip into one of the 2 outdoor swimming pools or enjoy other recreational amenities, which include an outdoor tennis court. Additional features include wireless Internet access (surcharge) and an arcade/game room. Getting to the surf and sand is a breeze with the complimentary beach shuttle. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 360 guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and microwaves. Rooms have private furnished balconies or patios. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and flat-screen televisions are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Pierre &amp; Vacances Residence Cannes Villa Francia in Cannes (La Bocca), you'll be convenient to Midi Beach and Palace of Festivals and Congress Hall. This family-friendly residence is within close proximity of Cannes Hospital and Castre Museum. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Midi Beach - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cannes Hospital - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Castre Museum - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cannes City Hall - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Forville Provencal Food Market - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;La Palestre - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cannes Harbour - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of the Sea - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palace of Festivals and Congress Hall - 2.2 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;La Croisette - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Croisette Beach - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dauphins Beach - 3.8 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sable d'Or Beach - 3.9 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Robinson Beach - 4.1 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gazagnaire Beach - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Pierre &amp; Vacances Residence Cannes Villa Francia is Nice (NCE-Cote d'Azur) - 22 km / 13.6 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Kitchen</Code><Text>Kitchen</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>NumberOfPool</Code><Text>Number Of Pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Fridge</Code><Text>Fridge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomTerraceBalcony</Code><Text>Terrace or balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>