<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>112883</Id><Name>Mercure Tours Nord</Name><Region><Id>20591</Id><Name>Tours</Name><CityId>16494</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>RUE DE L'AVIATION 11</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>TOURS</City><State /><Zip>37100</Zip><Country>FRANCE</Country><Tel>2 47495500</Tel><Fax>2 47495525</Fax><Email>mercure-tn@webtours.fr</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>47.4382325</Latitude><Longitude>0.7087585</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/TUF-MERhotel_Exterior_1.jpg</Url><Width>346</Width><Height>260</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/TUF-MERhotel_Exterior_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/TUF-MERhotel_Guest_Room_1.jpg</Url><Width>346</Width><Height>260</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/TUF-MERhotel_Guest_Room_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/TUF-MERhotel_Guest_Room_2.jpg</Url><Width>346</Width><Height>260</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/TUF-MERhotel_Guest_Room_2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/TUF-MERhotel_Exterior_2.jpg</Url><Width>346</Width><Height>260</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/TUF-MERhotel_Exterior_2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/TUF-MERhotel_Guest_Room_3.jpg</Url><Width>346</Width><Height>260</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/TUF-MERhotel_Guest_Room_3_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/TUF-MERhotel_Exterior_3.jpg</Url><Width>346</Width><Height>260</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/TUF-MERhotel_Exterior_3_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Mercure Tours Nord in Tours, you'll be near the airport and close to Tours Cathedral and Musee du Compagnonnage. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of Musee des Beaux-Arts and St. Julien Church.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 93 guestrooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a terrace and a garden. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and babysitting/childcare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, where you can enjoy drinks at a bar, take in a garden view, and even dine alfresco (weather permitting). You can also stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a business center, and a computer station. Planning an event in Tours? This hotel has 861 square feet (80 square meters) of space consisting of a conference center, conference space, and meeting rooms. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed      Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, where you can enjoy drinks at a bar, take in a garden view, and even dine alfresco (weather permitting). You can also stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a terrace and a garden. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and babysitting/childcare. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 93 guestrooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Mercure Tours Nord in Tours, you'll be near the airport and close to Tours Cathedral and Musee du Compagnonnage. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of Musee des Beaux-Arts and St. Julien Church. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Tours Cathedral - 4.9 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Musee du Compagnonnage - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Musee des Beaux-Arts - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Julien Church - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Musee du Gemmail - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place Plumereau - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vinci International Convention Centre - 5.4 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Saint Martin Basilica - 5.4 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Francois Rabelais University - 5.5 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Botanical Garden - 6.6 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Parc des Expositions de Tours - 6.7 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Prieure de St-Cosme - 7 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stade de la Vallee du Cher - 7.1 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Priory of Lavaray - 7.6 km / 4.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Domaine Sylvain Gaudron - 11.2 km / 6.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Tours (TUF-Tours - Loire Valley) - 1.6 km / 1 mi&lt;br /&gt;Tours (XSH-Saint Pierre des Corps SNCF Train Station) - 5.5 km / 3.4 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Mercure Tours Nord is Tours (TUF-Tours - Loire Valley). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Mercure Tours Nord is Tours (TUF-Tours - Loire Valley) - 1.6 km / 1 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreshWaterPool</Code><Text>Fresh Water Pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Fridge</Code><Text>Fridge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>