<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>112954</Id><Name>Dauphitel</Name><Region><Id>20469</Id><Name>Grenoble</Name><CityId>16432</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>16 AVENUE KIMBERLEY</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>ECHIROLLES (GRENOBLE)</City><State /><Zip>38130</Zip><Country>France</Country><Tel>0033476336060</Tel><Fax>0033476336000</Fax><Email>info@dauphitel.fr</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>68</CountRooms><CountFloors>4</CountFloors><Latitude>45.1480394</Latitude><Longitude>5.7295783</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1001/47536room1.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>230</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1001/47536room1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>97</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2151</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1001/47536room2.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>238</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1001/47536room2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>94</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2032</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Best Western Hotel Restaurant Dauphitel in Echirolles, you'll be in the business district and convenient to Summum and Palais des Congres Alpexpo. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Stade Lesdiguieres and Grenoble Seyssins Golf Club.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 68 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as a seasonal outdoor pool or take in the view from a garden. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, a fireplace in the lobby, and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar and a garden view. You can also stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, express check-in, and express check-out. Planning an event in Echirolles? This hotel has facilities measuring 2153 square feet (200 square meters), including meeting rooms. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar and a garden view. You can also stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as a seasonal outdoor pool or take in the view from a garden. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, a fireplace in the lobby, and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 68 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Best Western Hotel Restaurant Dauphitel in Echirolles, you'll be in the business district and convenient to Summum and Palais des Congres Alpexpo. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Stade Lesdiguieres and Grenoble Seyssins Golf Club. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Summum - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palais des Congres Alpexpo - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stade Lesdiguieres - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Grenoble Seyssins Golf Club - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Parcours de Bresson - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place Paul Mistral - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;La Caserne de Bonne - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Alps Stadium - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of Resistance and Deportation - 4.8 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place Grenette - 4.9 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jardin de Ville - 5.1 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place Notre Dame - 5.1 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eglise Notre Dame - 5.1 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;WTC Grenoble - 5.2 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Grenoble Theater - 5.2 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Best Western Hotel Restaurant Dauphitel is Grenoble (GNB-Grenoble - Isere) - 39 km / 24.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MoneyExchange</Code><Text>Money exchange</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioned</Code><Text>Air-conditioned</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CloakRoom</Code><Text>Cloak Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DiningRoom</Code><Text>Dining Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestuarantHighChair</Code><Text>Restuarant High Chair</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WLANAccessPoint</Code><Text>WLAN Access Point</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreshWaterPool</Code><Text>Fresh Water Pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parasol</Code><Text>Parasol</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomPrivateBathroom</Code><Text>Private bathrooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Carpeted</Code><Text>Carpeted</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>