<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>113081</Id><Name>Saint Nicolas Hotel</Name><Region><Id>16433</Id><Name>La Rochelle</Name><CityId>16433</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>RUE SARDINERIE 13</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>LA ROCHELLE</City><State /><Zip>17000</Zip><Country>FRANCE</Country><Tel>0033546417155</Tel><Fax>0033546417046</Fax><Email>info@hotel-saint-nicolas.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>46.1581221</Latitude><Longitude>-1.1490088</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1213410-exterior_Thumbnailed.jpg</Url><Width>70</Width><Height>70</Height><Bytes>2129</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1213410-exterior_Thumbnailed.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2120</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Saint Nicolas, you'll be centrally located in La Rochelle, steps from Grand Temple and minutes from La Rochelle Hotel de Ville. This hotel is within close proximity of Porte de la Grosse Horloge and Musee du Nouveau Monde.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of 86 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include safes, and cribs/infant beds (surcharge) can be requested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and a fireplace in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a computer station, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and a 24-hour front desk. Planning an event in La Rochelle? This hotel has facilities measuring 431 square feet (40 square meters), including meeting rooms. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 1 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and a fireplace in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of 86 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include safes, and cribs/infant beds (surcharge) can be requested.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Saint Nicolas, you'll be centrally located in La Rochelle, steps from Grand Temple and minutes from La Rochelle Hotel de Ville. This hotel is within close proximity of Porte de la Grosse Horloge and Musee du Nouveau Monde. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Grand Temple - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;La Rochelle Hotel de Ville - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Porte de la Grosse Horloge - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Musee du Nouveau Monde - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tour St. Nicolas - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tour de la Chaine - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Musee des Beaux-Arts - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maritime Museum - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aquarium La Rochelle - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;L'Espace Encan de La Rochelle - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Musee d'Orbigny-Bernon - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tour de la Lanterne - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Natural History Museum - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Parc des Expositions de La Rochelle - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Musee des Automates - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Saint Nicolas is La Rochelle (LRH-La Rochelle - Ile de Re) - 4 km / 2.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Hotel Saint Nicolas is La Rochelle (LRH-La Rochelle - Ile de Re) - 4 km / 2.5 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BicycleStorage</Code><Text>Bicycle Storage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Garage</Code><Text>Garage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccessible</Code><Text>Wheelchair Accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>