<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>113041</Id><Name>Grand Hotel De Grenoble</Name><Region><Id>20469</Id><Name>Grenoble</Name><CityId>16432</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>RUE DE LA REPUBLIQUE</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>GRENOBLE</City><State /><Zip>38000</Zip><Country>France</Country><Tel>+33 476444936</Tel><Fax>+33 476631406</Fax><Email>GRAND.HOTEL.GRENOBLE@WANADOO.FR</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>56</CountRooms><CountFloors>4</CountFloors><Latitude>45.1905729</Latitude><Longitude>5.7290591</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1001/24117room1.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>233</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1001/24117room1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>96</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2438</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1001/24117bar1.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>233</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1001/24117bar1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>96</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2438</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>HotelAmenities</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Le Grand Hotel Grenoble Centre, you'll be centrally located in Grenoble, steps from Place Grenette and minutes from Grenoble Theater. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Jardin de Ville and Place Notre Dame.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 68 air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and minibars. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, and LCD televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms have rainfall showerheads and designer toiletries. Conveniences include laptop-compatible safes and desks, as well as phones with free local calls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a bite to eat at a coffee shop/café, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour business center, a computer station, and express check-in. Planning an event in Grenoble? This hotel has 1291 square feet (120 square meters) of space consisting of conference space and a meeting room. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a bite to eat at a coffee shop/café, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 68 air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and minibars. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, and LCD televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms have rainfall showerheads and designer toiletries. Conveniences include laptop-compatible safes and desks, as well as phones with free local calls.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Le Grand Hotel Grenoble Centre, you'll be centrally located in Grenoble, steps from Place Grenette and minutes from Grenoble Theater. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Jardin de Ville and Place Notre Dame. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Place Grenette - 0.1 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;Grenoble Theater - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jardin de Ville - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place Notre Dame - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Grenoble-Bastille Cable Car - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eglise Notre Dame - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of Grenoble - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dauphinois Museum - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of Resistance and Deportation - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;La Caserne de Bonne - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place Paul Mistral - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Alps Stadium - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fort de la Bastille - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;WTC Grenoble - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Minatec - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Le Grand Hotel Grenoble Centre is Lyon (LYS-Saint-Exupery) - 77.9 km / 48.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioned</Code><Text>Air-conditioned</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BicycleStorage</Code><Text>Bicycle Storage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomPrivateBathroom</Code><Text>Private bathrooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DoubleBeds</Code><Text>Double Beds</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Carpeted</Code><Text>Carpeted</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Balcony</Code><Text>Balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>