<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>113101</Id><Name>Paradis</Name><Region><Id>20484</Id><Name>Lourdes</Name><CityId>16449</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>AVENUE DU PARADIS</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>LOURDES</City><State /><Zip>65100</Zip><Country>France</Country><Tel>5 62421414</Tel><Fax>5 62946404</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>298</CountRooms><CountSuites>2</CountSuites><Latitude>43.093481</Latitude><Longitude>-0.053424</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAG681600_0.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>492</Height><Bytes>60788</Bytes><Caption>Exterior view</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAG681600_0.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>68</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>15665</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAG681600_2.jpg</Url><Width>382</Width><Height>480</Height><Bytes>50443</Bytes><Caption>Detailed map</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAG681600_2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>55</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>5923</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAG681600_1.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>495</Height><Bytes>48650</Bytes><Caption>Lobby</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAG681600_1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>67</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>14888</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAG681600_3.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>487</Height><Bytes>49374</Bytes><Caption>Standard bedroom</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAG681600_3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>68</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>14671</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Hotel Paradis places you in the heart of Lourdes, walking distance from Musee Grevin de Lourdes and Basilica of St. Pius X. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Chateau de Lourdes and Sanctuary of our Lady of Lourdes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 300 air-conditioned guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Bathrooms have bathtubs or showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, and cribs/infant beds can be requested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and a terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. This hotel also features gift shops/newsstands, shopping on site, and a television in the lobby. Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the area shuttle (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or grab a snack at a coffee shop/café. Relax with a refreshing drink at one of the 2 bars/lounges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a computer station, and express check-out. Planning an event in Lourdes? This hotel has 2691 square feet (250 square meters) of space consisting of a conference center and meeting rooms. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed    Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or grab a snack at a coffee shop/café. Relax with a refreshing drink at one of the 2 bars/lounges. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and a terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. This hotel also features gift shops/newsstands, shopping on site, and a television in the lobby. Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the area shuttle (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 300 air-conditioned guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Bathrooms have bathtubs or showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, and cribs/infant beds can be requested.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Hotel Paradis places you in the heart of Lourdes, walking distance from Musee Grevin de Lourdes and Basilica of St. Pius X. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Chateau de Lourdes and Sanctuary of our Lady of Lourdes. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Musee Grevin de Lourdes - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Basilica of St. Pius X - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chateau de Lourdes - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sanctuary of our Lady of Lourdes - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Basilica of the Immaculate Conception - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Grotte de Massabielle - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;House of Sainte Bernadette - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stade Antoine-Beguere - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pic du Jer - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lourdes Golf Club - 2.8 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hautacam Ski Resort - 14 km / 8.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Laloubere Golf Club - 15.6 km / 9.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Golf de Tumulus Tarbes - 16.2 km / 10.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tarbes Golf Course - 16.4 km / 10.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bigorre Golf Club - 16.8 km / 10.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Paradis is Lourdes (LDE-Tarbes - Lourdes - Pyrenees Intl.) - 11.4 km / 7.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>