<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>113165</Id><Name>Park Inn Ouest</Name><Region><Id>20487</Id><Name>Lyon </Name><CityId>16450</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>2 Allee du Levant</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>LA TOUR DE SALVAGNY</City><State /><Zip>69890</Zip><Country>FRANCE</Country><Tel>++33 78 87 29 87</Tel><Fax>++33 4 78 87 29 89</Fax><Email>info.lyonouest@rezidorparkinn.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>73</CountRooms><Latitude>45.8167316</Latitude><Longitude>4.7253731</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1327203-main100_Thumbnailed.jpg</Url><Width>100</Width><Height>100</Height><Bytes>4002</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1327203-main100_Thumbnailed.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2366</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1327203-room.jpg</Url><Width>200</Width><Height>200</Height><Bytes>6164</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1327203-room.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1766</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1327203-dining.jpg</Url><Width>200</Width><Height>200</Height><Bytes>8437</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1327203-dining.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2078</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1327203-main100.jpg</Url><Width>200</Width><Height>200</Height><Bytes>9442</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1327203-main100.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2307</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1327203-meeting.jpg</Url><Width>200</Width><Height>200</Height><Bytes>11877</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1327203-meeting.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2339</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>HotelAmenities</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in La Tour-de-Salvagny (Greater North Lyon), Qualys-Hotel Lyon Nord is close to Lyon Salvagny Golf Club and Casino Le Lyon Vert. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of EM Lyon Business School and Sainte Marie de la Tourette.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 74 guestrooms featuring refrigerators and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have bathtubs or showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreational opportunities offered, including an outdoor pool, a sauna, and a steam room. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a computer station, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and a 24-hour front desk. Planning an event in La Tour-de-Salvagny? This hotel has facilities measuring 4842 square feet (450 square meters), including conference space. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreational opportunities offered, including an outdoor pool, a sauna, and a steam room. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 74 guestrooms featuring refrigerators and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have bathtubs or showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in La Tour-de-Salvagny (Greater North Lyon), Qualys-Hotel Lyon Nord is close to Lyon Salvagny Golf Club and Casino Le Lyon Vert. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of EM Lyon Business School and Sainte Marie de la Tourette. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Lyon Salvagny Golf Club - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Casino Le Lyon Vert - 3.3 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;EM Lyon Business School - 4.6 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sainte Marie de la Tourette - 7.9 km / 4.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ile Barbe - 8.6 km / 5.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maison des Canuts - 9.6 km / 6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place de la Croix Rousse - 9.6 km / 6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Metallic Tower - 9.7 km / 6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Notre Dame Basilica - 9.7 km / 6.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Roman Theatres of Fourviere - 9.8 km / 6.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Esplanade de Fourviere - 9.8 km / 6.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gallo-Roman Museum - 9.9 km / 6.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Quai de Bondy Vaporetto Stop - 9.9 km / 6.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Guignol Theater - 9.9 km / 6.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lyon History Museum - 10 km / 6.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Lyon (XYD-Part-Dieu SNCF Train Station) - 12.3 km / 7.6 mi&lt;br /&gt;Lyon (LYN-Lyon Bron) - 19.5 km / 12.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;Lyon (LYS-Saint-Exupery) - 29.2 km / 18.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Qualys-Hotel Lyon Nord is Lyon (LYS-Saint-Exupery). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>