<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>113227</Id><Name>Auberge Cavaliere</Name><Region><Id>20493</Id><Name>Arles</Name><CityId>16452</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>ROUTE D'ARLES</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>SAINTE MARIE DE LA MER</City><State /><Zip>13460</Zip><Country>France</Country><Tel>0033490978407</Tel><Fax>0033490978407</Fax><Email>AUBERGE.CAVALERIE@WANADOO.FR</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>43.453833</Latitude><Longitude>4.427771</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1001/22836hotel1.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>317</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1001/22836hotel1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2224</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1001/22836room1.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>311</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1001/22836room1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>72</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2053</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Auberge Cavalière du Pont Des Bannes in Saintes-Maries-de-la-Mer, you'll be by the sea and minutes from Parc Ornithologique de Pont de Gau and Church of Saintes-Maries. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Museum Baroncelli and Saintes-Maries-de-la-Mer Arena.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 69 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Bathrooms with bathtubs are provided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Relax at the full-service spa, where you can enjoy massages. You're sure to appreciate the recreational amenities, including a spa tub, a sauna, and a seasonal outdoor pool. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Auberge Cavalière du Pont Des Bannes. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk. Planning an event in Saintes-Maries-de-la-Mer? This hotel features 4896 square feet (455 square meters) of event facilities. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 4 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Auberge Cavalière du Pont Des Bannes. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Relax at the full-service spa, where you can enjoy massages. You're sure to appreciate the recreational amenities, including a spa tub, a sauna, and a seasonal outdoor pool. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 69 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Bathrooms with bathtubs are provided.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Auberge Cavalière du Pont Des Bannes in Saintes-Maries-de-la-Mer, you'll be by the sea and minutes from Parc Ornithologique de Pont de Gau and Church of Saintes-Maries. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Museum Baroncelli and Saintes-Maries-de-la-Mer Arena. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Parc Ornithologique de Pont de Gau - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of Saintes-Maries - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum Baroncelli - 0.2 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Saintes-Maries-de-la-Mer Arena - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Saintes-Maries-de-la-Mer Beach - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Musee de la Camargue - 21.8 km / 13.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Camargue - 23.8 km / 14.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Langlois Bridge - 27.5 km / 17.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Musee de l'Arles et de la Provence Antique - 28.7 km / 17.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Alyscamps - 29.5 km / 18.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place de la Republique - 29.5 km / 18.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of St. Trophime - 29.6 km / 18.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Theater-Antique - 29.7 km / 18.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place du Forum - 29.7 km / 18.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cirque Romain - 29.7 km / 18.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Auberge Cavalière du Pont Des Bannes is Montpellier (MPL-Montpellier - Mediterranean) - 40.3 km / 25.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioned</Code><Text>Air-conditioned</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantAirconditioned</Code><Text>Restaurant Air-Conditioned</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MobilePhoneNetwork</Code><Text>Mobile Phone Network</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BicycleRental</Code><Text>Bicycle Rental</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreshWaterPool</Code><Text>Fresh Water Pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SnackBar</Code><Text>Snack Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SunLounge</Code><Text>SunLounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parasol</Code><Text>Parasol</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomPrivateBathroom</Code><Text>Private bathrooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>KingSizeBeds</Code><Text>KingSizeBeds</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>