<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>113301</Id><Name>Saint Ferreol</Name><Region><Id>20491</Id><Name>Marseille</Name><CityId>16452</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>RUE PISANÇON</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>MARSEILLE</City><State /><Zip>13001</Zip><Country>France</Country><Tel>0033491331221</Tel><Fax>0033491542997</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>24</CountRooms><CountFloors>4</CountFloors><Latitude>43.2943579</Latitude><Longitude>5.3789752</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1001/17708hotel1.jpg</Url><Width>229</Width><Height>347</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1001/17708hotel1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>46</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1870</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1001/17708hotel2.jpg</Url><Width>350</Width><Height>226</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1001/17708hotel2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>108</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2948</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Hotel Saint Ferreol places you in the heart of Marseille, walking distance from Marseille Opera House and Musee de la Marine. This hotel is within close proximity of Marseille Tourism Office and Vieux Port.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 19 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have bathtubs or showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones and safes, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 19 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have bathtubs or showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones and safes, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Hotel Saint Ferreol places you in the heart of Marseille, walking distance from Marseille Opera House and Musee de la Marine. This hotel is within close proximity of Marseille Tourism Office and Vieux Port. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Marseille Opera House - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Musee de la Marine - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marseille Tourism Office - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vieux Port - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Centre Bourse - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Musee d'Histoire de Marseille - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jardin des Vestiges - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;La Plaine - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hotel de Ville - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Saint Vincent de Paul Church - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;La Criee National Theater of Marseille - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Musee des Docks Romains - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Abbaye de Saint Victor - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place Castellane - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;La Vieille Charite - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Aix-en-Provence (QXB-Aix en Provence TGV Train Station) - 18.6 km / 11.5 mi&lt;br /&gt;Marseille (MRS-Marseille - Provence) - 20.7 km / 12.9 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Saint Ferreol is Marseille (MRS-Marseille - Provence). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Hotel Saint Ferreol is Marseille (MRS-Marseille - Provence) - 20.8 km / 12.9 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CloakRoom</Code><Text>Cloak Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomPrivateBathroom</Code><Text>Private bathrooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>