<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>113768</Id><Name>Viator</Name><Region><Id>20529</Id><Name>(Arr12/13) Bastille - Bercy</Name><CityId>16471</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>RUE PARROT 1</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>PARIS</City><State /><Zip>75012</Zip><Country>FRANCE</Country><Tel>+33 143431100</Tel><Fax>+33 143431089</Fax><Email>info@hotelviator.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>48.8468306</Latitude><Longitude>2.3725345</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/54/27/4/54274-HAB-1.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>212</Height><Bytes>12127</Bytes><Caption>Room</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/54/27/4/54274-HAB-1thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2393</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/54/27/4/54274-HAB-2.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>208</Height><Bytes>12286</Bytes><Caption>Room</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/54/27/4/54274-HAB-2thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>107</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2482</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Viator Paris places you in the heart of Paris, minutes from Pont d'Austerlitz and close to Notre Dame Cathedral. This hotel is within close proximity of Opera Bastille and Place de la Bastille.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 45 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have shower/tub combinations and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a computer station, express check-in, and complimentary newspapers in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 1 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 45 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have shower/tub combinations and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Viator Paris places you in the heart of Paris, minutes from Pont d'Austerlitz and close to Notre Dame Cathedral. This hotel is within close proximity of Opera Bastille and Place de la Bastille. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Pont d'Austerlitz - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Opera Bastille - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place de la Bastille - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gallery of Comparative Anatomy and Paleontology - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;July Column - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ministry of Finance - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bercy Arena - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Victor Hugo's House - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Menagerie du Jardin des Plantes - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pitie-Salpetriere Hospital - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place des Vosges - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pont de Sully - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Arab World Institute - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pierre et Marie Curie University - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pont Marie - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Paris (ORY-Orly) - 12.7 km / 7.9 mi&lt;br /&gt;Paris (CDG-Roissy-Charles de Gaulle) - 22.7 km / 14.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Viator Paris is Paris (CDG-Roissy-Charles de Gaulle). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Carpeted</Code><Text>Carpeted</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Balcony</Code><Text>Balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>