<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>114066</Id><Name>Marceau Bastille</Name><Region><Id>20529</Id><Name>(Arr12/13) Bastille - Bercy</Name><CityId>16471</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>RUE JULES CESAR 13</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>PARIS</City><State /><Zip>75012</Zip><Country>FRANCE</Country><Tel>0033143431165</Tel><Fax>0033143416770</Fax><Email>BOOKINGS@HOTELMARCEAUBASTILLE.COM</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>48.8489257</Latitude><Longitude>2.3697906</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1039049-marceau_bastille_reception_Thumbnailed.jpg</Url><Width>70</Width><Height>70</Height><Bytes>2407</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1039049-marceau_bastille_reception_Thumbnailed.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2398</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1039049-marceau_bastille_reception.jpg</Url><Width>200</Width><Height>200</Height><Bytes>8948</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1039049-marceau_bastille_reception.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2184</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1039049-marceau_bastille_room.jpg</Url><Width>200</Width><Height>200</Height><Bytes>8061</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1039049-marceau_bastille_room.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1987</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Le Marceau Bastille in Paris (Gare de Lyon - Bercy), you'll be minutes from Pont d'Austerlitz and Opera Bastille. This 4-star hotel is close to Notre Dame Cathedral and Louvre Museum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 55 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and DVD players. Flat-screen televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include safes and desks, and you can also request irons/ironing boards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, limo/town car service, and dry cleaning/laundry services.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 1 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 55 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and DVD players. Flat-screen televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include safes and desks, and you can also request irons/ironing boards.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Le Marceau Bastille in Paris (Gare de Lyon - Bercy), you'll be minutes from Pont d'Austerlitz and Opera Bastille. This 4-star hotel is close to Notre Dame Cathedral and Louvre Museum. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Pont d'Austerlitz - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Opera Bastille - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place de la Bastille - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;July Column - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Victor Hugo's House - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gallery of Comparative Anatomy and Paleontology - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place des Vosges - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pont de Sully - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Arab World Institute - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Menagerie du Jardin des Plantes - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pont Marie - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pont de la Tournelle - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Carnavalet Museum - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pierre et Marie Curie University - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ministry of Finance - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Paris (ORY-Orly) - 13 km / 8 mi&lt;br /&gt;Paris (CDG-Roissy-Charles de Gaulle) - 22.7 km / 14.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Le Marceau Bastille is Paris (CDG-Roissy-Charles de Gaulle). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>