<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>114209</Id><Name>Relax Torreruja Thalasso &amp; Spa</Name><Region><Id>20884</Id><Name>Sassari</Name><CityId>17049</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>VIA TANCA DELLA TORRE</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>ISOLA ROSSA</City><State /><Zip>07038</Zip><Country>ITALY</Country><Tel>00390789790083</Tel><Fax>0039078979008</Fax><Email>BOOKING@DELPHINA.IT</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>41.0127098</Latitude><Longitude>8.8774881</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/22/46/3/22463-GEN-1.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>15783</Bytes><Caption>General</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/22/46/3/22463-GEN-1thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1475</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/22/46/3/22463-HAB-2.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>19125</Bytes><Caption>Room</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/22/46/3/22463-HAB-2thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2152</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/22/46/3/22463-PIS-3.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>20892</Bytes><Caption>Pool</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/22/46/3/22463-PIS-3thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2298</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>SwimmingPool</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Relax Torreruja Thalasso &amp; Spa in Trinita d'Agultu e Vignola (Costa Paradiso), you'll be minutes from Isola Rossa Beach and close to La Marinedda Beach. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of Aquafantasy and Li Cossi Beach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 124 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Rooms have private furnished balconies or patios. Cable television is provided for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. You can take advantage of recreational amenities such as a health club, an outdoor pool, and a spa tub. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access and babysitting/childcare (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at one of the hotel's dining establishments, which include 2 restaurants and a coffee shop/café. Relax with a refreshing drink from a poolside bar or one of the 2 bars/lounges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff. Event facilities at this hotel consist of a conference center and a meeting room. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available 24 hours), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at one of the hotel's dining establishments, which include 2 restaurants and a coffee shop/café. Relax with a refreshing drink from a poolside bar or one of the 2 bars/lounges. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. You can take advantage of recreational amenities such as a health club, an outdoor pool, and a spa tub. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 124 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Rooms have private furnished balconies or patios. Cable television is provided for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Relax Torreruja Thalasso &amp; Spa in Trinita d'Agultu e Vignola (Costa Paradiso), you'll be minutes from Isola Rossa Beach and close to La Marinedda Beach. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of Aquafantasy and Li Cossi Beach. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Isola Rossa Beach - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;La Marinedda Beach - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aquafantasy - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Li Cossi Beach - 6.2 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cala Sarraina Beach - 12.1 km / 7.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Baia Ostina - 16.2 km / 10.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sant'Antonio Abate Cathedral - 17.5 km / 10.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Doria Castle - 17.6 km / 10.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of Mediterranean Weaving - 17.6 km / 10.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Elephant Rock - 17.6 km / 11 mi &lt;br /&gt;Olivia Carta Cannas Ethnographic Museum - 18.4 km / 11.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of Banditry - 18.4 km / 11.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Domus de Janas Museum - 19 km / 11.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of St. Lucia - 19.8 km / 12.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Nuraghe Majori - 21.1 km / 13.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Relax Torreruja Thalasso &amp; Spa is Olbia (OLB-Costa Smeralda) - 54.9 km / 34.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Hotel Relax Torreruja Thalasso &amp; SPA is Olbia (OLB-Costa Smeralda) - 54.9 km / 34.1 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>