<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>114212</Id><Name>Marinedda Thalasso and Spa</Name><Region><Id>20884</Id><Name>Sassari</Name><CityId>17049</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>LOCALITA ISOLA ROSSA</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>ISOLA ROSSA</City><State /><Zip /><Country>ITALY</Country><Tel>00390789790092</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/19/11/8/19118-HAB-1.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>14589</Bytes><Caption>Room</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/19/11/8/19118-HAB-1thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2267</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/19/11/8/19118-PIS-2.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>15061</Bytes><Caption>Pool</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/19/11/8/19118-PIS-2thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2144</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>SwimmingPool</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Marinedda Thalasso &amp; Spa in Trinita d'Agultu e Vignola (Costa Paradiso), you'll be minutes from La Marinedda Beach and close to Isola Rossa Beach. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of Aquafantasy and Li Cossi Beach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 195 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Rooms have private furnished patios. Satellite television is provided for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Relax at the full-service spa, where you can enjoy massages, body treatments, and facials. If you're looking for recreational opportunities, you'll find a health club, a spa tub, and an outdoor tennis court. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). If you'd like to spend the day shopping, you can hop on the complimentary shuttle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at one of the hotel's dining establishments, which include 3 restaurants and a coffee shop/café. Relax with a refreshing drink from a bar/lounge or one of the 2 poolside bars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff. Event facilities at this hotel consist of a conference center and meeting rooms. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at one of the hotel's dining establishments, which include 3 restaurants and a coffee shop/café. Relax with a refreshing drink from a bar/lounge or one of the 2 poolside bars. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Relax at the full-service spa, where you can enjoy massages, body treatments, and facials. If you're looking for recreational opportunities, you'll find a health club, a spa tub, and an outdoor tennis court. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). If you'd like to spend the day shopping, you can hop on the complimentary shuttle. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 195 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Rooms have private furnished patios. Satellite television is provided for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Marinedda Thalasso &amp; Spa in Trinita d'Agultu e Vignola (Costa Paradiso), you'll be minutes from La Marinedda Beach and close to Isola Rossa Beach. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of Aquafantasy and Li Cossi Beach. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;La Marinedda Beach - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Isola Rossa Beach - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aquafantasy - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Li Cossi Beach - 5.9 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cala Sarraina Beach - 11.9 km / 7.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Baia Ostina - 16.5 km / 10.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Olivia Carta Cannas Ethnographic Museum - 17.8 km / 11 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of Banditry - 17.8 km / 11 mi &lt;br /&gt;Elephant Rock - 17.8 km / 11.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sant'Antonio Abate Cathedral - 17.9 km / 11.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Doria Castle - 17.9 km / 11.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of Mediterranean Weaving - 17.9 km / 11.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Domus de Janas Museum - 18.9 km / 11.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of St. Lucia - 19.1 km / 11.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vignola Mare Beach - 19.8 km / 12.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Marinedda Thalasso &amp; Spa is Olbia (OLB-Costa Smeralda) - 54.3 km / 33.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Hotel Marinedda Thalasso &amp; Spa is Olbia (OLB-Costa Smeralda) - 54.3 km / 33.8 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniClub</Code><Text>Mini Club</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>