<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>114318</Id><Name>Savoia</Name><Region><Id>20887</Id><Name>Sorrento (and Vicinity)</Name><CityId>17050</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>VIA FUORIMURA 46/48</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>SORRENTO</City><State /><Zip>80067</Zip><Country>ITALY</Country><Tel>00390818782511</Tel><Fax>00390818773871</Fax><Email>INFO@SAVOIA-HOTEL.COM</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>40.6235361</Latitude><Longitude>14.3778593</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/56/27/3/56273-GEN-1.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>207</Height><Bytes>14653</Bytes><Caption>General</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/56/27/3/56273-GEN-1thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>108</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2594</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/56/27/3/56273-HAB-2.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>10656</Bytes><Caption>Room</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/56/27/3/56273-HAB-2thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1831</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Savoia in Sorrento, you'll be minutes from Deep Valley of the Mills and Piazza Tasso. This hotel is within close proximity of Sorrento Lift and Sedile Dominova.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 20 air-conditioned guestrooms. Rooms have private balconies. Satellite television is provided for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have bidets and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as wireless Internet access (surcharge), a television in the lobby, and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). A complimentary buffet breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). A complimentary buffet breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as wireless Internet access (surcharge), a television in the lobby, and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 20 air-conditioned guestrooms. Rooms have private balconies. Satellite television is provided for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have bidets and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Savoia in Sorrento, you'll be minutes from Deep Valley of the Mills and Piazza Tasso. This hotel is within close proximity of Sorrento Lift and Sedile Dominova. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Deep Valley of the Mills - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza Tasso - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sorrento Lift - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sedile Dominova - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza Lauro - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sorrento Cathedral - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza Sant'Antonino - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tasso Theatre - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Basilica di Sant'Antonio - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sorrento Foundation - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marcello Aversa Workshop - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museo Bottega della Tarsia Lignea - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wonderwall Art Gallery - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dali Universe - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chiesa di San Francesco - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Savoia is Naples (NAP-Naples Intl.) - 29.4 km / 18.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Hotel Savoia is Naples (NAP-Naples Intl.) - 29.4 km / 18.3 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVRoom</Code><Text>TV Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantAirconditioned</Code><Text>Restaurant Air-Conditioned</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WLANAccessPoint</Code><Text>WLAN Access Point</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MedicalService</Code><Text>Medical Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Balcony</Code><Text>Balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Cafe(s)</Code><Text>Cafe(s)</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>