<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>114693</Id><Name>UNAWAY Hotel Bologna Fiera (Formerly Holiday Inn)</Name><Region><Id>20898</Id><Name>Bologna</Name><CityId>17061</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>PIAZZA DELLA COSTITUZIONE 1</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>BOLOGNA</City><State /><Zip>40128</Zip><Country>ITALY</Country><Tel>39-051-41666</Tel><Fax>39-051-41665</Fax><Email>hibolognacity@libero.it</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>44.5126753</Latitude><Longitude>11.3580961</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/BLQ-98hotel_Lobby_1.jpg</Url><Width>270</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/BLQ-98hotel_Lobby_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>60</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>80</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Bologna Fiera in Bologna (Exhibition Center), you'll be minutes from EuropAuditorium Theater and close to BolognaFiere. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Santurario del sacro Cuore and Aldini Valeriani Sirani.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 211 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature bidets and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. This hotel also features babysitting/childcare and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves lunch and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk. Planning an event in Bologna? This hotel has 4855 square feet (451 square meters) of space consisting of conference space and meeting rooms. Limited parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves lunch and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. This hotel also features babysitting/childcare and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 211 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature bidets and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Bologna Fiera in Bologna (Exhibition Center), you'll be minutes from EuropAuditorium Theater and close to BolognaFiere. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Santurario del sacro Cuore and Aldini Valeriani Sirani. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;EuropAuditorium Theater - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;BolognaFiere - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Santurario del sacro Cuore - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aldini Valeriani Sirani - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ippodromo Arcoveggio - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Caserme Rosse - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bologna Botanical Gardens - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Parco Nord Arena - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Montagnola Park - 1.7 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Art Gallery of Bologna - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza VIII Agosto - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museo Aldovrandi - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museo della Specola - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of Military Architechture - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Naval Museum - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Bologna Fiera is Bologna (BLQ-Guglielmo Marconi) - 5.5 km / 3.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Unaway Hotel Bologna Fiera is Bologna (BLQ-Guglielmo Marconi) - 5.5 km / 3.4 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>CoffeeTeaMaker</Code><Text>Tea and Coffee maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MoneyExchange</Code><Text>Money exchange</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantAirconditioned</Code><Text>Restaurant Air-Conditioned</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>NumberOfPool</Code><Text>Number Of Pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Fridge</Code><Text>Fridge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>