<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>114655226</Id><Name>Best Western Bay View Suites</Name><Region><Id>15455</Id><Name>Nassau</Name><CityId>15455</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Casa Del Sol Condominiums</Address1><Address2>Harbour Rd</Address2><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip /><Country>BHS</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>A true tropical escape awaits couples, families and friends at the Best Western Bay View Suites on Paradise Island. The Bahamas hotel, filled with tropical gardens and world-class service is less than an hour from South Florida and 3 hours from New York City. And, best of all you are just minutes away from the fun and excitement that is Paradise Island.The Paradise Island hotel offers spacious accommodations at budget-friendly rates, matched with warm Bahamian hospitality and is surrounded by four acres of flowering hibiscus, bougainvillea, alamanda and coconut palms. When it comes to complete guest comfort and satisfaction, the hotel likes to go the extra mile. Thats why they  provide a long list of well thought of hotel and guest amenities including a multilingual staff offering personalized service, Iron &amp; ironing board , coffee/tea maker, free Internet access, and fully equipped kitchens, just to name a few! The Best Western Bay View Suites is proud to offer the following amenities: 100% smoke free rooms, Cocktail lounge poolside, exterior corridor, baggage hold, three freshwater swimming pools, 24-hour exercise facility, dry cleaning, and late checkout.Guest can find a little piece of Paradise in every bite at the Hibiscus Terrace which offers deli, sandwiches, and salads and thanks to the hotels convenient location, youre never too far from some of the best restaurants on Paradise Island. Also, each room is equipped with complete kitchens, giving guest the chance to prepare a little home-cooked Bahamian meal.The Best Western is on the Paradise Island and is 19.5 miles from the Lynden Pindling International Airport. It is also just half a mile from Hartford Beach and the Paradise Island Ferry terminal. The Paradise Island Golf Course and Paradise Beach are both just over one mile away.</Text></Description><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>