<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>114654875</Id><Name>Beach House</Name><Region><Id>18862</Id><Name>Turks and Caicos Island</Name><CityId>18862</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>218 Lower Bight Rd</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip /><Country>TCA</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Beach House is one of the first authentically boutique Turks and Caicos resorts on Grace Bay. Our luxuriantly playful 21-suite abode overlooks the bright white dunes, swaying sea grass and azure waters of one of the worlds most beautiful destinations  Grace Bay Beach.Join the Beach House Movement!Our passion for exquisite service and sublime relaxation is matched only by our commitment to spontaneity and unmatched by any of the Turks and Caicos resorts.  From suites with names instead of numbers, to gourmet picnics on Grace Bay beach, The Beach House Movement is all about breeziness going well beyond the weather and into your soul.At Beach House, minds dont simply change, they go somewhere else entirely. To a place where letting go, laying back and living it up are as natural as breathing. Premium beers are on ice, lobster is on the grill, the powder-soft sand is running between your toes and the work of your day-to-day life is but a faint recollection. The Movement is happening. Youre at Beach House.Let yourself go.  We are here to catch you.  The relaxing spirit of the Turks and Caicos Islands is highly contagious and The Beach House Movement was born to create the ultimate atmosphere in which to revel in your newfound sense of freedom.  This is bliss!The 21 suites are amongst the most generously sized rooms of all Turks and Caicos resorts ranging from 1,150 sq ft to 1,580 sq ft for the one and two bedroom suites. Our Beach House Restaurant is renowned for its French contemporary cuisine with a lovely twist of Turks and Caicos and is ideally suited for romantic dinners for two and large events alike. With a spa, gym, complimentary watersports equipment and bicycles activities are plentiful and your relaxing holiday is awaiting.</Text></Description><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>