<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>114604279</Id><Name>Arlo Nomad</Name><Region><Id>64379</Id><Name>Midtown Manhattan</Name><CityId>19793</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>11 East 31st Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>.New York, NY</City><State /><Zip /><Country>USA</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Located in the thriving midtown neighborhood known as NoMad, the hotel is mere steps from NYC icons like Madison Square Garden and the Empire State Building. The hotel features stylishly appointed rooms that maximize the cool factor while still providing a value-conscious alternative to other boutique chains. The hotel offers numerous public spaces for both business and social activities including a second floor lobby bar with terrace; a 75-seat Italian-American restaurant serving breakfast, lunch, and dinner; and a cozy outdoor rooftop bar with unparalleled views of the city's iconic skyline. For the corporate traveler, our flexible meeting and event spaces allow for creative company events ranging from intimate boardroom meetings to expansive product launch receptions.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in the thriving midtown neighborhood known as NoMad. Very close to few Subway station and few minutes walk from the Empire State Building. This property is strategically located to visit the main attractions in the City.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PropertyInformation</Type><Text>This is a modern building.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DiningFacilities</Type><Text>- Massoni: Type of cuisine: Italian with a modern twist; Hours of operation: 7am - 11pm; Are reservations required: no; - The Heights (rooftop): Type of cuisine: Bar; Hours of operation: 4pm - 1am; Are reservations required: no;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>Short</Type><Text>This accommodation has a small lobby.</Text></Description><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>