<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>114655269</Id><Name>Warwick Paradise Island Bahamas</Name><Region><Id>15455</Id><Name>Nassau</Name><CityId>15455</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Harbor Drive Paradise Island</Address1><Address2>New Providence</Address2><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip /><Country>BHS</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The resort offers an incredible 7,000 square foot sea terrace which overlooks Nassau Harbour ? one of the island?s highlights. Other attractions at this resort include a harbour-front beach, an impressive pool, uplifting modern interiors, and 5 eateries, 4 of which are included in the all-inclusive package, serving anything from poolside pizzas to fine à la carte fare. If you want to experience Atlantis, with its world-famous features for the day (including its water park, casino, marine habitat, and endless restaurants), it is just a short stroll away and afterwards, you can return to the calm retreat of the Warwick to indulge and unwind.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Warwick Paradise Island Bahamas is an all-inclusive resort that is exclusively for adults and is located overlooking Nassau Harbour. It is also just a leisurely stroll from the hugely popular Atlantis Paradise Island. A signature feature of the resort is its 10,000 sq. ft. harbour terrace overlooking the harbour marinas. The terrace also has an arrivals? dock and an expansive boardwalk. Cabbage Beach is a 10-minute walk away with dining and shopping nearby.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PropertyInformation</Type><Text>This is a modern building.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DiningFacilities</Type><Text>All inclusive resort</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>Short</Type><Text>This accommodation has a small lobby.</Text></Description><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>