<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>114741</Id><Name>Dal Moro Gallery</Name><Region><Id>21067</Id><Name>Assisi</Name><CityId>17170</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>VIA SANTARELLI SANTA MARIA DEGLI ANGELI 6</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>ASSISI</City><State /><Zip /><Country>ITALY</Country><Tel>0039 758043688</Tel><Fax>0039 0758041666</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>43.0590448</Latitude><Longitude>12.5785912</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAG711200_0.jpg</Url><Width>383</Width><Height>480</Height><Bytes>47109</Bytes><Caption>Exterior view</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAG711200_0.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>55</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>12503</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAG711200_2.jpg</Url><Width>393</Width><Height>480</Height><Bytes>33129</Bytes><Caption>Detailed map</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAG711200_2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>57</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>7678</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAG711200_1.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>310</Height><Bytes>32429</Bytes><Caption>Lobby</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAG711200_1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>108</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>24453</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAG711200_3.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>455</Height><Bytes>31062</Bytes><Caption>Standard bedroom</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAG711200_3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>73</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>14850</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Dal Moro Gallery Hotel is centrally located in Assisi, walking distance from St. Mary of the Angels and close to Papal Basilica of St. Francis of Assisi. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Oratorio dei Pellegrini and Roman Temple of Minerva.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 51 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including an outdoor pool, a seasonal outdoor pool, and bicycles to rent. Additional features include wireless Internet access (surcharge), wedding services, and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, a computer station, and express check-in. Guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle for a surcharge, and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM   &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including an outdoor pool, a seasonal outdoor pool, and bicycles to rent. Additional features include wireless Internet access (surcharge), wedding services, and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 51 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Dal Moro Gallery Hotel is centrally located in Assisi, walking distance from St. Mary of the Angels and close to Papal Basilica of St. Francis of Assisi. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Oratorio dei Pellegrini and Roman Temple of Minerva. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;St. Mary of the Angels - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Papal Basilica of St. Francis of Assisi - 2.8 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Oratorio dei Pellegrini - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Roman Temple of Minerva - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza del Comune - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Damiano - 3.3 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Santa Maria delle Rose - 3.3 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Basilica of Santa Chiara - 3.3 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rocca Maggiore - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cathedral of San Rufino - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eremo delle Carceri - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Di Filippo - 7.3 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fondazione Lungarotti - 12.1 km / 7.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Olive Oil Museum - 12.3 km / 7.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wine Museum - 12.4 km / 7.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Dal Moro Gallery Hotel is Perugia (PEG-Sant Egidio) - 7.3 km / 4.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Dal Moro Gallery Hotel is Perugia (PEG-Sant Egidio) - 7.2 km / 4.5 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Garage</Code><Text>Garage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>