<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>114783</Id><Name>Hotel Bologna</Name><Region><Id>114189</Id><Name>Mestre</Name><CityId>17175</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Via Piave, 214</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Venice</City><State /><Zip>30171</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel>0039 041931000</Tel><Fax>0039 041931095</Fax><Email>info@hotelbologna.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>45.4829399</Latitude><Longitude>12.2320929</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/VCEM-BOLhotel_Guest_Room_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>308</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/VCEM-BOLhotel_Guest_Room_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Best Western Hotel Bologna in Mestre, you'll be convenient to Porto Marghera and San Giuliano Park. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Toniolo Theatre and Piazza Ferretto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 109 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and dry cleaning/laundry services. Planning an event in Mestre? This hotel has 2690 square feet (250 square meters) of space consisting of conference space and meeting rooms. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 109 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Best Western Hotel Bologna in Mestre, you'll be convenient to Porto Marghera and San Giuliano Park. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Toniolo Theatre and Piazza Ferretto. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Porto Marghera - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Toniolo Theatre - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza Ferretto - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Municipal Tower of Mestre - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Forte Marghera - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Giuliano Park - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ospedale dell'Angelo - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Villa Salus Hospital - 3.5 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Villa Foscari La Malcontenta - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Terminal Fusina - 7.3 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tronchetto Waterbus Stop - 7.7 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Port of Venice - 7.8 km / 4.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Forte Bazzera - 8 km / 5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Villa Valmarana at Mira - 8 km / 5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Villa Widmann Rezzonico Foscari - 8 km / 5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Venice (VCE-Marco Polo) - 8.8 km / 5.4 mi&lt;br /&gt;Treviso (TSF) - 19.2 km / 12 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Best Western Hotel Bologna is Venice (VCE-Marco Polo). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Best Western Hotel Bologna is Venice (VCE-Marco Polo) - 8.8 km / 5.4 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Fridge</Code><Text>Fridge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>