<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>115017</Id><Name>Semifonte</Name><Region><Id>21054</Id><Name>Val d'Elsa</Name><CityId>17157</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>VIA PISANA 1</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>POGGIBONSI</City><State /><Zip>50021</Zip><Country>ITALY</Country><Tel>00390558068051</Tel><Fax>0039 0558069283</Fax><Email>SEMIFONTE@SEMIFONTEHOTEL.IT</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>43.4880615</Latitude><Longitude>11.1246143</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/18/47/1/18471-GEN-1.jpg</Url><Width>350</Width><Height>226</Height><Bytes>9573</Bytes><Caption>General</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/18/47/1/18471-GEN-1thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>108</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2068</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/18/47/1/18471-GEN-2.jpg</Url><Width>350</Width><Height>263</Height><Bytes>16404</Bytes><Caption>General</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/18/47/1/18471-GEN-2thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2451</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/18/47/1/18471-GEN-3.jpg</Url><Width>350</Width><Height>233</Height><Bytes>15104</Bytes><Caption>General</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/18/47/1/18471-GEN-3thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2468</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/18/47/1/18471-GEN-4.jpg</Url><Width>350</Width><Height>233</Height><Bytes>16008</Bytes><Caption>General</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/18/47/1/18471-GEN-4thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2686</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Semifonte in Barberino Val d'Elsa (Val d'Elsa), you'll be close to Castello di Monsanto. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of Castello della Paneretta and Piazza Arnolfo di Cambio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 48 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LED televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including an outdoor pool, a fitness center, and a seasonal outdoor pool. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast and dinner, or grab a snack at a coffee shop/café. Mingle with other guests at a complimentary reception, held daily. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff. Planning an event in Barberino Val d'Elsa? This hotel has 495 square feet (46 square meters) of space consisting of conference space, meeting rooms, and a meeting room. Guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle for a surcharge, and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 12:30 PM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast and dinner, or grab a snack at a coffee shop/café. Mingle with other guests at a complimentary reception, held daily. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including an outdoor pool, a fitness center, and a seasonal outdoor pool. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 48 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LED televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Semifonte in Barberino Val d'Elsa (Val d'Elsa), you'll be close to Castello di Monsanto. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of Castello della Paneretta and Piazza Arnolfo di Cambio. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Castello di Monsanto - 4.9 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Castello della Paneretta - 5.8 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza Arnolfo di Cambio - 6.2 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Colle di Val d'Elsa Cathedral - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of Torture - 7 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza della Cisterna - 7.2 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Collegiata di San Gimignano - 7.2 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Loggia del Comune - 7.2 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza Duomo - 7.2 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Podesta's Palace - 7.2 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Torre Grossa - 7.2 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza delle Erbe - 7.2 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Gimignano Communal Palace - 7.2 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chiesa di Sant'Agostino - 7.3 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Staggia Castle - 7.3 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Semifonte is Florence (FLR-Peretola) - 36.4 km / 22.6 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Hotel Semifonte is Florence (FLR-Peretola) - 36.1 km / 22.4 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>