<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>115072</Id><Name>Resort Cala di Falco</Name><Region><Id>20923</Id><Name>Olbia</Name><CityId>17078</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>CANNIGIONE</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Cannigione (Arzachena)OT</City><State /><Zip>07020</Zip><Country>ITALY</Country><Tel>00390789790083</Tel><Fax>00390789790084</Fax><Email>booking@delphina.it</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>41.1120856</Latitude><Longitude>9.4406769</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/18/19/0/18190-GEN-2.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>32323</Bytes><Caption>General</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/18/19/0/18190-GEN-2thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>3060</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/18/19/0/18190-HAB-1.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>14344</Bytes><Caption>Room</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/18/19/0/18190-HAB-1thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2218</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Resort Cala di Falco, you'll be centrally located in Arzachena, convenient to Tanca Manna Beach and Aquadream.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Nuragic Temple of Malchittu and Vigne Surrau Winery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 120 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Rooms have private furnished patios. Satellite television is provided for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities including an outdoor tennis court and a seasonal outdoor pool. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). The complimentary beach shuttle makes getting to the surf and sand a breeze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at one of the hotel's dining establishments, which include 2 restaurants and a coffee shop/café. Relax with a refreshing drink from a poolside bar or one of the 2 bars/lounges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff. Event facilities at this hotel consist of a conference center and a meeting room. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 4 PM  Check-out time is 10:30 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at one of the hotel's dining establishments, which include 2 restaurants and a coffee shop/café. Relax with a refreshing drink from a poolside bar or one of the 2 bars/lounges. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities including an outdoor tennis court and a seasonal outdoor pool. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). The complimentary beach shuttle makes getting to the surf and sand a breeze. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 120 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Rooms have private furnished patios. Satellite television is provided for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Resort Cala di Falco, you'll be centrally located in Arzachena, convenient to Tanca Manna Beach and Aquadream.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Nuragic Temple of Malchittu and Vigne Surrau Winery. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Tanca Manna Beach - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aquadream - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Nuragic Temple of Malchittu - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vigne Surrau Winery - 4.9 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Nuraghe Albucciu - 5.4 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Arzachena Museum - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Giants' Grave - 6.7 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bear's Rock - 7 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stella Maris Church - 8 km / 5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gregoland - 8 km / 5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piccolo Pevero Beach - 8.4 km / 5.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Louise Alexander Gallery - 8.6 km / 5.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Liscia Ruja Beach - 8.7 km / 5.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pevero Golf Club - 8.8 km / 5.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palau Harbor - 9 km / 5.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Resort Cala di Falco is Olbia (OLB-Costa Smeralda) - 24.1 km / 15 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Resort Cala di Falco is Olbia (OLB-Costa Smeralda) - 24.1 km / 15 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>GameRoom</Code><Text>GameRoom</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BicycleRental</Code><Text>Bicycle Rental</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniClub</Code><Text>Mini Club</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Playground</Code><Text>Playground</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreshWaterPool</Code><Text>Fresh Water Pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SunLounge</Code><Text>SunLounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>