<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11547374</Id><Name>Sundowner Hume Country Motor Inn</Name><Region><Id>15268</Id><Name>Albury</Name><CityId>15268</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>736 Logan Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Albury</City><State /><Zip>2640</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>02 6025 8233</Tel><Fax>02 60 404999</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Glenroy, Hume Country Motor Inn is in the suburbs and convenient to Commercial Golf Resort and Monument Hill.  This family-friendly motel is within close proximity of Albury Art Gallery and Hothouse Theatre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 21 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and microwaves. Rooms have private patios. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and 32-inch LCD televisions are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include desks and minibars, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a seasonal outdoor pool, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and an arcade/game room. Additional amenities include tour/ticket assistance, a picnic area, and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite from a snack bar/deli serving guests of Hume Country Motor Inn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, luggage storage, and laundry facilities. Planning an event in Glenroy? This motel has facilities measuring 538 square feet (50 square meters), including a meeting room. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite from a snack bar/deli serving guests of Hume Country Motor Inn. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a seasonal outdoor pool, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and an arcade/game room. Additional amenities include tour/ticket assistance, a picnic area, and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 21 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and microwaves. Rooms have private patios. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and 32-inch LCD televisions are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include desks and minibars, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Glenroy, Hume Country Motor Inn is in the suburbs and convenient to Commercial Golf Resort and Monument Hill.  This family-friendly motel is within close proximity of Albury Art Gallery and Hothouse Theatre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Commercial Golf Resort - 1.5 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Monument Hill - 2.8 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albury Art Gallery - 3 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hothouse Theatre - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wonga Wetlands - 5.1 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Belvoir Park - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wodonga Golf Course - 9.3 km / 5.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albury Wodonga Golf Driving Range - 9.5 km / 5.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lake Hume - 13.6 km / 8.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hume Country Motor Inn is Albury, NSW (ABX) - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>GameRoom</Code><Text>GameRoom</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>