<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11545716</Id><Name>Holiday Inn Hotel And Suites Phoenix Airport North</Name><Region><Id>21775</Id><Name>Phoenix Int'l Airport (PHX)</Name><CityId>19858</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1515 North 44th Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Phoenix</City><State /><Zip>85008</Zip><Country>USA</Country><Tel>+6022448800</Tel><Fax>+6022448114</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1258117-photo-not-available-small.jpg</Url><Width>70</Width><Height>70</Height><Bytes>1454</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1258117-photo-not-available-small.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1454</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Opening in April 2011, the Holiday Inn And Suites Phoenix-Airport North is the Newest in Contemporary Styling. Conveniently located just 1 mile from Phoenix Sky Harbor Airport , we are within minutes from Metro Light rail , downtown Phoenix, Tempe and Scottsdale . Our beautiful 100% non-smoking all suites hotel is minutes from Chase Field, US Airways Stadium and the Phoenix Zoo. Our modern, sophisticated design offers a plethora of amenities such as spacious two room suites featuring our luxurious new bedding, full service restaurant, bar, room service, and a beautiful lush courtyard with a sparkling pool, whirlpool and gazebo. Our 12,000 square feet of meeting space can comfortably accommodate up to 400 people. Our convenient location places you minutes from Papago Park Golf Course, Pueblo Grande Indian Museum, Chase Field (Diamondback Baseball), Herberger Theater, Orpheum Theater, Phoenix Convention Center, Arizona State University (ASU), Tempe Town Lake, Old Town Scottsdale, Casino Arizona, University of Phoenix Stadium (Arizona Cardinal Football), Phoenix International Raceway (PIR) , minutes from the TPC Golf Course (home of the Phoenix Open) and a variety of local restaurants, shopping and entertainment. Many popular area attractions including Saguaro/Canyon Lake, Sedona and Flagstaff are all a short drive away.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Whirlpool</Code><Text>Whirlpool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Icemachine</Code><Text>Ice Machine</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConvenienceShop</Code><Text>Convenience Shop</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>