<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11545011</Id><Name>Le Suffren Hotel and Marina</Name><Region><Id>264141</Id><Name>Mauritius</Name><CityId>264141</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Le Caudan</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Port Louis</City><State /><Zip /><Country>Mauritius</Country><Tel>(230) 202 4900</Tel><Fax>+230 (230) 202 4999</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Le Suffren Hotel &amp; Marina is in the heart of Port Louis, walking distance from Blue Penny Museum and Caudan Waterfront.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Caudan Waterfront Casino and Port Louis Market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 100 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. You can soak up the sun at the private beach or enjoy other recreational amenities including an outdoor pool and a sauna. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, express check-out, and dry cleaning/laundry services. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. You can soak up the sun at the private beach or enjoy other recreational amenities including an outdoor pool and a sauna. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 100 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Le Suffren Hotel &amp; Marina is in the heart of Port Louis, walking distance from Blue Penny Museum and Caudan Waterfront.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Caudan Waterfront Casino and Port Louis Market. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Blue Penny Museum - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Caudan Waterfront - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Caudan Waterfront Casino - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Port Louis Market - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;National History Museum of Port Louis - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mauritius Postal Museum - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Immigration Depot - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Port Louis Theater - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jummah Mosque - 1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chinatown - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tamil Temple - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. James Cathedral - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fort Adelaide - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Champs de Mars Racecourse - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Le Pouce Mountain - 5.5 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Le Suffren Hotel &amp; Marina is Mahebourg (MRU-Sir Seewoosagur Ramgoolam Intl.) - 35.6 km / 22.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Le Suffren Hotel And Marina is Mahebourg (MRU-Sir Seewoosagur Ramgoolam Intl.) - 35.9 km / 22.3 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>