<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11542468</Id><Name>Ole Tai Sam Un Hotel</Name><Region><Id>17366</Id><Name>Macau</Name><CityId>17366</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Rua Da Caldeira</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Macau</City><State /><Zip>853</Zip><Country>Macau</Country><Tel>+853 28938818</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Ole Tai Sam Un Hotel, you'll be centrally located in Macau, steps from Yuet Tung Ferry Terminal and minutes from Senado Square. This hotel is close to Ruins of St. Paul's Cathedral and Fortaleza do Monte.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 40 air-conditioned rooms featuring LCD televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include blackout drapes/curtains, as well as phones with free local calls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and complimentary babysitting/childcare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Ole Tai Sam Un Hotel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, luggage storage, and a safe deposit box at the front desk.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Ole Tai Sam Un Hotel. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and complimentary babysitting/childcare. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 40 air-conditioned rooms featuring LCD televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include blackout drapes/curtains, as well as phones with free local calls.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Ole Tai Sam Un Hotel, you'll be centrally located in Macau, steps from Yuet Tung Ferry Terminal and minutes from Senado Square. This hotel is close to Ruins of St. Paul's Cathedral and Fortaleza do Monte. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Yuet Tung Ferry Terminal - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Senado Square - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Leal Senado - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Holy House of Mercy - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sir Robert Ho Tung Library - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Dominic's Church - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Augustine's Square - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Joseph's Seminary and Church - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dom Pedro V Theatre - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Augustine's Church - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lou Kau Mansion - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Macau Cathedral - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ruins of St. Paul's Cathedral - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Na Tcha Temple - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Macau Legislative Assembly Building - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Ole Tai Sam Un Hotel is Macau (MFM-Macau Intl.) - 5.7 km / 3.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>