<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11544083</Id><Name>Pereybere Hotel and Apartments</Name><Region><Id>264141</Id><Name>Mauritius</Name><CityId>264141</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Pereybere Hotel &amp;amp; Apartments</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Pereybere</City><State /><Zip /><Country>Mauritius</Country><Tel>2638165 / 2638320</Tel><Fax>+230 263 6353</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Pereybere Hotel and Apartments places you in the heart of Pereybere, steps from Pereybere Beach and close to Merville Beach.  This family-friendly aparthotel is within close proximity of Bain Boeuf Beach and Grand Bay Beach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 40 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring DVD players and LCD televisions. Your Select Comfort bed comes with down comforters and Egyptian cotton sheets. Rooms have private furnished balconies. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature hair dryers and slippers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take time to pamper yourself with a visit to the full-service spa. If you're looking for recreational opportunities, you'll find an outdoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna. This Mediterranean aparthotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and a television in the lobby. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant or in a coffee shop/café. Or stay in and take advantage of the aparthotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, limo/town car service, and express check-in. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 10 AM  Check-out time is 12:30 PM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant or in a coffee shop/café. Or stay in and take advantage of the aparthotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take time to pamper yourself with a visit to the full-service spa. If you're looking for recreational opportunities, you'll find an outdoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna. This Mediterranean aparthotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and a television in the lobby. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 40 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring DVD players and LCD televisions. Your Select Comfort bed comes with down comforters and Egyptian cotton sheets. Rooms have private furnished balconies. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature hair dryers and slippers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Pereybere Hotel and Apartments places you in the heart of Pereybere, steps from Pereybere Beach and close to Merville Beach.  This family-friendly aparthotel is within close proximity of Bain Boeuf Beach and Grand Bay Beach. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Pereybere Beach - 0.1 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;Merville Beach - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bain Boeuf Beach - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Grand Bay Beach - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Grand Bay Shopping Center - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cap Malheureux Beach - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;La Croisette - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Red Roof Chapel - 3.3 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Blue Water Diving Center - 4.1 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Canonnier Beach - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mont Choisy Beach - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Anse la Raie - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Calodyne Beach - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Trou aux Biches Beach - 6.7 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maheswarnath - 6.8 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Pereybere Hotel and Apartments is Mahebourg (MRU-Sir Seewoosagur Ramgoolam Intl.) - 49.5 km / 30.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CurrencyExchangeService</Code><Text>Currency Exchange Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Doctoroncall</Code><Text>Doctor on call</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>