<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11544746</Id><Name>Holiday Inn Athens-university Area</Name><Region><Id>124356</Id><Name>Athens</Name><CityId>19614</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>197 E. Broad St.</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Athens</City><State>Alabama</State><Zip>30603</Zip><Country>USA</Country><Tel>+17065494433</Tel><Fax>+17065483031</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>0</CountRooms></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1257132-325292922063190051_Thumb.jpg</Url><Width>100</Width><Height>100</Height><Bytes>2568</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1257132-325292922063190051_Thumb.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1687</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Quaint College Town Entertains Athens Hotel's Guests Adjacent to the campus of UGA, the Holiday Inn Athens - University Area hotel's location affords guests numerous opportunities. Not only is the hotel close to campus, but it also exudes the vibrant, exciting atmosphere that is so apparent in downtown Athens, GA. The hotel's business guests appreciate the convenient downtown Athens setting. In addition to being the closest hotel to the campus of UGA, we're near a number of area companies, including Weyerhaeuser, Carrier Transicold and Eaton Corp, as well as Athens Regional Medical Center and St. Mary's Hospital. Athens - Ben Epps Airport (AHN) is also within four miles of the hotel's location. Downtown Athens, GA provides the hotel's guests with all kinds of entertainment. In keeping with the college spirit of Athens, the city's downtown buzzes with activity in bars, clubs, restaurants, shops and more. When guests are not enjoying UGA Bulldogs' sporting events, they can catch a show at the Classic Center or visit historic sites throughout the city. Visitors to the State Botanical Garden of Georgia find it easy to become enamored with the beautiful foliage, while the Georgia Museum of Art intrigues visitors with its outstanding exhibits. This hotel has everything you need on site, from the full-service restaurant to the Business and Fitness Centers. An indoor pool and whirlpool ensure plenty of RANDR. We hope to welcome you soon!</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>Short</Type><Text>Quaint College Town Entertains Athens Hotel's Guests Adjacent to the campus of UGA; the Holiday Inn Athens - Unive</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>