<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11543944</Id><Name>Candlewood Suites Birmingham</Name><Region><Id>19386</Id><Name>Birmingham, AL</Name><CityId>19386</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>600 Corporate Ridge Drive</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Birmingham</City><State>Alabama</State><Zip>35242</Zip><Country>USA</Country><Tel>+12059910272</Tel><Fax>+12059911549</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>0</CountRooms></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1256620-52532269-1596441221_Thumb.jpg</Url><Width>100</Width><Height>100</Height><Bytes>2510</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1256620-52532269-1596441221_Thumb.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1679</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Birmingham, AL Hotel's Staff Offers Warm Hospitality An ideal and quiet location, easy access to downtown and warm Southern hospitality are why our guests choose the Candlewood Suites Birmingham hotel for their extended stay. Are you looking for a place to call home while you're in Birmingham? Our suites are the perfect answer for business travelers. A location off Hwy-280 puts all of Birmingham within minutes of us. You can get to meetings at Southern Company, Altec or Computer Science Corporation easily. Each suite offers the convenience of a spacious, functional workspace and free Wi-Fi access. And you can ask the friendly front desk staff to assist with faxes and printing. If you're headed to the heart of Dixie for vacation, then our Birmingham suites are the right choice. We're three miles from I-459, so you can be in downtown Birmingham within 15 minutes. Take an afternoon to visit the Birmingham Civil Rights Museum, the art museum or spend a day at the zoo. The Summit offers excellent shopping, too. Did we mention that Barber Motorsports Park is about 20 minutes away? Classic Southern charm and thoughtful amenities make every stay a pleasure. From the convenience of free YMCA access to an on-site Fitness Center, your daily routine can remain the same. A fully-equipped kitchen and a budget-friendly convenience store make daily meals simple during an extended stay in Birmingham, AL. Our hotel's staff is ready to welcome you home!</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>Short</Type><Text>Birmingham; AL Hotel's Staff Offers Warm Hospitality An ideal and quiet location; easy access to downtown and warm Sout</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>