<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11551890</Id><Name>Central Cosmo Apartments Brisbane</Name><Region><Id>20180</Id><Name>Brisbane City</Name><CityId>15281</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>60 Park Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Brisbane</City><State /><Zip>4064</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61-738585999</Tel><Fax>011-61-738585988</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Central Cosmo is centrally located in Milton, walking distance from Castlemaine Perkins Brewery and close to Frew Park.  This 4-star aparthotel is within close proximity of Green Flea Markets and Davies Park.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 73 guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and flat-screen televisions are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include complimentary newspapers and minibars, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities including a sauna and a fitness center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Central Cosmo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and dry cleaning/laundry services. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Central Cosmo. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities including a sauna and a fitness center. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 73 guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and flat-screen televisions are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include complimentary newspapers and minibars, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Central Cosmo is centrally located in Milton, walking distance from Castlemaine Perkins Brewery and close to Frew Park.  This 4-star aparthotel is within close proximity of Green Flea Markets and Davies Park. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Castlemaine Perkins Brewery - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Frew Park - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Green Flea Markets - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Davies Park - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Markets - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Wesley Hospital - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Suncorp Stadium - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Skyneedle - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gallery of Modern Art - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;State Library of Queensland - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queensland Art Gallery - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queensland Museum - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queensland Museum and Sciencentre - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queensland Performing Arts Centre - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brisbane Convention and Exhibition Centre - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Central Cosmo is Brisbane, QLD (BNE) - 14.9 km / 9.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>