<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11551862</Id><Name>The Limes Hotel Brisbane</Name><Region><Id>20180</Id><Name>Brisbane City</Name><CityId>15281</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>142 Constance Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Brisbane</City><State /><Zip>4006</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>617 3852 9000</Tel><Fax>617 3852 9099</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Limes Hotel in Fortitude Valley, you'll be in the business district and minutes from Tivoli and Brunswick Street Mall.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of RNA Showgrounds and Chinatown Mall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 21 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and minibars. LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include limo/town car service, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and dry cleaning/laundry services.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 21 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and minibars. LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Limes Hotel in Fortitude Valley, you'll be in the business district and minutes from Tivoli and Brunswick Street Mall.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of RNA Showgrounds and Chinatown Mall. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Tivoli - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brunswick Street Mall - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;RNA Showgrounds - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chinatown Mall - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Emporium - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Institute of Modern Art - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Judith Wright Centre of Contemporary Arts - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Centenary Place - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Twelfth Night Theatre - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Children's Hospital - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Story Bridge - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. John's Anglican Cathedral - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brisbane Customs House - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Perry Park - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;ANZAC Square War Memorial - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Limes Hotel is Brisbane, QLD (BNE) - 11.4 km / 7.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>NightClub</Code><Text>Night Club</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>