<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11553580</Id><Name>Blue Seas Resort</Name><Region><Id>15282</Id><Name>Broome</Name><CityId>15282</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>10 Sanctuary Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Broome</City><State /><Zip>6725</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61 8 9192 0999</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Blue Seas Resort in Cable Beach, you'll be near the airport and close to Sun Pictures and Courthouse Markets.  This 4.5-star aparthotel is within close proximity of Pearl Luggers Museum and Matso's Brewery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and microwaves. Satellite programming and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include separate sitting areas and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. This aparthotel also features a picnic area and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and laundry facilities. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge at scheduled times, and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. This aparthotel also features a picnic area and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and microwaves. Satellite programming and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include separate sitting areas and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Blue Seas Resort in Cable Beach, you'll be near the airport and close to Sun Pictures and Courthouse Markets.  This 4.5-star aparthotel is within close proximity of Pearl Luggers Museum and Matso's Brewery. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Sun Pictures - 3.8 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Courthouse Markets - 3.8 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pearl Luggers Museum - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Matso's Brewery - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bedford Memorial Park - 4.3 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Broome Historical Society Museum - 4.6 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Town Beach - 4.9 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;McDaniel's Lookout - 4.9 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Broome Golf Club - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gantheaume Point - 6.4 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Willie Creek Pearl Farm - 18.9 km / 11.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eco Beach - 46.5 km / 28.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Osprey Rock - 46.7 km / 29 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Blue Seas Resort is Broome, WA (BME-Broome Intl.) - 3 km / 1.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>