<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11552563</Id><Name>Oaks Mon Komo</Name><Region><Id>20180</Id><Name>Brisbane City</Name><CityId>15281</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>99 Marine Parade</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Brisbane</City><State /><Zip>4020</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>07 32839300</Tel><Fax>+61 (07) 32839399</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Oaks Mon Komo in Redcliffe, you'll be by the ocean and minutes from Settlement Cove Lagoon and Bluewater Square. This 4.5-star aparthotel is within close proximity of Bee Gees Way and Redcliffe Museum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 70 air-conditioned rooms featuring DVD players and flat-screen televisions. Cable programming provides entertainment, and wired and wireless Internet access is available for a surcharge. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and irons/ironing boards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreational amenities such as an outdoor pool and a fitness center. Additional amenities include wireless Internet access (surcharge) and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Oaks Mon Komo. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include high-speed (wired) Internet access (surcharge), dry cleaning/laundry services, and an elevator (lift). Event facilities at this aparthotel consist of a conference center and meeting rooms. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Oaks Mon Komo. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreational amenities such as an outdoor pool and a fitness center. Additional amenities include wireless Internet access (surcharge) and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 70 air-conditioned rooms featuring DVD players and flat-screen televisions. Cable programming provides entertainment, and wired and wireless Internet access is available for a surcharge. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and irons/ironing boards.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Oaks Mon Komo in Redcliffe, you'll be by the ocean and minutes from Settlement Cove Lagoon and Bluewater Square. This 4.5-star aparthotel is within close proximity of Bee Gees Way and Redcliffe Museum. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Settlement Cove Lagoon - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bluewater Square - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bee Gees Way - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Redcliffe Museum - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Redcliffe Jetty Markets - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sutton's Beach - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Redcliffe Showgrounds - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Redcliffe Botanic Gardens - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Scarborough Marina - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Redcliffe Golf Club - 4.8 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Alma Park Zoo - 12.8 km / 7.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brisbane Entertainment Centre - 13.1 km / 8.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Boondall Ice Rink - 13.4 km / 8.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Centro Taigum - 15 km / 9.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Joseph's Nudgee College - 15.2 km / 9.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Oaks Mon Komo is Brisbane, QLD (BNE) - 17.1 km / 10.6 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>