<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11552206</Id><Name>Annerley Motor Inn Brisbane</Name><Region><Id>20180</Id><Name>Brisbane City</Name><CityId>15281</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>591 Ipswich Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Brisbane</City><State /><Zip>4103</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61 7  3892 1500</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Annerley Motor Inn in Annerley, you'll be close to Greenslopes Private Hospital and The Gabba. This motel is within close proximity of Princess Alexandra Hospital and University of Queensland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 27 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool or make use of other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, express check-out, and luggage storage. RV/bus/truck parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy the recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool or make use of other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 27 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Annerley Motor Inn in Annerley, you'll be close to Greenslopes Private Hospital and The Gabba. This motel is within close proximity of Princess Alexandra Hospital and University of Queensland. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Greenslopes Private Hospital - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Princess Alexandra Hospital - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Queensland - 2.8 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Gabba - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mater Private Hospital Brisbane - 3.6 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queensland Maritime Museum - 3.8 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;West End Ferry Terminal - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Griffith University South Bank - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Goodwill Bridge - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kangaroo Point Cliffs - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;South Bank Lifestyle Market - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Southbank Parklands - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brisbane Convention and Exhibition Centre - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Southbank Institute of Technology - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;QUT Old Government House - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Annerley Motor Inn is Brisbane, QLD (BNE) - 17 km / 10.6 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>