<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11551854</Id><Name>Toowong Central Motel Brisbane</Name><Region><Id>20180</Id><Name>Brisbane City</Name><CityId>15281</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>38 Jephson Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Brisbane</City><State /><Zip>4066</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61 7 38703522</Tel><Fax>61 7 38703576</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Toowong Central Motel in Toowong (Inner West), you'll be minutes from Toowong Village and close to Sir Thomas Brisbane Planetarium.  This family-friendly motel is within close proximity of The Wesley Hospital and West End Ferry Terminal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 28 guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and stovetops. Rooms have private furnished balconies. Flat-screen televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and microwaves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and babysitting/childcare (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-out, dry cleaning/laundry services, and multilingual staff. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 28 guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and stovetops. Rooms have private furnished balconies. Flat-screen televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and microwaves.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Toowong Central Motel in Toowong (Inner West), you'll be minutes from Toowong Village and close to Sir Thomas Brisbane Planetarium.  This family-friendly motel is within close proximity of The Wesley Hospital and West End Ferry Terminal. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Toowong Village - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Wesley Hospital - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;West End Ferry Terminal - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mt Coot-Tha Gardens - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tsuki-yama-chisen Japanese Garden - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Davies Park - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Green Flea Markets - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sir Thomas Brisbane Planetarium - 1.7 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Frew Park - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mt. Coot-Tha - 2 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Castlemaine Perkins Brewery - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Markets - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Skyneedle - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Queensland - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Suncorp Stadium - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Toowong Central Motel is Brisbane, QLD (BNE) - 16.7 km / 10.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>