<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11556053</Id><Name>Clifton Sands Holiday Units</Name><Region><Id>20182</Id><Name>Cairns</Name><CityId>15284</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>87 Guide Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Cairns</City><State /><Zip>4879</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>07 4055 3355</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Clifton Sands Holiday Apartments in Clifton Beach, you'll be by the ocean and minutes from Clifton Beach and close to Cairns Tropical Zoo.  This family-friendly apartment is within the vicinity of Palm Cove Beach and Half Moon Bay Golf Course.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 18 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies or patios. LCD televisions with satellite programming are available for your entertainment, and DVD players are also provided. Conveniences include phones, as well as microwaves and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss out on recreational opportunities including an outdoor pool and bicycles to rent. This apartment also features wireless Internet access (surcharge), tour/ticket assistance, and a picnic area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include multilingual staff, luggage storage, and laundry facilities. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Don’t miss out on recreational opportunities including an outdoor pool and bicycles to rent. This apartment also features wireless Internet access (surcharge), tour/ticket assistance, and a picnic area. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 18 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies or patios. LCD televisions with satellite programming are available for your entertainment, and DVD players are also provided. Conveniences include phones, as well as microwaves and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Clifton Sands Holiday Apartments in Clifton Beach, you'll be by the ocean and minutes from Clifton Beach and close to Cairns Tropical Zoo.  This family-friendly apartment is within the vicinity of Palm Cove Beach and Half Moon Bay Golf Course. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Clifton Beach - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palm Cove Beach - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cairns Tropical Zoo - 3.5 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Half Moon Bay Golf Course - 6.2 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Yorkeys Knob Beach - 6.5 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tjapukai Cultural Park - 7.1 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Skyrail Rainforest Cableway - 7.1 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kuranda Koala Gardens - 7.2 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cattana Wetlands - 7.3 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tjapukai Aboriginal Cultural Park - 9.1 km / 5.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Barron Gorge National Park - 11.5 km / 7.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Great Barrier Reef - 13.6 km / 8.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hartley's Crocodile Adventures - 13.6 km / 8.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Skydive The Reef Cairns - 14.6 km / 9.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mount Whitfield Conservation Park - 16 km / 9.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Clifton Sands Holiday Apartments is Cairns, QLD (CNS-Cairns Intl.) - 14.5 km / 9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>