<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11553647</Id><Name>Q Resorts Gabba Central Apartments</Name><Region><Id>20180</Id><Name>Brisbane City</Name><CityId>15281</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>803 Stanley Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Brisbane</City><State /><Zip>4102</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61-738913155</Tel><Fax>61-738913255</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Gabba Central Apartments in Woolloongabba, you'll be minutes from The Gabba and close to Brisbane Convention and Exhibition Centre. This 4-star apartment is within close proximity of Mater Private Hospital Brisbane and Kangaroo Point Cliffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned guestrooms. Complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers and irons/ironing boards, and housekeeping is provided weekly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including an outdoor pool, an indoor pool, and a sauna. Additional amenities include gift shops/newsstands, a hair salon, and shopping on site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Gabba Central Apartments, or find a snack in a coffee shop/café.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, dry cleaning/laundry services, and luggage storage. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed    Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Gabba Central Apartments, or find a snack in a coffee shop/café. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including an outdoor pool, an indoor pool, and a sauna. Additional amenities include gift shops/newsstands, a hair salon, and shopping on site. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned guestrooms. Complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers and irons/ironing boards, and housekeeping is provided weekly.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Gabba Central Apartments in Woolloongabba, you'll be minutes from The Gabba and close to Brisbane Convention and Exhibition Centre. This 4-star apartment is within close proximity of Mater Private Hospital Brisbane and Kangaroo Point Cliffs. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;The Gabba - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mater Private Hospital Brisbane - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kangaroo Point Cliffs - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Goodwill Bridge - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queensland Maritime Museum - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;QUT Old Government House - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queensland University of Technology - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Griffith University South Bank - 1.4 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Vincent's Hospital Brisbane - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Princess Alexandra Hospital - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Southbank Parklands - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;South Bank Lifestyle Market - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brisbane Parliament House - 1.5 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brisbane Botanic Gardens - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queensland Conservatorium - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Gabba Central Apartments is Brisbane, QLD (BNE) - 14 km / 8.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BeautyShop</Code><Text>Beauty Shop</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>