<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>115569</Id><Name>Villa Ambrosina</Name><Region><Id>20939</Id><Name>Florence City</Name><CityId>17090</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>VIA MONTEBUONI - LOC. TAVARNUZZE 95</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>IMPRUNETA</City><State /><Zip>50029</Zip><Country>ITALY</Country><Tel>00390552020491</Tel><Fax>0039055020492</Fax><Email>INFO@LAVALLOMBROSINA.IT</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>43.705108</Latitude><Longitude>11.212202</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/57/25/4/57254-GEN-1.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>234</Height><Bytes>16085</Bytes><Caption>General</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/57/25/4/57254-GEN-1thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>95</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2298</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/57/25/4/57254-HAB-2.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>209</Height><Bytes>12399</Bytes><Caption>Room</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/57/25/4/57254-HAB-2thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>107</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2192</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/57/25/4/57254-RES-4.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>214</Height><Bytes>13889</Bytes><Caption>Restaurant</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/57/25/4/57254-RES-4thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>104</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2404</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/57/25/4/57254-TER-3.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>211</Height><Bytes>21518</Bytes><Caption>Terrace</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/57/25/4/57254-TER-3thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>106</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2921</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Villa Ambrosina in Impruneta (Tavarnuzze), you'll be convenient to World War II Florence American Cemetery and Memorial and Florence Charterhouse. This hotel is within close proximity of Certosa Museum and Piazza Niccolo Acciaioli.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 37 air-conditioned guestrooms. Satellite programming provides entertainment, and wired and wireless Internet access is available for a surcharge. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a spa tub or take in the view from a rooftop terrace and a garden. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves lunch and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, express check-in, and a 24-hour front desk. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 1 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves lunch and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a spa tub or take in the view from a rooftop terrace and a garden. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 37 air-conditioned guestrooms. Satellite programming provides entertainment, and wired and wireless Internet access is available for a surcharge. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Villa Ambrosina in Impruneta (Tavarnuzze), you'll be convenient to World War II Florence American Cemetery and Memorial and Florence Charterhouse. This hotel is within close proximity of Certosa Museum and Piazza Niccolo Acciaioli. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;World War II Florence American Cemetery and Memorial - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Florence Charterhouse - 2.8 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Certosa Museum - 3 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza Niccolo Acciaioli - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Villa del Poggio Imperiale - 5.8 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Arcetri Observatory - 6 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Circolo Golf Ugolino - 6.6 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Boboli Gardens - 6.6 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Porta Romana - 6.6 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museo Zoologico La Specola - 7.2 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Galleria d'Arte Moderna - 7.4 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pitti Palace - 7.4 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gallery of Modern Art - 7.4 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palatine Gallery - 7.4 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza Santo Spirito - 7.4 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Villa Ambrosina is Florence (FLR-Peretola) - 10.9 km / 6.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Hotel Villa Ambrosina is Florence (FLR-Peretola) - 10.9 km / 6.7 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HandicapAccessible</Code><Text>Handicap accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVRoom</Code><Text>TV Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WLANAccessPoint</Code><Text>WLAN Access Point</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomTerraceBalcony</Code><Text>Terrace or balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>