<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11553626</Id><Name>Alexandra Lodge Bundaberg</Name><Region><Id>15283</Id><Name>Bundaberg</Name><CityId>15283</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>77 Woondooma Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Bundaberg</City><State /><Zip>4670</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>1800658565</Tel><Fax>61 7 41532294</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Alexandra Lodge in Bundaberg, you'll be near the airport and minutes from Bundaberg Tourist Information Centre and Buss Park. This bed &amp; breakfast is within close proximity of Bundaberg Regional Art Gallery and Bundaberg and District Historical Museum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 7 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Bathrooms with showers are provided. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers and irons/ironing boards, and housekeeping is provided weekly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, express check-out, and laundry facilities. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 7 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Bathrooms with showers are provided. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers and irons/ironing boards, and housekeeping is provided weekly.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Alexandra Lodge in Bundaberg, you'll be near the airport and minutes from Bundaberg Tourist Information Centre and Buss Park. This bed &amp; breakfast is within close proximity of Bundaberg Regional Art Gallery and Bundaberg and District Historical Museum. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Bundaberg Tourist Information Centre - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Buss Park - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bundaberg Regional Art Gallery - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bundaberg and District Historical Museum - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sugarland Shoppingtown - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kelly's Beach - 13.6 km / 8.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Neilson Park - 13.8 km / 8.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bargara Beach - 13.8 km / 8.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Innes Park - 14 km / 8.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Life Savers Park - 15.9 km / 9.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Burrum Coast National Park - 21.3 km / 13.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Alexandra Lodge is Bundaberg, QLD (BDB) - 3.8 km / 2.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>