<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11552179</Id><Name>Essence Apartments Brisbane</Name><Region><Id>20180</Id><Name>Brisbane City</Name><CityId>15281</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>541 Rode Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Brisbane</City><State /><Zip>4032</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>617 3613 7400</Tel><Fax>07 32564042</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Chermside, Essence Serviced Apartments is in the business district and minutes from The Prince Charles Hospital and Holy Spirit Northside Private Hospital.  This 4.5-star apartment is within close proximity of Westfield Chermside and 7th Brigade Park.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 60 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and flat-screen televisions are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and microwaves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby. Additional features include tour/ticket assistance, barbecue grills, and complimentary use of a nearby fitness facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, laundry facilities, and an elevator (lift). Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby. Additional features include tour/ticket assistance, barbecue grills, and complimentary use of a nearby fitness facility. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 60 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and flat-screen televisions are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and microwaves.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Chermside, Essence Serviced Apartments is in the business district and minutes from The Prince Charles Hospital and Holy Spirit Northside Private Hospital.  This 4.5-star apartment is within close proximity of Westfield Chermside and 7th Brigade Park. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;The Prince Charles Hospital - 0.1 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;Holy Spirit Northside Private Hospital - 0.1 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;Westfield Chermside - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;7th Brigade Park - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Big Easy Golf Driving Range - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Centro Taigum - 5.1 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Joseph's Nudgee College - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albion Park Raceway - 5.7 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Perry Park - 5.7 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ballymore Stadium - 5.7 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eagle Farm Racecourse - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Newstead House - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Twelfth Night Theatre - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Doomben Racecourse - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Children's Hospital - 6.4 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Essence Serviced Apartments is Brisbane, QLD (BNE) - 9.4 km / 5.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>GameRoom</Code><Text>GameRoom</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>