<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11556044</Id><Name>Marlin Waters Beachfront Apartments</Name><Region><Id>20184</Id><Name>Palm Cove</Name><CityId>15284</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>131-133 Williams Esplanade</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Palm Cove</City><State /><Zip>4879</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>0740553933</Tel><Fax>0740553935</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Marlin Waters in Palm Cove, you'll be on the beach and minutes from Palm Cove Beach and close to Cairns Tropical Zoo.  This 4-star apartment is within the vicinity of Clifton Beach and Half Moon Bay Golf Course.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 20 individually furnished guestrooms, featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. 38-inch LCD televisions with premium TV channels provide entertainment, while wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as microwaves and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including wireless Internet access (surcharge) and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include laundry facilities, a library, and an elevator (lift). Guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle for a surcharge, and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 1 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including wireless Internet access (surcharge) and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 20 individually furnished guestrooms, featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. 38-inch LCD televisions with premium TV channels provide entertainment, while wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as microwaves and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Marlin Waters in Palm Cove, you'll be on the beach and minutes from Palm Cove Beach and close to Cairns Tropical Zoo.  This 4-star apartment is within the vicinity of Clifton Beach and Half Moon Bay Golf Course. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Palm Cove Beach - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cairns Tropical Zoo - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Clifton Beach - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Half Moon Bay Golf Course - 8.9 km / 5.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Yorkeys Knob Beach - 8.9 km / 5.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kuranda Koala Gardens - 9.4 km / 5.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tjapukai Cultural Park - 10.1 km / 6.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Skyrail Rainforest Cableway - 10.1 km / 6.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cattana Wetlands - 10.2 km / 6.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hartley's Crocodile Adventures - 11.4 km / 7.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Great Barrier Reef - 11.6 km / 7.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tjapukai Aboriginal Cultural Park - 12 km / 7.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Barron Gorge National Park - 14.3 km / 8.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Skydive The Reef Cairns - 17.4 km / 10.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mount Whitfield Conservation Park - 18.8 km / 11.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Marlin Waters is Cairns, QLD (CNS-Cairns Intl.) - 17.3 km / 10.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>