<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11551857</Id><Name>Ambassador Motor Inn Brisbane</Name><Region><Id>20180</Id><Name>Brisbane City</Name><CityId>15281</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>180 Gladstone Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Brisbane</City><State /><Zip>4101</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>1800629134</Tel><Fax>61 07 38462031</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Ambassador Motor Inn is a popular choice amongst travelers in Brisbane, whether exploring or just passing through. Featuring a complete list of amenities, guests will find their stay at the property a comfortable one. Take advantage of the hotel's free Wi-Fi in all rooms, facilities for disabled guests, express check-in/check-out, luggage storage, Wi-Fi in public areas. Guestrooms are designed to provide an optimal level of comfort with welcoming decor and some offering convenient amenities like internet access – wireless, internet access – wireless (complimentary), non smoking rooms, air conditioning, desk. Recuperate from a full day of sightseeing in the comfort of your room or take advantage of the hotel's recreational facilities, including outdoor pool, garden. Friendly staff, great facilities and close proximity to all that Brisbane has to offer are three great reasons you should stay at Ambassador Motor Inn. &lt;br/&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>Short</Type><Text>Ambassador Motor Inn is a popular choice amongst travelers in Brisbane, whether exploring or just pa &lt;br/&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>