<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11551867</Id><Name>Abbey Apartments Brisbane</Name><Region><Id>20180</Id><Name>Brisbane City</Name><CityId>15281</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>160 Roma Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Brisbane</City><State /><Zip>4000</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61-732-360-600</Tel><Fax>61-732-360-333</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Abbey on Roma Hotel &amp; Apartments in Brisbane, you'll be minutes from Roma Street Parkland and Brisbane Private Hospital.  This family-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Tower Mill and Brisbane City Hall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Rooms have private balconies. High-speed (wired) Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have shower/tub combinations and complimentary toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities, including an outdoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna. Additional features include babysitting/childcare (surcharge) and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at a coffee shop/café serving guests of Abbey on Roma Hotel &amp; Apartments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include high-speed (wired) Internet access (surcharge), dry cleaning/laundry services, and luggage storage. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at a coffee shop/café serving guests of Abbey on Roma Hotel &amp; Apartments. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities, including an outdoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna. Additional features include babysitting/childcare (surcharge) and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Rooms have private balconies. High-speed (wired) Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have shower/tub combinations and complimentary toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Abbey on Roma Hotel &amp; Apartments in Brisbane, you'll be minutes from Roma Street Parkland and Brisbane Private Hospital.  This family-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Tower Mill and Brisbane City Hall. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Roma Street Parkland - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brisbane Private Hospital - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tower Mill - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brisbane City Hall - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gallery of Modern Art - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;King George Square - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;State Library of Queensland - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of Brisbane - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queensland Art Gallery - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queen Street Mall - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queensland Museum - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Treasury Casino - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queensland Museum and Sciencentre - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;ANZAC Square War Memorial - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Stephens Cathedral - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Abbey on Roma Hotel &amp; Apartments is Brisbane, QLD (BNE) - 13.4 km / 8.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>