<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11567093</Id><Name>Victor Apartments</Name><Region><Id>20206</Id><Name>Victor Harbor</Name><CityId>15307</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>10 Adare Avenue</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Victor Harbor</City><State /><Zip>5211</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61 8 8410 8189</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Victor Apartments offers accommodations throughout the area in McCracken.   &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 9 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchens with refrigerators and microwaves. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Rooms have private balconies or patios. Digital television is provided for your entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as a fireplace in the lobby and tour/ticket assistance. Additional amenities at this Beaux Arts apartment include a picnic area and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include luggage storage, laundry facilities, and a library. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as a fireplace in the lobby and tour/ticket assistance. Additional amenities at this Beaux Arts apartment include a picnic area and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 9 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchens with refrigerators and microwaves. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Rooms have private balconies or patios. Digital television is provided for your entertainment.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Victor Apartments offers accommodations throughout the area in McCracken.   &amp;nbsp; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;p&gt;Accommodations are located at multiple addresses. Regional attractions include:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hindmarsh River Estuary Boardwalk&lt;br /&gt;McCracken Golf Course&lt;br /&gt;Victor Harbor Convention Centre&lt;br /&gt;Greenhills Adventure Park&lt;br /&gt;Soldier Memorial Gardens&lt;br /&gt;Warland Reserve&lt;br /&gt;Granite Island&lt;br /&gt;Victor Harbor Golf Club&lt;br /&gt;Goolwa Golf Course&lt;br /&gt;Artworx Gallery&lt;br /&gt;Ballast Stone Estate Winery&lt;br /&gt;Currency Creek Estate Wines&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Victor Apartments is Adelaide, SA (ADL). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>