<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11567328</Id><Name>Cedar Creek Lodges Gold Coast</Name><Region><Id>20214</Id><Name>North Gold Coast</Name><CityId>15311</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Corner Cedar Creek Falls Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Gold Coast</City><State /><Zip>4272</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61 7 5545 1468</Tel><Fax>61 7 5545 2707</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in North Tamborine, Cedar Creek Lodges is in a national park and minutes from Thunderbird Park and Tamborine National Park Cedar Creek Section. This 4-star lodge is within close proximity of Tamborine National Park Knoll Section and Tamborine Mountain Distillery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the guestrooms featuring refrigerators and microwaves. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as separate sitting areas and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at one of the lodge's 2 restaurants. Breakfast is available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The front desk is staffed during limited hours. This lodge has 3 meeting rooms available for events. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at one of the lodge's 2 restaurants. Breakfast is available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the guestrooms featuring refrigerators and microwaves. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as separate sitting areas and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in North Tamborine, Cedar Creek Lodges is in a national park and minutes from Thunderbird Park and Tamborine National Park Cedar Creek Section. This 4-star lodge is within close proximity of Tamborine National Park Knoll Section and Tamborine Mountain Distillery. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Thunderbird Park - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tamborine National Park Cedar Creek Section - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tamborine National Park Knoll Section - 1.7 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tamborine Mountain Distillery - 2.8 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tamborine National Park Joalah Section - 3 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tamborine National Park MacDonald Section - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tamborine National Park Palm Grove Section - 3.8 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mount Tamborine Winery - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tamborine National Park Witches Falls Section - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cedar Creek Estate Vineyard and Winery - 4.1 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Movie World - 12.9 km / 8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Australian Outback Spectacular - 13.1 km / 8.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wet'n'Wild Water World - 13.6 km / 8.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;WhiteWater World - 13.9 km / 8.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dreamworld - 14.1 km / 8.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Cedar Creek Lodges is Gold Coast, QLD (OOL-Coolangatta) - 44 km / 27.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>