<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11566499</Id><Name>Bentleigh Motor Inn</Name><Region><Id>15289</Id><Name>Coffs Harbour</Name><CityId>15289</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>94-96 Grafton Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Coffs Harbour</City><State /><Zip>2450</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61-266-522-566</Tel><Fax>61-266-529-424</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;In the heart of Coffs Harbour, Bentleigh Motor Inn is close to Coffs Harbour Golf Club and Tabatinga Family Fun Centre.  This family-friendly motel is within close proximity of Coffs Harbour Racecourse and Dolphin Marine Magic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 33 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and flat-screen televisions. Satellite programming and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as microwaves and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Cooked-to-order breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, dry cleaning/laundry services, and luggage storage. Planning an event in Coffs Harbour? This motel has facilities measuring 1722 square feet (160 square meters), including a meeting room. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 1 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Cooked-to-order breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 33 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and flat-screen televisions. Satellite programming and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as microwaves and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>In the heart of Coffs Harbour, Bentleigh Motor Inn is close to Coffs Harbour Golf Club and Tabatinga Family Fun Centre.  This family-friendly motel is within close proximity of Coffs Harbour Racecourse and Dolphin Marine Magic. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Coffs Harbour Golf Club - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tabatinga Family Fun Centre - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Coffs Harbour Racecourse - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dolphin Marine Magic - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Coffs Harbour Marina - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Big Banana Coffs Harbour - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Diggers Beach - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Coffs Harbour Butterfly House - 8.7 km / 5.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Guru Nanak Sikh Temple - 21.1 km / 13.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Woolgoolga Beach - 22.8 km / 14.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Woolgoolga Golf Course - 23.6 km / 14.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Corindi River Park - 36.3 km / 22.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Red Rock Beach - 36.6 km / 22.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Bentleigh Motor Inn is Coffs Harbour, NSW (CFS) - 3.2 km / 2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>