<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11569509</Id><Name>Diamond Sands Resort Gold Coast</Name><Region><Id>20210</Id><Name>Burleigh Heads</Name><CityId>15311</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>2320 Gold Coast Highway</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Gold Coast</City><State /><Zip>4218</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61 7 55255199</Tel><Fax>61 7 55255199</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Diamond Sands Resort in Mermaid Beach, you'll be by the ocean and convenient to Putt Putt Golf Mermaid Beach and Jupiters Casino. This family-friendly apartment is within close proximity of Pizzey Park Sporting Complex and Burleigh Golf Club.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 55 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Your room comes with a Select Comfort bed. Rooms have private patios. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities including an outdoor pool and a spa tub. Additional amenities include wireless Internet access (surcharge), babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and an arcade/game room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The front desk is staffed during limited hours. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge at scheduled times, and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities including an outdoor pool and a spa tub. Additional amenities include wireless Internet access (surcharge), babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and an arcade/game room. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 55 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Your room comes with a Select Comfort bed. Rooms have private patios. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Diamond Sands Resort in Mermaid Beach, you'll be by the ocean and convenient to Putt Putt Golf Mermaid Beach and Jupiters Casino. This family-friendly apartment is within close proximity of Pizzey Park Sporting Complex and Burleigh Golf Club. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Putt Putt Golf Mermaid Beach - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pizzey Park Sporting Complex - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Burleigh Golf Club - 1.7 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gold Coast Seniors Tennis Club - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dracula's Queensland - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pacific Fair Shopping Centre - 2.2 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Broadbeach Sports and Recreation Centre - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Oracle Boulevard - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jupiters Casino - 2.5 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pratten Park - 2.5 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kurrawa Beach - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Oasis Shopping Centre - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Broadbeach Mall - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gold Coast Convention and Exhibition Centre - 2.8 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bond University - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Diamond Sands Resort is Gold Coast, QLD (OOL-Coolangatta) - 14.7 km / 9.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>GameRoom</Code><Text>GameRoom</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>