<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11567192</Id><Name>Swansea Beach Chalets</Name><Region><Id>20202</Id><Name>Swansea</Name><CityId>15302</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>27 Shaw Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Swansea (Au)</City><State /><Zip>7190</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61-362578177</Tel><Fax>61-362578511</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Swansea, Swansea Beach Chalets is minutes from Bark Mill Museum and close to Glamorgan War Memorial.  This beach apartment is within close proximity of Waterloo Point and Kates Berry Farm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 20 guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. Digital programming and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include microwaves and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided on a limited basis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Head down to the water and enjoy a day at the private beach, or take advantage of other recreational amenities, which include an outdoor pool. This apartment also features complimentary wireless Internet access, tour/ticket assistance, and a picnic area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include luggage storage and laundry facilities. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Head down to the water and enjoy a day at the private beach, or take advantage of other recreational amenities, which include an outdoor pool. This apartment also features complimentary wireless Internet access, tour/ticket assistance, and a picnic area. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 20 guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. Digital programming and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include microwaves and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided on a limited basis.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Swansea, Swansea Beach Chalets is minutes from Bark Mill Museum and close to Glamorgan War Memorial.  This beach apartment is within close proximity of Waterloo Point and Kates Berry Farm. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Bark Mill Museum - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Glamorgan War Memorial - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Waterloo Point - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kates Berry Farm - 3.3 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Spring Vale Wines - 10.3 km / 6.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gala Estate Winery - 12.5 km / 7.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Freycinet Vineyards - 18.5 km / 11.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wineglass Bay - 19.4 km / 12.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Freycinet National Park - 19.7 km / 12.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maria Island Ferry - 45.4 km / 28.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maria Island National Park - 51.1 km / 31.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Four Mile Creek Lookout - 66.1 km / 41 mi &lt;br /&gt;Henderson Lagoon - 70.3 km / 43.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Scamander River Golf Club - 75.4 km / 46.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Percy Steel Reserve - 89.5 km / 55.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Swansea Beach Chalets is Hobart, TAS (HBA-Hobart Intl.) - 92.5 km / 57.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>GameRoom</Code><Text>GameRoom</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>