<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11569406</Id><Name>Kutuk by Wyndham Vacation Rentals</Name><Region><Id>19991</Id><Name>Steamboat Springs, CO</Name><CityId>19991</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>2000 Ski Time Square Drive</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Steamboat Springs</City><State>Colorado</State><Zip>80487</Zip><Country>USA</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>0</CountRooms></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1323644-photo-not-available-small.jpg</Url><Width>70</Width><Height>70</Height><Bytes>1454</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1323644-photo-not-available-small.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1454</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Kutuk is uniquely situated in Ski Time Square - convenient to the ski slopes, dining and shopping. The property has undergone a recent exterior renovation including the enclosure of its formerly open air garage and a new grand staircase leading to the clubhouse and sun deck. The Kutuk offers 2- 4- bedroom options, all moments away from the Christie Ski Lift. The individual interiors of the condos are inviting and warm with Southwestern to traditional decor. Enjoy amenities such as two outdoor hot tubs, large sun deck with gas grills, on-site complimentary ski lockers, complimentary internet and morning coffee with doughnuts. A private guest shuttle is available for convenient transportation for guests during the cold winter months. During the summer enjoy convenient access to hiking and biking trails on the mountain or simply relax on the sun deck taking in the beautiful views.Minimum age at check-in is 21. Aero-beds are available for USD 10 per night. A la carte housekeeping available for a fee (varies by service). Aero-beds are available for USD 10 per night. A la carte housekeeping available for a fee (varies by service).</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>Short</Type><Text>Kutuk is uniquely situated in Ski Time Square - convenient to the ski slopes; dining and shopping</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>