<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11569403</Id><Name>La Casa by Wyndham Vacation Rentals</Name><Region><Id>19991</Id><Name>Steamboat Springs, CO</Name><CityId>19991</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>2315 Ski Trail Lane</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Steamboat Springs</City><State>Colorado</State><Zip>80487</Zip><Country>USA</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>0</CountRooms></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1323643-photo-not-available-small.jpg</Url><Width>70</Width><Height>70</Height><Bytes>1454</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1323643-photo-not-available-small.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1454</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Located just 100 yards from the gondola and the powdery slopes, La Casa blends relaxation and recreation. Boasting high soaring ceilings, expansive multi-level space, distinguished furnishings and spectacular views of Mt. Werner from private balconies, La Casa is an ideal choice for ski vacations, intimate retreats or festive holiday gatherings. Our multi-level 2-, 3- and 4-bedroom accommodations include a washer and dryer, gas fireplace, an extra guest bath and more. Outdoor hot tubs, a shuttle service (ski season only) to shopping and dining as well as our signature guest service will ensure that you enjoy a pampered lifestyle while you’re here. With its mountainous terrain and snow-filled winters, the Steamboat Springs area offers world-class skiing and winter activities fit for the entire family and people of all ages and skill levels. Summer visitors can enjoy great hiking, biking, fishing, water sports and other outdoor activities that showcase the natural beauty of this location.Minimum age at check-in is 21. Aero-beds are available for USD 10 per night. A la carte housekeeping available for a fee (varies by service). Aero-beds are available for USD 10 per night. A la carte housekeeping available for a fee (varies by service).</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>Short</Type><Text>Located just 100 yards from the gondola and the powdery slopes; La Casa blends relaxation and recreation</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>