<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11566487</Id><Name>Smugglers On The Beach</Name><Region><Id>15289</Id><Name>Coffs Harbour</Name><CityId>15289</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>36 Sandy Beach Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Coffs Harbour</City><State /><Zip>2450</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>0266536166</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Korora, Smugglers on the Beach is by the ocean and convenient to Big Banana Coffs Harbour and Diggers Beach.  This 4-star apartment is within close proximity of Tabatinga Family Fun Centre and Dolphin Marine Magic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 16 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies or patios. 48-inch LCD televisions with digital programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as microwaves and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities including an outdoor pool and an outdoor tennis court. This apartment also features complimentary wireless Internet access and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and luggage storage. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities including an outdoor pool and an outdoor tennis court. This apartment also features complimentary wireless Internet access and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 16 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies or patios. 48-inch LCD televisions with digital programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as microwaves and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Korora, Smugglers on the Beach is by the ocean and convenient to Big Banana Coffs Harbour and Diggers Beach.  This 4-star apartment is within close proximity of Tabatinga Family Fun Centre and Dolphin Marine Magic. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Big Banana Coffs Harbour - 1.7 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Diggers Beach - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tabatinga Family Fun Centre - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dolphin Marine Magic - 4.3 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Coffs Harbour Marina - 4.8 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Coffs Harbour Racecourse - 5.5 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Coffs Harbour Golf Club - 5.8 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Coffs Harbour Butterfly House - 13.2 km / 8.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Guru Nanak Sikh Temple - 16.7 km / 10.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Woolgoolga Beach - 18.4 km / 11.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Woolgoolga Golf Course - 19.1 km / 11.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Corindi River Park - 31.9 km / 19.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Red Rock Beach - 32.2 km / 20 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Smugglers on the Beach is Coffs Harbour, NSW (CFS) - 7.4 km / 4.6 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>