<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11567802</Id><Name>Island Beach Resort Broadbeach</Name><Region><Id>20209</Id><Name>Broadbeach</Name><CityId>15311</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>9 Margaret Avenue</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Gold Coast</City><State /><Zip>4218</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>+61 7 5592 4112</Tel><Fax>+61 7 5592 4550</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Island Beach Resort is in the heart of Broadbeach, walking distance from Oracle Boulevard and Pratten Park.  This family-friendly apartment is within close proximity of Dracula's Queensland and Oasis Shopping Centre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 29 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while 32-inch flat-screen televisions with digital programming provide entertainment. Conveniences include microwaves and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided weekly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreational opportunities offered, including an outdoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and tour/ticket assistance. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, limo/town car service, and express check-in. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge at scheduled times, and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed    Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 18 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreational opportunities offered, including an outdoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and tour/ticket assistance. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 29 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while 32-inch flat-screen televisions with digital programming provide entertainment. Conveniences include microwaves and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided weekly.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Island Beach Resort is in the heart of Broadbeach, walking distance from Oracle Boulevard and Pratten Park.  This family-friendly apartment is within close proximity of Dracula's Queensland and Oasis Shopping Centre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Oracle Boulevard - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pratten Park - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dracula's Queensland - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Oasis Shopping Centre - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kurrawa Beach - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Broadbeach Mall - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jupiters Casino - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pacific Fair Shopping Centre - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gold Coast Convention and Exhibition Centre - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Putt Putt Golf Mermaid Beach - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Broadbeach Sports and Recreation Centre - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pizzey Park Sporting Complex - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Surfers Paradise Golf Club - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;SkyPoint Observation Deck - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gold Coast Seniors Tennis Club - 3.3 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Island Beach Resort is Gold Coast, QLD (OOL-Coolangatta) - 16.7 km / 10.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 18 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>