<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>115638</Id><Name>Abitart</Name><Region><Id>21037</Id><Name>Near Centre</Name><CityId>17149</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>PELLEGRINO MATTEUCCI ST</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>ROME</City><State /><Zip /><Country>ITALY</Country><Tel>0039 064543191</Tel><Fax>003906454319899</Fax><Email>info@abitarthotel.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>41.8719048</Latitude><Longitude>12.482662</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/73/75/7375-HAB-1.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>12624</Bytes><Caption>Room</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/73/75/7375-HAB-1thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2030</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/73/75/7375-HAB-2.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>14549</Bytes><Caption>Room</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/73/75/7375-HAB-2thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2329</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Abitart Hotel in Rome (Aventine), you'll be minutes from Porta San Paolo and close to Colosseum. This 4-star hotel is close to Roman Forum and St. Peter's Basilica.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 65 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and babysitting/childcare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Abitart Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary buffet breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk. This hotel has 6 meeting rooms available for events. For a surcharge, guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle (available on request) and a train station pick-up service.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Abitart Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary buffet breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and babysitting/childcare. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 65 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Abitart Hotel in Rome (Aventine), you'll be minutes from Porta San Paolo and close to Colosseum. This 4-star hotel is close to Roman Forum and St. Peter's Basilica. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Porta San Paolo - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pyramid of Caius Cestius - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Montemartini Museum - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Roma Tre University - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sant'Alessio all'Aventino - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Santa Prisca - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza dei Cavalieri di Malta - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sant'Anselmo - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Santa Sabina - 1.4 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Baths of Caracalla - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Porta Portese Market - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Savello Park - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Basilica of St. Paul Outside the Walls - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Circus Maximus - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Rome (CIA-Ciampino) - 12.2 km / 7.6 mi&lt;br /&gt;Rome (FCO-Fiumicino - Leonardo da Vinci Intl.) - 20.9 km / 13 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Abitart Hotel is Rome (FCO-Fiumicino - Leonardo da Vinci Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndoorPool</Code><Text>Indoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Garage</Code><Text>Garage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HeatedPool</Code><Text>Heated Pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SunBathingTerrace</Code><Text>Sun Bathing Terrace</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Fridge</Code><Text>Fridge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>