<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11566896</Id><Name>Eurong Beach Resort Fraser Island</Name><Region><Id>20207</Id><Name>Fraser Island</Name><CityId>15308</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Fraser Island</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Fraser Island</City><State /><Zip>4581</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>617 30322805</Tel><Fax>617 16001644</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Eurong, Eurong Beach Resort is by the ocean and within the region of Lake McKenzie and Maheno Shipwreck.  This beach motel is within the region of The Pinnacles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 124 guestrooms featuring refrigerators. Rooms have private balconies. Digital television is provided for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Dip into one of the 2 outdoor swimming pools or enjoy other recreational amenities, which include an outdoor tennis court. This motel also features wireless Internet access (surcharge), gift shops/newsstands, and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the motel's restaurant, which features a bar and a pool view. Dining is also available at a coffee shop/café. Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a beach bar. Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, luggage storage, and laundry facilities. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2:00 PM  Check-out time is 10:00 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the motel's restaurant, which features a bar and a pool view. Dining is also available at a coffee shop/café. Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a beach bar. Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Dip into one of the 2 outdoor swimming pools or enjoy other recreational amenities, which include an outdoor tennis court. This motel also features wireless Internet access (surcharge), gift shops/newsstands, and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 124 guestrooms featuring refrigerators. Rooms have private balconies. Digital television is provided for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Eurong, Eurong Beach Resort is by the ocean and within the region of Lake McKenzie and Maheno Shipwreck.  This beach motel is within the region of The Pinnacles. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Eurong Beach - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hammerstone Sandblows - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lake Wabby - 5.7 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Central Station - 7.9 km / 4.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lake McKenzie - 10.3 km / 6.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maheno Shipwreck - 29.3 km / 18.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Pinnacles - 32.3 km / 20.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Reefworld Aquarium - 32.9 km / 20.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hervey Bay Botanic Garden - 33.5 km / 20.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hervey Bay Historical Village Museum - 37.5 km / 23.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;WetSide Water Education Park - 38.5 km / 23.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hervey Bay Golf and Country Club - 39.5 km / 24.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brolga Theatre and Convention Centre - 42.2 km / 26.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maryborough Customs House Museum - 42.2 km / 26.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queens Park - 42.4 km / 26.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Eurong Beach Resort is Hervey Bay, QLD (HVB) - 31.9 km / 19.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>