<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11567182</Id><Name>Geelong Riverview Tourist Park</Name><Region><Id>15309</Id><Name>Geelong</Name><CityId>15309</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>59 Barrabool Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Geelong</City><State /><Zip>3216</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>08 9220 8484</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Geelong Riverview Tourist Park in Belmont, you'll be convenient to Kardinia Park and Simonds Stadium.  This 4-star cabin is within close proximity of Geelong Performing Arts Center and Geelong Showground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 35 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. Conveniences include separate sitting areas and microwaves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including an arcade/game room and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You can find a meal at a coffee shop/café serving guests of Geelong Riverview Tourist Park, or stop in at a grocery/convenience store.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include high-speed (wired) Internet access (surcharge) and laundry facilities. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; You can find a meal at a coffee shop/café serving guests of Geelong Riverview Tourist Park, or stop in at a grocery/convenience store. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including an arcade/game room and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 35 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. Conveniences include separate sitting areas and microwaves.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Geelong Riverview Tourist Park in Belmont, you'll be convenient to Kardinia Park and Simonds Stadium.  This 4-star cabin is within close proximity of Geelong Performing Arts Center and Geelong Showground. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Kardinia Park - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Simonds Stadium - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Geelong Performing Arts Center - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Geelong Showground - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Deakin University - 3.3 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Waurn Ponds Shopping Centre - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Geelong Waurn Ponds Campus - 4.6 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Geelong Golf Course - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lake Connwarre - 12.5 km / 7.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Warbird Air Adventures - 12.9 km / 8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Thirteenth Beach Golf Links - 16.2 km / 10.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Adventure Park Geelong - 16.2 km / 10.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jirrahlinga Koala and Wildlife Sanctuary - 16.7 km / 10.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Surf World Museum - 17.9 km / 11.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Barwon Heads Golf Club - 18.5 km / 11.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Melbourne, VIC (AVV-Avalon) - 19.5 km / 12.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;Melbourne, VIC (MEL-Tullamarine) - 71.1 km / 44.2 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Geelong Riverview Tourist Park is Melbourne, VIC (MEL-Tullamarine). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>