<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11574234</Id><Name>Corindas Cottages</Name><Region><Id>20229</Id><Name>Hobart City</Name><CityId>15320</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>17 Glebe Street, Glebe</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Hobart</City><State /><Zip>7000</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>0362341590</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Corinda's Cottages in Glebe, you'll be in the historical district and minutes from Domain Tennis Centre and Penitentiary Chapel Historic Site.  This 4-star cottage is within close proximity of Hobart Aquatic Centre and Hobart Synagogue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Treat yourself to a stay in one of the 3 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring fireplaces. Your room comes with a Select Comfort bed. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Conveniences include desks and separate sitting areas, and housekeeping is provided once per stay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include multilingual staff and luggage storage. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Treat yourself to a stay in one of the 3 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring fireplaces. Your room comes with a Select Comfort bed. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Conveniences include desks and separate sitting areas, and housekeeping is provided once per stay.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Corinda's Cottages in Glebe, you'll be in the historical district and minutes from Domain Tennis Centre and Penitentiary Chapel Historic Site.  This 4-star cottage is within close proximity of Hobart Aquatic Centre and Hobart Synagogue. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Domain Tennis Centre - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Penitentiary Chapel Historic Site - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hobart Aquatic Centre - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hobart Synagogue - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Theatre Royal - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;146 ArtSpace - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Tasmanian Botanical Gardens - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Playhouse Theatre - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tasmanian Museum and Art Gallery - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;State Library of Tasmania - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hobart Town Hall - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Franklin Wharf - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maritime Museum of Tasmania - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Constitution Dock - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lark Distillery - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Corinda's Cottages is Hobart, TAS (HBA-Hobart Intl.) - 15.1 km / 9.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>