<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11574602</Id><Name>Arrow on Swanston</Name><Region><Id>20252</Id><Name>Carlton</Name><CityId>15340</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>488 Swanston Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Melbourne</City><State /><Zip>3053</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>+61 3 9225 9000</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Arrow on Swanston, you'll be centrally located in Carlton, steps from Melbourne City Baths and minutes from RMIT University. This family-friendly apartment is close to Crown Casino and Entertainment Complex and Melbourne Cricket Ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 90 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and stovetops. 32-inch LCD televisions with digital programming provide entertainment, while wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected. Conveniences include desks and microwaves, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including an outdoor pool, a fitness center, and a seasonal outdoor pool. Additional features include wireless Internet access (surcharge), concierge services, and a hair salon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the apartment's restaurant, which serves breakfast and lunch, or grab a snack at a coffee shop/café.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, multilingual staff, and luggage storage. Event facilities at this apartment consist of a conference center, conference space, and meeting rooms. A shuttle from the hotel to the airport is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10:00 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the apartment's restaurant, which serves breakfast and lunch, or grab a snack at a coffee shop/café. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including an outdoor pool, a fitness center, and a seasonal outdoor pool. Additional features include wireless Internet access (surcharge), concierge services, and a hair salon. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 90 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and stovetops. 32-inch LCD televisions with digital programming provide entertainment, while wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected. Conveniences include desks and microwaves, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Arrow on Swanston, you'll be centrally located in Carlton, steps from Melbourne City Baths and minutes from RMIT University. This family-friendly apartment is close to Crown Casino and Entertainment Complex and Melbourne Cricket Ground. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Melbourne City Baths - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;RMIT University - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Melbourne Gaol - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queen Victoria Market - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;State Library of Victoria - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Melbourne Central - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Exhibition Building - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;QV Centre - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Carlton Gardens - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Her Majesty's Theatre - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bourke Street Mall - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ian Potter Museum of Art - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Flagstaff Gardens - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Melbourne Museum - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Melbourne Hospital - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Arrow on Swanston is Melbourne, VIC (MEL-Tullamarine) - 18.1 km / 11.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BeautyShop</Code><Text>Beauty Shop</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>