<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11570999</Id><Name>Baronnet Apartments Gold Coast</Name><Region><Id>20215</Id><Name>Surfers Paradise</Name><CityId>15311</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>10-14 Enderley Avenue</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Gold Coast</City><State /><Zip>4217</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61-7-55921099</Tel><Fax>61-7-55922861</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Baronnet Apartments, you'll be centrally located in Surfers Paradise, walking distance from SkyPoint Observation Deck and close to Surfers Paradise Beach. This 4-star apartment is within close proximity of Timezone and Centro Surfers Paradise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 30 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring refrigerators and microwaves. Rooms have private balconies. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreational opportunities offered, including an outdoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna. Additional amenities include wireless Internet access (surcharge) and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, laundry facilities, and an elevator (lift). Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreational opportunities offered, including an outdoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna. Additional amenities include wireless Internet access (surcharge) and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 30 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring refrigerators and microwaves. Rooms have private balconies. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Baronnet Apartments, you'll be centrally located in Surfers Paradise, walking distance from SkyPoint Observation Deck and close to Surfers Paradise Beach. This 4-star apartment is within close proximity of Timezone and Centro Surfers Paradise. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;SkyPoint Observation Deck - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Surfers Paradise Beach - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Timezone - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Centro Surfers Paradise - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cavill Avenue - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ripley's Believe It or Not - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;RaceCentre Race Simulators Australia - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Draculas Haunted House - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chevron Renaissance - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Infinity Gold Coast - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wax Museum - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Adrenalin Park - 1.4 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Slingshot - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Arts Centre Gold Coast - 1.7 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;King Tutts Putt Putt - 1.7 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Gold Coast, QLD (OOL-Coolangatta) - 19.3 km / 12 mi&lt;br /&gt;Adelaide, SA (ADL) - 1,606.8 km / 998.4 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Baronnet Apartments is Adelaide, SA (ADL). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>