<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11574155</Id><Name>Emu Beach Chalets</Name><Region><Id>20225</Id><Name>Albany</Name><CityId>15316</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>9 Medcalf Parade</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Albany</City><State /><Zip>6330</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>089-844-8889</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Emu Beach Chalets in Emu Point, you'll be next to a golf course and close to Emu Beach and National Anzac Centre.  This beach apartment is within the vicinity of Albany Convict Gaol Museum and Brig Amity Replica.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 12 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Flat-screen televisions with digital programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include microwaves and coffee/tea makers, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (complimentary).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as outdoor tennis courts or take in the view from a garden. This apartment also features complimentary wireless Internet access, tour/ticket assistance, and a picnic area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as outdoor tennis courts or take in the view from a garden. This apartment also features complimentary wireless Internet access, tour/ticket assistance, and a picnic area. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 12 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Flat-screen televisions with digital programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include microwaves and coffee/tea makers, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (complimentary).</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Emu Beach Chalets in Emu Point, you'll be next to a golf course and close to Emu Beach and National Anzac Centre.  This beach apartment is within the vicinity of Albany Convict Gaol Museum and Brig Amity Replica. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Emu Beach - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Middleton Beach - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Farm on Strawberry Hill - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Anzac Centre - 4.1 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albany Visitor Centre - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albany Entertainment Centre - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albany Convict Gaol Museum - 6 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brig Amity Replica - 6.2 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Denmark Country Club - 52 km / 32.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Berridge Park - 53.1 km / 33 mi &lt;br /&gt;Denmark Visitor Information Centre - 53.7 km / 33.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ocean Beach Park - 55.7 km / 34.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stirling Range National Park - 59.1 km / 36.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Valley of the Giants - 95.1 km / 59.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Emu Beach Chalets is Albany, WA (ALH) - 13.7 km / 8.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>