<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11574425</Id><Name>Atrium Resort Hotel</Name><Region><Id>15338</Id><Name>Mandurah</Name><CityId>15338</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>65 Ormsby Terrace</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Mandurah</City><State /><Zip>6210</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>08 9535 6633</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Atrium Resort in Mandurah, you'll be near the beach and minutes from Mandurah Performing Arts Center, and close to Mandurah Community Museum.  This family-friendly hotel is within the vicinity of King's Carnival and Abingdon Miniature Village.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 117 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchenettes. Rooms have private balconies. Flat-screen televisions are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include refrigerators and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities, including outdoor tennis courts, an indoor pool, and a spa tub. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). While enjoying a refreshing dip in the hotel pool, you can order your favorite drink at the poolside bar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, express check-out, and dry cleaning/laundry services.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). While enjoying a refreshing dip in the hotel pool, you can order your favorite drink at the poolside bar. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities, including outdoor tennis courts, an indoor pool, and a spa tub. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 117 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchenettes. Rooms have private balconies. Flat-screen televisions are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include refrigerators and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Atrium Resort in Mandurah, you'll be near the beach and minutes from Mandurah Performing Arts Center, and close to Mandurah Community Museum.  This family-friendly hotel is within the vicinity of King's Carnival and Abingdon Miniature Village. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Mandurah Performing Arts Center - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mandurah Community Museum - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;King's Carnival - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Abingdon Miniature Village - 5.8 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Centenary Park - 8.5 km / 5.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kingfisher Recreational Reserve - 9.2 km / 5.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;South Yunderup Oval - 9.7 km / 6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pyramids Beach - 12.1 km / 7.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Cut Golf Course - 12.8 km / 7.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Peel Zoo - 16.6 km / 10.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pinjarra Golf Club - 16.8 km / 10.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pinjarra Visitor Information Centre - 18.7 km / 11.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Battle of Pinjarra Memorial Park - 19 km / 11.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pinjarra Race Club - 19.3 km / 12 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Atrium Resort is Perth, WA (PER) - 69.5 km / 43.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndoorPool</Code><Text>Indoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>