<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11574148</Id><Name>BEST WESTERN Torbay Sea View Holiday Apartments</Name><Region><Id>20225</Id><Name>Albany</Name><CityId>15316</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>252 Cosy Corner Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Albany</City><State /><Zip>6330</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>+61 +61 8 9845 1904</Tel><Fax>+61 +61 8 9845 1903</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Best Western Torbay Sea View Holiday Apartments in Kronkup, you'll be by the ocean and within the region of Shelley Beach and Brig Amity Replica.  This 4-star apartment is within the region of Albany Visitor Centre and Albany Entertainment Centre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 12 air-conditioned rooms featuring private spa tubs. Rooms have private balconies. Kitchens are outfitted with full-sized refrigerators/freezers, stovetops, and microwaves. Digital programming and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities including a spa tub and an outdoor tennis court. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, express check-out, and dry cleaning/laundry services. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities including a spa tub and an outdoor tennis court. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 12 air-conditioned rooms featuring private spa tubs. Rooms have private balconies. Kitchens are outfitted with full-sized refrigerators/freezers, stovetops, and microwaves. Digital programming and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Best Western Torbay Sea View Holiday Apartments in Kronkup, you'll be by the ocean and within the region of Shelley Beach and Brig Amity Replica.  This 4-star apartment is within the region of Albany Visitor Centre and Albany Entertainment Centre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Shelley Beach - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lowlands Beach - 10.5 km / 6.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brig Amity Replica - 22.7 km / 14.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albany Visitor Centre - 23.2 km / 14.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albany Entertainment Centre - 23.3 km / 14.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Farm on Strawberry Hill - 24.8 km / 15.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Middleton Beach - 26.1 km / 16.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Denmark Country Club - 26.4 km / 16.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Berridge Park - 27.3 km / 17 mi &lt;br /&gt;Denmark Visitor Information Centre - 27.8 km / 17.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ocean Beach Park - 28.2 km / 17.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Emu Beach - 29.3 km / 18.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Valley of the Giants - 67.9 km / 42.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stirling Range National Park - 75.3 km / 46.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Best Western Torbay Sea View Holiday Apartments is Albany, WA (ALH) - 19.9 km / 12.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WakeUpService</Code><Text>Wake up service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lounge</Code><Text>Lounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>