<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11570079</Id><Name>South Pacific Plaza Gold Coast</Name><Region><Id>20209</Id><Name>Broadbeach</Name><CityId>15311</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Corner Victoria Avenue &amp; Old Burleigh Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Gold Coast</City><State /><Zip>4218</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61-755383911</Tel><Fax>61-755920170</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at South Pacific Plaza, you'll be centrally located in Broadbeach, steps from Broadbeach Mall and Kurrawa Beach.  This 4-star apartment is within close proximity of Oasis Shopping Centre and Pratten Park.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 84 individually furnished guestrooms, featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and DVD players are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include separate sitting areas and microwaves, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including an outdoor pool, a spa tub, and an outdoor tennis court. This apartment also features tour/ticket assistance and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The front desk is staffed during limited hours. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including an outdoor pool, a spa tub, and an outdoor tennis court. This apartment also features tour/ticket assistance and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 84 individually furnished guestrooms, featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and DVD players are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include separate sitting areas and microwaves, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (surcharge).</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at South Pacific Plaza, you'll be centrally located in Broadbeach, steps from Broadbeach Mall and Kurrawa Beach.  This 4-star apartment is within close proximity of Oasis Shopping Centre and Pratten Park. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Broadbeach Mall - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kurrawa Beach - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Oasis Shopping Centre - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pratten Park - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Oracle Boulevard - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gold Coast Convention and Exhibition Centre - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jupiters Casino - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dracula's Queensland - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pacific Fair Shopping Centre - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Putt Putt Golf Mermaid Beach - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Broadbeach Sports and Recreation Centre - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;SkyPoint Observation Deck - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Surfers Paradise Beach - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Timezone - 3 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Centro Surfers Paradise - 3 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Gold Coast, QLD (OOL-Coolangatta) - 17.2 km / 10.7 mi&lt;br /&gt;Maroochydore, QLD (MCY-Sunshine Coast) - 161.9 km / 100.6 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for South Pacific Plaza is Maroochydore, QLD (MCY-Sunshine Coast). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>