<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11574099</Id><Name>Huon Bush Retreats</Name><Region><Id>20229</Id><Name>Hobart City</Name><CityId>15320</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>300 Browns Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Hobart</City><State /><Zip>7109</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>0362642233</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Huonville (Ranelagh), Huon Bush Retreats is within the vicinity of Home Hill Winery and The Huon Apple and Heritage Museum.  This apartment is within the region of Hartz Mountains National Park.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Treat yourself to a stay in one of the 7 guestrooms, featuring fireplaces. Rooms have private balconies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as wedding services, a picnic area, and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The front desk is staffed during limited hours. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as wedding services, a picnic area, and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Treat yourself to a stay in one of the 7 guestrooms, featuring fireplaces. Rooms have private balconies.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Huonville (Ranelagh), Huon Bush Retreats is within the vicinity of Home Hill Winery and The Huon Apple and Heritage Museum.  This apartment is within the region of Hartz Mountains National Park. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Home Hill Winery - 4.1 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Huon Apple and Heritage Museum - 7.1 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wooden Boat Centre - 11.4 km / 7.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Myrtle Forest - 18.8 km / 11.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mt. Wellington - 21.6 km / 13.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Organ Pipes - 21.9 km / 13.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rosedown Gardens - 23.1 km / 14.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kingborough Sports Centre - 23.3 km / 14.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Peter Murrell Nature Reserve - 23.9 km / 14.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cascade Brewery - 25.8 km / 16 mi &lt;br /&gt;Salmon Ponds Heritage Hatchery and Gardens - 26 km / 16.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lady Franklin Gallery - 26.2 km / 16.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cascades Female Factory Historic Site - 26.4 km / 16.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kettering Ferry Terminal - 26.4 km / 16.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Taroona Shot Tower - 27.7 km / 17.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Huon Bush Retreats is Hobart, TAS (HBA-Hobart Intl.) - 44.4 km / 27.6 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>