<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11571484</Id><Name>Oscar On Main Resort Gold Coast</Name><Region><Id>20212</Id><Name>Main Beach</Name><CityId>15311</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1 Hughes Avenue</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Gold Coast</City><State /><Zip>4217</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61-7-55270966</Tel><Fax>61-7-55270933</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Oscar on Main Resort in Main Beach, you'll be by the sea and convenient to Mariner's Cove Marina and Sea World.  This 4.5-star apartment is within close proximity of Marina Mirage Shopping Centre and Australia Fair Shopping Centre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 35 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private furnished balconies. Flat-screen televisions with digital programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as microwaves and washers/dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreational opportunities offered, including an outdoor pool, an indoor pool, and a sauna. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and tour/ticket assistance. If you're planning a day at a nearby theme park, you can hop on the shuttle (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, luggage storage, and an elevator (lift). A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreational opportunities offered, including an outdoor pool, an indoor pool, and a sauna. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and tour/ticket assistance. If you're planning a day at a nearby theme park, you can hop on the shuttle (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 35 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private furnished balconies. Flat-screen televisions with digital programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as microwaves and washers/dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Oscar on Main Resort in Main Beach, you'll be by the sea and convenient to Mariner's Cove Marina and Sea World.  This 4.5-star apartment is within close proximity of Marina Mirage Shopping Centre and Australia Fair Shopping Centre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Mariner's Cove Marina - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marina Mirage Shopping Centre - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Australia Fair Shopping Centre - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rockpools - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Broadwater Parklands - 1.7 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;King Tutts Putt Putt - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Philip Park - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Budds Beach - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Allamanda Private Hospital - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gold Coast Hospital - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sea World - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Slingshot - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Adrenalin Park - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gold Coast Aquatic Centre - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wax Museum - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Oscar on Main Resort is Gold Coast, QLD (OOL-Coolangatta) - 22.6 km / 14 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>