<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11573860</Id><Name>Surfers International Apartments</Name><Region><Id>20215</Id><Name>Surfers Paradise</Name><CityId>15311</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>7-9 Trickett Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Gold Coast</City><State /><Zip>4217</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61 7 5579 1299</Tel><Fax>61 7 5579 1230</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Surfers International Gold Coast Accommodation in Surfers Paradise, you'll be near the beach and minutes from Timezone and Surfers Paradise Beach.  This family-friendly apartment is within close proximity of Centro Surfers Paradise and Cavill Avenue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 48 guestrooms, featuring kitchens with refrigerators and microwaves. Rooms have private balconies. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as coffee/tea makers and ceiling fans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including an outdoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna. Additional features include wireless Internet access (surcharge), tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, luggage storage, and laundry facilities. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 1 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including an outdoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna. Additional features include wireless Internet access (surcharge), tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 48 guestrooms, featuring kitchens with refrigerators and microwaves. Rooms have private balconies. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as coffee/tea makers and ceiling fans.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Surfers International Gold Coast Accommodation in Surfers Paradise, you'll be near the beach and minutes from Timezone and Surfers Paradise Beach.  This family-friendly apartment is within close proximity of Centro Surfers Paradise and Cavill Avenue. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Timezone - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Centro Surfers Paradise - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Surfers Paradise Beach - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cavill Avenue - 0.2 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;SkyPoint Observation Deck - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ripley's Believe It or Not - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;RaceCentre Race Simulators Australia - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Draculas Haunted House - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chevron Renaissance - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Infinity Gold Coast - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wax Museum - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Adrenalin Park - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Slingshot - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;King Tutts Putt Putt - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Budds Beach - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Surfers International Gold Coast Accommodation is Gold Coast, QLD (OOL-Coolangatta) - 19.8 km / 12.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>