<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11570911</Id><Name>Kirra Beach Apartments Gold Coast</Name><Region><Id>20211</Id><Name>Coolangatta</Name><CityId>15311</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>4-10 Douglas Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Gold Coast</City><State /><Zip>4225</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61-755237900</Tel><Fax>61-755994900</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Kirra Beach Apartments in Coolangatta (Kirra), you'll be minutes from Kirra Beach and close to Bilinga Beach. This 4-star apartment is within close proximity of Border Park Raceway and The Strand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 51 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and microwaves. Rooms have private balconies. Cable programming and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and irons/ironing boards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities including an outdoor pool and a spa tub. This apartment also features complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite from a grocery/convenience store serving guests of Kirra Beach Apartments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, luggage storage, and an elevator (lift). Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 8:30 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite from a grocery/convenience store serving guests of Kirra Beach Apartments. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities including an outdoor pool and a spa tub. This apartment also features complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 51 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and microwaves. Rooms have private balconies. Cable programming and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and irons/ironing boards.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Kirra Beach Apartments in Coolangatta (Kirra), you'll be minutes from Kirra Beach and close to Bilinga Beach. This 4-star apartment is within close proximity of Border Park Raceway and The Strand. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Kirra Beach - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bilinga Beach - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Border Park Raceway - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Strand - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Coolangatta Beach - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Greenmount Beach - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Centro Tweed - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Snapper Rocks - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Point Danger Light - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Point Danger - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Duranbah Beach - 2.3 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;John Flynn Private Hospital - 4.1 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tugun Beach - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fingal Lighthouse - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Surf World Gold Coast - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Kirra Beach Apartments is Gold Coast, QLD (OOL-Coolangatta) - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>