<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11570746</Id><Name>Escarpment Retreat Mt Tamborine</Name><Region><Id>20214</Id><Name>North Gold Coast</Name><CityId>15311</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>123 Alpine Terrace</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Gold Coast</City><State /><Zip>4272</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61 7 55453300</Tel><Fax>61 7 55453600</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Mount Tamborine, The Escarpment Retreat is in the mountains and close to Cedar Creek Estate Vineyard and Winery and Mount Tamborine Winery. This 5-star condominium resort is within close proximity of Tamborine National Park Witches Falls Section and Tamborine National Park Palm Grove Section.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 6 air-conditioned rooms featuring fireplaces and private spa tubs. Rooms have private balconies. Kitchenettes are outfitted with refrigerators. Flat-screen televisions and DVD players are available for your entertainment, while iPod docking stations help you enjoy your music in the comfort of your room. Private bathrooms have deep soaking bathtubs and complimentary toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with onsite massages and facials. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a fireplace in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of the condominium resort's room service (during limited hours).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center and a library. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of the condominium resort's room service (during limited hours). &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with onsite massages and facials. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a fireplace in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 6 air-conditioned rooms featuring fireplaces and private spa tubs. Rooms have private balconies. Kitchenettes are outfitted with refrigerators. Flat-screen televisions and DVD players are available for your entertainment, while iPod docking stations help you enjoy your music in the comfort of your room. Private bathrooms have deep soaking bathtubs and complimentary toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Mount Tamborine, The Escarpment Retreat is in the mountains and close to Cedar Creek Estate Vineyard and Winery and Mount Tamborine Winery. This 5-star condominium resort is within close proximity of Tamborine National Park Witches Falls Section and Tamborine National Park Palm Grove Section. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Cedar Creek Estate Vineyard and Winery - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mount Tamborine Winery - 3.8 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tamborine National Park Witches Falls Section - 3.9 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tamborine National Park Palm Grove Section - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tamborine National Park Joalah Section - 4.9 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tamborine Mountain Distillery - 5.2 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tamborine National Park MacDonald Section - 5.5 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tamborine National Park Knoll Section - 6 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Thunderbird Park - 7.8 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tamborine National Park Cedar Creek Section - 7.9 km / 4.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Movie World - 13.1 km / 8.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Australian Outback Spectacular - 13.1 km / 8.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wet'n'Wild Water World - 13.2 km / 8.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Go Karting Gold Coast - 15.1 km / 9.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lakeside Country Club - 16.4 km / 10.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Escarpment Retreat is Gold Coast, QLD (OOL-Coolangatta) - 37.9 km / 23.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>GameRoom</Code><Text>GameRoom</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>