<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11573840</Id><Name>Pethers Rainforest Retreat Gold Coast</Name><Region><Id>20214</Id><Name>North Gold Coast</Name><CityId>15311</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>28b Geissmann Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Gold Coast</City><State /><Zip>4272</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61-755454577</Tel><Fax>61-755454463</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1033/91/59/9/mSW0IssH_9a0f2ad94d0e6f4e4aba1932dcd4e7f1.jpg</Url><Width>170</Width><Height>180</Height><Bytes>10241</Bytes><Caption>mSW0IssH_9a0f2ad94d0e6f4e4aba1932dcd4e7f1</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1033/91/59/9/mSW0IssH_9a0f2ad94d0e6f4e4aba1932dcd4e7f1thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>66</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2429</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1033/91/59/9/bDfyVoJw_d0ec5b870c1310258ad4d517703cd7f5.jpg</Url><Width>170</Width><Height>180</Height><Bytes>10440</Bytes><Caption>bDfyVoJw_d0ec5b870c1310258ad4d517703cd7f5</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1033/91/59/9/bDfyVoJw_d0ec5b870c1310258ad4d517703cd7f5thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>66</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2267</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1033/91/59/9/epJBZCgL_66bb4c4d87f2c2ef8a8c09c023f278b6.jpg</Url><Width>170</Width><Height>180</Height><Bytes>9422</Bytes><Caption>epJBZCgL_66bb4c4d87f2c2ef8a8c09c023f278b6</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1033/91/59/9/epJBZCgL_66bb4c4d87f2c2ef8a8c09c023f278b6thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>66</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2221</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1033/91/59/9/iZBJuhjI_daeaff579d2e496ba60ec296bcc1b27b.jpg</Url><Width>170</Width><Height>180</Height><Bytes>6348</Bytes><Caption>iZBJuhjI_daeaff579d2e496ba60ec296bcc1b27b</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1033/91/59/9/iZBJuhjI_daeaff579d2e496ba60ec296bcc1b27bthumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>66</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1839</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Pethers Rainforest Retreat in North Tamborine, you'll be in the mountains and minutes from Tamborine National Park Knoll Section and Tamborine Mountain Distillery. This 5-star hotel is within close proximity of Tamborine National Park Joalah Section and Tamborine National Park Witches Falls Section.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Treat yourself to a stay in one of the 10 guestrooms, featuring private spa tubs. Rooms have private furnished balconies. Private kitchens make it easy to prepare your meals. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature jetted bathtubs and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a spa tub or take in the view from a terrace and a garden. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Pethers Rainforest Retreat. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, luggage storage, and a library. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed    Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Pethers Rainforest Retreat. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a spa tub or take in the view from a terrace and a garden. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Treat yourself to a stay in one of the 10 guestrooms, featuring private spa tubs. Rooms have private furnished balconies. Private kitchens make it easy to prepare your meals. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature jetted bathtubs and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Pethers Rainforest Retreat in North Tamborine, you'll be in the mountains and minutes from Tamborine National Park Knoll Section and Tamborine Mountain Distillery. This 5-star hotel is within close proximity of Tamborine National Park Joalah Section and Tamborine National Park Witches Falls Section. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Tamborine National Park Knoll Section - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tamborine Mountain Distillery - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tamborine National Park Joalah Section - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tamborine National Park Witches Falls Section - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mount Tamborine Winery - 1.7 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cedar Creek Estate Vineyard and Winery - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Thunderbird Park - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tamborine National Park Cedar Creek Section - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tamborine National Park MacDonald Section - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tamborine National Park Palm Grove Section - 2.7 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Movie World - 13 km / 8.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Australian Outback Spectacular - 13.2 km / 8.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wet'n'Wild Water World - 13.5 km / 8.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;WhiteWater World - 14.8 km / 9.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dreamworld - 15 km / 9.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Pethers Rainforest Retreat is Brisbane, QLD (BNE) - 60 km / 37.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>