<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11573920</Id><Name>City Central Motor Inn &amp; Apartments</Name><Region><Id>20224</Id><Name>Warrnambool</Name><CityId>15315</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>14 King Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Warrnambool</City><State /><Zip>3280</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>03 5562 2140</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at City Central Apartments, you'll be centrally located in Warrnambool, walking distance from Warrnambool Botanical Gardens and close to Flagstaff Hill Maritime Village. This hotel is within close proximity of Warrnambool Beach and Warrnambool Golf Club.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. LCD televisions with digital programming are available for your entertainment, and DVD players are also provided. Conveniences include separate sitting areas and microwaves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. This hotel also features a picnic area and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, express check-out, and luggage storage. A train station pick-up service is provided at no charge, and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. This hotel also features a picnic area and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. LCD televisions with digital programming are available for your entertainment, and DVD players are also provided. Conveniences include separate sitting areas and microwaves.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at City Central Apartments, you'll be centrally located in Warrnambool, walking distance from Warrnambool Botanical Gardens and close to Flagstaff Hill Maritime Village. This hotel is within close proximity of Warrnambool Beach and Warrnambool Golf Club. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Warrnambool Botanical Gardens - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Flagstaff Hill Maritime Village - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Warrnambool Beach - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Warrnambool Golf Club - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tower Hill Wildlife Reserve - 11 km / 6.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Port Fairy to Warrnambool Rail Trail - 14.1 km / 8.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Port Fairy Golf Club - 17.7 km / 11 mi &lt;br /&gt;Griffiths Island Lighthouse - 19.8 km / 12.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bay of Islands Coastal Park - 28.3 km / 17.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Port Campbell Foreshores - 52.3 km / 32.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Port Campbell Visitor Information Centre - 52.3 km / 32.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Twelve Apostles - 62.9 km / 39.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wreck Beach - 76.3 km / 47.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Johanna Beach - 89.1 km / 55.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Great Otway National Park - 108.6 km / 67.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for City Central Apartments is Melbourne, VIC (AVV-Avalon) - 178.3 km / 110.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>&lt;b&gt;Melbourne Airport (MEL):&lt;/b&gt; Approximate distance to City Central Apartments is 278 km (172.7 miles).</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>