<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11570042</Id><Name>Sunshine Beach Resort Gold Coast</Name><Region><Id>20210</Id><Name>Burleigh Heads</Name><CityId>15311</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>2004 Gold Coast Highway</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Gold Coast</City><State /><Zip>4220</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>+61 755 727171</Tel><Fax>+61 7 5572 0977</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Sunshine Beach Resort in Miami, you'll be on the Strip and close to Burleigh Golf Club and Jupiters Casino. This family-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Burleigh Beach and Pizzey Park Sporting Complex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 27 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring refrigerators and flat-screen televisions. Computers, wireless Internet access (surcharge), and DVD players provide entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and microwaves, and housekeeping is provided on a limited basis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities including an outdoor pool and a spa tub. Additional amenities include wireless Internet access (surcharge), tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The front desk is staffed during limited hours. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 21 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities including an outdoor pool and a spa tub. Additional amenities include wireless Internet access (surcharge), tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 27 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring refrigerators and flat-screen televisions. Computers, wireless Internet access (surcharge), and DVD players provide entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and microwaves, and housekeeping is provided on a limited basis.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Sunshine Beach Resort in Miami, you'll be on the Strip and close to Burleigh Golf Club and Jupiters Casino. This family-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Burleigh Beach and Pizzey Park Sporting Complex. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Burleigh Golf Club - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Burleigh Beach - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pizzey Park Sporting Complex - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gold Coast Seniors Tennis Club - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bond University - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Burleigh Head National Park - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Putt Putt Golf Mermaid Beach - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dracula's Queensland - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pacific Fair Shopping Centre - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;David Fleay Wildlife Park - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Broadbeach Sports and Recreation Centre - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Oracle Boulevard - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pratten Park - 4.6 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jupiters Casino - 4.6 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mallawa Drive Sports Complex - 4.6 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Sunshine Beach Resort is Gold Coast, QLD (OOL-Coolangatta) - 12.6 km / 7.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 21 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Giftshop</Code><Text>Gift Shop</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>