<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11574092</Id><Name>Zero Davey Boutique Apartments Hobart</Name><Region><Id>20229</Id><Name>Hobart City</Name><CityId>15320</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>15 Hunter Street Cnr Of Hunter &amp; Davey Streets</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Hobart</City><State /><Zip>7000</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61-3-62701444</Tel><Fax>61-3-62701400</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Hobart (Sullivan's Cove), Zero Davey Boutique Apartment Hotel is minutes from Mona Ferry Terminal and close to Salamanca Market.  This 4.5-star apartment is within close proximity of Royal Tasmanian Botanical Gardens and Cascade Brewery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 36 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and LCD televisions. Rooms have private balconies. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while iPod docking stations and cable programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). This apartment also features a television in the lobby and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant or in a coffee shop/café. Or stay in and take advantage of the apartment's room service (during limited hours).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, dry cleaning/laundry services, and luggage storage. Guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle for a surcharge, and self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant or in a coffee shop/café. Or stay in and take advantage of the apartment's room service (during limited hours). &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). This apartment also features a television in the lobby and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 36 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and LCD televisions. Rooms have private balconies. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while iPod docking stations and cable programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Hobart (Sullivan's Cove), Zero Davey Boutique Apartment Hotel is minutes from Mona Ferry Terminal and close to Salamanca Market.  This 4.5-star apartment is within close proximity of Royal Tasmanian Botanical Gardens and Cascade Brewery. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Franklin Wharf - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Constitution Dock - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tasmanian Museum and Art Gallery - 0.2 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maritime Museum of Tasmania - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lark Distillery - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Theatre Royal - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mawson's Huts Replica Museum - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hobart Town Hall - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hobart Function and Conference Centre - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hobart Cruise Terminal - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Franklin Square - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hobart Aquatic Centre - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mona Ferry Terminal - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hobart Synagogue - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. David's Cathedral - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Zero Davey Boutique Apartment Hotel is Hobart, TAS (HBA-Hobart Intl.) - 14.8 km / 9.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>