<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11583459</Id><Name>Hotel Barkly St Kilda</Name><Region><Id>20250</Id><Name>St. Kilda</Name><CityId>15340</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>109 Barkly Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Melbourne</City><State /><Zip>3182</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>03 9525 3332</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Barkly in St. Kilda, you'll be in a shopping district and minutes from Acland Street and close to St. Kilda Beach.  This hostel is close to Melbourne Cricket Ground and Crown Casino and Entertainment Complex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 40 air-conditioned guestrooms. Prepare your meals in the shared/communal kitchen. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as a nightclub or take in the view from a rooftop terrace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hotel Barkly. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include ATM/banking services and an elevator (lift).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hotel Barkly. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as a nightclub or take in the view from a rooftop terrace. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 40 air-conditioned guestrooms. Prepare your meals in the shared/communal kitchen. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Barkly in St. Kilda, you'll be in a shopping district and minutes from Acland Street and close to St. Kilda Beach.  This hostel is close to Melbourne Cricket Ground and Crown Casino and Entertainment Complex. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Acland Street - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jewish Museum of Australia - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palais Theatre - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Luna Park - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Kilda Pier - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Kilda Sea Baths - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Kilda Beach - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Astor Theatre - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albert Park Golf Course - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albert Park Lake - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Prahran Market - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rippon Lea House and Gardens - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Elwood Beach - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jam Factory - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Como Centre - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Barkly is Melbourne, VIC (MEL-Tullamarine) - 24.6 km / 15.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>