<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11586340</Id><Name>Friday on the Beach Byron Bay</Name><Region><Id>20267</Id><Name>Byron Bay</Name><CityId>15351</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>45 Lawson Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Byron Bay</City><State /><Zip>2481</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>+61 2 6685 6373</Tel><Fax>+61 2 6685 5513</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Friday on the Beach in Byron Bay, you'll be on the beach and convenient to Wategos Beach and Cape Byron Lighthouse.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Byron Bay Golf Course and Tallow Beach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and flat-screen televisions. Conveniences include minibars and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as wedding services and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as wedding services and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and flat-screen televisions. Conveniences include minibars and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Friday on the Beach in Byron Bay, you'll be on the beach and convenient to Wategos Beach and Cape Byron Lighthouse.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Byron Bay Golf Course and Tallow Beach. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Wategos Beach - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cape Byron Lighthouse - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Byron Bay Golf Course - 3.8 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tallow Beach - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tyagarah Nature Reserve - 5.8 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kings Beach - 6.5 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lake Ainsworth Sport and Recreation Centre - 15.6 km / 9.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lennox Head Surf Life Saving Club - 16 km / 9.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ballina Golf Club - 23.7 km / 14.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ballina Jockey Club - 23.8 km / 14.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shelly Beach - 24.6 km / 15.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ballina Fair Shopping Centre - 24.6 km / 15.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lighthouse Beach - 25.3 km / 15.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ballina Naval and Maritime Museum - 26.1 km / 16.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Friday on the Beach is Brisbane, QLD (BNE) - 148 km / 92 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>