<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11583584</Id><Name>Comfort Resort Alzburg</Name><Region><Id>20259</Id><Name>Mansfield</Name><CityId>15349</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>39 Malcolm Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Mansfield</City><State /><Zip>3722</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>+61 (3) 5775 2367</Tel><Fax>+61 (3) 5775 2719</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Mansfield, Alzburg Resort is in a rural location, minutes from Mansfield Oval, and close to Mansfield Botanic Park.  This family-friendly motel is within the vicinity of Mansfield Racecourse and Mansfield Zoo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 44 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Conveniences include safes and complimentary newspapers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreational opportunities offered, including an outdoor pool, an outdoor tennis court, and a sauna. This motel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, an arcade/game room, and ski storage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Alzburg Resort, or find a snack in a coffee shop/café. Meet other guests and eat at a complimentary reception. Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a computer station, dry cleaning/laundry services, and luggage storage. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Alzburg Resort, or find a snack in a coffee shop/café. Meet other guests and eat at a complimentary reception. Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreational opportunities offered, including an outdoor pool, an outdoor tennis court, and a sauna. This motel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, an arcade/game room, and ski storage. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 44 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Conveniences include safes and complimentary newspapers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Mansfield, Alzburg Resort is in a rural location, minutes from Mansfield Oval, and close to Mansfield Botanic Park.  This family-friendly motel is within the vicinity of Mansfield Racecourse and Mansfield Zoo. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Mansfield Oval - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mansfield Botanic Park - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mansfield Golf Club - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mansfield Racecourse - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mansfield Zoo - 8.6 km / 5.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mt. Buller Ski Slopes - 32.7 km / 20.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Alzburg Resort is Melbourne, VIC (MEL-Tullamarine) - 128.9 km / 80.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ContinentalBreakfast</Code><Text>Contintenal breakfast</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InRoomMovies</Code><Text>In-room movies</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Sauna</Code><Text>Sauna</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DiscoClub</Code><Text>Disco / Club</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>GameRoom</Code><Text>GameRoom</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Playground</Code><Text>Playground</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lounge</Code><Text>Lounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>