<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11583605</Id><Name>Boathaven Holiday Park</Name><Region><Id>20262</Id><Name>Wodonga</Name><CityId>15349</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>33 Boathaven Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Wodonga</City><State /><Zip>3691</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>089-220-8484</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Boathaven Holiday Park in Ebden, you'll be on the beach and within the vicinity of Lake Hume.  This beach cabin is within the region of Albury Art Gallery and Hothouse Theatre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 50 guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities including an outdoor pool and a spa tub. Additional features include an arcade/game room, tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities including an outdoor pool and a spa tub. Additional features include an arcade/game room, tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 50 guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Boathaven Holiday Park in Ebden, you'll be on the beach and within the vicinity of Lake Hume.  This beach cabin is within the region of Albury Art Gallery and Hothouse Theatre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Lake Hume - 6.2 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albury Art Gallery - 11 km / 6.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hothouse Theatre - 11.2 km / 7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Belvoir Park - 11.5 km / 7.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Commercial Golf Resort - 12 km / 7.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Monument Hill - 12.2 km / 7.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wodonga Golf Course - 15.1 km / 9.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wonga Wetlands - 16.3 km / 10.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albury Wodonga Golf Driving Range - 17.4 km / 10.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Albury, NSW (ABX) - 9.6 km / 5.9 mi&lt;br /&gt;Melbourne, VIC (MEL-Tullamarine) - 256.6 km / 159.5 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Boathaven Holiday Park is Melbourne, VIC (MEL-Tullamarine). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>