<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11583469</Id><Name>BEST WESTERN Alexander Motor Inn</Name><Region><Id>20254</Id><Name>Others</Name><CityId>15340</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>980 Mount Alexander Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Essendon</City><State /><Zip>3040</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>+61 +61 3 93741255</Tel><Fax>+61 03 93798784</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Best Western Alexander Motor Inn in Essendon, you'll be close to Moonee Valley Racecourse and Flemington Racecourse.  This family-friendly motel is within close proximity of Royal Melbourne Showgrounds and Highpoint Shopping Centre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 44 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. Additional features include babysitting/childcare (surcharge), wedding services, and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the motel's restaurant, which features a bar and a garden view. You can also stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, limo/town car service, and a computer station. Planning an event in Essendon? This motel has facilities measuring 861 square feet (80 square meters), including a meeting room. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the motel's restaurant, which features a bar and a garden view. You can also stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. Additional features include babysitting/childcare (surcharge), wedding services, and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 44 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Best Western Alexander Motor Inn in Essendon, you'll be close to Moonee Valley Racecourse and Flemington Racecourse.  This family-friendly motel is within close proximity of Royal Melbourne Showgrounds and Highpoint Shopping Centre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Moonee Valley Racecourse - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Melbourne Showgrounds - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Highpoint Shopping Centre - 3.3 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Flemington Racecourse - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;State Netball Hockey Centre - 4.6 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Melbourne Zoo - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Park - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Princes Park - 5.2 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Northern Golf Club - 5.2 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Children's Hospital - 5.4 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Women's Hospital - 6.2 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Martin Reserve - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Melbourne Hospital - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Melbourne - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ian Potter Museum of Art - 6.6 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Best Western Alexander Motor Inn is Melbourne, VIC (MEL-Tullamarine) - 10.8 km / 6.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Kitchen</Code><Text>Kitchen</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lounge</Code><Text>Lounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MultilingualStaff</Code><Text>Multilingual Staff</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>NightClub</Code><Text>Night Club</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>