<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11581378</Id><Name>Punthill Williamstown</Name><Region><Id>20254</Id><Name>Others</Name><CityId>15340</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>4-18 Ferguson Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Melbourne</City><State /><Zip>3016</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61 3 9916 8888</Tel><Fax>61-3-96311112</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Williamstown, Punthill Williamstown is near the bay, minutes from HMAS Castlemaine, and close to Melbourne Seaplanes. This 4.5-star apartment is within close proximity of Williamstown Botanic Gardens and Scienceworks and Melbourne Planetarium.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 48 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Rooms have private furnished balconies or patios. 32-inch LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and separate sitting areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities including a spa tub and a fitness center. This apartment also features wireless Internet access (surcharge) and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and dry cleaning/laundry services. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities including a spa tub and a fitness center. This apartment also features wireless Internet access (surcharge) and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 48 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Rooms have private furnished balconies or patios. 32-inch LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and separate sitting areas.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Williamstown, Punthill Williamstown is near the bay, minutes from HMAS Castlemaine, and close to Melbourne Seaplanes. This 4.5-star apartment is within close proximity of Williamstown Botanic Gardens and Scienceworks and Melbourne Planetarium. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;HMAS Castlemaine - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Melbourne Seaplanes - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Williamstown Botanic Gardens - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Scienceworks and Melbourne Planetarium - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Westgate Bridge - 3.3 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Spirit of Tasmania Ferry Terminal - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;South Melbourne Beach - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sun Theatre - 4.9 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;DFO South Wharf - 5.7 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;South Melbourne Market - 5.7 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Melbourne Convention and Exhibition Centre - 5.8 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Melbourne City Marina - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Polly Woodside - 6 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Etihad Stadium - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Kilda Beach - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Punthill Williamstown is Melbourne, VIC (MEL-Tullamarine) - 21.6 km / 13.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>