<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11580436</Id><Name>Barkly Apartments</Name><Region><Id>20250</Id><Name>St. Kilda</Name><CityId>15340</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>180 Barkly Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Melbourne</City><State /><Zip>3182</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61-395255000</Tel><Fax>61-395253618</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Barkly Apartments in St. Kilda, you'll be in a shopping district and minutes from Acland Street and Luna Park. This family-friendly aparthotel is within close proximity of Palais Theatre and St Kilda Pier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. 32-inch LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include microwaves and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided on a limited basis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include luggage storage and laundry facilities. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. 32-inch LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include microwaves and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided on a limited basis.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Barkly Apartments in St. Kilda, you'll be in a shopping district and minutes from Acland Street and Luna Park. This family-friendly aparthotel is within close proximity of Palais Theatre and St Kilda Pier. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Acland Street - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Luna Park - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palais Theatre - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Kilda Pier - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Kilda Sea Baths - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Kilda Beach - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jewish Museum of Australia - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Astor Theatre - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rippon Lea House and Gardens - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Elwood Beach - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albert Park Golf Course - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albert Park Lake - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Prahran Market - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jam Factory - 3.1 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;South Melbourne Beach - 3.3 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Barkly Apartments is Melbourne, VIC (MEL-Tullamarine) - 24.9 km / 15.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>