<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11583474</Id><Name>Paramount Serviced Apartments Melbourne</Name><Region><Id>20247</Id><Name>City Centre</Name><CityId>15340</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>181 Exhibition Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Melbourne</City><State /><Zip>3000</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61-392515555</Tel><Fax>61-392515566</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at The Paramount Serviced Apartments Melbourne, you'll be centrally located in Melbourne, steps from Her Majesty's Theatre and minutes from Princess Theatre.  This 4-star apartment is close to Melbourne Cricket Ground and Crown Casino and Entertainment Complex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 60 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens. Flat-screen televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected. Conveniences include separate sitting areas and coffee/tea makers, and you can also request microwaves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including an indoor pool, a spa tub, and an outdoor tennis court. Additional features include wireless Internet access (surcharge), concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite from a grocery/convenience store serving guests of The Paramount Serviced Apartments Melbourne.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include limo/town car service, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk. Planning an event in Melbourne? This apartment has 1108 square feet (103 square meters) of space consisting of a conference center and a meeting room. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite from a grocery/convenience store serving guests of The Paramount Serviced Apartments Melbourne. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including an indoor pool, a spa tub, and an outdoor tennis court. Additional features include wireless Internet access (surcharge), concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 60 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens. Flat-screen televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected. Conveniences include separate sitting areas and coffee/tea makers, and you can also request microwaves.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at The Paramount Serviced Apartments Melbourne, you'll be centrally located in Melbourne, steps from Her Majesty's Theatre and minutes from Princess Theatre.  This 4-star apartment is close to Melbourne Cricket Ground and Crown Casino and Entertainment Complex. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Her Majesty's Theatre - 0.1 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;Princess Theatre - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Parliament House of Victoria - 0.2 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;City Museum at Old Treasury Melbourne - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;QV Centre - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Treasury Gardens - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Regent Theatre - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Melbourne Town Hall - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Patrick's Cathedral - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Melbourne Gaol - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Carlton Gardens - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bourke Street Mall - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;State Library of Victoria - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Forum Theatre - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Melbourne Central - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Paramount Serviced Apartments Melbourne is Melbourne, VIC (MEL-Tullamarine) - 19 km / 11.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndoorPool</Code><Text>Indoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>