<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11581029</Id><Name>Apartments Ink St Kilda</Name><Region><Id>20250</Id><Name>St. Kilda</Name><CityId>15340</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>135 Inkerman Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Melbourne</City><State /><Zip>3182</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61-3-95255300</Tel><Fax>61-3-95255399</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Apartments Ink in St. Kilda, you'll be in the entertainment district and convenient to Jewish Museum of Australia and St. Kilda Beach.  This 4.5-star apartment is within close proximity of Acland Street and Astor Theatre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 59 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and DVD players. LCD televisions with cable programming are provided for your entertainment, with wired and wireless Internet access available for a surcharge. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as coffee/tea makers and irons/ironing boards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, shopping on site, and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite from a grocery/convenience store serving guests of Apartments Ink.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a computer station, and express check-out. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite from a grocery/convenience store serving guests of Apartments Ink. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, shopping on site, and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 59 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and DVD players. LCD televisions with cable programming are provided for your entertainment, with wired and wireless Internet access available for a surcharge. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as coffee/tea makers and irons/ironing boards.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Apartments Ink in St. Kilda, you'll be in the entertainment district and convenient to Jewish Museum of Australia and St. Kilda Beach.  This 4.5-star apartment is within close proximity of Acland Street and Astor Theatre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Jewish Museum of Australia - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Acland Street - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Astor Theatre - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palais Theatre - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Luna Park - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Kilda Pier - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Kilda Sea Baths - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Kilda Beach - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rippon Lea House and Gardens - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albert Park Golf Course - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Prahran Market - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albert Park Lake - 2.5 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jam Factory - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Elwood Beach - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Como Centre - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Apartments Ink is Melbourne, VIC (MEL-Tullamarine) - 24.9 km / 15.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>