<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11581350</Id><Name>City Edge North Melbourne Apartment Hotel</Name><Region><Id>20247</Id><Name>City Centre</Name><CityId>15340</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>188 Peel Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Melbourne</City><State /><Zip>3051</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>0394832222</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;City Edge North Melbourne is in the heart of North Melbourne, walking distance from Queen Victoria Market and Royal Melbourne Hospital. This aparthotel is close to Crown Casino and Entertainment Complex and Melbourne Cricket Ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 52 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and 32-inch LCD televisions are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include microwaves and irons/ironing boards, and housekeeping is provided weekly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Breakfast is available for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, express check-out, and luggage storage. Planning an event in North Melbourne? This aparthotel has facilities measuring 431 square feet (40 square meters), including a meeting room.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Breakfast is available for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 52 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and 32-inch LCD televisions are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include microwaves and irons/ironing boards, and housekeeping is provided weekly.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>City Edge North Melbourne is in the heart of North Melbourne, walking distance from Queen Victoria Market and Royal Melbourne Hospital. This aparthotel is close to Crown Casino and Entertainment Complex and Melbourne Cricket Ground. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Queen Victoria Market - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Melbourne Hospital - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Women's Hospital - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Melbourne City Baths - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Flagstaff Gardens - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Melbourne - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;RMIT University - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ian Potter Museum of Art - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;State Library of Victoria - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Melbourne Gaol - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Melbourne Central - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Exhibition Building - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;QV Centre - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Carlton Gardens - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Children's Hospital - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for City Edge North Melbourne is Melbourne, VIC (MEL-Tullamarine) - 17.6 km / 10.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>