<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11584312</Id><Name>Tamar River Villas</Name><Region><Id>20264</Id><Name>Launceston</Name><CityId>15350</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>23-27 Elouera Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Launceston</City><State /><Zip>7250</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>03 6327 1022</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Tamar River Villas in Riverside, you'll be convenient to Royal Park and Queen Victoria Museum.  This apartment is within close proximity of Cataract Gorge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 25 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with stovetops and microwaves. LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as complimentary newspapers and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Tamar River Villas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, express check-out, and complimentary newspapers in the lobby. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Tamar River Villas. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 25 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with stovetops and microwaves. LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as complimentary newspapers and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Tamar River Villas in Riverside, you'll be convenient to Royal Park and Queen Victoria Museum.  This apartment is within close proximity of Cataract Gorge. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Aurora Stadium - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Launceston Tramway Museum - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Park - 2.5 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queen Victoria Art Gallery - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Penny Royal World - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Boags Brewery - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queen Victoria Museum - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;1842 Gallery - 2.7 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cataract Gorge - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Launceston College - 2.8 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albert Hall Convention Centre - 2.8 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Automobile Museum - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brisbane Street Mall - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Design Centre of Tasmania - 3 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;City Park - 3 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Tamar River Villas is Launceston, TAS (LST) - 15.8 km / 9.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>