<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11583451</Id><Name>Hawthorn Gardens Serviced Apartments</Name><Region><Id>20253</Id><Name>East Melbourne</Name><CityId>15340</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>750 Toorak Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Melbourne</City><State /><Zip>3123</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61-3-98227699</Tel><Fax>61-3-98225287</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hawthorn Gardens Serviced Apartments in Hawthorn East, you'll be close to Swinburne University of Technology and Caulfield Racecourse.  This family-friendly apartment is within close proximity of Como House and Como Centre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 28 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. 32-inch LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as separate sitting areas and microwaves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include luggage storage and laundry facilities. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10:30 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 28 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. 32-inch LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as separate sitting areas and microwaves.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hawthorn Gardens Serviced Apartments in Hawthorn East, you'll be close to Swinburne University of Technology and Caulfield Racecourse.  This family-friendly apartment is within close proximity of Como House and Como Centre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Swinburne University of Technology - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Como House - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Caulfield Racecourse - 3.7 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Como Centre - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jam Factory - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Prahran Market - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Victoria Gardens Shopping Centre - 4.6 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Astor Theatre - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Carlton and United Breweries - 5.4 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jewish Museum of Australia - 5.4 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rippon Lea House and Gardens - 5.4 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Yarra Bend Park - 5.5 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chadstone Shopping Mall - 5.7 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;AAMI Park - 5.7 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Collingwood Children's Farm - 5.8 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hawthorn Gardens Serviced Apartments is Melbourne, VIC (MEL-Tullamarine) - 25.9 km / 16.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>