<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11580441</Id><Name>Ovolo Hotel Melbourne</Name><Region><Id>20247</Id><Name>City Centre</Name><CityId>15340</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>19 Little Bourke Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Melbourne</City><State /><Zip>3000</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>0409 176 730</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Ovolo Laneways, you'll be centrally located in Melbourne, steps from Princess Theatre and Parliament House of Victoria. This 4-star aparthotel is close to Melbourne Cricket Ground and Crown Casino and Entertainment Complex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 43 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and iPads. 32-inch LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature rainfall showerheads and designer toiletries. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided on a limited basis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. Additional amenities include babysitting/childcare (surcharge) and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;For your convenience, a complimentary breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include limo/town car service, a computer station, and express check-in. Guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle for a surcharge, and self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; For your convenience, a complimentary breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. Additional amenities include babysitting/childcare (surcharge) and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 43 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and iPads. 32-inch LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature rainfall showerheads and designer toiletries. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided on a limited basis.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Ovolo Laneways, you'll be centrally located in Melbourne, steps from Princess Theatre and Parliament House of Victoria. This 4-star aparthotel is close to Melbourne Cricket Ground and Crown Casino and Entertainment Complex. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Princess Theatre - 0.1 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;Parliament House of Victoria - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Her Majesty's Theatre - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;City Museum at Old Treasury Melbourne - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Patrick's Cathedral - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Vincent's Hospital - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Treasury Gardens - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Carlton Gardens - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;QV Centre - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Melbourne Gaol - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Exhibition Building - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Regent Theatre - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Melbourne Town Hall - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Forum Theatre - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;State Library of Victoria - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Ovolo Laneways is Melbourne, VIC (MEL-Tullamarine) - 19 km / 11.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The closest major airports to Somerset Gordon Heights are:&lt;br /&gt;Melbourne, VIC (MEL-Tullamarine) - 19 km / 11.8 mi&lt;br /&gt;Melbourne, VIC (AVV-Avalon) - 49.9 km / 31 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Somerset Gordon Heights is Melbourne, VIC (MEL-Tullamarine). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Doctoroncall</Code><Text>Doctor on call</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>