<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11580089</Id><Name>CitiClub Hotel Melbourne</Name><Region><Id>20247</Id><Name>City Centre</Name><CityId>15340</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>113 Queen Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Melbourne</City><State /><Zip>3000</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61 3 9602 1800</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Citiclub Hotel is in the heart of Melbourne, walking distance from Block Arcade and Royal Arcade.  This family-friendly hotel is close to Crown Casino and Entertainment Complex and Melbourne Cricket Ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 70 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and minibars. Digital programming provides entertainment, and wired and wireless Internet access is available for a surcharge. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a nightclub or take in the view from a rooftop terrace and a terrace. Additional amenities include wireless Internet access (surcharge), concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include high-speed (wired) Internet access (surcharge), a computer station, and complimentary newspapers in the lobby. Planning an event in Melbourne? This hotel has 5382 square feet (500 square meters) of space consisting of a conference center and conference space. Guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle for a surcharge, and self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed    Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a nightclub or take in the view from a rooftop terrace and a terrace. Additional amenities include wireless Internet access (surcharge), concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 70 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and minibars. Digital programming provides entertainment, and wired and wireless Internet access is available for a surcharge. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Citiclub Hotel is in the heart of Melbourne, walking distance from Block Arcade and Royal Arcade.  This family-friendly hotel is close to Crown Casino and Entertainment Complex and Melbourne Cricket Ground. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Block Arcade - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Arcade - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Victoria University of Technology - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bourke Street Mall - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rialto Towers - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Melbourne Town Hall - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Regent Theatre - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Melbourne Aquarium - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Paul's Cathedral - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Federation Square - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;QV Centre - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Melbourne Central - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eureka Tower - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Australian Centre for the Moving Image - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eureka Skydeck 88 - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Citiclub Hotel is Melbourne, VIC (MEL-Tullamarine) - 19 km / 11.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Giftshop</Code><Text>Gift Shop</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>NightClub</Code><Text>Night Club</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>