<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11581002</Id><Name>Punthill Essendon Grand Apartments Melbourne</Name><Region><Id>20254</Id><Name>Others</Name><CityId>15340</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1142 Mount Alexander Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Melbourne</City><State /><Zip>3040</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61-0396501299</Tel><Fax>61-0396504409</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Punthill Essendon Grand in Essendon, you'll be near the airport and close to Moonee Valley Racecourse and Flemington Racecourse.  This 4.5-star apartment is within close proximity of Highpoint Shopping Centre and Royal Melbourne Showgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring microwaves and LCD televisions. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as a fitness center or take in the view from a garden.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Punthill Essendon Grand. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, dry cleaning/laundry services, and luggage storage. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Punthill Essendon Grand. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as a fitness center or take in the view from a garden. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring microwaves and LCD televisions. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Punthill Essendon Grand in Essendon, you'll be near the airport and close to Moonee Valley Racecourse and Flemington Racecourse.  This 4.5-star apartment is within close proximity of Highpoint Shopping Centre and Royal Melbourne Showgrounds. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Moonee Valley Racecourse - 3 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Highpoint Shopping Centre - 3.7 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Melbourne Showgrounds - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Northern Golf Club - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Flemington Racecourse - 4.9 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;State Netball Hockey Centre - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Martin Reserve - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Melbourne Zoo - 6 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Park - 6 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Princes Park - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Children's Hospital - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Women's Hospital - 7.2 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Seabrook Reserve - 7.2 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Melbourne - 7.3 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Melbourne Hospital - 7.3 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Punthill Essendon Grand is Melbourne, VIC (MEL-Tullamarine) - 9.9 km / 6.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The closest major airports to Punthill Essendon Grand are:&lt;br /&gt;Melbourne, VIC (MEL-Tullamarine) - 9.9 km / 6.2 mi&lt;br /&gt;Melbourne, VIC (AVV-Avalon) - 49.6 km / 30.8 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Punthill Essendon Grand is Melbourne, VIC (MEL-Tullamarine). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>