<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11584914</Id><Name>Holiday Inn Club Vacations Panama City Beach Resort</Name><Region><Id>19841</Id><Name>Panama City, FL</Name><CityId>19841</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>17001 Front Beach Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Panama City Beach</City><State>Florida</State><Zip>32413</Zip><Country>USA</Country><Tel>+18502338830</Tel><Fax>+18502338845</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>0</CountRooms></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1324503-photo-not-available-small.jpg</Url><Width>70</Width><Height>70</Height><Bytes>1454</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1324503-photo-not-available-small.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1454</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Welcome To Our Panama City Beach, FL Waterfront Resort! Holiday InnandAcirc;andreg; Club Vacations Panama City Beach Resort is located on a sugar-white beach on the Gulf shore in one of the most popular, year-round vacation destinations for Florida family fun! The newly renovated beachfront resort, completed in October 2012, features fully renovated villa accommodations that all feature your own waterfront balcony, so youandacirc;and#128;and#153;ll always enjoy the spectacular emerald Gulf water views and stunning sunsets for which this vacation paradise is known. And if lounging by the waterfront pool and relaxing hot tub, keeping your exercise on-track at our fitness center and the kids enjoying the Activities Center and beach appeals to you, weandacirc;and#128;and#153;ve got you covered! But it doesnandacirc;and#128;and#153;t end there. All along the 15 miles of beautiful shoreline on the Panama City Beach coast, youandacirc;and#128;and#153;ll find just the right vacation activities to appeal to any age and taste. Pier Park, the areaandacirc;and#128;and#153;s largest waterside entertainment, shopping and dining complex with over 100 venues is within walking distance.There are also a wide range of other activities all along the shore to enjoy. Area dolphin and eco tours, family attractions and activities of almost every type, great dining options and some of the most beautiful waterfront towns and artsy villages in the country along Rt. 30A are all available nearby to make your Florida family vacation a memorable one.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>Short</Type><Text>Welcome To Our Panama City Beach; FL Waterfront Resort</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>