<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11583101</Id><Name>Melbourne Short Stay At SouthBankOne</Name><Region><Id>20248</Id><Name>Southbank</Name><CityId>15340</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>180 City Road, Southbank</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Melbourne</City><State /><Zip>3006</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>0396827311</Tel><Fax>61 3 8256 7503</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Melbourne Short Stay Apartment at SouthbankOne, you'll be centrally located in Southbank, minutes from Eureka Skydeck 88 and Crown Casino and Entertainment Complex.  This 4.5-star apartment is close to Melbourne Cricket Ground and St. Kilda Beach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 60 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. 32-inch LCD televisions with premium TV channels provide entertainment, with wired and wireless Internet access available for a surcharge. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and separate sitting areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities, including an indoor pool, an outdoor tennis court, and a fitness center. This apartment also features babysitting/childcare (surcharge), tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of the apartment's room service (during limited hours).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include limo/town car service, express check-out, and dry cleaning/laundry services. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of the apartment's room service (during limited hours). &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities, including an indoor pool, an outdoor tennis court, and a fitness center. This apartment also features babysitting/childcare (surcharge), tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 60 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. 32-inch LCD televisions with premium TV channels provide entertainment, with wired and wireless Internet access available for a surcharge. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and separate sitting areas.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Melbourne Short Stay Apartment at SouthbankOne, you'll be centrally located in Southbank, minutes from Eureka Skydeck 88 and Crown Casino and Entertainment Complex.  This 4.5-star apartment is close to Melbourne Cricket Ground and St. Kilda Beach. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Eureka Skydeck 88 - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Melbourne Recital Centre - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eureka Tower - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Crown Casino and Entertainment Complex - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Australian Centre for Contemporary Art - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Primrose Potter Australian Ballet Centre - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Melbourne Aquarium - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Gallery of Victoria - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Melbourne Arts Centre - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Victoria University of Technology - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hamer Hall - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rialto Towers - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Polly Woodside - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Paul's Cathedral - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Federation Square - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Melbourne Short Stay Apartment at SouthbankOne is Melbourne, VIC (MEL-Tullamarine) - 19.8 km / 12.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndoorPool</Code><Text>Indoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>