<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11584276</Id><Name>Shambhala Byron Bay</Name><Region><Id>20267</Id><Name>Byron Bay</Name><CityId>15351</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>14 Childe Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Byron Bay</City><State /><Zip>2481</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>+61 2 66807563</Tel><Fax>+61 2 66807563</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Shambhala@Byron in Byron Bay, you'll be close to Tyagarah Nature Reserve and Wategos Beach.  This 4-star apartment is within the vicinity of Cape Byron Lighthouse and Byron Bay Golf Course.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 4 air-conditioned rooms featuring private spa tubs and flat-screen televisions. Kitchens are outfitted with refrigerators. Cable programming and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include safes and coffee/tea makers, and you can also request rollaway/extra beds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including a spa tub, a sauna, and a steam room. This apartment also features complimentary wireless Internet access and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including a spa tub, a sauna, and a steam room. This apartment also features complimentary wireless Internet access and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 4 air-conditioned rooms featuring private spa tubs and flat-screen televisions. Kitchens are outfitted with refrigerators. Cable programming and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include safes and coffee/tea makers, and you can also request rollaway/extra beds.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Shambhala@Byron in Byron Bay, you'll be close to Tyagarah Nature Reserve and Wategos Beach.  This 4-star apartment is within the vicinity of Cape Byron Lighthouse and Byron Bay Golf Course. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Tyagarah Nature Reserve - 3.5 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wategos Beach - 3.7 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cape Byron Lighthouse - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Byron Bay Golf Course - 5.1 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tallow Beach - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kings Beach - 8 km / 4.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lake Ainsworth Sport and Recreation Centre - 16.7 km / 10.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lennox Head Surf Life Saving Club - 17.1 km / 10.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ballina Jockey Club - 24.7 km / 15.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ballina Golf Club - 24.8 km / 15.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ballina Fair Shopping Centre - 25.5 km / 15.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shelly Beach - 25.8 km / 16 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lighthouse Beach - 26.5 km / 16.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ballina Naval and Maritime Museum - 27.1 km / 16.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Shambhala@Byron is Gold Coast, QLD (OOL-Coolangatta) - 52.3 km / 32.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>