<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11581381</Id><Name>Quest Brighton On The Bay</Name><Region><Id>20254</Id><Name>Others</Name><CityId>15340</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>250 Esplanade</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Melbourne</City><State /><Zip>3186</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61 3 95915000</Tel><Fax>+61 (3) 95915006</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Quest Brighton on the Bay in Brighton, you'll be near the bay and close to Brighton Beach and Luna Park. This 4.5-star aparthotel is within close proximity of Elwood Beach and Rippon Lea House and Gardens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 59 air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take time to pamper yourself with a visit to the full-service spa. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, dry cleaning/laundry services, and luggage storage. Planning an event in Brighton? This aparthotel has 11 square feet (1 square meters) of space consisting of conference space and a meeting room. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take time to pamper yourself with a visit to the full-service spa. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 59 air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Quest Brighton on the Bay in Brighton, you'll be near the bay and close to Brighton Beach and Luna Park. This 4.5-star aparthotel is within close proximity of Elwood Beach and Rippon Lea House and Gardens. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Brighton Beach - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Elwood Beach - 2.3 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rippon Lea House and Gardens - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Luna Park - 4.6 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Acland Street - 4.6 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palais Theatre - 4.8 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Kilda Pier - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Kilda Sea Baths - 5.1 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Kilda Beach - 5.1 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jewish Museum of Australia - 5.4 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Astor Theatre - 5.7 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Caulfield Racecourse - 5.7 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albert Park Golf Course - 6.8 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Moorabin Hospital - 7 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Prahran Market - 7 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Quest Brighton on the Bay is Melbourne, VIC (MEL-Tullamarine) - 29.2 km / 18.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>