<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11584616</Id><Name>The Beach Resort Cabarita</Name><Region><Id>20268</Id><Name>Kingscliff</Name><CityId>15351</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>2-6 Pandanus Parade</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Kingscliff</City><State /><Zip>2488</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>+61 2 6670 0900</Tel><Fax>+61 2 6670 0999</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at The Beach Cabarita in Cabarita Beach, you'll be on the beach and within the vicinity of Tropical Fruit World and Kingscliff War Memorial.  This 4.5-star apartment is within the region of Coolangatta and Tweed Heads Golf Club and Fingal Lighthouse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 57 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private furnished balconies. Plasma televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected. Conveniences include separate sitting areas and microwaves, and housekeeping is provided weekly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Dip into one of the 3 outdoor swimming pools or enjoy other recreational amenities, which include a fitness center. Additional features include wireless Internet access (surcharge), babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and a hair salon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the apartment's beachfront restaurant, which features a bar. Dining is also available at a coffee shop/café. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include limo/town car service, dry cleaning/laundry services, and luggage storage. Guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle for a surcharge, and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the apartment's beachfront restaurant, which features a bar. Dining is also available at a coffee shop/café. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Dip into one of the 3 outdoor swimming pools or enjoy other recreational amenities, which include a fitness center. Additional features include wireless Internet access (surcharge), babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and a hair salon. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 57 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private furnished balconies. Plasma televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected. Conveniences include separate sitting areas and microwaves, and housekeeping is provided weekly.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at The Beach Cabarita in Cabarita Beach, you'll be on the beach and within the vicinity of Tropical Fruit World and Kingscliff War Memorial.  This 4.5-star apartment is within the region of Coolangatta and Tweed Heads Golf Club and Fingal Lighthouse. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Tropical Fruit World - 7.2 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kingscliff War Memorial - 9.1 km / 5.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Coolangatta and Tweed Heads Golf Club - 13.8 km / 8.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fingal Lighthouse - 14.6 km / 9.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Centro Tweed - 18 km / 11.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Border Park Raceway - 18.3 km / 11.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Duranbah Beach - 18.4 km / 11.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Greenmount Beach - 18.6 km / 11.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Strand - 18.6 km / 11.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Coolangatta Beach - 18.6 km / 11.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Point Danger Light - 18.7 km / 11.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Point Danger - 18.7 km / 11.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kirra Beach - 18.8 km / 11.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Snapper Rocks - 18.8 km / 11.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bilinga Beach - 19 km / 11.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Beach Cabarita is Gold Coast, QLD (OOL-Coolangatta) - 19.2 km / 12 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BeautyShop</Code><Text>Beauty Shop</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>