<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11586337</Id><Name>Glen Villa Resort</Name><Region><Id>20267</Id><Name>Byron Bay</Name><CityId>15351</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Butler Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Byron Bay</City><State /><Zip>2481</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61 2 6685 7382</Tel><Fax>61 2 6685 7382</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Glen Villa Resort places you in the heart of Byron Bay, convenient to Wategos Beach and Cape Byron Lighthouse.  This caravan park/campground is within close proximity of Byron Bay Golf Course and Tallow Beach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 40 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and stovetops. Rooms have private patios. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and LCD televisions are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include microwaves and coffee/tea makers, and you can also request irons/ironing boards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a garden. Additional features include tour/ticket assistance, a picnic area, and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, luggage storage, and laundry facilities. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a garden. Additional features include tour/ticket assistance, a picnic area, and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 40 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and stovetops. Rooms have private patios. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and LCD televisions are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include microwaves and coffee/tea makers, and you can also request irons/ironing boards.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Glen Villa Resort places you in the heart of Byron Bay, convenient to Wategos Beach and Cape Byron Lighthouse.  This caravan park/campground is within close proximity of Byron Bay Golf Course and Tallow Beach. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Wategos Beach - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cape Byron Lighthouse - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Byron Bay Golf Course - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tallow Beach - 4.1 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tyagarah Nature Reserve - 5.8 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kings Beach - 6 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lake Ainsworth Sport and Recreation Centre - 15 km / 9.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lennox Head Surf Life Saving Club - 15.4 km / 9.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ballina Golf Club - 23.1 km / 14.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ballina Jockey Club - 23.2 km / 14.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ballina Fair Shopping Centre - 24 km / 14.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shelly Beach - 24.1 km / 15 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lighthouse Beach - 24.8 km / 15.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ballina Naval and Maritime Museum - 25.5 km / 15.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Glen Villa Resort is Gold Coast, QLD (OOL-Coolangatta) - 54.3 km / 33.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>