<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11584301</Id><Name>Byron Bay Farmstay</Name><Region><Id>20267</Id><Name>Byron Bay</Name><CityId>15351</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>436 Bangalow Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Byron Bay</City><State /><Zip>2481</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>+61 2 6687 0468</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Byron Bay, Byron Bay Farmstay is on a lake and close to Byron Bay Golf Course and Tallow Beach.  This family-friendly apartment is within the vicinity of Kings Beach and Wategos Beach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 6 individually furnished guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private furnished balconies. 19-inch LCD televisions with DVD players and digital programming provide entertainment. Conveniences include complimentary weekday newspapers and microwaves, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as a picnic area and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby and laundry facilities. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as a picnic area and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 6 individually furnished guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private furnished balconies. 19-inch LCD televisions with DVD players and digital programming provide entertainment. Conveniences include complimentary weekday newspapers and microwaves, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (surcharge).</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Byron Bay, Byron Bay Farmstay is on a lake and close to Byron Bay Golf Course and Tallow Beach.  This family-friendly apartment is within the vicinity of Kings Beach and Wategos Beach. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Byron Bay Golf Course - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tallow Beach - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kings Beach - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wategos Beach - 6.7 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cape Byron Lighthouse - 6.8 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tyagarah Nature Reserve - 7.4 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lake Ainsworth Sport and Recreation Centre - 12.3 km / 7.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lennox Head Surf Life Saving Club - 12.7 km / 7.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ballina Jockey Club - 20 km / 12.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ballina Golf Club - 20.2 km / 12.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ballina Fair Shopping Centre - 20.8 km / 13 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shelly Beach - 21.3 km / 13.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lighthouse Beach - 22 km / 13.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ballina Naval and Maritime Museum - 22.4 km / 13.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Byron Bay Farmstay is Ballina, NSW (BNK-Ballina - Byron Gateway) - 18.5 km / 11.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>