<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11596833</Id><Name>Sundeck Gardens Holiday Apartments Sunshine Coast</Name><Region><Id>20296</Id><Name>Maroochydore</Name><CityId>15372</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>70-78 Alexandra Parade</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Sunshine Coast</City><State /><Zip>4558</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61-410129701</Tel><Fax>61-7-54514118</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Sundeck Gardens in Maroochydore, you'll be by the ocean and convenient to Sunshine Plaza and Mooloolaba Beach.  This beach apartment is within close proximity of Underwater World Sea Life and Twin Waters Golf Club.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 20 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private furnished balconies or patios. Flat-screen televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected. Conveniences include separate sitting areas and microwaves, and housekeeping is provided weekly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities including a spa tub and a seasonal outdoor pool. Additional features include wireless Internet access (surcharge), tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, luggage storage, and an elevator (lift).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities including a spa tub and a seasonal outdoor pool. Additional features include wireless Internet access (surcharge), tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 20 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private furnished balconies or patios. Flat-screen televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected. Conveniences include separate sitting areas and microwaves, and housekeeping is provided weekly.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Sundeck Gardens in Maroochydore, you'll be by the ocean and convenient to Sunshine Plaza and Mooloolaba Beach.  This beach apartment is within close proximity of Underwater World Sea Life and Twin Waters Golf Club. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Sunshine Plaza - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mooloolaba Beach - 3 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Underwater World Sea Life - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Twin Waters Golf Club - 3.8 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kawana Beach - 6 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mt Coolum Golf Club - 10.4 km / 6.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Big Pineapple - 11.3 km / 7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queensland Zoo - 11.4 km / 7.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aussie World - 11.5 km / 7.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dickey Beach - 13.9 km / 8.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Coolum Beach - 14.4 km / 9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Moffat Beach - 15 km / 9.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Caloundra Events Center - 16.1 km / 10 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shelly Beach - 16.1 km / 10 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kings Beach - 16.4 km / 10.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Sundeck Gardens is Maroochydore, QLD (MCY-Sunshine Coast) - 6.2 km / 3.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>