<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11594737</Id><Name>Mylos Holiday Apartments</Name><Region><Id>20296</Id><Name>Maroochydore</Name><CityId>15372</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Maroubra Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Alexandra Headland</City><State /><Zip>4572</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>07 5443 4077</Tel><Fax>07 5479 2737</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Mylos Apartments in Alexandra Headland, you'll be near the beach and convenient to Sunshine Plaza and Mooloolaba Beach.  This family-friendly aparthotel is within close proximity of Underwater World Sea Life and Twin Waters Golf Club.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and microwaves. Rooms have private balconies. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as separate sitting areas and washers/dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including an outdoor pool, a waterslide, and a sauna. Additional features include wireless Internet access (surcharge), an arcade/game room, and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Mylos Apartments.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Mylos Apartments. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including an outdoor pool, a waterslide, and a sauna. Additional features include wireless Internet access (surcharge), an arcade/game room, and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and microwaves. Rooms have private balconies. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as separate sitting areas and washers/dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Mylos Apartments in Alexandra Headland, you'll be near the beach and convenient to Sunshine Plaza and Mooloolaba Beach.  This family-friendly aparthotel is within close proximity of Underwater World Sea Life and Twin Waters Golf Club. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Sunshine Plaza - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mooloolaba Beach - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Underwater World Sea Life - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Twin Waters Golf Club - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kawana Beach - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mt Coolum Golf Club - 10.8 km / 6.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aussie World - 11.2 km / 7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Big Pineapple - 11.3 km / 7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queensland Zoo - 11.4 km / 7.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dickey Beach - 13.5 km / 8.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Moffat Beach - 14.6 km / 9.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Coolum Beach - 14.9 km / 9.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Caloundra Events Center - 15.7 km / 9.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shelly Beach - 15.7 km / 9.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kings Beach - 16 km / 9.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Maroochydore, QLD (MCY-Sunshine Coast) - 6.6 km / 4.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;Brisbane, QLD (BNE) - 80.3 km / 49.9 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Mylos Apartments is Brisbane, QLD (BNE). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>