<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11593787</Id><Name>Summerhill Motor Inn</Name><Region><Id>20291</Id><Name>Bega</Name><CityId>15367</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>22-26  Merimbula Drive</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>South Coast</City><State /><Zip>2548</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>612 6495 3111</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Summerhill Motor Inn is centrally located in Merimbula, walking distance from Merimbula Imlay Historical Society and close to Main Beach Recreation Reserve.  This motel is within close proximity of Magic Mountain Recreational Park and Merimbula Aquarium.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 18 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and microwaves. Rooms have private balconies. 32-inch flat-screen televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature rainfall showerheads and complimentary toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a garden. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of the motel's room service (during limited hours).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include multilingual staff and laundry facilities.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of the motel's room service (during limited hours). &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a garden. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 18 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and microwaves. Rooms have private balconies. 32-inch flat-screen televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature rainfall showerheads and complimentary toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Summerhill Motor Inn is centrally located in Merimbula, walking distance from Merimbula Imlay Historical Society and close to Main Beach Recreation Reserve.  This motel is within close proximity of Magic Mountain Recreational Park and Merimbula Aquarium. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Merimbula Imlay Historical Society - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Main Beach Recreation Reserve - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Magic Mountain Recreational Park - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Merimbula Aquarium - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Short Point Beach - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tura Beach Country Club - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pambula Merimbula Golf Club - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pambula Beach - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Potoroo Palace - 7.3 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Yurammie State Forest - 11 km / 6.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ben Boyd National Park - 11.9 km / 7.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eden Golf Course - 17.7 km / 11 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tathra Beach - 19.2 km / 11.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aslings Beach - 19.2 km / 11.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tathra Wharf - 19.4 km / 12.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Merimbula, NSW (MIM) - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi&lt;br /&gt;Canberra, ACT (CBR-Canberra Intl.) - 187.2 km / 116.3 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Summerhill Motor Inn is Canberra, ACT (CBR-Canberra Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>