<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11590762</Id><Name>Perth Vineyards Holiday Park</Name><Region><Id>20290</Id><Name>Others</Name><CityId>15359</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>91 Benara Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Perth</City><State /><Zip>6055</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>08 9279 6700</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at BIG4 Perth Vineyards Holiday Park in Caversham, you'll be in the suburbs and minutes from Lilac Hill Estate, and close to Pinelli Wines.  This 4-star cabin is within close proximity of Sandalford Winery and Houghton Winery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 19 guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and stovetops. Conveniences include microwaves, and irons/ironing boards can be requested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool or make use of other amenities including barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite from a grocery/convenience store serving guests of BIG4 Perth Vineyards Holiday Park.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include high-speed (wired) Internet access (surcharge) and laundry facilities. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite from a grocery/convenience store serving guests of BIG4 Perth Vineyards Holiday Park. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy the recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool or make use of other amenities including barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 19 guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and stovetops. Conveniences include microwaves, and irons/ironing boards can be requested.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at BIG4 Perth Vineyards Holiday Park in Caversham, you'll be in the suburbs and minutes from Lilac Hill Estate, and close to Pinelli Wines.  This 4-star cabin is within close proximity of Sandalford Winery and Houghton Winery. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Lilac Hill Estate - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pinelli Wines - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sandalford Winery - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Houghton Winery - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Caversham Wildlife Park - 4.8 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Whiteman Park - 5.1 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bayswater Waves - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Little River Winery - 6.7 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ascot Racecourse - 8 km / 5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Talijancich Winery - 8.4 km / 5.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;SuperCars Perth - 8.5 km / 5.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tranby House - 9.2 km / 5.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mann Winery - 10 km / 6.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Belmont Racecourse - 10.6 km / 6.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Burswood Dome - 11.3 km / 7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for BIG4 Perth Vineyards Holiday Park is Perth, WA (PER) - 6.4 km / 4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>