<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11594698</Id><Name>Macquarie Lodge Sunshine Coast</Name><Region><Id>20298</Id><Name>Noosa Head</Name><CityId>15372</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>53 Banksia Avenue</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Sunshine Coast</City><State /><Zip>4567</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61-754-480-822</Tel><Fax>61-754480248</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Macquarie Lodge Luxury Apartments in Noosa Heads (Noosa), you'll be convenient to Noosa Beach and Noosa National Park.  This 4.5-star lodge is within close proximity of Sunshine Beach Village Shops and Ed Webb Park.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 36 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while DVD players and cable programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature deep soaking bathtubs and complimentary toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities including an outdoor pool and a spa tub. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, dry cleaning/laundry services, and an elevator (lift). Guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle for a surcharge, and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities including an outdoor pool and a spa tub. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 36 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while DVD players and cable programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature deep soaking bathtubs and complimentary toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Macquarie Lodge Luxury Apartments in Noosa Heads (Noosa), you'll be convenient to Noosa Beach and Noosa National Park.  This 4.5-star lodge is within close proximity of Sunshine Beach Village Shops and Ed Webb Park. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Noosa Beach - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Noosa National Park - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sunshine Beach Village Shops - 2.8 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ed Webb Park - 2.8 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Noosa Marina - 4.6 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Coolum Beach - 15.3 km / 9.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eumundi Market - 16.3 km / 10.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cooroy Golf Club - 17.8 km / 11.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mt Coolum Golf Club - 19.5 km / 12.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ginger Factory - 22 km / 13.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Twin Waters Golf Club - 26.3 km / 16.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sunshine Plaza - 29.1 km / 18.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mooloolaba Beach - 32.2 km / 20 mi &lt;br /&gt;Underwater World Sea Life - 32.5 km / 20.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Big Pineapple - 32.6 km / 20.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Macquarie Lodge Luxury Apartments is Brisbane, QLD (BNE) - 110.5 km / 68.6 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Macquarie Lodge Noosa Heads is Brisbane, QLD (BNE) - 110.5 km / 68.7 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>