<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>115987</Id><Name>LHotel di Pisa (Formerly Easy Hotel)</Name><Region><Id>21021</Id><Name>Pisa</Name><CityId>17136</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Via Statale Abetone 13 San Giuliano Terme</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Pisa 56017</City><State /><Zip /><Country>Italy</Country><Tel>39-050-815029</Tel><Fax>39-050-818811</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>43.7609479</Latitude><Longitude>10.4413053</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/PSA-GRA5hotel_Exterior_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>242</Height><Bytes>32281</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/PSA-GRA5hotel_Exterior_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2756</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/PSA-GRA5hotel_Lobby_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>193</Height><Bytes>19165</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/PSA-GRA5hotel_Lobby_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2384</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/PSA-GRA5hotel_Meeting_Room_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>238</Height><Bytes>20830</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/PSA-GRA5hotel_Meeting_Room_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2380</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/PSA-GRA5hotel_Other_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>239</Height><Bytes>15826</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/PSA-GRA5hotel_Other_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1870</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/PSA-GRA5hotel_Guest_Room_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>297</Height><Bytes>18427</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/PSA-GRA5hotel_Guest_Room_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1801</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/PSA-GRA5hotel_Spa_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>239</Height><Bytes>13361</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/PSA-GRA5hotel_Spa_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1756</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/PSA-GRA5hotel_Spa_2.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>239</Height><Bytes>10533</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/PSA-GRA5hotel_Spa_2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1573</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at LHotel di Pisa in San Giuliano Terme, you'll be near the airport and within the vicinity of San Zeno Church and Leaning Tower. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of Arena Garibaldi and Santa Caterina.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 100 guestrooms featuring refrigerators. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature bidets and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and day beds, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (complimentary).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. You're sure to appreciate the recreational amenities, including a health club, a sauna, and a steam room. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar and a garden view. You can also stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, express check-in, and express check-out. Event facilities at this hotel consist of a conference center and conference space. Guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle for a surcharge, and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar and a garden view. You can also stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. You're sure to appreciate the recreational amenities, including a health club, a sauna, and a steam room. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 100 guestrooms featuring refrigerators. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature bidets and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and day beds, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (complimentary).</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at LHotel di Pisa in San Giuliano Terme, you'll be near the airport and within the vicinity of San Zeno Church and Leaning Tower. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of Arena Garibaldi and Santa Caterina. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;San Zeno Church - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Arena Garibaldi - 5.1 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Santa Caterina - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sant'Anna School of Advanced Studies - 5.4 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Francis Church - 5.5 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museo dell'Opera del Duomo - 5.5 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palazzo Agostini - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Leaning Tower - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cathedral of Pisa - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Camposanto - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pisa Baptistry - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;University Hospital of Santa Chiara - 5.7 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Paolo all'Orto - 5.7 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Scuola Normale - 5.7 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cathedral of St. Ranieri - 5.7 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for LHotel di Pisa is Pisa (PSA-Galileo Galilei) - 7.7 km / 4.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Hotel Granduca is Pisa (PSA-Galileo Galilei) - 7.7 km / 4.8 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Sauna</Code><Text>Sauna</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>