<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11591870</Id><Name>Pool Resort Port Douglas</Name><Region><Id>15361</Id><Name>Port Douglas</Name><CityId>15361</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>19 St Crispins Ave</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Port Douglas</City><State /><Zip>4877</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>07 4084 3400</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Pool Port Douglas in Port Douglas, you'll be next to a golf course and convenient to Four Mile Beach Park and Wildlife Habitat.  This 4.5-star apartment is within close proximity of Marina Mirage and St Mary's by the Sea Chapel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 72 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. 80-cm LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as separate sitting areas and microwaves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with onsite body treatments or enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool. This apartment also features wireless Internet access (surcharge), tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge) that operates within 5 km.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include luggage storage, laundry facilities, and a safe deposit box at the front desk. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available 24 hours), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with onsite body treatments or enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool. This apartment also features wireless Internet access (surcharge), tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge) that operates within 5 km. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 72 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. 80-cm LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as separate sitting areas and microwaves.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Pool Port Douglas in Port Douglas, you'll be next to a golf course and convenient to Four Mile Beach Park and Wildlife Habitat.  This 4.5-star apartment is within close proximity of Marina Mirage and St Mary's by the Sea Chapel. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Four Mile Beach Park - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wildlife Habitat - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marina Mirage - 3.5 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Mary's by the Sea Chapel - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sugar Wharf - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Anzac Park - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mossman Gorge Center - 12.9 km / 8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mossman Gorge - 13.5 km / 8.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Daintree Rainforest - 15.7 km / 9.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Pool Port Douglas is Cairns, QLD (CNS-Cairns Intl.) - 50.6 km / 31.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>