<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11592211</Id><Name>El Paso Motor Inn</Name><Region><Id>15362</Id><Name>Port Macquarie</Name><CityId>15362</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>29 Clarence Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Port Macquarie</City><State /><Zip>2444</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>0265831944</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;El Paso Motor Inn is centrally located in Port Macquarie, walking distance from Mid North Coast Maritime Museum Pilot Boat Shed and close to Port Macquarie Astronomical Association Observatory.  This 4-star motel is within close proximity of Macquarie Nature Reserve and Roto House.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 56 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and iPod docking stations. Rooms have private furnished balconies or patios. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a rooftop terrace. Additional features at this Art Deco motel include complimentary wireless Internet access, a hair salon, and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the motel's restaurant, which serves breakfast and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, dry cleaning/laundry services, and luggage storage. A roundtrip airport shuttle is complimentary at scheduled times.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 1 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the motel's restaurant, which serves breakfast and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a rooftop terrace. Additional features at this Art Deco motel include complimentary wireless Internet access, a hair salon, and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 56 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and iPod docking stations. Rooms have private furnished balconies or patios. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>El Paso Motor Inn is centrally located in Port Macquarie, walking distance from Mid North Coast Maritime Museum Pilot Boat Shed and close to Port Macquarie Astronomical Association Observatory.  This 4-star motel is within close proximity of Macquarie Nature Reserve and Roto House. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Mid North Coast Maritime Museum Pilot Boat Shed - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Port Macquarie Astronomical Association Observatory - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Macquarie Nature Reserve - 1.7 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Roto House - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Koala Hospital - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tacking Point Lighthouse - 5.7 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cassegrain Winery - 8.2 km / 5.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Billabong Koala Wildlife Park - 9.3 km / 5.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Long Point Vineyard &amp; Art Gallery - 13.6 km / 8.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Timbertown Heritage Theme Park - 19.3 km / 12 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for El Paso Motor Inn is Port Macquarie, NSW (PQQ) - 4 km / 2.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>