<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11591388</Id><Name>The Pavilions</Name><Region><Id>15361</Id><Name>Port Douglas</Name><CityId>15361</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>35 Macrossan St</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Port Douglas</City><State /><Zip>4877</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61-740-994-888</Tel><Fax>61-740-996-025</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at The Pavilions places you in the heart of Port Douglas, walking distance from St Mary's by the Sea Chapel and Marina Mirage.  This 4-star apartment is within close proximity of Sugar Wharf and Anzac Park.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 20 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and DVD players. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature jetted bathtubs and complimentary toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss out on recreational opportunities including an outdoor pool and a spa tub. Additional amenities at this Art Deco apartment include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and tour/ticket assistance. Guests can get around on the shuttle (surcharge), which operates within 8 km.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include limo/town car service and laundry facilities. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available 24 hours), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at Noon  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Don’t miss out on recreational opportunities including an outdoor pool and a spa tub. Additional amenities at this Art Deco apartment include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and tour/ticket assistance. Guests can get around on the shuttle (surcharge), which operates within 8 km. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 20 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and DVD players. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature jetted bathtubs and complimentary toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at The Pavilions places you in the heart of Port Douglas, walking distance from St Mary's by the Sea Chapel and Marina Mirage.  This 4-star apartment is within close proximity of Sugar Wharf and Anzac Park. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;St Mary's by the Sea Chapel - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marina Mirage - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sugar Wharf - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Anzac Park - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Four Mile Beach Park - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wildlife Habitat - 4.9 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mossman Gorge Center - 12.2 km / 7.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mossman Gorge - 12.9 km / 8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Daintree Rainforest - 14.4 km / 9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Pavilions is Port Douglas, QLD (PTI-Port Douglas Heliport) - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>