<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11591379</Id><Name>Macrossan House Boutique Holiday Apartments</Name><Region><Id>15361</Id><Name>Port Douglas</Name><CityId>15361</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>19 Macrossan Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Port Douglas</City><State /><Zip>4871</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61 7 4099 4366</Tel><Fax>-</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Macrossan House places you in the heart of Port Douglas, walking distance from St Mary's by the Sea Chapel and Sugar Wharf.  This 4-star apartment is within close proximity of Anzac Park and Marina Mirage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 16 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. 32-inch LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include safes and microwaves, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreational opportunities offered, including outdoor tennis courts, a health club, and an outdoor pool. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and tour/ticket assistance. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include limo/town car service, express check-in, and luggage storage. A shuttle from the airport to the hotel is provided for a surcharge (available 24 hours), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreational opportunities offered, including outdoor tennis courts, a health club, and an outdoor pool. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and tour/ticket assistance. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 16 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. 32-inch LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include safes and microwaves, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (surcharge).</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Macrossan House places you in the heart of Port Douglas, walking distance from St Mary's by the Sea Chapel and Sugar Wharf.  This 4-star apartment is within close proximity of Anzac Park and Marina Mirage. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;St Mary's by the Sea Chapel - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sugar Wharf - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Anzac Park - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marina Mirage - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Four Mile Beach Park - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wildlife Habitat - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mossman Gorge Center - 12.1 km / 7.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mossman Gorge - 12.8 km / 7.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Daintree Rainforest - 14.3 km / 8.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Macrossan House is Cairns, QLD (CNS-Cairns Intl.) - 53.7 km / 33.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>