<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11594181</Id><Name>Spicers Clovelly Estate</Name><Region><Id>20296</Id><Name>Maroochydore</Name><CityId>15372</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>68 Balmoral Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Sunshine Coast</City><State /><Zip>4560</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>07 54521111</Tel><Fax>07 54429311</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Montville, Spicers Clovelly Estate is close to Lake Baroon and Sunshine Coast Hinterland Great Walk. This 5-star guesthouse is within the vicinity of Kondalilla National Park and Queensland Zoo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and minibars. Digital programming and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and irons/ironing boards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Relax at the full-service spa, where you can enjoy massages and facials. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and a fireplace in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Spicers Clovelly Estate. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, luggage storage, and a library. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed    Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Spicers Clovelly Estate. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Relax at the full-service spa, where you can enjoy massages and facials. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and a fireplace in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and minibars. Digital programming and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and irons/ironing boards.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Montville, Spicers Clovelly Estate is close to Lake Baroon and Sunshine Coast Hinterland Great Walk. This 5-star guesthouse is within the vicinity of Kondalilla National Park and Queensland Zoo. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Lake Baroon - 3.7 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sunshine Coast Hinterland Great Walk - 3.8 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kondalilla National Park - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queensland Zoo - 9 km / 5.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Big Pineapple - 9 km / 5.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mapleton Falls National Park - 9.8 km / 6.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maleny Botanic Gardens - 11.4 km / 7.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Landsborough Museum - 13.7 km / 8.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aussie World - 15.3 km / 9.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Australia Zoo - 16.3 km / 10.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ginger Factory - 16.9 km / 10.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sunshine Plaza - 19.1 km / 11.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Twin Waters Golf Club - 19.5 km / 12.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mooloolaba Beach - 21.6 km / 13.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Underwater World Sea Life - 21.7 km / 13.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Spicers Clovelly Estate is Brisbane, QLD (BNE) - 79.4 km / 49.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>