<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11592191</Id><Name>Ambassador Motel</Name><Region><Id>15365</Id><Name>Rockhampton</Name><CityId>15365</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>353 Yaamba Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Rockhampton</City><State /><Zip>4701</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>07 4928 2222</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Ambassador Motel in Rockhampton, you'll be in the business district and minutes from Stockland Shopping Centre, and close to Central Queensland University.  This family-friendly motel is within close proximity of Rockhampton Art Gallery and Pilbeam Theatre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 32 air-conditioned rooms featuring microwaves and DVD players. Flat-screen televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers and ceiling fans, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the motel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The front desk is staffed during limited hours. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 11 AM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the motel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 32 air-conditioned rooms featuring microwaves and DVD players. Flat-screen televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers and ceiling fans, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Ambassador Motel in Rockhampton, you'll be in the business district and minutes from Stockland Shopping Centre, and close to Central Queensland University.  This family-friendly motel is within close proximity of Rockhampton Art Gallery and Pilbeam Theatre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Stockland Shopping Centre - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Central Queensland University - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rockhampton Art Gallery - 3 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pilbeam Theatre - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Archer Park Station &amp; Steam Train Museum - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aboriginal Dreamtime Cultural Centre - 3.8 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mount Archer National Park - 5.7 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rockhampton Botanic Gardens and Zoo - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Ambassador Motel is Rockhampton, QLD (ROK) - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>&lt;b&gt;Rockhampton (ROK):&lt;/b&gt; Approximate distance to Ambassador Motel is 6 km.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>