<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11592195</Id><Name>Sapphire Waters Motor Inn</Name><Region><Id>20293</Id><Name>Merimbula</Name><CityId>15367</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>32-34 Merimbula Drive</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Merimbula</City><State /><Zip>2548</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>02) 64951999</Tel><Fax>(02) 64953550</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Sapphire Waters Motor Inn places you in the heart of Merimbula, convenient to Main Beach Recreation Reserve and Magic Mountain Recreational Park.  This family-friendly motel is within the vicinity of Pambula Merimbula Golf Club and Pambula Beach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 29 guestrooms featuring refrigerators and minibars. LCD televisions with digital programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as coffee/tea makers and irons/ironing boards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss out on recreational opportunities including an outdoor pool and a spa tub. This motel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, tour/ticket assistance, and a picnic area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a computer station and laundry facilities. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Don’t miss out on recreational opportunities including an outdoor pool and a spa tub. This motel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, tour/ticket assistance, and a picnic area. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 29 guestrooms featuring refrigerators and minibars. LCD televisions with digital programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as coffee/tea makers and irons/ironing boards.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Sapphire Waters Motor Inn places you in the heart of Merimbula, convenient to Main Beach Recreation Reserve and Magic Mountain Recreational Park.  This family-friendly motel is within the vicinity of Pambula Merimbula Golf Club and Pambula Beach. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Merimbula Imlay Historical Society - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Main Beach Recreation Reserve - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Magic Mountain Recreational Park - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Merimbula Aquarium - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Short Point Beach - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tura Beach Country Club - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pambula Merimbula Golf Club - 4.1 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pambula Beach - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Potoroo Palace - 7.2 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Yurammie State Forest - 11 km / 6.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ben Boyd National Park - 11.9 km / 7.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eden Golf Course - 17.7 km / 11 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aslings Beach - 19.2 km / 11.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tathra Beach - 19.2 km / 11.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tathra Wharf - 19.5 km / 12.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Merimbula, NSW (MIM) - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi&lt;br /&gt;Sydney, NSW (SYD-Kingsford Smith Intl.) - 347.5 km / 215.9 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Sapphire Waters Motor Inn is Sydney, NSW (SYD-Kingsford Smith Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>