<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11603061</Id><Name>Avoca Lodge</Name><Region><Id>20310</Id><Name>Rest of Sydney</Name><CityId>15375</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>235 Avoca Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Sydney</City><State /><Zip>2031</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>+61293997779</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Avoca Lodge in Randwick (Randwick - Coogee), you'll be minutes from Prince of Wales Hospital and Community Health Service and close to Bondi Beach.  This hotel is within close proximity of University of New South Wales and Coogee Beach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, express check-out, and laundry facilities.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Avoca Lodge in Randwick (Randwick - Coogee), you'll be minutes from Prince of Wales Hospital and Community Health Service and close to Bondi Beach.  This hotel is within close proximity of University of New South Wales and Coogee Beach. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Prince of Wales Hospital and Community Health Service - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of New South Wales - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Coogee Beach - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wiley's Baths - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Randwick Racecourse - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gordon's Bay - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wedding Cake Island - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Clovelly Beach - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bronte Beach - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Supa Centa Moore Park - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Moore Park Golf Course - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fox Studio Australia - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Westfield Bondi Junction Shopping Centre - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Centennial Park - 3.3 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maroubra Beach - 3.5 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Avoca Lodge is Sydney, NSW (SYD-Kingsford Smith Intl.) - 7.1 km / 4.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>