<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11605256</Id><Name>Posh Hotel</Name><Region><Id>20300</Id><Name>Chinatown</Name><CityId>15375</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>8 Broadway, Chippendale</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Sydney</City><State /><Zip>2008</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>041-475-1289</Tel><Fax>61-292-126-668</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Posh Hotel, you'll be centrally located in Chippendale, steps from University of Technology Sydney and Railway Square. This family-friendly hotel is close to University of Sydney and Sydney Opera House.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 16 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring refrigerators and LCD televisions. Your pillowtop bed comes with Egyptian cotton sheets, and all rooms are furnished with sofa beds. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have designer toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and gift shops/newsstands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite from a grocery/convenience store serving guests of Posh Hotel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-out, dry cleaning/laundry services, and multilingual staff. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite from a grocery/convenience store serving guests of Posh Hotel. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 16 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and gift shops/newsstands. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 16 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring refrigerators and LCD televisions. Your pillowtop bed comes with Egyptian cotton sheets, and all rooms are furnished with sofa beds. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have designer toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Posh Hotel, you'll be centrally located in Chippendale, steps from University of Technology Sydney and Railway Square. This family-friendly hotel is close to University of Sydney and Sydney Opera House. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;University of Technology Sydney - 0 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;Railway Square - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sydney Institute Ultimo College - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Paddy's Market - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Market City - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Powerhouse Museum - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Broadway Shopping Center - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sydney Entertainment Centre - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Capitol Theatre - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chinatown Night Market - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chinese Garden of Friendship - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;World Square Shopping Centre - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Seymour Centre - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Glebe Markets - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sydney Convention Centre - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Posh Hotel is Sydney, NSW (SYD-Kingsford Smith Intl.) - 6.6 km / 4.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 16 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>