<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11601325</Id><Name>Top Spot Motel Maroochydore</Name><Region><Id>20296</Id><Name>Maroochydore</Name><CityId>15372</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>8 Beach Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Sunshine Coast</City><State /><Zip>4558</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>61 7 54431245</Tel><Fax>61 7 54433371</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Top Spot Motel is centrally located in Maroochydore, walking distance from Sunshine Plaza and close to Twin Waters Golf Club. This motel is within close proximity of Mooloolaba Beach and Underwater World Sea Life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 16 individually furnished guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and microwaves. Flat-screen televisions are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include sofa beds and irons/ironing boards, and housekeeping is provided weekly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include luggage storage and laundry facilities. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 1 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 16 individually furnished guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and microwaves. Flat-screen televisions are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include sofa beds and irons/ironing boards, and housekeeping is provided weekly.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Top Spot Motel is centrally located in Maroochydore, walking distance from Sunshine Plaza and close to Twin Waters Golf Club. This motel is within close proximity of Mooloolaba Beach and Underwater World Sea Life. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Sunshine Plaza - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Twin Waters Golf Club - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mooloolaba Beach - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Underwater World Sea Life - 4.8 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kawana Beach - 7.5 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mt Coolum Golf Club - 9.4 km / 5.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Big Pineapple - 10 km / 6.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queensland Zoo - 10.1 km / 6.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aussie World - 11.7 km / 7.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Coolum Beach - 13.6 km / 8.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dickey Beach - 15.1 km / 9.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Moffat Beach - 16.2 km / 10.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ginger Factory - 16.8 km / 10.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Caloundra Events Center - 17.3 km / 10.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shelly Beach - 17.4 km / 10.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Top Spot Motel is Maroochydore, QLD (MCY-Sunshine Coast) - 5.2 km / 3.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>