<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11607562</Id><Name>Port Arthur Villas</Name><Region><Id>20312</Id><Name>Port Arthur</Name><CityId>15377</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>52 Safety Cove Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Port Arthur</City><State /><Zip>7182</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>0362502239</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Port Arthur, Port Arthur Villas is in the historical district and convenient to Port Arthur Historic Site and Tasman Golf Course.  This 4-star vacation home is within the vicinity of Remarkable Cave and Tasmanian Devil Unzoo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 9 individually furnished guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private furnished patios. Flat-screen televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as separate sitting areas and minibars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Continental breakfasts are available for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a computer station and laundry facilities. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 1 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Continental breakfasts are available for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 18 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 9 individually furnished guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private furnished patios. Flat-screen televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as separate sitting areas and minibars.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Port Arthur, Port Arthur Villas is in the historical district and convenient to Port Arthur Historic Site and Tasman Golf Course.  This 4-star vacation home is within the vicinity of Remarkable Cave and Tasmanian Devil Unzoo. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Port Arthur Historic Site - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tasman Golf Course - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Remarkable Cave - 4.4 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tasmanian Devil Unzoo - 9.8 km / 6.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eaglehawk Neck - 16 km / 10 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Port Arthur Villas is Sydney, NSW (SYD-Kingsford Smith Intl.) - 1,064 km / 661.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 18 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>