<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11609336</Id><Name>Peppers Airlie Beach</Name><Region><Id>20321</Id><Name>Airlie Beach</Name><CityId>15389</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>9a Hermitage Drive</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Airlie Beach</City><State /><Zip>4802</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>07 5665 4133</Tel><Fax>+61 (7) 40464299</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Peppers Airlie Beach in Airlie Beach, you'll be near the beach and convenient to Airlie Beach Lagoon and Abell Point Marina. This 4.5-star aparthotel is within close proximity of Bicentennial Park and Cannonvale Beach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 102 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. Flat-screen televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature jetted bathtubs and complimentary toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers body treatments and facials. You can take advantage of recreational amenities such as an outdoor pool, a spa tub, and a fitness center. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the aparthotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, limo/town car service, and laundry facilities. Guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle for a surcharge, and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the aparthotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers body treatments and facials. You can take advantage of recreational amenities such as an outdoor pool, a spa tub, and a fitness center. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 102 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. Flat-screen televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature jetted bathtubs and complimentary toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Peppers Airlie Beach in Airlie Beach, you'll be near the beach and convenient to Airlie Beach Lagoon and Abell Point Marina. This 4.5-star aparthotel is within close proximity of Bicentennial Park and Cannonvale Beach. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Airlie Beach Lagoon - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Abell Point Marina - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bicentennial Park - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cannonvale Beach - 2.5 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shute Harbour Jetty - 7 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Great Whitsunday Walk - 7.7 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Conway National Park - 9.1 km / 5.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Daydream Port - 10.2 km / 6.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Daydream Reef - 10.2 km / 6.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Daydream Beach - 10.3 km / 6.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sandy Bay - 11.3 km / 7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cedar Creek Falls - 11.5 km / 7.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;South Molle Island Golf Course - 12.2 km / 7.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;South Molle Island Jetty - 12.4 km / 7.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palm Bay - 15.3 km / 9.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Peppers Airlie Beach is Proserpine, QLD (PPP-Whitsunday Coast) - 29.5 km / 18.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>