<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11601306</Id><Name>Coolum Beach Resort</Name><Region><Id>20296</Id><Name>Maroochydore</Name><CityId>15372</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>7 Beach Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Sunshine Coast</City><State /><Zip>4573</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>+61 7 5471 7744</Tel><Fax>+61 7 5455 7177</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Coolum Beach Resort in Coolum Beach, you'll be near the airport and minutes from Coolum Beach, and close to Mt Coolum Golf Club.  This family-friendly apartment is within the region of Twin Waters Golf Club and Ginger Factory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 14 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. 68-cm plasma televisions and DVD players are provided, while wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as microwaves and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including an outdoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna. Additional features include wireless Internet access (surcharge), babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and an arcade/game room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at one of the apartment's 3 restaurants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The front desk is staffed during limited hours. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge at scheduled times, and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 11:30 AM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at one of the apartment's 3 restaurants. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 18 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including an outdoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna. Additional features include wireless Internet access (surcharge), babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and an arcade/game room. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 14 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and stovetops. Rooms have private balconies. 68-cm plasma televisions and DVD players are provided, while wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as microwaves and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Coolum Beach Resort in Coolum Beach, you'll be near the airport and minutes from Coolum Beach, and close to Mt Coolum Golf Club.  This family-friendly apartment is within the region of Twin Waters Golf Club and Ginger Factory. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Coolum Beach - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mt Coolum Golf Club - 4.1 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Twin Waters Golf Club - 10.9 km / 6.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ginger Factory - 13.3 km / 8.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sunshine Plaza - 13.7 km / 8.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sunshine Beach Village Shops - 14.1 km / 8.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ed Webb Park - 14.2 km / 8.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eumundi Market - 15.2 km / 9.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Noosa National Park - 15.5 km / 9.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Noosa Marina - 16.1 km / 10 mi &lt;br /&gt;Noosa Beach - 16.3 km / 10.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mooloolaba Beach - 16.8 km / 10.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Underwater World Sea Life - 17.1 km / 10.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Big Pineapple - 18.6 km / 11.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queensland Zoo - 18.6 km / 11.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Maroochydore, QLD (MCY-Sunshine Coast) - 8.2 km / 5.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;Brisbane, QLD (BNE) - 95 km / 59 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Coolum Beach Resort is Brisbane, QLD (BNE). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 18 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>GameRoom</Code><Text>GameRoom</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>