<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11603050</Id><Name>Perouse Lodge</Name><Region><Id>20310</Id><Name>Rest of Sydney</Name><CityId>15375</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>6 Perouse Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Sydney</City><State /><Zip>2031</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>+61 2 9314 6686</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Perouse Lodge in Randwick (Randwick - Coogee), you'll be minutes from Prince of Wales Hospital and Community Health Service and close to Bondi Beach. This hotel is within close proximity of Coogee Beach and University of New South Wales.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 27 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and LCD televisions. Prepare your meals in the shared/communal kitchen. Cable programming and iPod docking stations are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Bathrooms have showers and complimentary toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Perouse Lodge, or find a snack in a coffee shop/café. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, express check-out, and multilingual staff.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Perouse Lodge, or find a snack in a coffee shop/café. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 27 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and LCD televisions. Prepare your meals in the shared/communal kitchen. Cable programming and iPod docking stations are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Bathrooms have showers and complimentary toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Perouse Lodge in Randwick (Randwick - Coogee), you'll be minutes from Prince of Wales Hospital and Community Health Service and close to Bondi Beach. This hotel is within close proximity of Coogee Beach and University of New South Wales. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Prince of Wales Hospital and Community Health Service - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Coogee Beach - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of New South Wales - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wiley's Baths - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gordon's Bay - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Randwick Racecourse - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wedding Cake Island - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Clovelly Beach - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bronte Beach - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Supa Centa Moore Park - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Westfield Bondi Junction Shopping Centre - 3.1 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fox Studio Australia - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Moore Park Golf Course - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Centennial Park - 3.3 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tamarama Beach - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Perouse Lodge is Sydney, NSW (SYD-Kingsford Smith Intl.) - 7.3 km / 4.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>