<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>116098</Id><Name>Paradise Beach</Name><Region><Id>21011</Id><Name>Trapani</Name><CityId>17128</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>CONTRADA BELICE DI MARE</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>SELINUNTE-CATELVETRANO</City><State /><Zip>91022</Zip><Country>ITALY</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>37.5858882</Latitude><Longitude>12.8766157</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/16/79/6/16796-GEN-2.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>231</Height><Bytes>16111</Bytes><Caption>General</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/16/79/6/16796-GEN-2thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>96</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2317</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/16/79/6/16796-HAB-1.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>231</Height><Bytes>8965</Bytes><Caption>Room</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/16/79/6/16796-HAB-1thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>96</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1741</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Paradise Beach Resort in Castelvetrano (Marinella di Selinunte), you'll be close to Porto Palo Harbour and Selinunte.  This beach hotel is within the vicinity of Menfi Beach and Menfi Civic Museum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 248 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Satellite television is provided for your entertainment. Bathrooms have bidets and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Head down to the water and enjoy a day at the private beach, or take advantage of other recreational amenities including an outdoor pool and a seasonal outdoor pool. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, supervised childcare/activities, and an arcade/game room. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge) that operates within 15 km.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Paradise Beach Resort. Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar. A complimentary buffet breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, express check-out, and dry cleaning/laundry services. Planning an event in Castelvetrano? This hotel has 3229 square feet (300 square meters) of space consisting of a conference center, conference space, and meeting rooms. A train station pick-up service is provided at no charge (available on request), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 4 PM  Check-out time is Noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Paradise Beach Resort. Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar. A complimentary buffet breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Head down to the water and enjoy a day at the private beach, or take advantage of other recreational amenities including an outdoor pool and a seasonal outdoor pool. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, supervised childcare/activities, and an arcade/game room. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge) that operates within 15 km. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 248 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Satellite television is provided for your entertainment. Bathrooms have bidets and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Paradise Beach Resort in Castelvetrano (Marinella di Selinunte), you'll be close to Porto Palo Harbour and Selinunte.  This beach hotel is within the vicinity of Menfi Beach and Menfi Civic Museum. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Porto Palo Harbour - 2.8 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Selinunte - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Menfi Beach - 6.6 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Menfi Civic Museum - 8.4 km / 5.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Acquasplash - 11.1 km / 6.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of San Domenico - 12.7 km / 7.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Castelvetrano Civic Museum - 12.7 km / 7.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Teatro Selinus - 12.9 km / 8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cusa Quarry - 14.3 km / 8.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Grifeo Castle - 15.4 km / 9.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of the Holy Trinity of Delia - 15.5 km / 9.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Vitus on the Sea - 24.9 km / 15.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Norman Arch - 26.1 km / 16.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cathedral of the Holy Savior - 26.2 km / 16.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Saint Nicholas - 26.2 km / 16.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Paradise Beach Resort is Palermo (PMO-Punta Raisi) - 70.1 km / 43.6 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Hotel Paradise Beach Club is Palermo (PMO-Punta Raisi) - 70.2 km / 43.6 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Garage</Code><Text>Garage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreshWaterPool</Code><Text>Fresh Water Pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Balcony</Code><Text>Balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>