<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11609330</Id><Name>Paradise Bay Eco Escape Whitsundays Resort</Name><Region><Id>20325</Id><Name>Long Island</Name><CityId>15389</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>South Long Island</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Whitsundays</City><State /><Zip>4802</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>07 4946 9777</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Paradise Bay Island Resort in Long Island, you'll be near the bay and minutes from Molle Islands National Park. This 4-star apartment is within the vicinity of Palm Bay and Pelican Island.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 10 guestrooms. Your pillowtop bed comes with down comforters and Egyptian cotton sheets. Rooms have private balconies. Bathrooms have showers and designer toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Treat yourself with massages, body treatments, and facials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Paradise Bay Island Resort. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 8 AM  Check-out time is 4:30 PM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Paradise Bay Island Resort. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 18 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Treat yourself with massages, body treatments, and facials. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 10 guestrooms. Your pillowtop bed comes with down comforters and Egyptian cotton sheets. Rooms have private balconies. Bathrooms have showers and designer toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Paradise Bay Island Resort in Long Island, you'll be near the bay and minutes from Molle Islands National Park. This 4-star apartment is within the vicinity of Palm Bay and Pelican Island. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Molle Islands National Park - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palm Bay - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pelican Island - 5.8 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hamilton Island Golf Club - 8.7 km / 5.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hamilton Island Marina - 10.3 km / 6.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Catseye Beach - 11 km / 6.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Conway National Park - 11.7 km / 7.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sandy Bay - 12.6 km / 7.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shute Harbour Jetty - 13.1 km / 8.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;South Molle Island Golf Course - 14.1 km / 8.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;South Molle Island Jetty - 14.2 km / 8.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cid Island - 15 km / 9.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cedar Creek Falls - 15.5 km / 9.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Daydream Reef - 15.6 km / 9.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Daydream Port - 15.6 km / 9.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Paradise Bay Island Resort is Hamilton Island, QLD (HTI-Great Barrier Reef) - 10 km / 6.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 18 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>