<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>116051</Id><Name>Villa Flori</Name><Region><Id>20956</Id><Name>Como</Name><CityId>17099</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>VIA CERNOBBIO</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>COMO</City><State /><Zip>22100</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel>0039 03133820</Tel><Fax>0039 031570379</Fax><Email>info@hotelvillaflori.it</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>46</CountRooms><CountFloors>4</CountFloors><CountSuites>3</CountSuites><Latitude>45.8263712</Latitude><Longitude>9.0686176</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAF558400_0.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>481</Height><Bytes>40776</Bytes><Caption>Exterior view</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAF558400_0.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>58</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>10363</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAF558400_1.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>52852</Bytes><Caption>Standard bedroom</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAF558400_1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>15347</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Villa Flori in Como, you'll be on a lake and convenient to Villa Bernasconi and Villa Olmo. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Villa Erba and Villa Saporiti.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 52 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include safes and desks, and you can also request irons/ironing boards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including a sauna, a steam room, and a fitness center. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare, and tour/ticket assistance. Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the area shuttle (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hotel Villa Flori. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include limo/town car service, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hotel Villa Flori. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including a sauna, a steam room, and a fitness center. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare, and tour/ticket assistance. Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the area shuttle (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 52 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include safes and desks, and you can also request irons/ironing boards.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Villa Flori in Como, you'll be on a lake and convenient to Villa Bernasconi and Villa Olmo. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Villa Erba and Villa Saporiti. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Villa Bernasconi - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Villa Olmo - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Villa Erba - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Villa Saporiti - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Caduti Monument - 1.5 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Volta Temple - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Como-Brunate Funicular - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stadio Giuseppe Sinigaglia - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza Cavour - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Torre del Comune - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Broletto Plaza - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cathedral of Como - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Casa del Fascio - 2.2 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Teatro Sociale - 2.2 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of San Fedele - 2.3 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Villa Flori is Milan (MXP-Malpensa Intl.) - 35.6 km / 22.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>