<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11601421</Id><Name>Regents Court Apartments - by 8Hotels</Name><Region><Id>20304</Id><Name>Kings Cross</Name><CityId>15375</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>18 Springfield Avenue</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Sydney</City><State /><Zip>2011</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>+ 61 2 9331  2099</Tel><Fax>61 2 9357 2384</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Regents Court Sydney in Potts Point (Potts Point - Kings Cross), you'll be minutes from Fitzroy Gardens and Elizabeth Bay House.  This 4-star apartment is close to Sydney Opera House and Sydney Harbour Bridge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 26 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and stovetops. Flat-screen televisions and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include desks and microwaves, and housekeeping is provided on a limited basis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. This Art Deco apartment also features babysitting/childcare (surcharge), tour/ticket assistance, and a picnic area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, luggage storage, and laundry facilities. A shuttle from the hotel to the airport is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. This Art Deco apartment also features babysitting/childcare (surcharge), tour/ticket assistance, and a picnic area. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 26 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and stovetops. Flat-screen televisions and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include desks and microwaves, and housekeeping is provided on a limited basis.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Regents Court Sydney in Potts Point (Potts Point - Kings Cross), you'll be minutes from Fitzroy Gardens and Elizabeth Bay House.  This 4-star apartment is close to Sydney Opera House and Sydney Harbour Bridge. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Fitzroy Gardens - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Elizabeth Bay House - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;King Street Gallery - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Woolloomooloo Wharf - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Art Gallery of New South Wales - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Domain - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sydney Jewish Museum - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Green Park - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Vincent’s Hospital - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Botanic Gardens - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Mary's Cathedral - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Art School Gallery - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Australian Museum - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Notre Dame Australia - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Taylor Square - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Regents Court Sydney is Sydney, NSW (SYD-Kingsford Smith Intl.) - 8.9 km / 5.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>