<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11609537</Id><Name>Thousand Hills Golf Resort</Name><Region><Id>19407</Id><Name>Branson, MO</Name><CityId>19407</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>245 South Wildwood Drive</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Branson</City><State /><Zip>65616</Zip><Country>USA</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/BRAW-THOhotel_Swimming_Pool_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/BRAW-THOhotel_Swimming_Pool_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>60</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>80</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>SwimmingPool</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/BRAW-THOhotel_Golf_Course_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/BRAW-THOhotel_Golf_Course_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>60</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>80</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/BRAW-THOhotel_Other_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>216</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/BRAW-THOhotel_Other_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/BRAW-THOhotel_Golf_Course_2.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/BRAW-THOhotel_Golf_Course_2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>60</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>80</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/BRAW-THOhotel_Guest_Room_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>216</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/BRAW-THOhotel_Guest_Room_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/BRAW-THOhotel_Other_2.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>216</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/BRAW-THOhotel_Other_2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/BRAW-THOhotel_Guest_Room_2.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>216</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/BRAW-THOhotel_Guest_Room_2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Situated in the heart of Branson, only minutes from exciting live entertainment, fabulous dining and tremendous shopping opportunities, Thousand Hills Golf Resort offers a variety of choices for the Branson visitor looking for more than just a room. If you are looking for a luxurious condominium with a golf view and lake front lodging that is second to none, Thousand Hills has the perfect accommodations for your family, friends, co-workers or group.All of our units provide you with a dining area, a living area with a queen-sized sleeper sofa, bedrooms with king-sized beds, washers and dryers, and the same number of bathrooms as bedrooms. Our fully-furnished kitchens include a microwave, toaster, coffee pot, blender, stove and refrigerator with freezer. In addition, all linens, towels, dishes, glassware, silverware and standard cooking utensils are provided.  Our resort amenities include seven indoor and outdoor swimming pools, outdoor hot tubs, sports courts and equipment, a play area for children and an exercise facility for guest use at no additional charge.  In addition, our resort is built around our beautiful 18 hole golf course, which guests can use at a discounted rate.  Golf clubs are also available for rent in our pro shop.It is our goal at Thousand Hills to give each of our guests a vacation experience that is second to none.  Whether you are coming for a romantic weekend, a family vacation, or a group event, our luxurious condo units, coupled with our superior service and convenient center-city location, make Thousand Hills Golf Resort the premier place to stay in Branson. And, with the addition of beautiful new lake front condos, we have even more options for our guests. We hope you will give us the opportunity to make your Branson vacation one you will never forget.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Welcome to Branson, MO, the live music show capital of the world. Nestled in the natural Ozark Mountains, you will find over 50 theaters, shopping, dining, golf and lakes, which make Branson a truly remarkable vacation destination.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Our condos are located on and around our beautiful 18-hole golf course and offer over 700 square feet of luxury. Units feature a private bedroom with king bed, private bathroom with whirlpool tub, a living area with queen sleeper sofa, cable TV, DVD player, and a fully-furnished kitchen.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>