<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11604754</Id><Name>Sleep Express Motel</Name><Region><Id>20310</Id><Name>Rest of Sydney</Name><CityId>15375</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>97 Hume Highway</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Sydney</City><State /><Zip>2190</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>029-758-7999</Tel><Fax>029-758-8808</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Chullora, Sleep Express Motel is in the entertainment district and close to Sydney Markets and DFO Homebush. This family-friendly motel is within close proximity of Sydney Olympic Park Athletic Centre and Urban Jungle Adventure Park.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 88 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and flat-screen televisions. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) is available to keep you connected. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers and irons/ironing boards, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as wireless Internet access (surcharge), a television in the lobby, and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Continental breakfasts are available for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, express check-out, and dry cleaning/laundry services. Guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle for a surcharge, and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 1 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Continental breakfasts are available for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as wireless Internet access (surcharge), a television in the lobby, and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 88 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and flat-screen televisions. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) is available to keep you connected. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers and irons/ironing boards, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Chullora, Sleep Express Motel is in the entertainment district and close to Sydney Markets and DFO Homebush. This family-friendly motel is within close proximity of Sydney Olympic Park Athletic Centre and Urban Jungle Adventure Park. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Sydney Markets - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;DFO Homebush - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sydney Olympic Park Athletic Centre - 4.6 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Urban Jungle Adventure Park - 4.6 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sydney International Aquatic Centre - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;ANZ Stadium - 4.9 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bicentennial Park - 4.9 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sydney Showground - 5.1 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Allphones Arena - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Skoda Stadium - 5.5 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Crest Sporting Complex - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bankstown Golf Club - 8 km / 5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rosehill Gardens Racecourse - 8.4 km / 5.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Elizabeth Farm - 8.6 km / 5.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Italian Forum - 9.2 km / 5.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Sleep Express Motel is Sydney, NSW (SYD-Kingsford Smith Intl.) - 11.2 km / 6.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Sleep Express Motel is Sydney, NSW (SYD-Kingsford Smith Intl.) - 11.2 km / 6.9 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>