<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11601413</Id><Name>Woolloomooloo Waters Apartment Hotel Sydney</Name><Region><Id>20304</Id><Name>Kings Cross</Name><CityId>15375</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>88 Dowling Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Sydney</City><State /><Zip>2011</Zip><Country>Australia</Country><Tel>028-837-8000</Tel><Fax>+61 (2) 93564839</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Woolloomooloo, Waldorf Apartments in Woolloomooloo Waters is in the entertainment district and minutes from Woolloomooloo Wharf and Fitzroy Gardens. This family-friendly apartment is close to Sydney Opera House and Sydney Harbour Bridge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 40 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and microwaves. Flat-screen televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected. Conveniences include separate sitting areas and irons/ironing boards, and you can also request cribs/infant beds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including an indoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, luggage storage, and laundry facilities. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including an indoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 40 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and microwaves. Flat-screen televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected. Conveniences include separate sitting areas and irons/ironing boards, and you can also request cribs/infant beds.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Woolloomooloo, Waldorf Apartments in Woolloomooloo Waters is in the entertainment district and minutes from Woolloomooloo Wharf and Fitzroy Gardens. This family-friendly apartment is close to Sydney Opera House and Sydney Harbour Bridge. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Woolloomooloo Wharf - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fitzroy Gardens - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Art Gallery of New South Wales - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Elizabeth Bay House - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Domain - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;King Street Gallery - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Botanic Gardens - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Mary's Cathedral - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sydney Mint - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hyde Park Barracks Museum - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Australian Museum - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sydney Parliament House - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;State Library of New South Wales - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. James Church - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hyde Park - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Waldorf Apartments in Woolloomooloo Waters is Sydney, NSW (SYD-Kingsford Smith Intl.) - 8.9 km / 5.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndoorPool</Code><Text>Indoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>