<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>116124964</Id><Name>Salamander Resort &amp; Spa</Name><Region><Id>20071</Id><Name>Washington D.C. (and vicinity)</Name><CityId>20071</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>500 North Pendleton Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Middleburg</City><State /><Zip>20117</Zip><Country>U.S.A.</Country><Tel>001 844 303 2723</Tel><Fax>0015406875495</Fax><Email>reservations@salamanderresort.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>A stunning belle in Virginia`s horse country, with historic stables, a farm-fresh restaurant and a spa spread over a bucolic 340-acre estate Sprawling over 340 acres of rolling foothill outside historic Middleburg, this is Horse Country`s blue ribbon steed, with a 168-room French manor hotel, a splurge-worthy spa and a state-of-the-art equestrian center. Salamander Hotel &amp; Resorts CEO Sheila C. Johnson was personally involved in every detail, from the manicured entry to the clubby Gold Cup billiards room to the spa`s infinity pool terrace, which is based on the one on her own estate (just down the tree-lined country lane). Her boldest statement is the formal parlor, where a classic French aesthetic is updated with bright robin`s egg-blues, pops of sunny yellow and sleek wood and leather furnishings bracketed by white stone fireplaces; a wall of three French doors opens onto the Grand Lawn and the hills beyond. The clubby, equestrian vibe works well in the guestrooms and suites, too, with leather chairs, rich wood furnishings and pops of baby blue. Dinner is served at Harrimans Virginia Piedmont Grill - the name is a nod to the estate`s former owners, and the menu is an ode to the countryside, with local meat, fish and cheese, and many vegetables grown in the property`s garden, just outside the window.
Guests should note that a resort fee is payable direct to the hotel upon arrival. Resort fees are subject to change and guests are advised to check the hotel`s website for current charges.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>