<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11625033</Id><Name>Springhill Suites Midtown Manhattan/Fifth Avenue</Name><Region><Id>64379</Id><Name>Midtown Manhattan</Name><CityId>19793</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>25 West 37th Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>New York</City><State>New York</State><Zip>10018</Zip><Country>USA</Country><Tel>+ 1 212 391 2255</Tel><Fax>+ 1 212 391 4949</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>0</CountRooms></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/NYC-9Yhotel_Lobby_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>199</Height><Bytes>13884</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/NYC-9Yhotel_Lobby_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2251</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/NYC-9Yhotel_Guest_Room_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>215</Height><Bytes>16189</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/NYC-9Yhotel_Guest_Room_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2242</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at SpringHill Suites by Marriott New York Midtown Manhattan in New York (Midtown West), you'll be minutes from Empire State Building and Macy's. This family-friendly hotel is close to Times Square and Grand Central Terminal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 173 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and microwaves. LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the recreation opportunities such as a fitness center or make use of other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A complimentary buffet breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, dry cleaning/laundry services, and laundry facilities.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 4 PM  Check-out time is Noon &lt;br/&gt; A complimentary buffet breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy the recreation opportunities such as a fitness center or make use of other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 173 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and microwaves. LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at SpringHill Suites by Marriott New York Midtown Manhattan in New York (Midtown West), you'll be minutes from Empire State Building and Macy's. This family-friendly hotel is close to Times Square and Grand Central Terminal. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Empire State Building - 0.2 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;New York Public Library - 0.2 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Macy's - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bryant Park - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Herald Square - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Morgan Library and Museum - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Manhattan Mall - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;International Center of Photography - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Penn Plaza Pavilion - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Madison Square Garden - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Times Square - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Grand Central Terminal - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Toys 'R' Us Times Square - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;New Amsterdam Theater - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Madame Tussauds Wax Museum - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;New York, NY (JRB-Downtown Manhattan Heliport) - 5.9 km / 3.6 mi&lt;br /&gt;New York, NY (LGA-LaGuardia) - 9.8 km / 6.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;Newark, NJ (EWR-Liberty Intl.) - 17.6 km / 10.9 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for SpringHill Suites by Marriott New York Midtown Manhattan is New York, NY (LGA-LaGuardia). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>