<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11625027</Id><Name>Holiday Inn Nyc Lower East Side</Name><Region><Id>20051</Id><Name>Utica, NY</Name><CityId>20051</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>150 Delancey Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>New York</City><State /><Zip>10002</Zip><Country>USA</Country><Tel>212-475-2500</Tel><Fax>212-475-2501</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>0</CountRooms></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1324216-photo-not-available-small.jpg</Url><Width>70</Width><Height>70</Height><Bytes>1454</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1324216-photo-not-available-small.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1454</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Discover all that downtown has to offer at the convenient, comfortable Holiday Inn NYC / Lower East Side. You are at the heart of everything, shopping, dining, entertainment and the arts. You are within walking distance of the Tenement Museum, Katz Delicatessen and Soho. When getting there has to be fast and convenient, we are only 9 Miles from LaGuardia Airport, so you' will spend less time in traffic and more time doing what you came to New York City to do. We also offer easy access to the Brooklyn-Queens Expressway. Whether you are coming to New York City for business or just for fun your room at the Holiday Inn NYC / Lower East Side is your personal retreat. You will have room to work, relax and make the most of your day. Amenities such as high speed Internet, a work center, plush towels and luxurious bedding mean every night is a great night and every day starts right. You can enjoy a great meal or a cold beverage at our restaurant, Retro Bar andamp; Grill. The best of New York City is waiting for you at the Holiday Inn NYC / Lower East Side!</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>Short</Type><Text>Discover all that downtown has to offer at the convenient; comfortable Holiday Inn NYC / Lower East Side</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>