<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11631098</Id><Name>Village Loano 2 Htl</Name><Region><Id>17108</Id><Name>Loano</Name><CityId>17108</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Via Degli Alpini, 6</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Savona</City><State /><Zip>17025</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Loano 2 Village in Loano, you'll be convenient to Toirano Caves. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of Caravel Water Park and Archaeological Museum of Finale Ligure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 360 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Rooms have private balconies. Dial-up Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Dip into one of the 3 outdoor swimming pools or enjoy other recreational amenities, which include bicycles to rent. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Loano 2 Village, or stop in at a grocery/convenience store. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff. Limited parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 5 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Loano 2 Village, or stop in at a grocery/convenience store. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Dip into one of the 3 outdoor swimming pools or enjoy other recreational amenities, which include bicycles to rent. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 360 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Rooms have private balconies. Dial-up Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Loano 2 Village in Loano, you'll be convenient to Toirano Caves. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of Caravel Water Park and Archaeological Museum of Finale Ligure. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Toirano Caves - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Caravel Water Park - 5.2 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Archaeological Museum of Finale Ligure - 8.3 km / 5.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Capo San Donato Port - 11.2 km / 7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gallinara Island - 12 km / 7.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Varigotti Beach - 13.4 km / 8.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marina di Alassio - 13.6 km / 8.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Baia dei Saraceni - 14.4 km / 8.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Golf Club Garlenda - 15 km / 9.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wall of Alassio - 15 km / 9.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Parish Church of St Ambrogio - 15.2 km / 9.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Budello di Alassio - 15.4 km / 9.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Altare Glass Museum - 23.9 km / 14.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Carretto Castle - 25.6 km / 15.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Monument to the Fallen - 25.9 km / 16.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Loano 2 Village is Nice (NCE-Cote d'Azur) - 97.3 km / 60.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>&lt;b&gt;Nice-Cote d'Azur International Airport (NCE):&lt;/b&gt; Approximate distance to Loano 2 Village is 130 kilometres (81 miles).</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Entertainment</Code><Text>Entertainment</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bike Rental</Code><Text>Bike Rental</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>