<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11631479</Id><Name>Sant' Eligio</Name><Region><Id>21002</Id><Name>Naples</Name><CityId>17120</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Via Bernardino Rota, 36/38</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip>80133</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Hotel Sant'Eligio is in the heart of Naples, walking distance from Museo Civico Filangeri and Santa Maria del Carmine. This hotel is within close proximity of Palazzo Marigliano and University of Naples Federico II.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 12 individually furnished guestrooms, featuring refrigerators and minibars. 22-inch LED televisions with digital programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature rainfall showerheads and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include desks and complimentary newspapers, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. Additional features include babysitting/childcare, a television in the lobby, and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves lunch and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, express check-out, and complimentary newspapers in the lobby. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at noon  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves lunch and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. Additional features include babysitting/childcare, a television in the lobby, and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 12 individually furnished guestrooms, featuring refrigerators and minibars. 22-inch LED televisions with digital programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature rainfall showerheads and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include desks and complimentary newspapers, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Hotel Sant'Eligio is in the heart of Naples, walking distance from Museo Civico Filangeri and Santa Maria del Carmine. This hotel is within close proximity of Palazzo Marigliano and University of Naples Federico II. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Museo Civico Filangeri - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Santa Maria del Carmine - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palazzo Marigliano - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Naples Federico II - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Gregorio Armeno Church - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pio Monte della Misericordia - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church Of Girolamini - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza Sisto Riario Sforza - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Spire of San Gennaro - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Port of Naples - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Lorenzo Maggiore - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Napoli Sotterranea - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza Giuseppe Garibaldi - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chiesa di Sant'Angelo A Nilo - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;La Statua del Nilo - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Sant'Eligio is Naples (NAP-Naples Intl.) - 3.8 km / 2.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Garage</Code><Text>Garage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Entertainment</Code><Text>Entertainment</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>