<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11633584</Id><Name>Royal Victoria</Name><Region><Id>21021</Id><Name>Pisa</Name><CityId>17136</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Via Lungarno Pacinotti, 12</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City /><State /><Zip>56126</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Royal Victoria Hotel, you'll be centrally located in Pisa, steps from Piazza Garibaldi and Palazzo Gambacorti. This hotel is within close proximity of San Michele in Borgo and Palazzo Blu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 48 air-conditioned guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have bathtubs or showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, and both irons/ironing boards and cribs/infant beds (complimentary) are available on request.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as bicycles to rent or take in the view from a garden. This Victorian hotel also features wireless Internet access (surcharge), concierge services, and babysitting/childcare. Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the area shuttle (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite from a snack bar/deli, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, express check-out, and dry cleaning/laundry services. Event facilities at this hotel consist of conference space and meeting rooms. A roundtrip airport shuttle and a train station pick-up service are provided for an additional charge.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite from a snack bar/deli, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as bicycles to rent or take in the view from a garden. This Victorian hotel also features wireless Internet access (surcharge), concierge services, and babysitting/childcare. Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the area shuttle (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 48 air-conditioned guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have bathtubs or showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, and both irons/ironing boards and cribs/infant beds (complimentary) are available on request.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Royal Victoria Hotel, you'll be centrally located in Pisa, steps from Piazza Garibaldi and Palazzo Gambacorti. This hotel is within close proximity of San Michele in Borgo and Palazzo Blu. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Piazza Garibaldi - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palazzo Gambacorti - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Michele in Borgo - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palazzo Blu - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Pisa - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of San Frediano - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Santo Sepolcro - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Paolo all'Orto - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pisa Royal Palace - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palazzo Agostini - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Knight's Square - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palace of the Putean College - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palazzo della Carovana - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Santo Stefano dei Cavalieri - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Torre dei Gualandi - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Royal Victoria Hotel is Pisa (PSA-Galileo Galilei) - 2 km / 1.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Royal Victoria Hotel is Pisa (PSA-Galileo Galilei) - 2 km / 1.3 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Garage</Code><Text>Garage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MultilingualStaff</Code><Text>Multilingual Staff</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>