<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>116381015</Id><Name>Sokha Siem Reap Resort &amp; Convention</Name><Region><Id>15672</Id><Name>Siem Reap</Name><CityId>15672</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Road 60, Angkor Cultural &amp; Tourism Complex</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Siem Reap</City><State /><Zip /><Country>Cambodia</Country><Tel>+85523998075</Tel><Fax>+85523220665</Fax><Email>salespp@sokhahotels.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Sokha Siem Reap Resort &amp; Convention Center is the perfect combination of luxury and tranquility set amidst lush tropical gardens. The setting offers the authenticity of traditional Cambodian design infused with fresh modern features and 5 star facilities creating a unique space in Siem Reap. The primary focus of Sokha Siem Reap Resort &amp; Convention Center  is providing an exceptional guest experience. This is a property which prides itself on personalized service and personal touches offering the kind of experience you would gain from a smaller hotel yet possessing the wealth of facilities that can only be expected of a property of this size. Offering 776 guest rooms, multiple dining outlets, the largest swimming pool in Siem Reap complete with its own cascading waterfall, signature Jasmine Spa &amp; Fitness Centre, state-of-the-art meeting &amp; convention facilities, onsite beauty salon and retail outlets, Sokha Siem Reap Resort &amp; Convention Centre has all the tools to create a truly unforgettable experience.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Sokha Siem Reap Resort &amp; Convention Center exudes convenience with the famed Temples of Angkor located only minutes from the resort entrance. The ease of access to remarkable locations such as Angkor Wat, Bayon and Ta Phrom is only the beginning. Sokha Siem Reap Resort &amp; Convention Center is positioned only 15 minutes from Siem Reap International Airport and 10 minutes outside of the city Center. This central location offers the opportunity for guests to enjoy a secluded and peaceful visit which still offers direct and easy access to the Angkor Tourist &amp; Cultural Complex and city Center locations such as Pub Street and Old Market.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PropertyInformation</Type><Text>This is a modern building.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DiningFacilities</Type><Text>There are five restaurants in the hotel. The Lotus: Tantalizes the taste buds with a fusion menu of east-meets-west blended cuisine, showcasing the finest of Cambodia’s fresh produce and ingredients. Champa Café: offers patrons the ability to enjoy a beverage or a tasty snack from the comfort of casual seating overlooking the magnificence of the Sokha Siem Reap Resort &amp; Convention Center Lobby or the splendor of the gardens. Teppanyaki: this Japanese restaurant is divided into three different settings - where you can see our artistic chefs perform the art of cooking in front of guests. Lemongrass: Private dining for discerning clientele providing a taste of pan Asian culture cuisine. Great dining experience matched with exclusive service. Khmer Bistro: will be a place for guests who want to unwind, relax, enjoy a drink or meet up with family and friends by the Pool. International casual cuisine, movie experience, BBQ and themes night supplemented by appropriate food &amp; beverage offering</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>Short</Type><Text>This accommodation has a large lobby.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>