<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11631101</Id><Name>Esplanade Hotel</Name><Region><Id>20985</Id><Name>Viareggio</Name><CityId>17112</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Piazza Puccini, 18</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Viareggio</City><State /><Zip>55049</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel>+39 0584 54321</Tel><Fax>+39 0584 53638</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Residence Esplanade, you'll be centrally located in Viareggio, walking distance from Pineta di Ponente and close to Statue of Burlamacco. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Villa Paolina and Piazza Shelley.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 45 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature designer toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include laptop-compatible safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities including a fitness center and bicycles to rent. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a hair salon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a business center, and express check-in. Planning an event in Viareggio? This hotel has facilities measuring 1722 square feet (160 square meters), including a meeting room.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities including a fitness center and bicycles to rent. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a hair salon. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 45 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature designer toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include laptop-compatible safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Residence Esplanade, you'll be centrally located in Viareggio, walking distance from Pineta di Ponente and close to Statue of Burlamacco. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Villa Paolina and Piazza Shelley. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Pineta di Ponente - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Statue of Burlamacco - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Villa Paolina - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza Shelley - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza Garibaldi - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;War Memorial - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Viareggio Harbor - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Matilde Tower - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Monument to the Resistance and to Peace - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Villa Borbone - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Massaciuccoli Lake - 7.7 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Villa Puccini - 7.8 km / 4.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Versiliana Park - 7.9 km / 4.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pietrasanta Cathedral - 8.8 km / 5.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Forte dei Marmi Beach - 10.2 km / 6.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Residence Esplanade is Pisa (PSA-Galileo Galilei) - 24.2 km / 15 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Hotel Residence Esplanade is Pisa (PSA-Galileo Galilei) - 24.2 km / 15 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PetsAllowed</Code><Text>Pets allowed</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MultilingualStaff</Code><Text>Multilingual Staff</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>