<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>116498886</Id><Name>Golden Tulip Jineng Resort Bali Hotel</Name><Region><Id>20876</Id><Name>Kuta - Tuban</Name><CityId>16956</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>JI. Sunset Road</Address1><Address2>Kuta</Address2><Address3 /><City>Bali</City><State /><Zip>80361</Zip><Country>INDONESIA</Country><Tel>0062 361 4727 488</Tel><Fax>00623614727499</Fax><Email>reservations@goldentulipjinengresortbali.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Golden Tulip Jineng Tamansari is a new prestigious International standards hotel with modern facilities blend with beautiful Balinese furnish and decor. The hotel presents a total of 184 unique rooms with its own decoration theme taken from Balinese culture, also completed with 2 F&amp;B outlets and 1 Ballroom that can be divided into 4 function rooms to cater meetings, seminars, wedding and another social events. The hotel is the perfect place where leisure and business harmonize in the unique culture of Bali and is set in private and spacious grounds where there is amphitheater and plunge pool to relax on whilst soaking up the sizzling Bali sun after having a refreshing dip. To complete the facilities, the hotel presents a state of the art fitness center and luxury "Dedari Spa" with various and amazing treatments from the well-trained therapists to pamper and rejuvenate the body, mind and soul.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>This hotel is centrally located in the most busy commercial area at the new heart of Kuta that has an easy access to Airport, Highways and major hubs.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PropertyInformation</Type><Text>This is a modern building.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DiningFacilities</Type><Text>Breakfast, Lunch and Dinner are available at this property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>Short</Type><Text>This accommodation has a medium lobby.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>