<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11641542</Id><Name>MF Hotel Rome</Name><Region><Id>21036</Id><Name>Central</Name><CityId>17149</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Via Savoia 44</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Rome</City><State /><Zip>00185</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel>+39 06 85357656</Tel><Fax>+39 06 8414809</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/ROM-91Qhotel_Guest_Room_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>21244</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/ROM-91Qhotel_Guest_Room_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2506</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/ROM-91Qhotel_Guest_Room_2.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>239</Height><Bytes>16147</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/ROM-91Qhotel_Guest_Room_2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2306</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/ROM-91Qhotel_Guest_Room_3.jpg</Url><Width>239</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>12386</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/ROM-91Qhotel_Guest_Room_3_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>60</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>80</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1882</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/ROM-91Qhotel_Guest_Room_4.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>239</Height><Bytes>14418</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/ROM-91Qhotel_Guest_Room_4_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2167</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at MF Hotel, you'll be centrally located in Rome, steps from Museum of Contemporary Art of Rome and minutes from Piazza Fiume. This hotel is close to Roman Forum and Colosseum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 17 individually furnished guestrooms, featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access is available. Private bathrooms with showers feature designer toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include safes and desks, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (complimentary).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and a television in the lobby. Additional amenities include tour/ticket assistance and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at one of the hotel's 12 restaurants and 14 coffee shops/cafés, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a business center, and express check-in.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at one of the hotel's 12 restaurants and 14 coffee shops/cafés, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and a television in the lobby. Additional amenities include tour/ticket assistance and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 17 individually furnished guestrooms, featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access is available. Private bathrooms with showers feature designer toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include safes and desks, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (complimentary).</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at MF Hotel, you'll be centrally located in Rome, steps from Museum of Contemporary Art of Rome and minutes from Piazza Fiume. This hotel is close to Roman Forum and Colosseum. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Museum of Contemporary Art of Rome - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza Fiume - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Porta Pia - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Galleria Borghese - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Borghese Gallery - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Globe Theatre Rome - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Central Library of Rome - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bioparco - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Santa Maria della Vittoria - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Villa Torlonia - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Umberto I Policlinic of Rome - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Santa Maria degli Angeli - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Diocletian Bath - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Octagonal Hall - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Academy of Fine Arts - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Rome (CIA-Ciampino) - 14.8 km / 9.2 mi&lt;br /&gt;Rome (FCO-Fiumicino - Leonardo da Vinci Intl.) - 24.3 km / 15.1 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for MF Hotel is Rome (FCO-Fiumicino - Leonardo da Vinci Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>