<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>116445</Id><Name>Naviglio Grande</Name><Region><Id>20996</Id><Name>Near Centre</Name><CityId>17117</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>VIA ALZALA TRIESTE 11</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>CORSICO</City><State /><Zip>20094</Zip><Country>ITALY</Country><Tel>0039024471808</Tel><Fax>00390245100392</Fax><Email>info@hotelnavigliogrande.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>45.4292861</Latitude><Longitude>9.1098658</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1047/17/04/1/17041-GEN-1.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>218</Height><Bytes>15364</Bytes><Caption>General</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1047/17/04/1/17041-GEN-1thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>102</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2134</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Naviglio Grande in Corsico, you'll be in a shopping district and close to Parrocchia Sant'Ambrogio Trezzano and Domus Academy. This hotel is within close proximity of Chiesa di San Cristoforo Sul Naviglio and San Carlo Borromeo Hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 37 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and flat-screen televisions. Digital television is provided for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities, which include concierge services and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, express check-out, and complimentary newspapers in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed      Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities, which include concierge services and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 37 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and flat-screen televisions. Digital television is provided for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Naviglio Grande in Corsico, you'll be in a shopping district and close to Parrocchia Sant'Ambrogio Trezzano and Domus Academy. This hotel is within close proximity of Chiesa di San Cristoforo Sul Naviglio and San Carlo Borromeo Hospital. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Parrocchia Sant'Ambrogio Trezzano - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Domus Academy - 3.6 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chiesa di San Cristoforo Sul Naviglio - 4.1 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Carlo Borromeo Hospital - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Assago Forum - 4.4 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Teatro Della Luna - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Centro Commerciale MilanoFiori - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;IULM University - 4.6 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Siro Stadium - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Teatro Ventaglio Nazionale - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Siro Race Course - 5.8 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Boscoincitta - 5.8 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Giuseppe Hospital - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Leonardo da Vinci Museum of Science and Technology - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Porta Ticinese - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Naviglio Grande is Milan (LIN-Linate) - 13.8 km / 8.6 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Hotel Naviglio Grande is Milan (LIN-Linate) - 13.8 km / 8.6 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HandicapAccessible</Code><Text>Handicap accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WLANAccessPoint</Code><Text>WLAN Access Point</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccessible</Code><Text>Wheelchair Accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Cafe(s)</Code><Text>Cafe(s)</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>