<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>116487</Id><Name>NH Milano 2 Hotel &amp; Residence</Name><Region><Id>20996</Id><Name>Near Centre</Name><CityId>17117</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Via Fratelli Cervi - Loc.</Address1><Address2>Segrate</Address2><Address3 /><City>Milan</City><State /><Zip>20090</Zip><Country>Italy</Country><Tel>34913984661</Tel><Fax>390221281</Fax><Email>JHMILANODUE@NH-HOTELS.COM</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>45.4970514</Latitude><Longitude>9.2631858</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/12/11/33/7/12113370.jpg</Url><Width>300</Width><Height>200</Height><Bytes>12611</Bytes><Caption>2001332178</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/12/11/33/7/12113370thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2629</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Segrate, NH Milano 2 is on a lake, minutes from National Institute of Nuclear Research, and close to San Raffaele Hospital. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Exhibition Park Novegro and Molinetto Country Club.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 143 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center or take in the view from a terrace and a garden. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of NH Milano 2, or find a snack in a coffee shop/café. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and dry cleaning/laundry services. This hotel has 11 meeting rooms available for events. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of NH Milano 2, or find a snack in a coffee shop/café. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center or take in the view from a terrace and a garden. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 143 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Segrate, NH Milano 2 is on a lake, minutes from National Institute of Nuclear Research, and close to San Raffaele Hospital. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Exhibition Park Novegro and Molinetto Country Club. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;National Institute of Nuclear Research - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Raffaele Hospital - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Exhibition Park Novegro - 3.5 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Molinetto Country Club - 3.7 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mondadori - 3.8 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Orto Botanico di Cascina Rosa - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piscina Romano Ponzio - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Istituto Besta - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza Aspromonte - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Politecnico di Milano - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Parco Dell'idroscalo - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazzale Loreto - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Circolo Arci Magnolia - 4.4 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Teatro degli Arcimboldi - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Milano-Bicocca - 4.6 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for NH Milano 2 is Milan (LIN-Linate) - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HandicapAccessible</Code><Text>Handicap accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Fridge</Code><Text>Fridge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccessible</Code><Text>Wheelchair Accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>