<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>116563</Id><Name>mD-Hotel Alpenrose</Name><Region><Id>116537</Id><Name>Fussen</Name><CityId>16517</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>JUPITERSTRASSE 9</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Nesselwang</City><State /><Zip>87484</Zip><Country>GERMANY</Country><Tel>49813133838</Tel><Fax>4981313383838</Fax><Email>alpenrose@minotel-deutschland.de</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>47.627</Latitude><Longitude>10.4986</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1205759-front1_Thumbnailed.jpg</Url><Width>100</Width><Height>100</Height><Bytes>3316</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1205759-front1_Thumbnailed.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1954</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/12/05/75/9/12057590.jpg</Url><Width>266</Width><Height>200</Height><Bytes>8203</Bytes><Caption>464038283</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/12/05/75/9/12057590thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2105</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Nesselwang, Hotel Alpenrose is in a rural location and within the vicinity of Alpspitzbahn Gondola and Jungholz Ski Resort. This hotel is within the vicinity of Breitenberg Cable Car and Falkenstein Castle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of 25 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with onsite massages or enjoy recreation amenities such as a sauna. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, ski storage, and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A complimentary breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and multilingual staff. Guests may use a train station pick-up service for a surcharge, and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; A complimentary breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with onsite massages or enjoy recreation amenities such as a sauna. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, ski storage, and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of 25 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Nesselwang, Hotel Alpenrose is in a rural location and within the vicinity of Alpspitzbahn Gondola and Jungholz Ski Resort. This hotel is within the vicinity of Breitenberg Cable Car and Falkenstein Castle. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Alpspitzbahn Gondola - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jungholz Ski Resort - 7.2 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Breitenberg Cable Car - 9 km / 5.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Falkenstein Castle - 9.4 km / 5.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wannenjoch Lift - 13.1 km / 8.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Leonhard's Chapel - 13.6 km / 8.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Iseler Cable Car - 14.1 km / 8.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of St. Nicholas - 14.3 km / 8.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vogelhorn Lift - 14.5 km / 9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fuessener Joechle Lift - 14.5 km / 9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mariahilf Pest Chapel - 14.7 km / 9.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fuessen Music Hall - 16.3 km / 10.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;State Gallery in the High Castle - 16.4 km / 10.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lech Fall - 16.5 km / 10.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Mang's Abbey - 16.5 km / 10.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Alpenrose is Friedrichshafen (FDH-Friedrichshafen - Lake Constance) - 73.2 km / 45.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for MINOTEL ALPENROSE is Friedrichshafen (FDH-Friedrichshafen - Lake Constance) - 73.2 km / 45.5 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Sauna</Code><Text>Sauna</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>GameRoom</Code><Text>GameRoom</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SunBathingTerrace</Code><Text>Sun Bathing Terrace</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Massage</Code><Text>Massage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>