<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>116684</Id><Name>InterCityHotel Stuttgart</Name><Region><Id>20707</Id><Name>Stuttgart</Name><CityId>16633</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>ARNULF KLETT PLATZ 2</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>STUTTGART</City><State /><Zip>70173</Zip><Country>GERMANY</Country><Tel>711 22500</Tel><Fax>711 2250499</Fax><Email>stuttgart@intercityhotel.de</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAF460800_0.jpg</Url><Width>363</Width><Height>480</Height><Bytes>57357</Bytes><Caption>Exterior view</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAF460800_0.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>52</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>11589</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;InterCityHotel Stuttgart is in the heart of Stuttgart, walking distance from Stuttgart National Theater and Carl Zeiss Planetarium. This hotel is within close proximity of State Gallery and Friedrichsbau Vaudeville Theater.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 76 guestrooms featuring minibars. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks, housekeeping is provided daily, and cribs/infant beds (complimentary) can be requested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities, which include wireless Internet access (surcharge) and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities, which include wireless Internet access (surcharge) and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 76 guestrooms featuring minibars. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks, housekeeping is provided daily, and cribs/infant beds (complimentary) can be requested.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>InterCityHotel Stuttgart is in the heart of Stuttgart, walking distance from Stuttgart National Theater and Carl Zeiss Planetarium. This hotel is within close proximity of State Gallery and Friedrichsbau Vaudeville Theater. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Stuttgart National Theater - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Carl Zeiss Planetarium - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;State Gallery - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Friedrichsbau Vaudeville Theater - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Schlossplatz - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Stuttgart - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Landtag - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Baden Wurttemberg History Museum - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stuttgart Art Museum - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;New Castle - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Charles Square - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Schillerplatz - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wurttemberg State Library - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Castle - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Catherine's Hospital - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for InterCityHotel Stuttgart is Stuttgart (STR) - 10.3 km / 6.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for InterCityHotel Stuttgart is Stuttgart (STR-Stuttgart Airport) - 10.3 km / 6.4 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Fridge</Code><Text>Fridge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>