<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11668687</Id><Name>Andaz Xintiandi Shanghai - A Hyatt Hotel</Name><Region><Id>20375</Id><Name>Downtown</Name><CityId>15982</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>88 Songhan Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Shanghai</City><State /><Zip>200021</Zip><Country>China</Country><Tel>+862123101200</Tel><Fax>011862123101210</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/SHA-9Thotel_Exterior_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/SHA-9Thotel_Exterior_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/SHA-9Thotel_Suite_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/SHA-9Thotel_Suite_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/SHA-9Thotel_Suite_2.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/SHA-9Thotel_Suite_2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/SHA-9Thotel_Guest_Room_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/SHA-9Thotel_Guest_Room_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Andaz Xintiandi Shanghai - a concept by Hyatt places you in the heart of Shanghai, walking distance from Shanghai Times Square and K11 Art Mall.  This 4.5-star hotel is close to The Bund and Jing An Temple.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 307 air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have hair dryers and bathrobes. Conveniences include safes and desks, as well as phones with free local calls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including an indoor pool, a sauna, and a fitness center. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a hair salon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite at one of the hotel's 2 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Buffet breakfasts are available for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include limo/town car service, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk. This hotel has 11 meeting rooms available for events. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite at one of the hotel's 2 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Buffet breakfasts are available for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including an indoor pool, a sauna, and a fitness center. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a hair salon. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 307 air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have hair dryers and bathrobes. Conveniences include safes and desks, as well as phones with free local calls.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Andaz Xintiandi Shanghai - a concept by Hyatt places you in the heart of Shanghai, walking distance from Shanghai Times Square and K11 Art Mall.  This 4.5-star hotel is close to The Bund and Jing An Temple. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Shanghai Times Square - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;K11 Art Mall - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;First National Congress of the CCP - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Xintiandi - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shanghai Museum - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Great World Entertainment Center - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;South Yunnan Road - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;People's Square - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shanghai Grand Theatre - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shanghai City Hall - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fuxing Park - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shanghai Urban Planning Exhibition Center - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;MOCA Shanghai - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shanghai Art Museum - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sun Yatsen Residence - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Andaz Xintiandi Shanghai - a concept by Hyatt is Shanghai (SHA-Hongqiao Intl.) - 12.7 km / 7.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FitnessFacility</Code><Text>Fitness facility</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarRentDesk</Code><Text>Car rental desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Massage</Code><Text>Massage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BarLounge</Code><Text>Bar/Lounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ValetLaundry</Code><Text>Valet Laundry</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CurrencyExchangeService</Code><Text>Currency Exchange Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>24HourFrontDesk</Code><Text>24 Hour Front Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>