<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>116621</Id><Name>Pentahotel Wiesbaden</Name><Region><Id>16650</Id><Name>Wiesbaden</Name><CityId>16650</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>ABRAHAM-LINCOLN-STRASSE 17</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>WIESBADEN</City><State /><Zip>65189</Zip><Country>GERMANY</Country><Tel>00496117970</Tel><Fax>0049611761372</Fax><Email>info.wiesbaden@pentahotels.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>50.06599982</Latitude><Longitude>8.272274223</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/UWE-RAMhotel_Other_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>239</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/UWE-RAMhotel_Other_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/UWE-RAMhotel_Bar_Lounge_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/UWE-RAMhotel_Bar_Lounge_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/UWE-RAMhotel_Bar_Lounge_2.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>211</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/UWE-RAMhotel_Bar_Lounge_2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/UWE-RAMhotel_Guest_Room_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/UWE-RAMhotel_Guest_Room_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;In the heart of Wiesbaden, pentahotel Wiesbaden is close to BRITA-Arena and Museum Wiesbaden. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Lilien Carree and Rhein-Main-Hallen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 209 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and complimentary bottled water, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as a fitness center or take in the view from a terrace. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a computer station, express check-in, and express check-out. Event facilities at this hotel consist of conference space and meeting rooms.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; Special cancellation policies or charges may apply for group reservations (more than 8 rooms for the same hotel / stay dates). &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as a fitness center or take in the view from a terrace. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 209 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and complimentary bottled water, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>In the heart of Wiesbaden, pentahotel Wiesbaden is close to BRITA-Arena and Museum Wiesbaden. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Lilien Carree and Rhein-Main-Hallen. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;BRITA-Arena - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum Wiesbaden - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lilien Carree - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rhein-Main-Hallen - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kurhaus - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hessian State Theatre - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Casino Wiesbaden - 2.8 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Market Church - 2.8 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wiesbaden Town Hall - 2.8 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Landtag of Hessen - 2.8 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Schlossplatz - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cuckoo Clock - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Goldgasse - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kochbrunnen - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Heathens Wall - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Mainz (QFZ-Mainz Finthen) - 13.7 km / 8.5 mi&lt;br /&gt;Frankfurt (FRA-Frankfurt Intl.) - 21.4 km / 13.3 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for pentahotel Wiesbaden is Frankfurt (FRA-Frankfurt Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for pentahotel Wiesbaden is Frankfurt (FRA-Frankfurt Intl.) - 20.9 km / 13 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; Special cancellation policies or charges may apply for group reservations (more than 8 rooms for the same hotel / stay dates).</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>GameRoom</Code><Text>GameRoom</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DiningRoom</Code><Text>Dining Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MobilePhoneNetwork</Code><Text>Mobile Phone Network</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>