<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>116603</Id><Name>Intercityhotel Goettingen</Name><Region><Id>20719</Id><Name>Gottingen</Name><CityId>16647</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>BAHNHOFSALLEE</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>GOETTINGEN</City><State /><Zip>37081</Zip><Country>Germany</Country><Tel>004955152110</Tel><Fax>00495515211500</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>145</CountRooms><CountSuites>4</CountSuites></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1001/17341hotel1.jpg</Url><Width>160</Width><Height>108</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1001/17341hotel1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>103</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2696</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1001/17341hotel2.jpg</Url><Width>160</Width><Height>128</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1001/17341hotel2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>87</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2539</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You'll be centrally located in Goettingen with a stay at InterCityHotel Göttingen, minutes from St John's Church and Ganseliesel. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Georg-August University of Goettingen and Hainberg Observatorium.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 152 guestrooms featuring minibars. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) is available to keep you connected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as a sauna or take in the view from a terrace. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, gift shops/newsstands, and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of InterCityHotel Göttingen. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, express check-out, and dry cleaning/laundry services. This hotel has 12 meeting rooms available for events.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3:00 PM  Check-out time is 11:00 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of InterCityHotel Göttingen. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as a sauna or take in the view from a terrace. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, gift shops/newsstands, and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 152 guestrooms featuring minibars. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) is available to keep you connected.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>You'll be centrally located in Goettingen with a stay at InterCityHotel Göttingen, minutes from St John's Church and Ganseliesel. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Georg-August University of Goettingen and Hainberg Observatorium. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;St John's Church - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ganseliesel - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Georg-August University of Goettingen - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hainberg Observatorium - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Heritage Museum - 19.6 km / 12.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Northeim Town Hall - 19.7 km / 12.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Theater of Night - 19.7 km / 12.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Forest Stage Northeim - 20 km / 12.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Welfenschloss - 22.7 km / 14.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tanzwerder Island - 23 km / 14.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Blasius Church - 23 km / 14.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Uslar Waterpark - 25.1 km / 15.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Alaris Butterfly Park - 25.1 km / 15.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Solling Tower - 28 km / 17.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eicke's House - 31.6 km / 19.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for InterCityHotel Göttingen is Hannover (HAJ) - 104.2 km / 64.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for InterCityHotel Goettingen is Hannover (HAJ-Hannover Airport) - 104.2 km / 64.8 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Garage</Code><Text>Garage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>