<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>116729</Id><Name>ACHAT Hotel Mannheim/Hockenheim</Name><Region><Id>20700</Id><Name>Mannheim</Name><CityId>16619</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>GLEISSTRASSE 8/1</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>HOCKENHEIM</City><State /><Zip>68766</Zip><Country>GERMANY</Country><Tel>004962052970</Tel><Fax>00496205297999</Fax><Email>hockenheim@achat-hotels.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>49.32794379</Latitude><Longitude>8.530373519</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1203111-Mannheim-front_Thumbnailed.jpg</Url><Width>100</Width><Height>100</Height><Bytes>3175</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1203111-Mannheim-front_Thumbnailed.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1847</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at ACHAT Comfort Mannheim/Hockenheim in Hockenheim, you'll be convenient to Hockenheim Racing Track. This hotel is within the vicinity of Schwetzingen Castle and Technik Museum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 100 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Housekeeping is provided daily, and both cribs/infant beds (surcharge) and rollaway/extra beds are available on request.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, express check-in, and express check-out. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 100 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Housekeeping is provided daily, and both cribs/infant beds (surcharge) and rollaway/extra beds are available on request.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at ACHAT Comfort Mannheim/Hockenheim in Hockenheim, you'll be convenient to Hockenheim Racing Track. This hotel is within the vicinity of Schwetzingen Castle and Technik Museum. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Hockenheim Racing Track - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Schwetzingen Castle - 6.8 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Technik Museum - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Speyer Cathedral - 7.1 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Corporate SAP Headquarters - 8.3 km / 5.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Heidelberg New Campus - 13.9 km / 8.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Heidelberg Old Campus - 15.2 km / 9.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;SAP Arena - 15.4 km / 9.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Heidelberg Church of the Holy Spirit - 15.5 km / 9.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Heidelberg Castle - 15.6 km / 9.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Karl Theodor Bridge - 15.7 km / 9.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Thingplatz - 16 km / 10 mi &lt;br /&gt;Planetarium Mannheim - 17.1 km / 10.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Luisenpark Gardens - 17.2 km / 10.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Holiday Park - 17.2 km / 10.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for ACHAT Comfort Mannheim/Hockenheim is Mannheim (MHG) - 16.7 km / 10.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Achat Comfort Hotel Mannheim / Hockenheim is Mannheim (MHG) - 16.7 km / 10.4 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MobilePhoneNetwork</Code><Text>Mobile Phone Network</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Carpeted</Code><Text>Carpeted</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>