<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11684856</Id><Name>The St. Regis Mumbai (Formerly Palladium)</Name><Region><Id>16906</Id><Name>Mumbai (Bombay)</Name><CityId>16906</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>462, Senapati Bapat Marg,</Address1><Address2>Lower Parel</Address2><Address3 /><City>Mumbai</City><State>Maharashtra</State><Zip>400 013</Zip><Country>India</Country><Tel>+91 (22) 6162 8000</Tel><Fax /><Email>enquiries@palladiumhotel.in</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>0</CountRooms></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/BOM-9Khotel_Guest_Room_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/BOM-9Khotel_Guest_Room_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/BOM-9Khotel_Guest_Room_2.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/BOM-9Khotel_Guest_Room_2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/BOM-9Khotel_Bar_Lounge_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/BOM-9Khotel_Bar_Lounge_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/BOM-9Khotel_Bar_Lounge_2.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/BOM-9Khotel_Bar_Lounge_2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/BOM-9Khotel_Restaurant_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>257</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/BOM-9Khotel_Restaurant_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/BOM-9Khotel_Swimming_Pool_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>239</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/BOM-9Khotel_Swimming_Pool_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>SwimmingPool</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You'll be centrally located in Mumbai with a stay at The St. Regis Mumbai, steps from High Street Phoenix Mall and close to Mahalaxmi Temple.  This 5-star hotel is close to Siddhi Vinayak Temple and Marine Drive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 386 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Your pillowtop bed comes with Egyptian cotton sheets. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while DVD players and cable programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature deep soaking bathtubs and rainfall showerheads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. You're sure to appreciate the recreational amenities, including a nightclub, an outdoor pool, and a sauna. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at one of the hotel's dining establishments, which include 6 restaurants and a coffee shop/café. While enjoying a refreshing dip in the hotel pool, you can order your favorite drink at the poolside bar. Breakfast is available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a 24-hour business center, and limo/town car service. Planning an event in Mumbai? This hotel has 42044 square feet (3906 square meters) of space consisting of a conference center and conference space. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and free valet parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at one of the hotel's dining establishments, which include 6 restaurants and a coffee shop/café. While enjoying a refreshing dip in the hotel pool, you can order your favorite drink at the poolside bar. Breakfast is available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. You're sure to appreciate the recreational amenities, including a nightclub, an outdoor pool, and a sauna. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 386 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Your pillowtop bed comes with Egyptian cotton sheets. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while DVD players and cable programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature deep soaking bathtubs and rainfall showerheads.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>You'll be centrally located in Mumbai with a stay at The St. Regis Mumbai, steps from High Street Phoenix Mall and close to Mahalaxmi Temple.  This 5-star hotel is close to Siddhi Vinayak Temple and Marine Drive. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;High Street Phoenix Mall - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mahalaxmi Racecourse - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Atria Mall - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Nehru Science Centre - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Nehru Planetarium - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jijamata Udyaan - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dr. Bhau Daji Lad Museum - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;KEM Hospital - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Haji Ali Dargah - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mahalaxmi Temple - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Siddhi Vinayak Temple - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shree Siddhivinayak Ganapati Temple - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Prince Aly Khan Hospital - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jaslok Hospital - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Breach Candy Hospital - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The St. Regis Mumbai is Mumbai (BOM-Chhatrapati Shivaji Intl.) - 12.4 km / 7.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>24</Rank></HotelElement>