<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11697139</Id><Name>Sefapane Lodge and Safaris</Name><Region><Id>18272</Id><Name>Phalaborwa</Name><CityId>18272</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Copper road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Phalaborwa</City><State /><Zip>1390</Zip><Country>South Africa</Country><Tel>+27 157806700</Tel><Fax>+ 27 157806711</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>0</CountRooms></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1233779-main_Thumbnailed.jpg</Url><Width>100</Width><Height>100</Height><Bytes>3497</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1233779-main_Thumbnailed.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1964</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Sefapane Lodge and Safaris in Phalaborwa, you'll be in a national park and close to Kruger National Park Phalaborwa Gate.  This 4-star lodge is within the vicinity of Hans Merensky Golf Estate and The Big Hole.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 50 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as complimentary newspapers and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with onsite massages, body treatments, and facials. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge) that operates within 5 km.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the lodge's restaurant, which features a bar and a garden view. Thirsty? Quench your thirst at a bar/lounge, a poolside bar, or a swim-up bar. Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk. Event facilities at this lodge consist of a conference center and a meeting room. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the lodge's restaurant, which features a bar and a garden view. Thirsty? Quench your thirst at a bar/lounge, a poolside bar, or a swim-up bar. Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with onsite massages, body treatments, and facials. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge) that operates within 5 km. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 50 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as complimentary newspapers and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Sefapane Lodge and Safaris in Phalaborwa, you'll be in a national park and close to Kruger National Park Phalaborwa Gate.  This 4-star lodge is within the vicinity of Hans Merensky Golf Estate and The Big Hole. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Kruger National Park Phalaborwa Gate - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hans Merensky Golf Estate - 6 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Big Hole - 6.7 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Masorini Archaeological Site - 14.1 km / 8.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kruger National Park - 37.4 km / 23.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Timbavati Game Reserve - 40.7 km / 25.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Khamai Reptile Centre - 61.6 km / 38.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hoedspruit Endangered Species Centre - 66.6 km / 41.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Moholoholo Wildlife Rehabilitation Centre - 69.8 km / 43.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Blyde River Canyon - 79.3 km / 49.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Modjadji Cycad Reserve - 88.6 km / 55.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Echo Caves - 89.1 km / 55.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;God's Window - 109.1 km / 67.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Elephant Whispers - 123 km / 76.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hazyview Elephant Sanctuary - 125.3 km / 77.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Sefapane Lodge and Safaris is Phalaborwa (PHW-Hendrik Van Eck) - 3 km / 1.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>