<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>117195</Id><Name>Marriott Leipzig</Name><Region><Id>16597</Id><Name>Leipzig</Name><CityId>16597</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>AM HALLISCHEN TOR 1</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>LEIPZIG</City><State /><Zip>04109</Zip><Country>GERMANY</Country><Tel>34196530</Tel><Fax>3419653999</Fax><Email>leipzig.marriott@marriotthotels.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAF464500_0.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>763</Height><Bytes>90741</Bytes><Caption>Exterior view</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAF464500_0.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>44</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>10196</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAF464500_1.jpg</Url><Width>822</Width><Height>487</Height><Bytes>178963</Bytes><Caption>Bar</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAF464500_1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>118</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>25240</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAF464500_2.jpg</Url><Width>1583</Width><Height>850</Height><Bytes>219945</Bytes><Caption>Indoor pool</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAF464500_2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>130</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>27277</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAF464500_3.jpg</Url><Width>1274</Width><Height>850</Height><Bytes>300010</Bytes><Caption>Conference room</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAF464500_3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>104</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>22465</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAF464500_4.jpg</Url><Width>822</Width><Height>1139</Height><Bytes>317319</Bytes><Caption>Lobby</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAF464500_4.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>50</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>11150</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Leipzig Marriott Hotel, you'll be centrally located in Leipzig, steps from Museum of Fine Arts and Leipzig City History Museum - Neubau. This luxury hotel is within close proximity of Naschmarkt and Leipzig's Old Town Hall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 231 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Satellite programming provides entertainment, and wired and wireless Internet access is available for a surcharge. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Relax and unwind with body treatments and facials. You can take advantage of recreational amenities such as a health club, an indoor pool, and a spa tub. This hotel also features wireless Internet access (surcharge), concierge services, and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or grab a snack at a coffee shop/café. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour business center, a computer station, and complimentary newspapers in the lobby. Planning an event in Leipzig? This hotel has 6943 square feet (645 square meters) of space consisting of conference space and meeting rooms. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or grab a snack at a coffee shop/café. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Relax and unwind with body treatments and facials. You can take advantage of recreational amenities such as a health club, an indoor pool, and a spa tub. This hotel also features wireless Internet access (surcharge), concierge services, and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 231 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Satellite programming provides entertainment, and wired and wireless Internet access is available for a surcharge. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Leipzig Marriott Hotel, you'll be centrally located in Leipzig, steps from Museum of Fine Arts and Leipzig City History Museum - Neubau. This luxury hotel is within close proximity of Naschmarkt and Leipzig's Old Town Hall. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Museum of Fine Arts - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Leipzig City History Museum - Neubau - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Naschmarkt - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Leipzig's Old Town Hall - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Leipzig Market Square - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Barfussgasse - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum Zum Arabischen Coffe Baum - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maedler Passage - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Nicholas Church - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stadtisches Kaufhaus - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Leipzig University - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Runde Ecke Memorial Museum - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Leipzig Opera - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Augustusplatz - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Thomas Church - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Leipzig Marriott Hotel is Leipzig (LEJ-Leipzig - Halle) - 13.4 km / 8.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Leipzig Marriott Hotel is Leipzig (LEJ-Leipzig - Halle) - 13.5 km / 8.4 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Fridge</Code><Text>Fridge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>