<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11710076</Id><Name>Beresheet</Name><Region><Id>17027</Id><Name>Mitspeh Ramon</Name><CityId>17027</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Derech Beresheet 1</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Mitspeh Ramon</City><State /><Zip>80600</Zip><Country>Israel</Country><Tel>+972 08 6387726</Tel><Fax>+972 03 7604623</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>0</CountRooms></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1236991-main_Thumbnailed.jpg</Url><Width>100</Width><Height>100</Height><Bytes>4199</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1236991-main_Thumbnailed.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2088</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Beresheet Hotel is an elegant 5-star property offering luxury accommodation in Mitzpe Ramon. Highlights include an indoor and an outdoor swimming pool, a spa and an excellent location near the edge of the Ramon crater cliffs. Mitzpe Ramon is a small desert town in the Negev region of southern Israel. Mitzpe is Hebew for 'watchtower' due to the town's high elevation above the dramatic Ramon crater giving spectacular views and extensive hiking trails. The town also boasts many galleries, shops and restaurants. Places of interest include the Albert Promenade, Bio Museum and the Mitzpe Ramon Visitors Center. The hotel is housed in a modern mid-rise building with a traditional Arabic facade surrounded by desert landscape. Facilities include an indoor and an outdoor swimming pool, a fitness centre, a spa, a sauna, a cinema and bicycle rental. Free Wi-Fi is available in public areas. Desert View rooms are 40sqm, bright, modern and elegantly furnished featuring a private balcony or a garden terrace with views of the desert. Amenities include air-conditioning, a 42-inch flat screen TV, a mini-bar and a safe. The en-suite bathrooms feature a bathtub, a shower and a hairdryer. Rosemary Restaurant offers local cuisine in a modern and relaxed setting with panoramic windows. Guests can also enjoy a range of drinks at the sophisticated Lobby Bar with great views of the surrounding landscape. A buffet breakfast is provided every morning. Free parking is possible onsite. The hotel has a 24-hour reception.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>