<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>117173</Id><Name>Achat Hotel Lausitz</Name><Region><Id>16584</Id><Name>Hoyerswerda</Name><CityId>16584</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>BAUTZENER ALLEE 1A</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>HOYERSWERDA</City><State /><Zip>02977</Zip><Country>GERMANY</Country><Tel>004935714700</Tel><Fax>00493571470999</Fax><Email>hoyerswerda@achat-hotels.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>51.4424</Latitude><Longitude>14.2592</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1203092-Hoyerswarda-hotel-front_Thumbnailed.jpg</Url><Width>100</Width><Height>100</Height><Bytes>3876</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1203092-Hoyerswarda-hotel-front_Thumbnailed.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2158</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at ACHAT Comfort Lausitz in Hoyerswerda, you'll be minutes from Hoyerswerda Zoo and Lausitzhalle. This hotel is within close proximity of Hoyerswerda Castle Museum and Lausitzbad Spa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 89 guestrooms. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes, and both cribs/infant beds (surcharge) and rollaway/extra beds are available on request.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a terrace and make use of amenities such as wireless Internet access (surcharge) and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of ACHAT Comfort Lausitz. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and dry cleaning/laundry services. Planning an event in Hoyerswerda? This hotel has facilities measuring 581 square feet (54 square meters), including a meeting room. A shuttle from the hotel to the airport is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of ACHAT Comfort Lausitz. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a terrace and make use of amenities such as wireless Internet access (surcharge) and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 89 guestrooms. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes, and both cribs/infant beds (surcharge) and rollaway/extra beds are available on request.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at ACHAT Comfort Lausitz in Hoyerswerda, you'll be minutes from Hoyerswerda Zoo and Lausitzhalle. This hotel is within close proximity of Hoyerswerda Castle Museum and Lausitzbad Spa. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Hoyerswerda Zoo - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lausitzhalle - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hoyerswerda Castle Museum - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lausitzbad Spa - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Konrad Zuse Computer Museum - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Knappenrode Energy Factory Museum - 7.1 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lessing Museum - 22.4 km / 13.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bautzen Rathaus - 31.5 km / 19.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bautzen Memorial - 32.3 km / 20.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Muskau Park - 34.3 km / 21.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Catholic Church of St. Benno - 35.6 km / 22.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Christ Church - 35.7 km / 22.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bischofswerda Rathaus - 35.7 km / 22.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lichtenberger Church - 35.9 km / 22.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wasserschloss Wurschen - 36.1 km / 22.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for ACHAT Comfort Lausitz is Dresden (DRS) - 49.4 km / 30.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;B&gt;Dresden Airport (DRS):&lt;/B&gt; Approximate driving time to ACHAT Hotel Lausitz is 60 minutes and distance is 50 kilometers (31 miles). &lt;/p&gt;&amp;#x0D;&amp;#x0A;&amp;#x0D;&amp;#x0A;&lt;p&gt;Take the train to Hoyerswerda station followed by the number 15 bus to Jugendclubhaus. The hotel is around the corner on the left. &lt;/p&gt;&amp;#x0D;&amp;#x0A;&lt;p&gt;&lt;B&gt;Driving directions: &lt;/B&gt; From the airport, take the A4 and exit at Hoyerswerda. &lt;/p&gt;&amp;#x0D;&amp;#x0A;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Kitchen</Code><Text>Kitchen</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant Smoking Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MobilePhoneNetwork</Code><Text>Mobile Phone Network</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Carpeted</Code><Text>Carpeted</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lounge</Code><Text>Lounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>