<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>117347</Id><Name>Radisson Blu Hannover</Name><Region><Id>20665</Id><Name>Hannover</Name><CityId>16575</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>EXPO-PLAZA 5</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>HANOVER</City><State /><Zip>30521</Zip><Country>GERMANY</Country><Tel>+49 511 383830</Tel><Fax>+49511383833590</Fax><Email>info.hannover@radissonsas.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAF895300_0.jpg</Url><Width>250</Width><Height>480</Height><Bytes>27115</Bytes><Caption>Exterior view</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAF895300_0.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>36</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>8424</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAF895300_1.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>319</Height><Bytes>39180</Bytes><Caption>Lobby</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAF895300_1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>23959</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAF895300_2.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>301</Height><Bytes>39192</Bytes><Caption>Standard bedroom</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAF895300_2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>111</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>20869</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Hannover (Mittelfeld), Radisson Blu Hotel, Hannover is minutes from TUI Arena and Hannover Convention Center. This 4.5-star hotel is within close proximity of Hannover Fairground and Expo Park.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 250 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature designer toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities, including a health club, a sauna, and a steam room. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You can find a meal at a coffee shop/café serving guests of Radisson Blu Hotel, Hannover, or stop in at a snack bar/deli. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a business center, and a computer station. Planning an event in Hannover? This hotel has 12299 square feet (1143 square meters) of space consisting of conference space and meeting rooms. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; You can find a meal at a coffee shop/café serving guests of Radisson Blu Hotel, Hannover, or stop in at a snack bar/deli. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities, including a health club, a sauna, and a steam room. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 250 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature designer toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Hannover (Mittelfeld), Radisson Blu Hotel, Hannover is minutes from TUI Arena and Hannover Convention Center. This 4.5-star hotel is within close proximity of Hannover Fairground and Expo Park. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;TUI Arena - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hannover Convention Center - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hannover Fairground - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Expo Park - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Luftfahrt Museum - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Leine Center Laatzen - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tiergarten Hannover - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Commedia Futura Theater - 6.2 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Foro Artistico - 6.2 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eilenriede Stadium - 6.6 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hannover Congress Centrum - 6.7 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sprengel Museum - 6.8 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maschsee - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Swiss Life Hall - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lower Saxony State Museum - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Radisson Blu Hotel, Hannover is Hannover (HAJ) - 17.3 km / 10.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Radisson Blu Hotel, Hannover is Hannover (HAJ-Hannover Airport) - 17.3 km / 10.8 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Sauna</Code><Text>Sauna</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Garage</Code><Text>Garage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Fridge</Code><Text>Fridge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>