<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>117479</Id><Name>mD-Hotel Schmidt Monnikes</Name><Region><Id>16539</Id><Name>Bochum</Name><CityId>16539</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Drusenbergstrasse 164</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Bochum</City><State /><Zip>44789</Zip><Country>Germany</Country><Tel>+49 234 333960</Tel><Fax>+49 234 3339666</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>0</CountRooms><Latitude>51.45934872</Latitude><Longitude>7.214546113</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1035592-Schmidt-Monnikes-Front_Thumbnailed.jpg</Url><Width>100</Width><Height>100</Height><Bytes>4867</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1013/hotel1035592-Schmidt-Monnikes-Front_Thumbnailed.thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2400</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Schmidt-Mönnikes in Bochum, you'll be convenient to Bochum Civic Theatre and Parish Church of St. Peter and Paul. This hotel is within close proximity of Zeiss Planetarium Bochum and German Mining Museum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of 31 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and complimentary bottled water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hotel Schmidt-Mönnikes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, multilingual staff, and luggage storage. Limited parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hotel Schmidt-Mönnikes. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of 31 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and complimentary bottled water.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Schmidt-Mönnikes in Bochum, you'll be convenient to Bochum Civic Theatre and Parish Church of St. Peter and Paul. This hotel is within close proximity of Zeiss Planetarium Bochum and German Mining Museum. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Bochum Civic Theatre - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Parish Church of St. Peter and Paul - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Zeiss Planetarium Bochum - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;German Mining Museum - 3.3 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ruhr University Bochum - 3.5 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bismarck Tower - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tierpark und Fossilium Bochum - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;RewirpowerSTADION - 3.6 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;RuhrCongress Bochum - 3.7 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bochum Botanical Garden - 3.7 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Starlight Express Theater - 3.9 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Industry Museum Henrichshuette - 6 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Haus Kemnade - 6.2 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Railway Museum Bochum - 6.8 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;LWL Industrial Museum Zeche Nachtigall - 7.6 km / 4.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Schmidt-Mönnikes is Dortmund (DTM) - 28.5 km / 17.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>