<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>117636</Id><Name>Steigenberger Grandhotel Petersberg</Name><Region><Id>20633</Id><Name>Bonn</Name><CityId>16545</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Petersberg, Koenigswinter</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Bonn</City><State /><Zip>53639</Zip><Country>Germany</Country><Tel>0049 (0)2223740</Tel><Fax>0049 (0)222374443</Fax><Email>reservierung@petersberg.steigenberger.de</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>50.6854278</Latitude><Longitude>7.2120578</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/GYSfront.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/GYSthumbfront.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>3043</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/GYSbed.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/GYSthumbbed.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1660</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/GYSmap.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/GYSthumbmap.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2016</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Koenigswinter, Steigenberger Grandhotel Petersberg is convenient to Reptilien-Zoo and Siebengebirgsmuseum. This 5-star hotel is within close proximity of Sea Life Koenigswinter and Drachenburg Palace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 99 guestrooms featuring minibars. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including a health club, an indoor pool, and a sauna. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant or in a coffee shop/café. Or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour business center, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is Noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant or in a coffee shop/café. Or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including a health club, an indoor pool, and a sauna. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 99 guestrooms featuring minibars. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Koenigswinter, Steigenberger Grandhotel Petersberg is convenient to Reptilien-Zoo and Siebengebirgsmuseum. This 5-star hotel is within close proximity of Sea Life Koenigswinter and Drachenburg Palace. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Reptilien-Zoo - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Siebengebirgsmuseum - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sea Life Koenigswinter - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Drachenburg Palace - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dragon's Rock - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sportpark Pennenfeld - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kammerspiele - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Deutsches Museum Bonn - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bundeskunsthalle - 6.8 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bonn Arts Museum - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;World Conference Center Bonn - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Bundestag - 7 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;House of the History of the Federal Republic of Germany - 7.2 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;University Hospital Bonn - 7.4 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Alexander Koenig Research Museum - 7.7 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Steigenberger Grandhotel Petersberg is Cologne (CGN-Cologne - Bonn) - 22.8 km / 14.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;B&gt;Cologne-Bonn Konrad Airport (CGN):&lt;/B&gt; Approximate driving time to the Steigenberger Grandhotel Petersberg is 25 minutes and distance is 27 kilometres (17 miles).&lt;/p&gt;&amp;#x0D;&amp;#x0A;&amp;#x0D;&amp;#x0A;&lt;p&gt; From the airport take bus number 161 to the train station Cologne/Porz. From Cologne/Porz station take the Regional Express from platform 2 to Königswinter station (travelling time: 40 minutes), five kilometres from the hotel. The hotel can also arrange airport transfers for €46.&lt;/p&gt;&amp;#x0D;&amp;#x0A;&amp;#x0D;&amp;#x0A;&lt;p&gt;&lt;B&gt;Driving directions: &lt;/B&gt; From the airport take the A59 in the direction of Bonn, then the B42 for Konigswater, exit at L331in the direction of the A3 and the hotel is on the left.&lt;/p&gt;&amp;#x0D;&amp;#x0A;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FitnessFacility</Code><Text>Fitness facility</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseDining</Code><Text>Hotel restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InHouseBar</Code><Text>Hotel bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingRooms</Code><Text>Meeting rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>