<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>117684</Id><Name>Hilton Nuremberg Hotel</Name><Region><Id>20647</Id><Name>Nuremberg</Name><CityId>16560</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Valznerweiherstrasse 200,</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Nuremberg</City><State /><Zip>90480</Zip><Country>GERMANY</Country><Tel>49-911-40290</Tel><Fax>49-911-4029666</Fax><Email>res_nurenburg@hilton.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>49.43425</Latitude><Longitude>11.13261</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/NUE-HOLhotel_Lobby_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>235</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/NUE-HOLhotel_Lobby_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hilton Nuernberg in Nuremberg (Oststadt), you'll be convenient to Norisring Race Track and Nuremberg Zoo. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Frankenstadion and Nuremberg Arena.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 152 air-conditioned rooms featuring MP3 docking stations. Satellite programming provides entertainment, and wired and wireless Internet access is available for a surcharge. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include laptop-compatible safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities including an outdoor pool and a fitness center. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hilton Nuernberg. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, a computer station, and express check-in. This hotel has 18 meeting rooms available for events. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hilton Nuernberg. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities including an outdoor pool and a fitness center. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 152 air-conditioned rooms featuring MP3 docking stations. Satellite programming provides entertainment, and wired and wireless Internet access is available for a surcharge. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include laptop-compatible safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hilton Nuernberg in Nuremberg (Oststadt), you'll be convenient to Norisring Race Track and Nuremberg Zoo. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Frankenstadion and Nuremberg Arena. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Norisring Race Track - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Frankenstadion - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Nuremberg Arena - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dokuzentrum's Fascination and Terror - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Nuremberg Zoo - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Zeppelin and March Fields - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Nuremberg Messe - 2 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Meistersinger Hall - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Congress Centre Nuremberg - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Nuremberg Hospital - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Industrial Culture Museum - 3.3 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Franken Center - 3.5 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;King's Gate - 3.9 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Handwerkerhof - 3.9 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;New Museum - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hilton Nuernberg is Nuremberg (NUE-Nuremberg Airport) - 7.4 km / 4.6 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Hilton Nuernberg is Nuremberg (NUE-Nuremberg Airport) - 7.5 km / 4.7 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreshWaterPool</Code><Text>Fresh Water Pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Fridge</Code><Text>Fridge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>