<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>117813</Id><Name>Euro Park Hotel</Name><Region><Id>20633</Id><Name>Bonn</Name><CityId>16545</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>REUTHERSTRASSE 1A-C</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>HENNEF</City><State /><Zip>53773</Zip><Country>GERMANY</Country><Tel>004922428760</Tel><Fax>00492242876199</Fax><Email>info@hennef-hotel.de</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>50.78148</Latitude><Longitude>7.25721</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/ZHIfront.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/ZHIfront.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2203</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/ZHIbed.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/ZHIbed.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2035</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/6/ZHImap.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>400</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/6/ZHImap.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>70</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2014</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Euro Park Hotel Hennef places you in the heart of Hennef and within the vicinity of Aggua Troisdorf and Bilderbuchmuseum Burg Wissem. This 4-star hotel is within the region of Gallery Acht P and Cultural Centre Brotfabrik.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of 78 guestrooms featuring LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include laptop-compatible safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and gift shops/newsstands. Additional amenities include wedding services, a fireplace in the lobby, and a television in the lobby. Guests can catch a ride on the shuttle (surcharge), which operates within 35 km.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a computer station, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and dry cleaning/laundry services. Planning an event in Hennef? This hotel has 323 square feet (30 square meters) of space consisting of conference space and meeting rooms. For a surcharge, guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle during limited hours and a train station pick-up service.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11:30 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and gift shops/newsstands. Additional amenities include wedding services, a fireplace in the lobby, and a television in the lobby. Guests can catch a ride on the shuttle (surcharge), which operates within 35 km. &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of 78 guestrooms featuring LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include laptop-compatible safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Euro Park Hotel Hennef places you in the heart of Hennef and within the vicinity of Aggua Troisdorf and Bilderbuchmuseum Burg Wissem. This 4-star hotel is within the region of Gallery Acht P and Cultural Centre Brotfabrik. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Aggua Troisdorf - 6.4 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bilderbuchmuseum Burg Wissem - 7.6 km / 4.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gallery Acht P - 10.1 km / 6.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cultural Centre Brotfabrik - 10.4 km / 6.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Beethoven Hall - 11.6 km / 7.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;World Conference Center Bonn - 11.6 km / 7.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Bundestag - 11.7 km / 7.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Alter Zoll - 11.7 km / 7.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rheinsteig - 11.7 km / 7.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Opera Bonn - 11.7 km / 7.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Deutsches Museum Bonn - 11.8 km / 7.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bonn City Museum - 11.8 km / 7.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bundeskunsthalle - 12 km / 7.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bonn Arts Museum - 12 km / 7.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old City Hall Bonn - 12 km / 7.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Euro Park Hotel Hennef is Cologne (CGN-Cologne - Bonn) - 15.2 km / 9.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;B&gt;Cologne-Bonn Konrad Airport (CGN):&lt;/B&gt; Approximate driving time to Euro Park Hotel is 15 minutes and distance is 22 kilometres (14 miles).&lt;/p&gt;&amp;#x0D;&amp;#x0A;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Getting there:&lt;/b&gt; Taxis are readily available outside Terminals 1 and 2 and typically cost €40 to the hotel. Price subject to change.&lt;/p&gt;&amp;#x0D;&amp;#x0A;&lt;P&gt;&lt;b&gt;Getting around:&lt;/b&gt; Hennef is easily explored on foot, although hiring a car is recommend for exploring the surrounding areas.&lt;/p&gt;&amp;#x0D;&amp;#x0A;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MoneyExchange</Code><Text>Money exchange</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MobilePhoneNetwork</Code><Text>Mobile Phone Network</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lounge</Code><Text>Lounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Cafe(s)</Code><Text>Cafe(s)</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>