<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>117819</Id><Name>Derag Livinghotel Kanzler</Name><Region><Id>20633</Id><Name>Bonn</Name><CityId>16545</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Adenauerallee 148</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Bonn</City><State /><Zip>53113</Zip><Country>Germany</Country><Tel>+49 228 68 44 0</Tel><Fax>+49 228 68 44 160</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>0</CountRooms><Latitude>50.72278</Latitude><Longitude>7.11303</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Derag Livinghotel Kanzler in Bonn (Gronau), you'll be minutes from Alexander Koenig Research Museum and close to House of the History of the Federal Republic of Germany. This 4.5-star hotel is within close proximity of Old Bundestag and World Conference Center Bonn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 150 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and microwaves. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. If you're looking for recreational opportunities, you'll find a sauna, a fitness center, and bicycles to rent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves lunch and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff. Planning an event in Bonn? This hotel has facilities measuring 7102 square feet (660 square meters), including conference space. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves lunch and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. If you're looking for recreational opportunities, you'll find a sauna, a fitness center, and bicycles to rent. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 150 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens with refrigerators and microwaves. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Derag Livinghotel Kanzler in Bonn (Gronau), you'll be minutes from Alexander Koenig Research Museum and close to House of the History of the Federal Republic of Germany. This 4.5-star hotel is within close proximity of Old Bundestag and World Conference Center Bonn. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Alexander Koenig Research Museum - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;House of the History of the Federal Republic of Germany - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Bundestag - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;World Conference Center Bonn - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bonn Arts Museum - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bundeskunsthalle - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Alter Zoll - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rheinsteig - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bonn City Museum - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Botanical Gardens of the University of Bonn - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Bonn - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bonn Minster - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old City Hall Bonn - 1.5 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Poppelsdorf Palace - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bonn Marketplace - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Derag Livinghotel Kanzler is Cologne (CGN-Cologne - Bonn) - 17.7 km / 11 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Derag Hotel and Living Hotel Kanzler is Cologne (CGN-Cologne - Bonn) - 17.7 km / 11 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>