<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>117927</Id><Name>Steigenberger Hotel Deidesheim</Name><Region><Id>16547</Id><Name>Deidesheim</Name><CityId>16547</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>AM PARADIESGARTEN</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>DEIDESHEIM</City><State /><Zip>67146</Zip><Country>Germany</Country><Tel>00496326970-0</Tel><Fax>00496326970-333</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1001/17239hotel1.jpg</Url><Width>248</Width><Height>148</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1001/17239hotel1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>117</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2700</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1001/17239hotel2.jpg</Url><Width>198</Width><Height>132</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1001/17239hotel2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>3551</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Steigenberger Hotel Deidesheim in Deidesheim, you'll be within the vicinity of Kurpfalz-Park and Limburg Abbey. This 4-star hotel is within the region of Hambach Castle and Holiday Park.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 123 guestrooms. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and ceiling fans, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including a spa tub, a sauna, and a steam room. Additional amenities include wireless Internet access (surcharge), gift shops/newsstands, and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, express check-in, and express check-out. Event facilities at this hotel consist of conference space and meeting rooms. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including a spa tub, a sauna, and a steam room. Additional amenities include wireless Internet access (surcharge), gift shops/newsstands, and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 123 guestrooms. Wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and ceiling fans, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Steigenberger Hotel Deidesheim in Deidesheim, you'll be within the vicinity of Kurpfalz-Park and Limburg Abbey. This 4-star hotel is within the region of Hambach Castle and Holiday Park. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Kurpfalz-Park - 6 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Limburg Abbey - 6.8 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hambach Castle - 9.9 km / 6.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Holiday Park - 12.6 km / 7.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Phillip Kuhn Winery - 17 km / 10.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Suedweststadion - 19.8 km / 12.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;German State Philharmonic of Rhineland-Palatinate - 20.3 km / 12.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Speyer Cathedral - 20.7 km / 12.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Technik Museum - 21.3 km / 13.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cathedral of Worms - 28.1 km / 17.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Schales Winery - 28.9 km / 18 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fritz-Walter-Stadion - 29.9 km / 18.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Martin's Church - 30.4 km / 18.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palatinate Gallery of Art - 30.7 km / 19.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sandstone Church - 31.1 km / 19.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Steigenberger Hotel Deidesheim is Frankfurt (FRA-Frankfurt Intl.) - 77.1 km / 47.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Steigenberger Hotel Deidesheim is Frankfurt am Main (FRA-Frankfurt) - 76.9 km / 47.8 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>