<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>118134698</Id><Name>Gateway Hotel</Name><Region><Id>9043415</Id><Name>Bur Dubai</Name><CityId>18870</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Khalid Bin Al Waleed Road, Al Nahdha St</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Dubai</City><State /><Zip>125448</Zip><Country>United Arab Emirates</Country><Tel>01197145079000</Tel><Fax>01197145079090</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>In Dubai, Gateway Hotel is a newly opened property that provides modern rooms and free Wi-Fi in all areas. It features an outdoor pool and offers a spa with sauna and hammam upon request. The Dubai Metro Green Line is a 5-minute drive away. It includes a turkish bath.
 
Each room here includes a flat-screen TV, air conditioning and a minibar. It also includes tea/coffee facilities and fridge. Featuring a bathtub, private bathroom also comes with a hairdryer and free toiletries. Extras include satellite channels.
 
At Gateway Hotel there's a fitness center. Other facilities available at the property include a shared lounge, a ticket service and a tour desk. Free covered parking is available on site.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Gateway hotel is on Khalid Bin Waleed Street, merely 15 minutes from Dubai International Airport via Dubai metro red line. Much of the best of Bur Dubai is within walking distance from Gateway. Centrally located in the heart of Dubai's financial and historical district, Bur Dubai.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PropertyInformation</Type><Text>This is a modern building.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DiningFacilities</Type><Text>Breakfast, lunch and dinner is available at this property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>Short</Type><Text>This accommodation has a medium lobby.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>