<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>118164760</Id><Name>Volney Opera</Name><Region><Id>20523</Id><Name>(Arr 2/3/4) Halles - Marais - Htl de Ville </Name><CityId>16471</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>11 Rue Volney</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Paris</City><State /><Zip>75002</Zip><Country>France</Country><Tel>+33 1 42 61 85 24</Tel><Fax>+33 1 42 61 19 65</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>“Situated on the Rue Volney, our hotel enjoys a privileged location in the heart of the capital, with the essential historical and cultural places of Paris just a few steps away.

Thus, in just a few minutes’ walk you can reach places that embody the magic of Paris, such as the Opera Garnier, the Madeleine and the Place Vendôme. While enjoying the benefits of our hotel you will be within easy reach of famous department stores such as Printemps and Galeries Lafayette. Many theatres and concert halls, such as the Olympia, the Théâtre de la Michodière and the Bouffes Parisiens, are also in close proximity.

Within a few minutes of extra walking you can reach the celebrated Champs-Elysees, the Louvre Museum and the Place de la Concorde and its famous obelisk. Thanks to a well-developed public transport network, which includes the Metro and various bus services, you can quickly and easily get to the other districts or arrondissements of the capital.”

Facilities
Guest accommodation comprises 29 rooms. Services and facilities at the hotel include a restaurant, a bar, a transfer service and room service. Wireless internet access is available to guests in the public areas.
Rooms
The hotel features rooms with a bathroom. A double bed ensures a good night's sleep. Cots are available for younger travellers. A safe and a minibar are also available. Guests will also find a mini fridge included as standard. Internet access, a TV and WiFi add to the comfort of the holiday. A shower and a bathtub can be found in the bathrooms. A hairdryer can also be found in each of the bathrooms. Special family rooms are available for families with children.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>The hotel features rooms with a bathroom. A double bed ensures a good night's sleep. Cots are available for younger travellers. A safe and a minibar are also available. Guests will also find a mini fridge included as standard. Internet access, a TV and WiFi add to the comfort of the holiday. A shower and a bathtub can be found in the bathrooms. A hairdryer can also be found in each of the bathrooms. Special family rooms are available for families with children.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PropertyInformation</Type><Text>Guest accommodation comprises 29 rooms. Services and facilities at the hotel include a restaurant, a bar, a transfer service and room service. Wireless internet access is available to guests in the public areas.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>