<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>118286</Id><Name>Le St-Martin Hotel &amp; Suites</Name><Region><Id>20339</Id><Name>Montreal City</Name><CityId>15741</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1400 RUE MAURICE GAUVIN</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>LAVAL</City><State /><Zip>H7S 2P1</Zip><Country>Canada</Country><Tel>4509023000</Tel><Fax>4509023030</Fax><Email>info@lestmartin.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>116</CountRooms><CountFloors>6</CountFloors><CountSuites>18</CountSuites></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAL407500_0.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>23572</Bytes><Caption>Exterior view</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAL407500_0.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>18946</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAL407500_1.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>79865</Bytes><Caption>Lobby</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAL407500_1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>19561</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAL407500_2.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>56000</Bytes><Caption>Bedroom</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAL407500_2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>17553</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAL407500_3.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>17903</Bytes><Caption>Bedroom</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAL407500_3.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>19972</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAL407500_4.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>13570</Bytes><Caption>Bedroom</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAL407500_4.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>17040</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAL407500_5.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>24183</Bytes><Caption>Breakfast room</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAL407500_5.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>21436</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAL407500_6.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>33578</Bytes><Caption>Outdoor pool</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAL407500_6.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>21550</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Le St-Martin Hotel &amp; Suites Laval in Laval, you'll be next to a golf course and minutes from Cosmodome and Sky Venture.  This eco-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Putting Edge Centropolis and Centropolis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 116 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and LCD televisions. Your pillowtop bed comes with down comforters. Cable programming and iPod docking stations are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities including a spa tub and a fitness center. Additional features at this Victorian hotel include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour business center, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and dry cleaning/laundry services. Planning an event in Laval? This hotel has 2200 total square feet (204 square meters) of space consisting of conference space and meeting rooms. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 4 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 21 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities including a spa tub and a fitness center. Additional features at this Victorian hotel include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 116 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and LCD televisions. Your pillowtop bed comes with down comforters. Cable programming and iPod docking stations are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Le St-Martin Hotel &amp; Suites Laval in Laval, you'll be next to a golf course and minutes from Cosmodome and Sky Venture.  This eco-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Putting Edge Centropolis and Centropolis. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Cosmodome - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sky Venture - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Putting Edge Centropolis - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Centropolis - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maeva Surf - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Carrefour Laval - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Quartier Laval - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;College Montmorency - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Arena Chomedey - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;La Recreatheque - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Musee Pour Enfants - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Arena Lucerne - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Arena Cartier - 4.1 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place Forzani - 4.6 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Arena Richard Trottier - 4.8 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Le St-Martin Hotel &amp; Suites Laval is Montreal, QC (YUL-Pierre Elliott Trudeau Intl.) - 12.1 km / 7.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Le St-Martin Hotel &amp; Suites Laval is Montreal, PQ (YUL-Pierre Elliott Trudeau Intl.) - 11.9 km / 7.4 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property’s location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 21 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>