<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>118331950</Id><Name>DoubleTree by Hilton Billings</Name><Region><Id>19383</Id><Name>Billings, MT</Name><CityId>19383</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>27 N. 27th Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Billings</City><State /><Zip>59101</Zip><Country>USA</Country><Tel>+1-406-252-7400</Tel><Fax>+1-406-252-2401</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Welcome to the DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel Billings. A towering landmark in downtown Billings since 1980, our renovated hotel is a quick walk to corporate offices, government buildings and local restaurants. Rocky Mountain College and Montana State University Billings are both a 10-minute drive, and family-friendly attractions like ZooMontana and The Reef Indoor Water Park are just 15 minutes away. For your convenience, the hotel offers a complimentary shuttle to BIL Airport every 30 minutes.Grab a warm DoubleTree chocolate chip cookie at check-in and settle into a guest room with complimentary WiFi, plush bedding, a 32-inch LCD TV and ergonomic workspace. Executive rooms offer access to the Executive Lounge for complimentary breakfast and evening snacks and drinks. Here a few days? Stretch out in a suite with a living area and private bedroom.Enjoy unique hotel dining in Billings, MT during your stay. Our rooftop restaurant Montana Sky serves a locally inspired menu along with gorgeous views from 20 floors up. Stop by Montanaâ??s Lounge to have a beer and shoot pool. The hotel also has a StarbucksÂ® Coffee, daily room service, and a convenience shop with drinks and snacks.Our Billings, MT hotel event space includes a beautiful Grand Ballroom for up to 400 guests, plus 12 conference rooms for bridal showers or small meetings. Work smart in the 24-hour business center, and exercise in the 24-hour fitness center.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>