<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>118479</Id><Name>The Suites At 1king West</Name><Region><Id>20350</Id><Name>Toronto City</Name><CityId>15796</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1 KING STREET WEST</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>TORONTO</City><State /><Zip>M5H 1A1</Zip><Country>Canada</Country><Tel>4165488100</Tel><Fax>4165488101</Fax><Email>reservations@onekingwest.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>500</CountRooms><CountFloors>51</CountFloors><CountSuites>500</CountSuites><Latitude>43.649005</Latitude><Longitude>-79.378499</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/YTO-SUIhotel_Exterior_1.jpg</Url><Width>270</Width><Height>293</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption>Exterior</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/YTO-SUIhotel_Exterior_1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>60</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>80</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/YTO-SUIhotel_Suite_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>188</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption>Suite</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/YTO-SUIhotel_Suite_1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;One King West Hotel &amp; Residence is in the heart of Toronto, walking distance from Hockey Hall of Fame and Sony Centre for the Performing Arts. This 4-star condo is close to CN Tower and University of Toronto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 370 individually furnished guestrooms, featuring refrigerators and microwaves. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. 47-inch LED televisions with digital programming provide entertainment, while wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected. Bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including an indoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and a fireplace in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant or in a coffee shop/café. Or stay in and take advantage of the condo's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour business center, limo/town car service, and a computer station. Event facilities at this condo consist of a conference center, conference space, and meeting rooms.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant or in a coffee shop/café. Or stay in and take advantage of the condo's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including an indoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and a fireplace in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 370 individually furnished guestrooms, featuring refrigerators and microwaves. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. 47-inch LED televisions with digital programming provide entertainment, while wireless Internet access (surcharge) keeps you connected. Bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>One King West Hotel &amp; Residence is in the heart of Toronto, walking distance from Hockey Hall of Fame and Sony Centre for the Performing Arts. This 4-star condo is close to CN Tower and University of Toronto. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Hockey Hall of Fame - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sony Centre for the Performing Arts - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Cathedral Church of St James - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brookfield Place - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Elgin and Winter Garden Theatres - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Lawrence Market - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Massey Hall - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Air Canada Centre - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Michael's Cathedral - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Nathan Phillips Square - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Toronto Eaton Centre - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Osgoode Hall - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of the Holy Trinity - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Four Seasons Centre - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Toronto City Hall - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Toronto, ON (YTZ-Billy Bishop Toronto City) - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi&lt;br /&gt;Toronto, ON (YYZ-Pearson Intl.) - 19.1 km / 11.9 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for One King West Hotel &amp; Residence is Toronto, ON (YYZ-Pearson Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The closest major airports to One King West Hotel &amp; Residence are:&lt;br /&gt;Toronto, ON (YTZ-Billy Bishop Toronto City Airport) - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi&lt;br /&gt;Toronto, ON (YYZ-Pearson Intl.) - 19.1 km / 11.9 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for One King West Hotel &amp; Residence is Toronto, ON (YYZ-Pearson Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property’s location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Sauna</Code><Text>Sauna</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TrouserPress</Code><Text>Trouser press</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shops</Code><Text>Shops</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>