<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>118461427</Id><Name>Embassy Suites by Hilton Greenville Downtown Riverplace</Name><Region><Id>21549</Id><Name>Greenville</Name><CityId>19587</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>250 Riverplace</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Greenville</City><State /><Zip>29601</Zip><Country>USA</Country><Tel>+1-864-263-4800</Tel><Fax>+1-864-263-4803</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;span class="hddesctitle"&gt;General Description&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Located along the Swamp Rabbit Trail in downtown Greenville, the Embassy Suites Greenville Downtown Riverplace provides guests with exceptional access to hundreds of shops, restaurants and the award-winning Falls Park. Contemporary patterns and styles combine with classic textures and finishes to bring a timeless quality to the interiors of this welcoming all-suites hotel.Make yourself at home in a comfortable studio suite or two-room suite with spacious living area. Each suite features complimentary WiFi, a mini refrigerator, microwave, wet bar, sofa bed and work desk. A select number of our suites offer balconies overlooking the downtown skyline while others include a premium room package with an assortment of treats. And beverages.You can start every day the right way, with our free cooked-to-order breakfast,. Enjoy drinks and snacks at the complimentary evening reception*. Sizzling USDA Prime steaks and award-winning wines are on the menu at Ruthâ??s Chris, an iconic American steakhouse, while our unique UP Rooftop restaurant and bar offers hand-crafted cocktails, delicious local cuisine and spectacular rooftop views.Take a dip in our saltwater swimming pool â?? the only indoor pool in downtown â?? and work out using the cardiovascular equipment and weights in the state-of-the-art fitness center. Our Greenville, SC hotel offers flexible event spaces, ideal for small to medium size meetings and weddings.*Service of alcohol subject to state and local laws. Must be of legal drinking age.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>