<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>118461440</Id><Name>Homewood Suites by Hilton Grand Rapids Downtown</Name><Region><Id>19582</Id><Name>Grand Rapids, MI</Name><CityId>19582</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>161 Ottawa Avenue N.W.</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Grand Rapids</City><State /><Zip>49503</Zip><Country>USA</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;span class="hddesctitle"&gt;General Description&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Enjoy all the comforts of home when you stay at Homewood Suites by Hilton Grand Rapids/Downtown. Discover shopping, dining and entertainment within walking distance, and enjoy easy access to downtown Grand Rapids attractions like the Gerald R. Ford Museum, the Grand Rapids Public Museum, the Van Andel Arena and the Grand Rapids Civic Theater. We are also just four blocks from DeVos Place, nominated Beer City USA, and 18 minutes from Gerald R. Ford International Airport.Join us each morning for a complimentary hot full breakfast, and unwind at our complimentary evening social*, Monday through Thursday. Sip cocktails in the only rooftop bar in Grand Rapids - the perfect spot to enjoy amazing views of downtown. There is an additional bar located on the second floor, and a warm and welcoming coffee shop, Jam 'N Bean, on the first floor of the hotel lobby. Open for breakfast, lunch and dinner, Sundance Grill &amp; Bar also boasts Grand Rapidsâ?? only Margarita Bar.Buy snacks, beer, wine, chilled meals and sundries in the 24-hour convenience mart. Feel at home in a spacious suite, featuring complimentary WiFi and a full kitchen. Refresh in the sparkling swimming pool and energize in the expanded 24-hour fitness center. Hold an event for up to 96 people at this extended-stay hotel in Grand Rapids with two flexible meeting rooms, or organize a small private party in our rooftop bar.*State and local laws apply.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>