<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>118462673</Id><Name>Ocean Oak Resort by Hilton Grand Vacations</Name><Region><Id>19607</Id><Name>Hilton Head, SC</Name><CityId>19607</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>41 South Forest Beach Drive</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Hilton Head Island</City><State /><Zip>29928</Zip><Country>USA</Country><Tel>+1-407-722-3466</Tel><Fax>+1-407-722-3333</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;span class="hddesctitle"&gt;General Description&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Daily Resort Charge will be added to the room rate and includes: Basic Guest Internet Access, Local and Toll-Free Calls, Self Parking for One Vehicle, unlimited DVD Rental and (2) 16 oz. Bottles of Water Per Day.Set along the breezy coastline of Hilton Head Island, SC, the Ocean Oak Resort by Hilton Grand Vacations offers a peaceful retreat in a park-like setting with all the comforts of home. This new resort is less than a mile from the oceanside paths and activities at Coligny Beach Park, just a 10-minute drive to South Beach and Harbour Town, and a quick ride to the vacation conveniences along Palmetto Bay Road/Highway 278. Enjoy easy access to 250 Hilton Head restaurants and 20 golf courses during your stay.Every unit at our all-suite resort has 2 bedrooms, a full kitchen with stainless steel appliances, a dining area, living space, washer/dryer, and 2 bathrooms. Relax watching a movie on the DVD player, and take in the view from your private balcony.Grab a cocktail from the pool bar and wade into the zero-entry pool with spray features. Relax on the sun shelf and enjoy the ocean breeze, then head for the lap pool for a swim. Want some exercise? Visit our well-equipped fitness center for a workout with free weights and cardio machines. Children will love our kids activity area and DVD kiosks.Daily Resort Charge of 20.00USD plus tax will be added to the room rate and includes: guest internet access; self parking for one vehicle; DVD NOW with unlimited movies; 2 16 oz. bottles of water per day; 1-800/local calls.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>