<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>118567825</Id><Name>Homewood Suites by Hilton Topeka</Name><Region><Id>20030</Id><Name>Topeka, KS</Name><CityId>20030</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1519 Southwest Arrowhead Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Topeka</City><State /><Zip>66604</Zip><Country>USA</Country><Tel>+1-785-861-7840</Tel><Fax>+1-785-861-7841</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;span class="hddesctitle"&gt;General Description&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Conveniently located in the heart of Topeka's business, entertainment and shopping district, the cozy Homewood Suites by Hilton Topeka hotel is less than a mile from the interstate. With a wide variety of restaurants nearby - many within walking distance - and lots of leisure activities available within a short five minute drive, our extended-stay hotel is an ideal base in the center of Topeka, Kansas. A complimentary shuttle service within a five mile radius makes it easy to explore the area.Join us in the lodge each morning for a complimentary hot full breakfast, and unwind with friends old and new at the complimentary evening social*, Monday through Thursday. Stock up on snacks, chilled meals and toiletries in the 24-hour convenience mart, or take advantage of our complimentary grocery shopping service. Feel at home in a spacious studio, one- or two-bedroom suite, featuring separate living, working and sleeping areas. Enjoy amenities including complimentary WiFi and a fully-equipped kitchen.Discover fantastic leisure amenities at this extended-stay Topeka hotel. Plunge into the heated indoor swimming pool, soak in the hot tub, and energize in the 24-hour fitness center. Challenge a friend to a game of pool or foosball in our modern games room. Watch TV in the lodge, or relax on the outdoor patio, which features a fire pit and communal BBQ grills. The 333 sq. ft. conference room is ideal for meetings for up to 15 people.*Subject to state and local laws. Must be of legal drinking age.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>