<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11855869</Id><Name>Cajupi</Name><Region><Id>15219</Id><Name>Tirana</Name><CityId>15219</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>CERCIZ TOPULLI SQUARE GJIRKOASTER</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>TIRANA</City><State /><Zip>1001</Zip><Country>ALBANIA</Country><Tel /><Fax /><Email>EUROPATRAVEL@ALBANIAONLIBNE.NET</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>40.074541</Latitude><Longitude>20.1401</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>This hotel is located in Gjirokastra, approximately 1 km from the centre. The hotel is recognised as the largest tourist complex in the region. It is situated on a central square, eriz Topulli Square, where a monument stands dedicated to the distinguished national hero of the same name. Shade is provided by the magnificent Argjiro Castle, which can be found 400 m from the hotel. Guests can visit Vlore, which is located roughly 109 km away. The nearby airport is situated 80 km away.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>All rooms come with an en suite bathroom with a shower and a hairdryer. Rooms also come equipped with a direct dial telephone. Standard in-room amenities include satellite/cable TV and Internet access. Furthermore, an ironing set and individually regulated air conditioning are provided in all accommodation as standard.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DiningFacilities</Type><Text>This air-conditioned hotel comprises a total of 40 rooms. The hotel was constructed with a variety of activities in mind, including family holidays, and offers plenty of space. From the roof garden of the complex, guests can enjoy views of the wonderful landscape of the city. Guests are welcomed at the 24-hour reception desk, which offers currency exchange facilities. Lift access to the upper floors is also available. Guests can enjoy a drink at the bar, and dine in the restaurant/pizzeria/confectionery. Conference facilities are available to business travellers, and the conference hall/meeting room is fitted with the necessary equipment. Guests can enjoy the convenience of Internet access. They can also take advantage of the room and laundry services. Those arriving by car may leave their vehicles in the hotel car park.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MoneyExchange</Code><Text>Money exchange</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MedicalService</Code><Text>Medical Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>