<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>118584</Id><Name>Le Saint-Anne</Name><Region><Id>20345</Id><Name>Quebec City</Name><CityId>15762</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>32, RUE SAINTE-ANNE</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>QUEBEC</City><State /><Zip>G1R 3X3</Zip><Country>Canada</Country><Tel>4186941455</Tel><Fax>4186924096</Fax><Email>info@hotelste-anne.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>28</CountRooms><CountSuites>1</CountSuites></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1001/55941hotel1.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>206</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1001/55941hotel1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>108</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>3148</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1001/55941bar1.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>209</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1001/55941bar1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>107</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2843</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>HotelAmenities</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hôtel Sainte-Anne, you'll be centrally located in Quebec, steps from Cathedral of the Holy Trinity and Quebec Experience. This romantic hotel is close to Place Royale and Citadelle of Quebec.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 28 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and minibars. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and complimentary newspapers, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and dry cleaning/laundry services. Planning an event in Quebec? This hotel has 1076 square feet (100 square meters) of space consisting of conference space and meeting rooms.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 28 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and minibars. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and complimentary newspapers, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hôtel Sainte-Anne, you'll be centrally located in Quebec, steps from Cathedral of the Holy Trinity and Quebec Experience. This romantic hotel is close to Place Royale and Citadelle of Quebec. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Cathedral of the Holy Trinity - 0 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;Quebec Experience - 0.1 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;Basilique Cathedrale Notre-Dame of Quebec - 0.1 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;Quebec City Town Hall - 0.1 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;Musee du Fort - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of French America - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Samuel de Champlain Statue - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Price Tower - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ursulines de Quebec Museum - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Parks Canada's Dufferin Terrace - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Quebec Funicular - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Quartier Petit Champlain - 0.2 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Seminary of Quebec - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maison Chevalier - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Theatre Petit Champlain - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hôtel Sainte-Anne is Quebec, QC (YQB-Jean Lesage Intl.) - 13.7 km / 8.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Hotel Sainte-Anne is Quebec, PQ (YQB-Jean Lesage Intl.) - 13.7 km / 8.5 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property’s location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioned</Code><Text>Air-conditioned</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DiningRoom</Code><Text>Dining Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantAirconditioned</Code><Text>Restaurant Air-Conditioned</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestuarantHighChair</Code><Text>Restuarant High Chair</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomPrivateBathroom</Code><Text>Private bathrooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniFridge</Code><Text>MiniFridge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DoubleBeds</Code><Text>Double Beds</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Carpeted</Code><Text>Carpeted</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditionedRooms</Code><Text>Air-conditioned rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomCentralHeating</Code><Text>Central heating in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Launderette</Code><Text>Launderette</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>