<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11852486</Id><Name>Villa Sarna Ubud Bali</Name><Region><Id>20873</Id><Name>Ubud</Name><CityId>16956</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Banjar Tangkup, Desa Kedisan</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Ubud</City><State /><Zip>80361</Zip><Country>Indonesia</Country><Tel>+62-361-977-265</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>-8.4894</Latitude><Longitude>115.2755</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Tegallalang, Villa Sarna is in a rural location and close to Tegallalang Handicraft Center and Gunung Kawi Temple. This 4-star villa is within the vicinity of Elephant Safari Park and Tirta Empul Temple.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Rooms have private patios. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a garden. This villa also features complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare, and wedding services. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A complimentary cooked-to-order breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, limo/town car service, and dry cleaning/laundry services. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; A complimentary cooked-to-order breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a garden. This villa also features complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare, and wedding services. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Rooms have private patios. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Tegallalang, Villa Sarna is in a rural location and close to Tegallalang Handicraft Center and Gunung Kawi Temple. This 4-star villa is within the vicinity of Elephant Safari Park and Tirta Empul Temple. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Tegallalang Handicraft Center - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gunung Kawi Temple - 3.8 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Elephant Safari Park - 4.9 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tirta Empul Temple - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Botanic Garden Ubud - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kehen Temple - 7.3 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Seniwati Gallery of Art by Women - 7.7 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gaya Art Space - 7.9 km / 4.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Puri Lukisan Museum - 8.1 km / 5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pura Taman Saraswati - 8.1 km / 5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ubud Royal Palace - 8.1 km / 5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ubud Market - 8.1 km / 5.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Neka Art Museum - 8.2 km / 5.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Blanco Museum - 8.2 km / 5.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Komaneka Fine Art Gallery - 8.8 km / 5.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Villa Sarna is Denpasar (DPS-Ngurah Rai Intl.) - 36.7 km / 22.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Villa Sarna is Denpasar (DPS-Ngurah Rai Intl.) - 31 km / 19.2 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>