<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>118687045</Id><Name>Grand Central Apartments</Name><Region><Id>15472</Id><Name>Brussels</Name><CityId>15472</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Boulevard Anspach 106</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Brussels</City><State /><Zip>1000</Zip><Country>Belgium</Country><Tel>+32 27 93 75 80</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><CheckInTime>15</CheckInTime><CheckOutTime>11</CheckOutTime></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Grand Central Apartments is a self-catering accommodation 500 meters from the Rue Neuve, the main shopping street.
 IMPORTANT NOTE : Guests arriving after 20:00 are required to contact Grand Central Apartments ( by telephone 32-2-7937580 or by email reservations@grandcentralapartments.be ) 24 hours prior to their arrival to make arrangements for check-in. For same day reservations, please also contact the property prior to arrival to make arrangements for check-in. Please note that the entrance of the hotel is situated around the corner on Rue Des Pierres. This property is located in a car-free zone. A security deposit of EUR 100 is required upon arrival for incidentals. This deposit is fully refundable upon check-out and subject to a damage inspection of the accommodation. Guests are required to show a photo identification and credit card upon check-in. Please note that all Special Requests are subject to availability and additional charges may apply. Please inform Grand Central Apartments in advance of your expected arrival time, wherever possible</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in the heart of Brussels, just steps away from the Stock Exchange Market, Grand Central Apartments is a self-catering accommodation offering stylish, refurbished apartments.  The property is 200 meters from Brussels City Hall and 300 meters from the famous Grand Place, in the middle of the car-free zone.
Many bars, restaurants and coffee shops are to be found in the near vicinity. The apartments are located above a supermarket.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PropertyInformation</Type><Text>This is a traditional building.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>Short</Type><Text>This accommodation has a very small lobby.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>