<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11862358</Id><Name>Horison Seminyak</Name><Region><Id>20874</Id><Name>Seminyak - Legian Beach</Name><CityId>16956</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Jl. Arjuna (Double Six Beach)</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Seminyak</City><State /><Zip>80361</Zip><Country>Indonesia</Country><Tel>+62361 730733</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>-8.696</Latitude><Longitude>115.1658</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/SMIN-9Bhotel_Guest_Room_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>241</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/SMIN-9Bhotel_Guest_Room_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/SMIN-9Bhotel_Suite_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>221</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/SMIN-9Bhotel_Suite_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/SMIN-9Bhotel_Suite_2.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>263</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/SMIN-9Bhotel_Suite_2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/SMIN-9Bhotel_Swimming_Pool_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>269</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/SMIN-9Bhotel_Swimming_Pool_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>SwimmingPool</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/SMIN-9Bhotel_Restaurant_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/SMIN-9Bhotel_Restaurant_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/SMIN-9Bhotel_Suite_3.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>247</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/SMIN-9Bhotel_Suite_3_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Horison Seminyak Bali in Seminyak, you'll be on the beach and minutes from Double Six Beach and close to Kuta Beach. This beach resort is within close proximity of Legian Beach and AJ Hackett Kuta Bali.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 154 air-conditioned rooms featuring LCD televisions. Your Select Comfort bed comes with down comforters. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature rainfall showerheads and complimentary toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and a hair salon. Additional amenities include shopping on site, wedding services, and barbecue grills. Getting to the surf and sand is a breeze with the complimentary beach shuttle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the resort's restaurant, where you can enjoy drinks at a bar, take in a pool view, and even dine alfresco (weather permitting). You can also stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, a computer station, and dry cleaning/laundry services. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available 24 hours).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the resort's restaurant, where you can enjoy drinks at a bar, take in a pool view, and even dine alfresco (weather permitting). You can also stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and a hair salon. Additional amenities include shopping on site, wedding services, and barbecue grills. Getting to the surf and sand is a breeze with the complimentary beach shuttle. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 154 air-conditioned rooms featuring LCD televisions. Your Select Comfort bed comes with down comforters. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature rainfall showerheads and complimentary toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Horison Seminyak Bali in Seminyak, you'll be on the beach and minutes from Double Six Beach and close to Kuta Beach. This beach resort is within close proximity of Legian Beach and AJ Hackett Kuta Bali. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Double Six Beach - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Legian Beach - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;AJ Hackett Kuta Bali - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Seminyak Beach - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Honorary Consulate of Brazil - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gado Gado Beach - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Padang Padang Beach - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eat Street - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Honorary Consulate of Malaysia - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Seminyak Square - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kendra Gallery - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Honorary Consulate of Spain - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kuta Galeria Shopping Arcade - 2 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Swiss Consulate - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;TAKSU Bali Gallery - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Horison Seminyak Bali is Denpasar (DPS-Ngurah Rai Intl.) - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>