<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11863401</Id><Name>Scape Condotel Sanur</Name><Region><Id>20878</Id><Name>Sanur</Name><CityId>16956</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Jl. Danau Tamblingan 80</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Bali</City><State /><Zip>80228</Zip><Country>Indonesia</Country><Tel>62361-285953</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>-8.7066</Latitude><Longitude>115.2622</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at S'Cape in Denpasar (Sanur), you'll be minutes from Honorary Consulate of Germany and close to Sanur Beach. This condo is within close proximity of Honorary Consulate of Hungary and Pura Segara Temple.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 16 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens. Rooms have private balconies. Premium TV channels and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and minibars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with onsite massages or enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Breakfast is available for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, a 24-hour front desk, and a library.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Breakfast is available for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with onsite massages or enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, tour/ticket assistance, and barbecue grills. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 16 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens. Rooms have private balconies. Premium TV channels and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and minibars.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at S'Cape in Denpasar (Sanur), you'll be minutes from Honorary Consulate of Germany and close to Sanur Beach. This condo is within close proximity of Honorary Consulate of Hungary and Pura Segara Temple. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Honorary Consulate of Germany - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Honorary Consulate of Hungary - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pura Segara Temple - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Honorary Consulate of Sweden and Finland - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maha Art Gallery - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bali Beach Golf Course - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sanur Beach - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Le Mayeur Museum - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;British Honorary Consulate - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pura Blanjong - 2 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Matahari Terbit Beach - 2.2 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Udayana Golf Driving Range - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Honorary Consulate of the Czech Republic - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Honorary Consulate of Chile - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Consulate Agency of France - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for S'Cape is Denpasar (DPS-Ngurah Rai Intl.) - 12.6 km / 7.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>