<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11868414</Id><Name>Mirihi Island Resort</Name><Region><Id>17412</Id><Name>Maldives (all islands)</Name><CityId>17412</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Mirihi</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>South Ari Atoll</City><State /><Zip /><Country>Maldives</Country><Tel>960 668 0500</Tel><Fax>960 668 0501</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>3.6198</Latitude><Longitude>72.7803</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Mirihi (South Ari Atoll), Mirihi Island Resort is within the region of Maafushivaru Island Pier and Maafushivaru Island Beach. This 5-star resort is within the region of Vakarufalhi Beach and Manta Point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 37 air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and minibars. Rooms have private furnished balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature rainfall showerheads and complimentary toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. After a day at the private beach, you can enjoy other recreational amenities, which include a fitness center. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at one of the resort's dining establishments, which include 3 restaurants and a coffee shop/café. From your room, you can also access room service (during limited hours). Relax with a refreshing drink at one of the 2 bars/lounges. A complimentary breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge at scheduled times.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at one of the resort's dining establishments, which include 3 restaurants and a coffee shop/café. From your room, you can also access room service (during limited hours). Relax with a refreshing drink at one of the 2 bars/lounges. A complimentary breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. After a day at the private beach, you can enjoy other recreational amenities, which include a fitness center. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 37 air-conditioned rooms featuring iPod docking stations and minibars. Rooms have private furnished balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature rainfall showerheads and complimentary toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Mirihi (South Ari Atoll), Mirihi Island Resort is within the region of Maafushivaru Island Pier and Maafushivaru Island Beach. This 5-star resort is within the region of Vakarufalhi Beach and Manta Point. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Maafushivaru Island Pier - 13.2 km / 8.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maafushivaru Island Beach - 13.3 km / 8.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vakarufalhi Beach - 14.2 km / 8.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Manta Point - 14.4 km / 8.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dhidhoofinolhu Marina - 18.6 km / 11.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dhangethi Beach - 19.2 km / 12 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ranveli beach - 19.3 km / 12 mi &lt;br /&gt;Villingilivaru Island Pier - 19.4 km / 12 mi &lt;br /&gt;Himendhoo Thila - 33.7 km / 20.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fish Head Dive Site - 37.9 km / 23.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Malhoss Thila - 42.9 km / 26.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fesdu House Reef - 43.4 km / 26.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gaathafushi Island - 45 km / 28 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maaya Thila - 53.9 km / 33.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kudafolhudhoo Harbor - 62.5 km / 38.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Mirihi Island Resort is Male (MLE-Male Intl.) - 104.1 km / 64.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Giftshop</Code><Text>Gift Shop</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CurrencyExchangeService</Code><Text>Currency Exchange Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>