<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>118681712</Id><Name>Sheraton Salta Hotel</Name><Region><Id>15255</Id><Name>Salta</Name><CityId>15255</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Coronel Francisco de Uriondo 330</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Salta</City><State /><Zip>A4406BKQ</Zip><Country>Argentina</Country><Tel>432 3000</Tel><Fax>432 3091</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Location
The hotel is located in one of the city's most exclusive districts, just 10 blocks from Salta's bustling centre. Guests enjoy panoramic views of the Lerma Valley and can relax and enjoy their time in the welcoming neighbourhood of Monumento. They will find the nearest shops (Alta Noa Shopping) at 10 minutes' walk and bars and pubs on Calle Balcarce and Plaza 9 de Julio are just a 15-minute walk from the hotel. It is 40 minutes by car to Dique Cabra Corral and 2 hours' drive to Cafayate
Facilities
The holiday village was built in 2005. Guests can enjoy a pleasant stay in one of the 145 rooms. Most storeys can be reached by lift. Amenities include a cloakroom, a safe and a currency exchange service. Wireless internet access in public areas allows travellers to stay connected. Among the culinary options available at the complex are a restaurant, a dining area, a breakfast room, a café and a bar. Shopping facilities are also available. The grounds of the accommodation feature a playground and an attractive garden. Additional facilities at the complex include a playroom. Guests arriving by car can leave their vehicles in the garage (for a fee) or in the car park (for a fee). Available services and facilities include medical assistance, room service and a laundry service.
Rooms
Each of the rooms is appointed with air conditioning, central heating and a bathroom. Most rooms feature a balcony with a view for guests' enjoyment. The rooms have a double bed or a king-size bed. There is also a safe. Guests will also find a mini fridge included as standard. Internet access, a telephone and a TV add to the comfort of the holiday. Rooms suitable for wheelchair access are bookable. The bathrooms are fitted with a shower and a bathtub. A hairdryer is also available. Bathrooms with wheelchair access can also be booked. The holiday village offers family rooms and non-smoking rooms.
Sports/Entertainment
The complex features a pool and an outdoor pool. Parasols are available to travellers. The hot tub is the perfect place to relax. The poolside bar serves a selection of refreshing drinks. A range of options are available, including a gym, gymnastics, a sauna, a steam bath, massage treatments and a solarium. A kids' club and a casino are among the available leisure options.
Meals
Catering options available at the accommodation include bed and breakfast, half board and full board. Guests can choose to book options such as breakfast, lunch or dinner. Special meals, including special dietary cuisine, are also available. The complex also offers special catering options. Drinks are included in the price for guests.
Payment
The following credit cards are accepted at the holiday village: American Express, VISA and MasterCard.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The hotel is located in one of the city's most exclusive districts, just 10 blocks from Salta's bustling centre. Guests enjoy panoramic views of the Lerma Valley and can relax and enjoy their time in the welcoming neighbourhood of Monumento. They will find the nearest shops (Alta Noa Shopping) at 10 minutes' walk and bars and pubs on Calle Balcarce and Plaza 9 de Julio are just a 15-minute walk from the hotel. It is 40 minutes by car to Dique Cabra Corral and 2 hours' drive to Cafayate</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Each of the rooms is appointed with air conditioning, central heating and a bathroom. Most rooms feature a balcony with a view for guests' enjoyment. The rooms have a double bed or a king-size bed. There is also a safe. Guests will also find a mini fridge included as standard. Internet access, a telephone and a TV add to the comfort of the holiday. Rooms suitable for wheelchair access are bookable. The bathrooms are fitted with a shower and a bathtub. A hairdryer is also available. Bathrooms with wheelchair access can also be booked. The holiday village offers family rooms and non-smoking rooms.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PropertyInformation</Type><Text>The holiday village was built in 2005. Guests can enjoy a pleasant stay in one of the 145 rooms. Most storeys can be reached by lift. Amenities include a cloakroom, a safe and a currency exchange service. Wireless internet access in public areas allows travellers to stay connected. Among the culinary options available at the complex are a restaurant, a dining area, a breakfast room, a café and a bar. Shopping facilities are also available. The grounds of the accommodation feature a playground and an attractive garden. Additional facilities at the complex include a playroom. Guests arriving by car can leave their vehicles in the garage (for a fee) or in the car park (for a fee). Available services and facilities include medical assistance, room service and a laundry service.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>AreaActivities</Type><Text>The complex features a pool and an outdoor pool. Parasols are available to travellers. The hot tub is the perfect place to relax. The poolside bar serves a selection of refreshing drinks. A range of options are available, including a gym, gymnastics, a sauna, a steam bath, massage treatments and a solarium. A kids' club and a casino are among the available leisure options.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DiningFacilities</Type><Text>Catering options available at the accommodation include bed and breakfast, half board and full board. Guests can choose to book options such as breakfast, lunch or dinner. Special meals, including special dietary cuisine, are also available. The complex also offers special catering options. Drinks are included in the price for guests.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>The following credit cards are accepted at the holiday village: American Express, VISA and MasterCard.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>