<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11879656</Id><Name>Grand Hotel D'Orleans</Name><Region><Id>20590</Id><Name>Toulouse</Name><CityId>16493</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>RUE DE BAYARD 72</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>TOULOUSE</City><State /><Zip>31000</Zip><Country>FRANCE</Country><Tel>0033561629847</Tel><Fax>0033561627824</Fax><Email>contact@grand-hotel-orleans.fr</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>43.6084842</Latitude><Longitude>1.4483821</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Grand Hotel d'Orléans in Toulouse, you'll be minutes from Toulouse National Theatre and Basilique Saint-Sernin. This family-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Place Wilson and Capitole de Toulouse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 56 air-conditioned guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, and cribs/infant beds (complimentary) can be requested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Grand Hotel d'Orléans. Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a computer station, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and a safe deposit box at the front desk. Event facilities at this hotel consist of conference space and meeting rooms. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Grand Hotel d'Orléans. Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 56 air-conditioned guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones, and cribs/infant beds (complimentary) can be requested.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Grand Hotel d'Orléans in Toulouse, you'll be minutes from Toulouse National Theatre and Basilique Saint-Sernin. This family-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Place Wilson and Capitole de Toulouse. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Toulouse National Theatre - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place Wilson - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Basilique Saint-Sernin - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Capitole de Toulouse - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place du Capitole - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place St. Georges - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Halle aux Grains Theater - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Toulouse I - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Musee des Augustins - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Saint Etienne Cathedrale - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palais des Sports - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jacobins Church - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Esquirol Place - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pierre Baudis Congress Center - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Japanese Garden Toulouse - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Grand Hotel d'Orléans is Toulouse (TLS-Blagnac) - 6.6 km / 4.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CloakRoom</Code><Text>Cloak Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DiningRoom</Code><Text>Dining Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantAirconditioned</Code><Text>Restaurant Air-Conditioned</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant Smoking Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BicycleStorage</Code><Text>Bicycle Storage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Garage</Code><Text>Garage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Carpeted</Code><Text>Carpeted</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Cafe(s)</Code><Text>Cafe(s)</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>