<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11876522</Id><Name>Mercure Belle Plagne 2100</Name><Region><Id>20574</Id><Name>La Plagne</Name><CityId>16487</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>La Montagne des Génisses</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>BELLE PLAGNE</City><State /><Zip>73210</Zip><Country>FRANCE</Country><Tel>0033479091209</Tel><Fax>0033479092952</Fax><Email>h5627@accor.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>45.508745</Latitude><Longitude>6.707143</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Mercure Belle Plagne in Macot-la-Plagne (Paradiski), you'll be convenient to Roche de Mio Gondola and Paradiski Ski Resort. This ski hotel is within close proximity of La Plagne Ski Resort and La Plagne Bobsleigh Track.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 144 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones and safes, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (complimentary).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the convenience of ski-in/ski-out access at this hotel, which also features a spa tub. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access and ski storage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at one of the hotel's 3 restaurants. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour front desk and an elevator (lift). Event facilities at this hotel consist of a conference center and meeting rooms.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 5 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at one of the hotel's 3 restaurants. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy the convenience of ski-in/ski-out access at this hotel, which also features a spa tub. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access and ski storage. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 144 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include phones and safes, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (complimentary).</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Mercure Belle Plagne in Macot-la-Plagne (Paradiski), you'll be convenient to Roche de Mio Gondola and Paradiski Ski Resort. This ski hotel is within close proximity of La Plagne Ski Resort and La Plagne Bobsleigh Track. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Roche de Mio Gondola - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Paradiski Ski Resort - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;La Plagne Ski Resort - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;La Plagne Bobsleigh Track - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bellecote Gondola - 2.8 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aime 2000 Ski Resort - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Telemetro Gondola - 3.3 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bellecote Glacier - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Espace Paradisio Aquatic Center - 6 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Champagny Gondola - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Peisey Ski Lift - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vanoise Express Cable Car - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Peisey-Vallandry Ski Resort - 6.4 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Montmayeur Tower - 6.7 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Transarc Gondola - 8.9 km / 5.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Mercure Belle Plagne is Lyon (LYS-Saint-Exupery) - 129.2 km / 80.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Mercure Belle Plagne is Lyon (LYS-Saint-Exupery) - 126.9 km / 78.8 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DiscoClub</Code><Text>Disco / Club</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>