<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11877206</Id><Name>Shishangeni Private Lodge</Name><Region><Id>18259</Id><Name>Kruger National Park</Name><CityId>18259</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Kruger National Park Mpanamana Consession Crocodile </Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Mpumalanga</City><State /><Zip>TBA</Zip><Country>South Africa</Country><Tel>+270137353300</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>-25.3894</Latitude><Longitude>31.975</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Kruger National Park, Shishangeni Private Lodge is in a national park and within the vicinity of Kambaku Komatipoort Golf Course and Kruger National Park Crocodile Bridge Gate.  This hotel is within the region of Lionspruit Game Reserve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 22 air-conditioned rooms featuring fireplaces. Rooms have private furnished patios. Conveniences include phones, as well as minibars and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities including an outdoor pool and a fitness center. This hotel also features wireless Internet access (surcharge), babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Shishangeni Private Lodge. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Breakfast is available for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services and a library. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Shishangeni Private Lodge. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Breakfast is available for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities including an outdoor pool and a fitness center. This hotel also features wireless Internet access (surcharge), babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 22 air-conditioned rooms featuring fireplaces. Rooms have private furnished patios. Conveniences include phones, as well as minibars and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Kruger National Park, Shishangeni Private Lodge is in a national park and within the vicinity of Kambaku Komatipoort Golf Course and Kruger National Park Crocodile Bridge Gate.  This hotel is within the region of Lionspruit Game Reserve. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Kambaku Komatipoort Golf Course - 5.4 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kruger National Park Crocodile Bridge Gate - 8.9 km / 5.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lionspruit Game Reserve - 17.1 km / 10.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kruger National Park Malelane Gate - 45.1 km / 28 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kruger National Park Numbi Gate - 82.8 km / 51.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Elephant Whispers - 94.4 km / 58.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hazyview Elephant Sanctuary - 97.5 km / 60.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lowveld Botanical Garden - 100.7 km / 62.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;God's Window - 123.4 km / 76.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sabie Falls - 125 km / 77.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sudwala Caves - 128.1 km / 79.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hoedspruit Endangered Species Centre - 136 km / 84.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Timbavati Game Reserve - 144.8 km / 90 mi &lt;br /&gt;Moholoholo Wildlife Rehabilitation Centre - 145.3 km / 90.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Blyde River Canyon - 150.3 km / 93.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Shishangeni Private Lodge is Kruger National Park (MQP-Kruger Mpumalanga Intl.) - 88 km / 54.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Shishangeni Private Lodge is Kruger National Park (MQP-Kruger Mpumalanga Intl.) - 88 km / 54.7 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>