<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11870199</Id><Name>Tarragona Lodge</Name><Region><Id>18240</Id><Name>Cape Town</Name><CityId>18240</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Corner Of Disa River Road And Valley Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Cape Town</City><State /><Zip>7800</Zip><Country>South Africa</Country><Tel>27217905080</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>-34.0147</Latitude><Longitude>18.3792</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Cape Town (Hout Bay), Tarragona Lodge is convenient to World of Birds and Bishopsford Bonsai Nursery.  This 4-star guesthouse is within close proximity of Original T Bag Designs and Constantia Glen Winery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of 10 guestrooms featuring plasma televisions. Your room comes with a Tempur-Pedic bed. Rooms have private balconies or patios. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature deep soaking bathtubs and complimentary toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and a terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. Additional amenities include wedding services, a fireplace in the lobby, and a television in the lobby. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite from a snack bar/deli serving guests of Tarragona Lodge. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and dry cleaning/laundry services. Event facilities at this guesthouse consist of a conference center and a meeting room. Guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle for a surcharge, and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite from a snack bar/deli serving guests of Tarragona Lodge. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and a terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. Additional amenities include wedding services, a fireplace in the lobby, and a television in the lobby. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of 10 guestrooms featuring plasma televisions. Your room comes with a Tempur-Pedic bed. Rooms have private balconies or patios. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature deep soaking bathtubs and complimentary toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Cape Town (Hout Bay), Tarragona Lodge is convenient to World of Birds and Bishopsford Bonsai Nursery.  This 4-star guesthouse is within close proximity of Original T Bag Designs and Constantia Glen Winery. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;World of Birds - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bishopsford Bonsai Nursery - 2.8 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Original T Bag Designs - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Constantia Glen Winery - 3.3 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eagles Nest - 3.3 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hout Bay Museum - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Art in the Forest - 3.5 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Llandudno Beach - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mainstream Village &amp; Mall - 3.7 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hout Bay Craft Market - 3.8 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hout Bay Beach - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Groot Constantia Winery - 4.1 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Klein Constantia Wine Estate - 4.1 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Constantiaberg - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sandy Bay Beach - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Tarragona Lodge is Cape Town (CPT-Cape Town Intl.) - 20.6 km / 12.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Tarragona Lodge is Cape Town (CPT-Cape Town Intl.) - 20.7 km / 12.9 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>