<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11879687</Id><Name>Ibis Strasbourg</Name><Region><Id>20582</Id><Name>Strasbourg</Name><CityId>16490</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1 RUE DE SEBASTOPOL 1</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>STRASBOURG</City><State /><Zip>67000</Zip><Country>FRANCE</Country><Tel>00330390224646</Tel><Fax>00330390224647</Fax><Email>h0640@accor.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>48.586118</Latitude><Longitude>7.74211</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hôtel ibis Strasbourg Centre Halles, you'll be centrally located in Strasbourg, steps from Place des Halles Shopping Centre and minutes from Saint-Pierre-le-Jeune Church. This hotel is within close proximity of Olympe de Gouges Media Library and Aubette.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of 97 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have shower/tub combinations and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks, and cribs/infant beds can be requested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, express check-in, and complimentary newspapers in the lobby. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at noon  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Buffet breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of 97 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have shower/tub combinations and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks, and cribs/infant beds can be requested.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hôtel ibis Strasbourg Centre Halles, you'll be centrally located in Strasbourg, steps from Place des Halles Shopping Centre and minutes from Saint-Pierre-le-Jeune Church. This hotel is within close proximity of Olympe de Gouges Media Library and Aubette. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Place des Halles Shopping Centre - 0 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;Saint-Pierre-le-Jeune Church - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Olympe de Gouges Media Library - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aubette - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of St. John - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stimultania - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kleber Square - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Galeries Lafayette Shopping Centre - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Saint Peter's Church - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Temple Neuf - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Broglie Square - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Train Station Square - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Haguenau Square - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Strasbourg Opera - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;National School of Administration - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Strasbourg (XER-Boulevard de Metz Bus Stop) - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi&lt;br /&gt;Strasbourg (SXB-Strasbourg Intl.) - 9.6 km / 6 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hôtel ibis Strasbourg Centre Halles is Strasbourg (SXB-Strasbourg Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>