<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>118735795</Id><Name>Eye Hotel</Name><Region><Id>17675</Id><Name>Utrecht</Name><CityId>17675</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Wijde Begijnestraat 1-3</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Utrecht</City><State /><Zip>3512 AW</Zip><Country>Netherlands</Country><Tel>01131302330033</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><CheckInTime>15</CheckInTime><CheckOutTime>12</CheckOutTime></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Eye Hotel is all about surprising people and eye for detail, about guests and the surrounding area. Eye Hotel is unique, with focus on a good night’s sleep.

The beautiful historic building inspired us to create rooms for different kinds of guests.
 A real family room, including a cot, changing table and baby bath tub. Eye for our smallest guests.
 Light, spacious rooms with an excellent view where you can work quietly. Eye for our business guests.
 The romantic rooms on the top floor all have original beams and offer an excellent view of the historic city centre. Eye for guests wanting to explore and enjoy Utrecht for a weekend.

No matter how different, all our rooms boast top quality beds. We consider fast and reliable WIFI and a Smart-tv to be basic amenities. 
 The realisation of the concept, the design and the styling of the hotel are the result of a close cooperation with Morph Design, the design department of Morpheus.

Sustainability was central to our refurbishment and is part of how we do things. By making use of the most modern techniques, we were able to create sustainable solutions that do not interfere with our most important goal: offering our guests an amazing night's rest.
 Additionally, Eye Hotel contributes to clean water projects in Asia and Africa through her partnership with EARTH Water.
 We have full confidence in the quality of our sustainability policy - and are in full preparation to be audited by Green Key, the international standard for sustainability in hospitality.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>