<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>118735255</Id><Name>Mosaique</Name><Region><Id>20339</Id><Name>Montreal City</Name><CityId>15741</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>345 de Gauchetiere West</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Montreal</City><State /><Zip>H2Z 0A2</Zip><Country>Canada</Country><Tel>+1 514 277 6464</Tel><Fax>15142776464</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><CheckInTime>16</CheckInTime><CheckOutTime>11</CheckOutTime></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Policies
At check in all guests will be required to present a Major  Credit Card for incidentals</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>At check in all guests will be required to present a Major  Credit Card for incidentals</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Your arrival date is coming soon and we would like to thank you again for choosing Corporatestays.com&lt;http://corporatestays.com/&gt; .

- Please note that check-in time is 4PM (earlier arrival is possible at a 75$ charge, and subject to availability, please contact your Corporate Housing Specialist)

- Your keys (maximum of 2 keys per apartment) will be available at our welcome desk in our office located at 360 Boulevard Rene Levesque West, H2Z 0A7 if during opening office hours (until 7PM on Monday to Friday, until 5:30PM Saturday &amp; Sunday). For security reasons, a photo identification and credit card is required.

If you are planning on arriving after our business hours, please contact your Corporate Housing Specialist immediately to find alternative ways to check-in after hours.

- Check-out time is 11AM (late check-out until 3PM is possible at a 75$ charge, and subject to availability, please contact your Corporate Housing Specialist). 
Please drop off the keys at our welcome desk in our office located at 360 Boulevard Rene Levesque West, H2Z 0A7 if during opening office hours (from 8AM Monday to Friday, and from 9:30AM Saturday &amp; Sunday). 
Alternatively, you may also leave your keys (and parking cards &amp; remotes) in the drop-box below the CorporateStays lock-box, which are both located at the entrance of the building.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>