<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11879675</Id><Name>Campanile Toulouse Cite de L'Espace</Name><Region><Id>20590</Id><Name>Toulouse</Name><CityId>16493</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>IMPASSE RENE MOUCHOTTE</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>TOULOUSE</City><State /><Zip>31500</Zip><Country>FRANCE</Country><Tel>0033561544625</Tel><Fax>0033561348295</Fax><Email>toulouse.citeespace@campanile.fr</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>43.58472804</Latitude><Longitude>1.494140863</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Campanile Toulouse Sud-Est - Cité De L'Espace in Toulouse, you'll be in the suburbs and minutes from Cite de l'Espace and close to Musee des Augustins. This family-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Canal du Midi and Musee Georges Labit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 85 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have bathtubs and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves lunch and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff. Planning an event in Toulouse? This hotel has facilities measuring 861 square feet (80 square meters), including meeting rooms. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 4 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves lunch and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 85 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have bathtubs and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Campanile Toulouse Sud-Est - Cité De L'Espace in Toulouse, you'll be in the suburbs and minutes from Cite de l'Espace and close to Musee des Augustins. This family-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Canal du Midi and Musee Georges Labit. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Cite de l'Espace - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Canal du Midi - 2.8 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Musee Georges Labit - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Toulouse III - 3.3 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jardin des Plantes - 3.5 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jardin Royal - 3.5 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Halle aux Grains Theater - 3.6 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum of Natural History Toulouse - 3.7 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Saint Etienne Cathedrale - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place St. Georges - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Toulouse National Theatre - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Musee des Augustins - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Esquirol Place - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place Wilson - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eglise Notre-Dame de la Dalbade - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Campanile Toulouse Sud-Est - Cité De L'Espace is Toulouse (TLS-Blagnac) - 10.9 km / 6.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Campanile Toulouse Cite Espace is Toulouse, France (TLS-Blagnac) - 10.5 km / 6.5 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>CoffeeTeaMaker</Code><Text>Tea and Coffee maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HandicapAccessible</Code><Text>Handicap accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DiningRoom</Code><Text>Dining Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantAirconditioned</Code><Text>Restaurant Air-Conditioned</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MobilePhoneNetwork</Code><Text>Mobile Phone Network</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WLANAccessPoint</Code><Text>WLAN Access Point</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BicycleStorage</Code><Text>Bicycle Storage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Garage</Code><Text>Garage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniClub</Code><Text>Mini Club</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lounge</Code><Text>Lounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Launderette</Code><Text>Launderette</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccessible</Code><Text>Wheelchair Accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Cafe(s)</Code><Text>Cafe(s)</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>