<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11870085</Id><Name>Kyriad Orange</Name><Region><Id>36909</Id><Name>Orange</Name><CityId>16398</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>AVENIDA L'ARC DE TRIOMFE 86 86</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>ORANGE</City><State /><Zip>84100</Zip><Country>FRANCE</Country><Tel>00330490518787</Tel><Fax>00330490343589</Fax><Email>orange@kyriad.fr</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>44.13953</Latitude><Longitude>4.8058</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Kyriad Orange Centre in Orange, you'll be minutes from Triumphal Arch of Orange and Orange Amphitheatre. This residence is within close proximity of Ancient Theatre of Orange and Orange Golf Club.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 59 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers, and irons/ironing boards can be requested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the residence's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, a safe deposit box at the front desk, and an elevator (lift). Planning an event in Orange? This residence has facilities measuring 377 square feet (35 square meters), including a meeting room. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the residence's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 59 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers, and irons/ironing boards can be requested.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Kyriad Orange Centre in Orange, you'll be minutes from Triumphal Arch of Orange and Orange Amphitheatre. This residence is within close proximity of Ancient Theatre of Orange and Orange Golf Club. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Triumphal Arch of Orange - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ancient Theatre of Orange - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Orange Amphitheatre - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Orange Golf Club - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jean-Henri Fabre Museum - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chateau de Vaudieu - 8.3 km / 5.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chateau de la Gardine - 8.5 km / 5.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chateauneuf-du-Pape - 9.2 km / 5.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place du Portail - 9.5 km / 5.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chateau Fortia - 10.2 km / 6.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Domaine Armand - 14.3 km / 8.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place Mallet - 15 km / 9.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albert-Andre Museum - 15.1 km / 9.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Three Crosses Chapel - 16.1 km / 10 mi &lt;br /&gt;Caveau du Gigondas - 16.1 km / 10 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Kyriad Orange Centre is Marseille (MRS-Marseille - Provence) - 84.3 km / 52.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Inter-hotel des Princes is Marseille (MRS-Marseille - Provence) - 84.4 km / 52.4 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>