<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>118755158</Id><Name>Hilton Dali Resort &amp; Spa</Name><Region><Id>15875</Id><Name>Dali</Name><CityId>15875</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Qili Bridge, South of Gantong Temple, Yunan Province</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Dali City</City><State /><Zip>671000</Zip><Country>China</Country><Tel>011868726688888</Tel><Fax>011868722562098</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo><CheckInTime>15</CheckInTime><CheckOutTime>12</CheckOutTime></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>null</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Hilton Dali Resort &amp; Spa is nestled in the Cangshan Mountains, offering sweeping views of the mountains and Erhai Lake. Situated between the Dali Ancient Town and Dali's Xia Guan commercial and administrative district, the resort is just 30 minutes from Dali Airport.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PropertyInformation</Type><Text>null</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DiningFacilities</Type><Text>Osteria - Welcome to Osteria. a traditional Italian trattoria in the heart of Dali. Pasta and breads are prepared daily from scratch using imported ingredients and the large communal table is laden with irresistible antipasti. Browse the most extensive list of Italian wines in Yunnan Province and let our wine stew. Yu Xi - Come discover the unique fresh flavors of Yunnan cuisine at Yu Xi restaurant like you*ve never experienced before. Traditional Yunnan Chinese cuisines are prepared with the freshest local vegetables spices and delectable fresh fish and meats. For more familar fare the menu offers Cantonese classics as we. Spices - Spices offers an impressive variety of Western specialties and Chinese favorites making it the ideal choice for families and casual gatherings. Sample local and international buffet dishes for breakfast lunch or dinner or select from the delectable a la carte options.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>Short</Type><Text>null</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>