<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11870208</Id><Name>The Farmhouse Hotel</Name><Region><Id>18240</Id><Name>Cape Town</Name><CityId>18240</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>5 Egret Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Cape Town</City><State /><Zip>-</Zip><Country>South Africa</Country><Tel>+2721 772 2062</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>-33.1049</Latitude><Longitude>18.035</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at The Farmhouse Hotel in Langebaan, you'll be by the ocean and convenient to Langebaan Beach.  This 4-star hotel is within the region of Calypso Beach and West Coast National Park.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 17 guestrooms featuring minibars and DVD players. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Relax at the full-service spa, where you can enjoy massages, body treatments, and facials. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and an arcade/game room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of The Farmhouse Hotel, or stop in at a snack bar/deli. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a computer station and a safe deposit box at the front desk. Event facilities at this hotel consist of a conference center and a meeting room. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of The Farmhouse Hotel, or stop in at a snack bar/deli. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 18 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Relax at the full-service spa, where you can enjoy massages, body treatments, and facials. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and an arcade/game room. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 17 guestrooms featuring minibars and DVD players. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at The Farmhouse Hotel in Langebaan, you'll be by the ocean and convenient to Langebaan Beach.  This 4-star hotel is within the region of Calypso Beach and West Coast National Park. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Langebaan Beach - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Calypso Beach - 5.5 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;West Coast National Park - 12.6 km / 7.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;West Coast Fossil Park - 17.8 km / 11.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cape Columbine Lighthouse - 35.1 km / 21.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Paternoster Beach - 35.6 km / 22.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kastelbeerg - 78.7 km / 48.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Allesverloren Estate - 82.9 km / 51.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bird Island - 115.6 km / 71.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cederberg Wilderness Area - 128.8 km / 80 mi &lt;br /&gt;Betty's Bay Penguin Colony - 161.6 km / 100.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kogelberg Biosphere Reserve - 163.5 km / 101.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kleinmond Beach - 165.8 km / 103 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bot River Estuary - 170.3 km / 105.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Whalehaven Winery - 180.7 km / 112.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Farmhouse Hotel is Johannesburg (JNB-O.R. Tambo Intl.) - 1,252.8 km / 778.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for The Farmhouse Hotel is Johannesburg (JNB-O.R. Tambo Intl.) - 1,252.9 km / 778.5 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 18 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>