<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11876518</Id><Name>Interhotel Des Puys</Name><Region><Id>16418</Id><Name>Clermont-Ferrand</Name><CityId>16418</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>PLACE DELILLE 16</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>CLERMONT FERRAND</City><State /><Zip>63000</Zip><Country>FRANCE</Country><Tel>0033473919206</Tel><Fax>0033473916025</Fax><Email>contact@hoteldespuys.fr</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>45.7802274</Latitude><Longitude>3.0916235</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel des Puys, you'll be centrally located in Clermont-Ferrand, steps from Notre Dame du Port and minutes from Blaise Pascal University. This hotel is within close proximity of Clermont-Ferrand Cathedral and Musee du Ranquet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 63 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars (stocked with some free items) and espresso makers. 32-inch LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and gift shops/newsstands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves lunch and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, express check-out, and complimentary newspapers in the lobby. Planning an event in Clermont-Ferrand? This hotel has facilities measuring 538 square feet (50 square meters), including meeting rooms. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves lunch and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and gift shops/newsstands. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 63 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars (stocked with some free items) and espresso makers. 32-inch LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel des Puys, you'll be centrally located in Clermont-Ferrand, steps from Notre Dame du Port and minutes from Blaise Pascal University. This hotel is within close proximity of Clermont-Ferrand Cathedral and Musee du Ranquet. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Notre Dame du Port - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Blaise Pascal University - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Clermont-Ferrand Cathedral - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Musee du Ranquet - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Musee Lecoq - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Musee Bargoin - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place de Jaude - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Parc des Sports Marcel Michelin - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;L'Aventure Michelin - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Musee d'Art Roger-Quillot - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gabriel Montpied Stadium - 4.6 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Zenith d'Auvergne - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Charade Circuit - 6.5 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Grande Halle d'Auvergne - 6.5 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Puy de Pariou - 9.5 km / 5.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel des Puys is Clermont-Ferrand (CFE-Clermont-Ferrand - Auvergne Intl.) - 5.4 km / 3.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Inter-Hotel des Puys is Clermont-Ferrand (CFE-Clermont-Ferrand - Auvergne Intl.) - 5.4 km / 3.4 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>CoffeeTeaMaker</Code><Text>Tea and Coffee maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HandicapAccessible</Code><Text>Handicap accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantAirconditioned</Code><Text>Restaurant Air-Conditioned</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WLANAccessPoint</Code><Text>WLAN Access Point</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BicycleStorage</Code><Text>Bicycle Storage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Garage</Code><Text>Garage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccessible</Code><Text>Wheelchair Accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>