<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11870196</Id><Name>Alphen Boutique Hotel</Name><Region><Id>18240</Id><Name>Cape Town</Name><CityId>18240</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Alphen Drive</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Cape Town</City><State /><Zip>7806</Zip><Country>South Africa</Country><Tel>+27217956300</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>-34.0479</Latitude><Longitude>18.4603</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Alphen Boutique Hotel in Cape Town (Constantia), you'll be convenient to Wynberg Park and Kirstenbosch National Botanical Gardens.  This 5-star hotel is within close proximity of Constantia Village and Maynardville Open-Air Theatre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 19 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and DVD players. 42-inch plasma televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature rainfall showerheads and designer toiletries. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a garden. Additional features include a picnic area and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite at one of the hotel's 2 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Relax with a refreshing drink at one of the 2 bars/lounges. A complimentary breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, a 24-hour front desk, and luggage storage. Event facilities at this hotel consist of a conference center and meeting rooms. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite at one of the hotel's 2 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Relax with a refreshing drink at one of the 2 bars/lounges. A complimentary breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a garden. Additional features include a picnic area and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 19 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and DVD players. 42-inch plasma televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature rainfall showerheads and designer toiletries. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Alphen Boutique Hotel in Cape Town (Constantia), you'll be convenient to Wynberg Park and Kirstenbosch National Botanical Gardens.  This 5-star hotel is within close proximity of Constantia Village and Maynardville Open-Air Theatre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Wynberg Park - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Constantia Village - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maynardville Open-Air Theatre - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Neo-Gothic Dutch Reformed Church - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maynardville Park - 1.5 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kirstenbosch National Botanical Gardens - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kenilworth Race Course - 3 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Arderne Gardens - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Claremont Hospital - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Art in the Forest - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Royal Cape Golf Club - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kingsbury Hospital - 3.3 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eagles Nest - 3.3 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Constantia Glen Winery - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cavendish Square - 3.7 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Alphen Boutique Hotel is Cape Town (CPT-Cape Town Intl.) - 14.1 km / 8.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Alphen Hotel is Cape Town (CPT-Cape Town Intl.) - 14.3 km / 8.9 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Doctoroncall</Code><Text>Doctor on call</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>