<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>118755137</Id><Name>DoubleTree by Hilton Chongqing - Nan'an</Name><Region><Id>15872</Id><Name>Chongqing</Name><CityId>15872</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>No 38 Nanping West Road Nan'an District</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Chongqing</City><State /><Zip>400060</Zip><Country>China</Country><Tel>+86-23-62308888</Tel><Fax>+86-21-62308999</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><CheckInTime>15</CheckInTime><CheckOutTime>12</CheckOutTime></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Located in the center of Nan'an district, a commercial, administrative and cultural area of the city, DoubleTree by Hilton Chongqing Nan'an is ideal if you are here for business or leisure. The hotel is adjustment to a convention center and is within walking distance from a large shopping mall and popular attractions. The hotel is 40 minutes away from Chongqing Airport, 1½ hours away via the express train from Chengdu and is close to a bus stop and metro station, offering you an easy way to travel around. We look forward to welcoming you with our signature chocolate chip cookie upon arrival. Enjoy your stay in a luxuriously-appointed guest room with modern décor, WiFi access, sitting area and a 42-inch LCD TV. Select an executive room or suite for extra amenities and exclusive access to the Executive Lounge serving complimentary breakfast and refreshments. All rooms are located on floors 13 to 21 offering breathtaking views of the city. Our Chongqing Nan'an hotel also has a number of accessible rooms, which include all the standard amenities plus a few extra features for your comfort.Dine on local favourites and international cuisine in our all-day-dining restaurants, OPEN. Enjoy an authentic dining experience in our Chinese Specialty Restaurant, or relax in a casual environment of the Lobby Lounge, serving light bites and drinks. If you fancy staying in, 24-hour room service with a variety of delicious options is also available. To help you keep fit during your stay, our hotel in Chongqing offers a well-equipped fitness center, a steam room, sauna, hot tubs and a 6th-floor indoor pool with city views. DoubleTree by Hilton Chongqing Nan'an provides audio visual equipment and meeting facilities, including four function rooms and an elegant ballroom for up to 250 guests. Host various types of events from corporate conferences, intimate meetings to weddings and social gatherings, and let our experienced staff help make your event a success.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>