<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11877332</Id><Name>Rivierbos Guest House</Name><Region><Id>18288</Id><Name>Stellenbosch</Name><CityId>18288</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1 Hamman Street</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Stellenbosch</City><State /><Zip>7600</Zip><Country>South Africa</Country><Tel>+27 (0)21 887 2412</Tel><Fax>+27 (86) 6386338</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>-33.9411</Latitude><Longitude>18.8574</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Rivierbos Guest House in Stellenbosch (Cape Winelands), you'll be minutes from Toy &amp; Miniature Museum and VOC Kruithuis.  This family-friendly guesthouse is within close proximity of Fick House and St Mary’s Anglican Church.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 12 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include safes and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a garden. This guesthouse also features complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A complimentary full breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, dry cleaning/laundry services, and luggage storage. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; A complimentary full breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a garden. This guesthouse also features complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 12 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include safes and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Rivierbos Guest House in Stellenbosch (Cape Winelands), you'll be minutes from Toy &amp; Miniature Museum and VOC Kruithuis.  This family-friendly guesthouse is within close proximity of Fick House and St Mary’s Anglican Church. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Toy &amp; Miniature Museum - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;VOC Kruithuis - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fick House - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Mary’s Anglican Church - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stellenbosch Town Hall - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Stellenbosch Village Museum - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rupert Museum - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sasol Art Museum - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Stellenbosch Botanical Garden - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Oude Molen Distillery - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Coetzenburg Stadium - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stellenbosch University - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Oude Libertas Amphitheatre - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stellenbosch Golf Club - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dutch Reform Church - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Rivierbos Guest House is Cape Town (CPT-Cape Town Intl.) - 24.3 km / 15.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>