<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11877126</Id><Name>Dock Ouest -groupe Paul Bocuse</Name><Region><Id>20487</Id><Name>Lyon </Name><CityId>16450</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>RUE DES DOCKS 39</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>LYON</City><State /><Zip>69009</Zip><Country>FRANCE</Country><Tel>0033478223434</Tel><Fax>0033478477831</Fax><Email>contact@dockouest.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>45.786419</Latitude><Longitude>4.811438</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Dock Ouest Residence in Lyon (Vaise), you'll be convenient to Ile Barbe and Terreaux Square. This residence is within close proximity of Maison des Canuts and Place de la Croix Rousse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 43 guestrooms featuring refrigerators and flat-screen televisions. Your room comes with a memory foam bed. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk. Planning an event in Lyon? This residence has facilities measuring 2153 square feet (200 square meters), including a meeting room. Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is Noon &lt;br/&gt; Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 43 guestrooms featuring refrigerators and flat-screen televisions. Your room comes with a memory foam bed. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Dock Ouest Residence in Lyon (Vaise), you'll be convenient to Ile Barbe and Terreaux Square. This residence is within close proximity of Maison des Canuts and Place de la Croix Rousse. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Ile Barbe - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maison des Canuts - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place de la Croix Rousse - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Quai de Bondy Vaporetto Stop - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Metallic Tower - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Guignol Theater - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Terreaux Square - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lyon Museum of Fine Arts - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lyon City Hall - 2.8 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tete d'Or Park - 2.8 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Notre Dame Basilica - 2.8 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lyon Opera - 2.8 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Esplanade de Fourviere - 2.8 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lyon History Museum - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Interpol Headquarters - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Lyon (XYD-Part-Dieu SNCF Train Station) - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi&lt;br /&gt;Lyon (LYN-Lyon Bron) - 12 km / 7.4 mi&lt;br /&gt;Lyon (LYS-Saint-Exupery) - 21.6 km / 13.4 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Dock Ouest Residence is Lyon (LYS-Saint-Exupery). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>CoffeeTeaMaker</Code><Text>Tea and Coffee maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HandicapAccessible</Code><Text>Handicap accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantAirconditioned</Code><Text>Restaurant Air-Conditioned</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WLANAccessPoint</Code><Text>WLAN Access Point</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Balcony</Code><Text>Balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Fridge</Code><Text>Fridge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccessible</Code><Text>Wheelchair Accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>