<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>118729651</Id><Name>Helena Sands</Name><Region><Id>15667</Id><Name>Sunny Beach</Name><CityId>15667</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Sunny Beach</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Sunny Beach</City><State /><Zip>8240</Zip><Country>Bulgaria</Country><Tel>+359 554 200 43</Tel><Fax>01135955420023</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo><CheckInTime>15</CheckInTime><CheckOutTime>11</CheckOutTime></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Location
The hotel is located in a quiet area only 100 m away from the sandy beach, 3 km from the centre of Sunny Beach resort and just a short walk from the nearest public transport services. It is 35 km from Burgas Airport.
Facilities
The hotel features 213 accommodation units. Guests of the hotel are welcomed in the lobby, which has a 24-hour reception and a 24-hour check-out service. A lift provides easy access to the upper floors. Amenities include a cloakroom, a safe and currency exchange facilities. Internet access (for a fee) and wireless internet access (for a fee) are available in the public areas. The hotel offers a range of amenities for a comfortable stay, including gastronomic options such as a restaurant, a dining area, a breakfast room, a café and a bar. Shopping facilities are available. The grounds of the hotel feature a playground and an attractive garden. A playroom is also among the amenities at the hotel. Parking facilities available to guests include a garage and a car park. Additional services include a childcare service, medical assistance, room service, a laundry and a hairdressing salon. Active guests can make use of the bicycle hire service to explore the surrounding area (for a fee).
Rooms
All rooms feature air conditioning, central heating and a bathroom. Bathrooms with wheelchair access can also be booked. Most accommodation units feature a balcony or terrace. Many of the rooms also offer a sea view, adding to the ambience. The carpeted accommodation units feature a double bed, a king-size bed or a sofa-bed. A safe and a minibar also feature. The rooms offer a range of amenities, including a mini-fridge. Each accommodation unit offers internet access, a telephone, a TV and wireless internet access. Wheelchair-accessible accommodation units are also bookable. Amenities in the bathrooms include a shower, a bathtub and a bidet. The bathrooms feature a hairdryer, a vanity mirror and bathrobes.
Sports/Entertainment
Both an indoor and an outdoor pool are available for swimming. A terrace, a sun terrace, sun loungers and parasols are available. The hot tub offers revitalisation. There is also a poolside snack bar. The hotel offers a very extensive outdoor sport and leisure programme, which includes bocce, beach volleyball, basketball and archery. For a fee, cycling/mountain biking and tennis can also be enjoyed. Cycling/mountain biking is organised by third-party operators. For those who enjoy watersports, aquafit is available. The hotel offers a number of indoor sporting opportunities, including a gym and gymnastics, or for a fee, table tennis and pool/billiards. The hotel offers various wellness options, including a sauna, a hammam, a beauty salon and a solarium, or for a fee, a spa, a steam bath and massage treatments. Other options and services include an entertainment programme for adults, an entertainment programme for children, live music and a kids' club.
Meals
The hotel offers a wide range of bookable meals and board options, including breakfast, lunch, dinner, half board and All-inclusive. The menu also offers special dietary cuisine and vegetarian dishes. Special deals can be enjoyed at the hotel. The show cooking is a particular attraction.
Payment
The following credit cards are accepted at the hotel: VISA and MasterCard.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The hotel is located in a quiet area only 100 m away from the sandy beach, 3 km from the centre of Sunny Beach resort and just a short walk from the nearest public transport services. It is 35 km from Burgas Airport.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>All rooms feature air conditioning, central heating and a bathroom. Bathrooms with wheelchair access can also be booked. Most accommodation units feature a balcony or terrace. Many of the rooms also offer a sea view, adding to the ambience. The carpeted accommodation units feature a double bed, a king-size bed or a sofa-bed. A safe and a minibar also feature. The rooms offer a range of amenities, including a mini-fridge. Each accommodation unit offers internet access, a telephone, a TV and wireless internet access. Wheelchair-accessible accommodation units are also bookable. Amenities in the bathrooms include a shower, a bathtub and a bidet. The bathrooms feature a hairdryer, a vanity mirror and bathrobes.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PropertyInformation</Type><Text>The hotel features 213 accommodation units. Guests of the hotel are welcomed in the lobby, which has a 24-hour reception and a 24-hour check-out service. A lift provides easy access to the upper floors. Amenities include a cloakroom, a safe and currency exchange facilities. Internet access (for a fee) and wireless internet access (for a fee) are available in the public areas. The hotel offers a range of amenities for a comfortable stay, including gastronomic options such as a restaurant, a dining area, a breakfast room, a café and a bar. Shopping facilities are available. The grounds of the hotel feature a playground and an attractive garden. A playroom is also among the amenities at the hotel. Parking facilities available to guests include a garage and a car park. Additional services include a childcare service, medical assistance, room service, a laundry and a hairdressing salon. Active guests can make use of the bicycle hire service to explore the surrounding area (for a fee).</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>AreaActivities</Type><Text>Both an indoor and an outdoor pool are available for swimming. A terrace, a sun terrace, sun loungers and parasols are available. The hot tub offers revitalisation. There is also a poolside snack bar. The hotel offers a very extensive outdoor sport and leisure programme, which includes bocce, beach volleyball, basketball and archery. For a fee, cycling/mountain biking and tennis can also be enjoyed. Cycling/mountain biking is organised by third-party operators. For those who enjoy watersports, aquafit is available. The hotel offers a number of indoor sporting opportunities, including a gym and gymnastics, or for a fee, table tennis and pool/billiards. The hotel offers various wellness options, including a sauna, a hammam, a beauty salon and a solarium, or for a fee, a spa, a steam bath and massage treatments. Other options and services include an entertainment programme for adults, an entertainment programme for children, live music and a kids' club.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DiningFacilities</Type><Text>The hotel offers a wide range of bookable meals and board options, including breakfast, lunch, dinner, half board and All-inclusive. The menu also offers special dietary cuisine and vegetarian dishes. Special deals can be enjoyed at the hotel. The show cooking is a particular attraction.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>The following credit cards are accepted at the hotel: VISA and MasterCard.


*There is a city tax payable by the guest.*</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>