<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11877190</Id><Name>Halyards Hotel</Name><Region><Id>18278</Id><Name>Port Alfred</Name><CityId>18278</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>The Royal Alfred Marina, Albany Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Port Alfred</City><State /><Zip>TBA</Zip><Country>South Africa</Country><Tel>+27 21 425 1171</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>-33.594</Latitude><Longitude>26.893</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Halyards Hotel and Spa places you in the heart of Port Alfred, convenient to East Beach and Kelly's Beach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 49 air-conditioned guestrooms. Rooms have private balconies. Satellite television is provided for your entertainment. Bathrooms have separate bathtubs and showers and designer toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including a nightclub, an outdoor pool, and a sauna. Additional features include babysitting/childcare and complimentary use of a nearby fitness facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Halyards Hotel and Spa. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-out, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk. This hotel has 5 meeting rooms available for events. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Halyards Hotel and Spa. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a range of recreational amenities, including a nightclub, an outdoor pool, and a sauna. Additional features include babysitting/childcare and complimentary use of a nearby fitness facility. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 49 air-conditioned guestrooms. Rooms have private balconies. Satellite television is provided for your entertainment. Bathrooms have separate bathtubs and showers and designer toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Halyards Hotel and Spa places you in the heart of Port Alfred, convenient to East Beach and Kelly's Beach. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;East Beach - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kelly's Beach - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Great Fish Lighthouse - 21.3 km / 13.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kenton on Sea Beach - 22.8 km / 14.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Egazini Park - 44.7 km / 27.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Observatory Museum - 46.2 km / 28.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;1820 Settlers National Monument - 46.3 km / 28.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rhodes University - 46.3 km / 28.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cathedral of St. Michael and St. George - 46.4 km / 28.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Albany History Museum Complex - 46.4 km / 28.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;South African Institute for Aquatic Biodiversity - 46.8 km / 29.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;African Pride Pumba Private Game Reserve - 52.1 km / 32.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lalibela Game Reserve - 61 km / 37.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Amakhala Game Reserve - 72.9 km / 45.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Addo Elephant National Park - 107.7 km / 66.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Halyards Hotel and Spa is Port Elizabeth (PLZ) - 126.2 km / 78.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>