<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>118729647</Id><Name>Royal Castle Hotel &amp; Spa</Name><Region><Id>289400</Id><Name>Sveti Vlas</Name><CityId>289400</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Royal Club Victoria</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Elenite</City><State /><Zip>8259</Zip><Country>Bulgaria</Country><Tel>+359 554 69 500</Tel><Fax>01135955468450</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo><CheckInTime>15</CheckInTime><CheckOutTime>11</CheckOutTime></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Location
Situated in the resort village of Elenite, this design hotel offers panoramic views of the Black Sea. Elenite is the only Bulgarian resort with southern exposure along the Bulgarian Black Sea coast. There is a pleasant combination of sea and mountains, and calm, curved hills sloping directly into the sea. The hotel is just 35 km from Bourgas airport and just 10 km away from Sunny Beach.
Facilities
This hotel was built recently, in 2011. Guest accommodation comprises 139 rooms. In the air-conditioned establishment, travellers are welcomed at the reception area with 24-hour reception and a 24-hour check-in/check-out service. Most storeys are accessible by lift. Amenities include a safe and a currency exchange service. Wireless internet access (no extra charge) is available to guests in the public areas. Among the culinary options available at the accommodation are a restaurant, a dining area, a breakfast room, a café, a bar and a pub. Shopping facilities are also available. Those arriving in their own vehicles can leave them in the car park of the hotel. Additional services include a childcare service, medical assistance, translation services, room service, a laundry service and a hairdresser. In addition, a shuttle service is offered.
Rooms
Each of the rooms is appointed with air conditioning, central heating and a bathroom. Most rooms feature a balcony with a view for guests' enjoyment. Many rooms feature a sea view, which further enhances the ambience. The carpeted rooms feature a double bed or a sofabed. Cots and extra beds are available. A safe and a minibar are also available. Additional features include a mini fridge and a tea/coffee station. An ironing set is also available for travellers' convenience. Little extras, including internet access, a telephone and a TV, contribute to a great stay. The bathrooms are fitted with a shower and a bathtub. A hairdryer and bathrobes are provided for everyday use.
Sports/Entertainment
A refreshing dip in the indoor or outdoor pool is an enjoyable way to cool down on hot days. A waterslide offers fun for all ages. A terrace, a sun terrace, sun loungers and parasols are available. The hot tub is the perfect place to relax. There is also a poolside snack bar. A variety of sporting activities are available at the establishment, for example beach volleyball and volleyball, or for a fee, tennis and crazy golf. The accommodation offers a wide range of indoor sporting activities, for example a gym, billiards and darts, or for a fee, table tennis, bowling and squash. The hotel offers various wellness options, including a hammam and a beauty salon, or for a fee, a spa, a sauna, a steam bath, massage treatments and a solarium. Other options and services include a disco, a kids' club and a casino.
Meals
Catering options available at the establishment include bed and breakfast and half board. Guests can choose to book options such as breakfast, lunch or dinner.
Payment
All major credit cards, including VISA and MasterCard, are accepted for payment.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Situated in the resort village of Elenite, this design hotel offers panoramic views of the Black Sea. Elenite is the only Bulgarian resort with southern exposure along the Bulgarian Black Sea coast. There is a pleasant combination of sea and mountains, and calm, curved hills sloping directly into the sea. The hotel is just 35 km from Bourgas airport and just 10 km away from Sunny Beach.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Each of the rooms is appointed with air conditioning, central heating and a bathroom. Most rooms feature a balcony with a view for guests' enjoyment. Many rooms feature a sea view, which further enhances the ambience. The carpeted rooms feature a double bed or a sofabed. Cots and extra beds are available. A safe and a minibar are also available. Additional features include a mini fridge and a tea/coffee station. An ironing set is also available for travellers' convenience. Little extras, including internet access, a telephone and a TV, contribute to a great stay. The bathrooms are fitted with a shower and a bathtub. A hairdryer and bathrobes are provided for everyday use.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PropertyInformation</Type><Text>This hotel was built recently, in 2011. Guest accommodation comprises 139 rooms. In the air-conditioned establishment, travellers are welcomed at the reception area with 24-hour reception and a 24-hour check-in/check-out service. Most storeys are accessible by lift. Amenities include a safe and a currency exchange service. Wireless internet access (no extra charge) is available to guests in the public areas. Among the culinary options available at the accommodation are a restaurant, a dining area, a breakfast room, a café, a bar and a pub. Shopping facilities are also available. Those arriving in their own vehicles can leave them in the car park of the hotel. Additional services include a childcare service, medical assistance, translation services, room service, a laundry service and a hairdresser. In addition, a shuttle service is offered.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>AreaActivities</Type><Text>A refreshing dip in the indoor or outdoor pool is an enjoyable way to cool down on hot days. A waterslide offers fun for all ages. A terrace, a sun terrace, sun loungers and parasols are available. The hot tub is the perfect place to relax. There is also a poolside snack bar. A variety of sporting activities are available at the establishment, for example beach volleyball and volleyball, or for a fee, tennis and crazy golf. The accommodation offers a wide range of indoor sporting activities, for example a gym, billiards and darts, or for a fee, table tennis, bowling and squash. The hotel offers various wellness options, including a hammam and a beauty salon, or for a fee, a spa, a sauna, a steam bath, massage treatments and a solarium. Other options and services include a disco, a kids' club and a casino.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DiningFacilities</Type><Text>Catering options available at the establishment include bed and breakfast and half board. Guests can choose to book options such as breakfast, lunch or dinner.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>All major credit cards, including VISA and MasterCard, are accepted for payment.


*Please be advised there is a fee for early departures.*</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>