<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11876534</Id><Name>Terra Nova</Name><Region><Id>20574</Id><Name>La Plagne</Name><CityId>16487</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>PLAGNE CENTRE 73210</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>LA PLAGNE</City><State /><Zip /><Country>FRANCE</Country><Tel>33479081010</Tel><Fax>33479077401</Fax><Email>info@hotel-terranova.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>45.55341667</Latitude><Longitude>6.672083333</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hôtel Terra Nova, you'll be centrally located in Macot-la-Plagne, walking distance from La Plagne Ski Resort and close to Paradiski Ski Resort. This eco-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Aime 2000 Ski Resort and Telemetro Gondola.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 119 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have shower/tub combinations and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and blackout drapes/curtains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the convenience of ski-in/ski-out access at this hotel, which also features a sauna and a fitness center. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, ski storage, and a fireplace in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hôtel Terra Nova. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour front desk, multilingual staff, and an elevator (lift). Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 6 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hôtel Terra Nova. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy the convenience of ski-in/ski-out access at this hotel, which also features a sauna and a fitness center. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, ski storage, and a fireplace in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 119 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have shower/tub combinations and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and blackout drapes/curtains.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hôtel Terra Nova, you'll be centrally located in Macot-la-Plagne, walking distance from La Plagne Ski Resort and close to Paradiski Ski Resort. This eco-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Aime 2000 Ski Resort and Telemetro Gondola. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;La Plagne Ski Resort - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Paradiski Ski Resort - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aime 2000 Ski Resort - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Telemetro Gondola - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Roche de Mio Gondola - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;La Plagne Bobsleigh Track - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bellecote Gondola - 4.6 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Champagny Gondola - 5.7 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Montmayeur Tower - 5.9 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bellecote Glacier - 7.3 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Espace Paradisio Aquatic Center - 7.4 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Peisey Ski Lift - 8.2 km / 5.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vanoise Express Cable Car - 8.2 km / 5.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Peisey-Vallandry Ski Resort - 8.3 km / 5.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Praz Gondola - 9.4 km / 5.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hôtel Terra Nova is Grenoble (GNB-Grenoble - Isere) - 106.3 km / 66.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Sauna</Code><Text>Sauna</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DiningRoom</Code><Text>Dining Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WLANAccessPoint</Code><Text>WLAN Access Point</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniClub</Code><Text>Mini Club</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Carpeted</Code><Text>Carpeted</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Balcony</Code><Text>Balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomTerraceBalcony</Code><Text>Terrace or balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>