<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>118884</Id><Name>Lucknam Park</Name><Region><Id>52374</Id><Name>Bath</Name><CityId>52374</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>COLERNE BATH</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>BATH</City><State /><Zip>SN14 8AZ</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>1225742777</Tel><Fax>1225743536</Fax><Email>reservations@lucknampark.co.uk</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>41</CountRooms><CountFloors>2</CountFloors><CountSuites>9</CountSuites><Latitude>51.439895</Latitude><Longitude>-2.261508</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAF519700_0.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>317</Height><Bytes>17788</Bytes><Caption>Detailed map</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAF519700_0.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>105</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>11505</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAF519700_1.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>337</Height><Bytes>54291</Bytes><Caption>Unknown</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAF519700_1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>99</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>22180</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CAF519700_2.jpg</Url><Width>480</Width><Height>331</Height><Bytes>48372</Bytes><Caption>Unknown</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CAF519700_2.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>101</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>23255</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Lucknam Park in Chippenham (Colerne), you'll be within the vicinity of Corsham Court and Bath Abbey. This 5-star hotel is within the vicinity of Castle Combe Circuit and Alice Park.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 42 guestrooms. Satellite television is provided for your entertainment. Bathrooms have designer toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take time to pamper yourself with a visit to the full-service spa. You can take advantage of recreational amenities such as an outdoor pool, an indoor pool, and a fitness center. This hotel also features concierge services and a hair salon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This hotel has 4 meeting rooms available for events.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take time to pamper yourself with a visit to the full-service spa. You can take advantage of recreational amenities such as an outdoor pool, an indoor pool, and a fitness center. This hotel also features concierge services and a hair salon. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 42 guestrooms. Satellite television is provided for your entertainment. Bathrooms have designer toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Lucknam Park in Chippenham (Colerne), you'll be within the vicinity of Corsham Court and Bath Abbey. This 5-star hotel is within the vicinity of Castle Combe Circuit and Alice Park. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Corsham Court - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Castle Combe Circuit - 6.2 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Alice Park - 7.4 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dyrham Park - 7.6 km / 4.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rondo Theater - 7.7 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Claverton Pumping Station - 8.3 km / 5.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bath Golf Club - 8.5 km / 5.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Bath - 8.5 km / 5.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;American Museum in Britain - 8.7 km / 5.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sydney Gardens - 8.9 km / 5.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Beckford's Tower - 8.9 km / 5.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Holburne Museum - 9 km / 5.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hedgemead Park - 9 km / 5.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Henrietta Park - 9.2 km / 5.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Building of Bath Museum - 9.2 km / 5.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Lucknam Park is Bristol (BRS-Bristol Intl.) - 31.1 km / 19.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Lucknam Park is Bristol (BRS-Bristol Intl.) - 31.1 km / 19.3 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Sauna</Code><Text>Sauna</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TV</Code><Text>TeleVision</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>