<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>118806578</Id><Name>Hilton Haikou</Name><Region><Id>15899</Id><Name>Haikou</Name><CityId>15899</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>109-9 Binhai Avenue</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Haikou</City><State /><Zip>570105</Zip><Country>China</Country><Tel>+86-898-3679 8888</Tel><Fax>+86-898-3679 8777</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><CheckInTime>14</CheckInTime><CheckOutTime>12</CheckOutTime></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>null</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Hilton Haikou is set in the heart of bustling downtown; steps from the beach and lots of offices, businesses, restaurants, bars and entertainment. Attend a seasonal festival at Century Park, shop at RT-Mart or Carrefour, or visit Evergreen Park or Hainan Volcanic Crater Park.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PropertyInformation</Type><Text>null</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DiningFacilities</Type><Text>YUXI Chinese Restaurant - With a name meaning *the seal belonging to the emperor* Yuxi takes inspiration from the authentic sense of tradition that is so important in Chinese culture and culinary heritage. Enter the dramatic corridor beyond the massive main doors and you will be immersed in an atmosphere of modern elegance. Indiv. GRILL*33 - A luxurious and contemporary seafood restaurant Grill*33 features elegant decor and a grand staircase that is encased between two impressive wine displays. Indulge in an evening of sophisticated fine-dining and savor western-style seafood dishes grilled and baked to perfection. Senses - All Day Dining - Located on level 33 of the hotel our all-day dining venue Senses offers sumptuous buffet spreads as well as Western and Southeast Asian delicacies international favorites traditional Chinese cuisine and local Hainan specialties. Be entertained by our skilled chefs as they prepare a variety of delicious d.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>Short</Type><Text>null</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>