<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>118818936</Id><Name>Sheraton Wuhan Hankou Hotel</Name><Region><Id>16013</Id><Name>Wuhan</Name><CityId>16013</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>N.80, Fanhu Road, Oceanwide City Square</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Wuhan</City><State /><Zip>430 000</Zip><Country>China</Country><Tel>8373 8888</Tel><Fax>8373 9999</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>null</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Lying to the east of the Jianghan Plain, Wuhan is the capital of central China's Hubei Province. Dating back some 3,500 years, the "thoroughfare of nine provinces" is deemed one of China's cultural gems. Located in between two retail malls, the Sheraton Wuhan Hankou Hotel sits in the northeast part of Wangjiadun's Central Business District (CBD). Wuhan Tianhe International Airport (WUH) is 21 kilometers away, Hankou Train Station is less than 2 kilometers away, and nearby attractions are within easy reach.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PropertyInformation</Type><Text>null</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DiningFacilities</Type><Text>Feast Signature Restaurant - With open kitchens that add the visual appeal of live cooking, Feast presents a modern approach to Asian and international flavors and favorites. Red Basil Thai Restaurant - Red Basil's naturally-illuminated ambience and contemporary decor are complemented by regional Thai dishes, authentically prepared in a friendly open kitchen and immaculately presented. Two private rooms are available. Yue Chinese Restaurant - Amid chic decor, Yue specializes in authentic Cantonese cuisine, favorites from throughout China, and many premium teas. Large private dining rooms feature personalized menus, exhibition kitchens, flat screen TVs, sound systems, and restrooms.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>Short</Type><Text>null</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>