<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11895263</Id><Name>Panorama</Name><Region><Id>20923</Id><Name>Olbia</Name><CityId>17078</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>VIA MAZZINI 7</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>OLBIA</City><State /><Zip>07026</Zip><Country>ITALY</Country><Tel>0039078926656</Tel><Fax>0039078927521</Fax><Email>info@hotelpanoramaolbia.it</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>40.9234561</Latitude><Longitude>9.5012295</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Panorama, you'll be centrally located in Olbia, steps from Church of San Paolo and minutes from National Archaeological Museum of Olbia.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Basilica of San Simplicio and Mario Cervo Archive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 34 air-conditioned rooms featuring LCD televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take time to pamper yourself with a visit to the full-service spa. You can take advantage of recreational amenities such as a health club, a spa tub, and a sauna. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite from a snack bar/deli serving guests of Hotel Panorama. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary hot/cold buffet breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, a computer station, and express check-in. Guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle for a surcharge, and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite from a snack bar/deli serving guests of Hotel Panorama. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary hot/cold buffet breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take time to pamper yourself with a visit to the full-service spa. You can take advantage of recreational amenities such as a health club, a spa tub, and a sauna. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 34 air-conditioned rooms featuring LCD televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Panorama, you'll be centrally located in Olbia, steps from Church of San Paolo and minutes from National Archaeological Museum of Olbia.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Basilica of San Simplicio and Mario Cervo Archive. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Church of San Paolo - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Archaeological Museum of Olbia - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Basilica of San Simplicio - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mario Cervo Archive - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Port of Olbia - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sacred Well of Sa Testa - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Nuraghe Riu Mulinu - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Giant's Tomb Su Monte 'e s'Ape - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Medieval Castle of Pedres - 5.3 km / 3.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pittulongu Beach - 5.8 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Le Saline Beach - 6.5 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pellicano Beach - 6.5 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marina Maria Beach - 7 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bados Beach - 7.9 km / 4.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sos Aranzos Beach - 9 km / 5.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Panorama is Olbia (OLB-Costa Smeralda) - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>CoffeeTeaMaker</Code><Text>Tea and Coffee maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>GameRoom</Code><Text>GameRoom</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVRoom</Code><Text>TV Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DiningRoom</Code><Text>Dining Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WLANAccessPoint</Code><Text>WLAN Access Point</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BicycleStorage</Code><Text>Bicycle Storage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SunLounge</Code><Text>SunLounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SunBathingTerrace</Code><Text>Sun Bathing Terrace</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccessible</Code><Text>Wheelchair Accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Cafe(s)</Code><Text>Cafe(s)</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>