<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11898566</Id><Name>Palazzo Paruta</Name><Region><Id>21076</Id><Name>Venice</Name><CityId>17175</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>SAN MARCO 3824</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>VENICE</City><State /><Zip>30124</Zip><Country>ITALY</Country><Tel>00390412410835</Tel><Fax>00390412414944</Fax><Email>booking@palazzoparuta.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>45.434283</Latitude><Longitude>12.331188</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Palazzo Paruta, you'll be centrally located in Venice, steps from Campo Santo Stefano and Museo della Musica. This 4-star hotel is close to Rialto Bridge and St. Mark's Basilica.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 13 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include phones and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 13 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include phones and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Palazzo Paruta, you'll be centrally located in Venice, steps from Campo Santo Stefano and Museo della Musica. This 4-star hotel is close to Rialto Bridge and St. Mark's Basilica. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;p&gt;Accommodations are located at multiple addresses. Regional attractions include:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Campo Santo Stefano&lt;br /&gt;Museo della Musica&lt;br /&gt;Fortuny Museum&lt;br /&gt;La Fenice Opera House&lt;br /&gt;Mocenigo Palace&lt;br /&gt;Santa Maria del Giglio&lt;br /&gt;Palazzo Barbarigo&lt;br /&gt;Palazzo Malipiero&lt;br /&gt;San Samuele Square&lt;br /&gt;Palazzo Grassi&lt;br /&gt;Palazzo Barbaro&lt;br /&gt;Palazzo Cavalli-Franchetti&lt;br /&gt;Palazzo Contarini del Bovolo&lt;br /&gt;San Toma Waterbus&lt;br /&gt;Academy Bridge&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Palazzo Paruta is Venice (VCE-Marco Polo). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomTerraceBalcony</Code><Text>Terrace or balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>