<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11895190</Id><Name>Guangzhou Sanflowery</Name><Region><Id>15895</Id><Name>Guangzhou</Name><CityId>15895</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1 TUHUA ROAD, HAIZHU DISTRICT</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>GUANGZHOU</City><State /><Zip>510320</Zip><Country>CHINA</Country><Tel>00862083969111</Tel><Fax>00862089886096</Fax><Email>sanfloweryhotel@hotmail.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>23.06495</Latitude><Longitude>113.34504</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Sanflowery Hotel Guangzhou in Guangzhou (Haizhu), you'll be close to Yingzhou Ecological Park and Guangdong Science Center.  This hotel is within the vicinity of Whampoa Military Academy and Lingnan Impression Park.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Treat yourself to a stay in one of the 85 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring private spa tubs and LCD televisions. Your pillowtop bed comes with down comforters. Rooms have private balconies or patios. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while DVD players and cable programming provide entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the recreation opportunities such as a fitness center or make use of other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the complimentary area shuttle that operates within 13 km.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a business center, and express check-in. Event facilities at this hotel consist of conference space and meeting rooms.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 6 AM  Check-out time is 2 PM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy the recreation opportunities such as a fitness center or make use of other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the complimentary area shuttle that operates within 13 km. &lt;br /&gt; Treat yourself to a stay in one of the 85 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring private spa tubs and LCD televisions. Your pillowtop bed comes with down comforters. Rooms have private balconies or patios. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while DVD players and cable programming provide entertainment.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Sanflowery Hotel Guangzhou in Guangzhou (Haizhu), you'll be close to Yingzhou Ecological Park and Guangdong Science Center.  This hotel is within the vicinity of Whampoa Military Academy and Lingnan Impression Park. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Yingzhou Ecological Park - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Guangdong Science Center - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pazhou Complex - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Canton Tower - 5.1 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Guangzhou Library - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Redtory Art and Design Factory - 5.7 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Flower City Square - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Guangdong Museum - 6 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Guangzhou Opera House - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Xinghai Concert Hall - 6.2 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Guangdong Museum of Art - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Whampoa Military Academy - 6.4 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tianhe Park - 6.7 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Xiangjiang Safari Park - 6.8 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chimelong Paradise - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Sanflowery Hotel Guangzhou is Guangzhou (CAN-Baiyun Intl.) - 37.2 km / 23.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Sauna</Code><Text>Sauna</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CoffeeTeaMaker</Code><Text>Tea and Coffee maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MoneyExchange</Code><Text>Money exchange</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Hairdresser</Code><Text>Hairdresser</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CloakRoom</Code><Text>Cloak Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DiscoClub</Code><Text>Disco / Club</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DiningRoom</Code><Text>Dining Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantAirconditioned</Code><Text>Restaurant Air-Conditioned</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MedicalService</Code><Text>Medical Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Massage</Code><Text>Massage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HiFiStereoSystem</Code><Text>HiFiStereoSystem</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniFridge</Code><Text>MiniFridge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lounge</Code><Text>Lounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Freenewspaper</Code><Text>Free Newspaper</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shops</Code><Text>Shops</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Cafe(s)</Code><Text>Cafe(s)</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>