<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11893217</Id><Name>La Certosa Hotel</Name><Region><Id>40885</Id><Name>Massa Lubrense</Name><CityId>17050</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>VIA MARINA DEL CANTONE 23</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>MASSALUBRENSE</City><State /><Zip>80061</Zip><Country>ITALY</Country><Tel>00390818081245</Tel><Fax>00390818081245</Fax><Email>alessia@internethotelservices.it</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>40.60797</Latitude><Longitude>14.347041</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel La Certosa in Massa Lubrense (Marina del Cantone), you'll be close to Recommone Beach and Marina Grande.  This beach hotel is within close proximity of Baia di Ieranto and Crapolla Cove.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 16 air-conditioned guestrooms. Satellite television is provided for your entertainment. Bathrooms have bathtubs or showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks, housekeeping is provided daily, and cribs/infant beds (complimentary) can be requested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a private beach, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and babysitting/childcare (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hotel La Certosa. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a computer station, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and dry cleaning/laundry services. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 1 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hotel La Certosa. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a private beach, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 16 air-conditioned guestrooms. Satellite television is provided for your entertainment. Bathrooms have bathtubs or showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks, housekeeping is provided daily, and cribs/infant beds (complimentary) can be requested.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel La Certosa in Massa Lubrense (Marina del Cantone), you'll be close to Recommone Beach and Marina Grande.  This beach hotel is within close proximity of Baia di Ieranto and Crapolla Cove. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Recommone Beach - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Baia di Ieranto - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Crapolla Cove - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cala di Mitigliano Beach - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Baia delle Sirene - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of Santa Maria delle Grazie - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Monastery of Deserto - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lobra Marina - 3.3 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dali Universe - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wonderwall Art Gallery - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marcello Aversa Workshop - 4.8 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sorrento Foundation - 4.8 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wooden Marquetry Workshop-Museum - 4.8 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sorrento Cathedral - 4.8 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cala di Puolo Beach - 4.8 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel La Certosa is Naples (NAP-Naples Intl.) - 33.3 km / 20.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>