<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11893905</Id><Name>For Star North Renminbei Road</Name><Region><Id>15871</Id><Name>Chengdu</Name><CityId>15871</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>2 WEST CHENGHUA STREET, JINNIU DISTRICT, CHENGDU</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>CHENGDU</City><State /><Zip>610081</Zip><Country>CHINA</Country><Tel>00862883181177</Tel><Fax>00862883171177</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>30.678457</Latitude><Longitude>104.077227</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Chengdu, For Star Hotel-Renmin North Road is convenient to Wenshu Monastery and Chengdu City Sports Center.  This hotel is within close proximity of Southwest Jiaotong University and Yong Ling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 155 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access is available to keep you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature rainfall showerheads and designer toiletries. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, dry cleaning/laundry services, and multilingual staff. Event facilities at this hotel consist of conference space and meeting rooms. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at noon  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 155 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access is available to keep you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature rainfall showerheads and designer toiletries. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Chengdu, For Star Hotel-Renmin North Road is convenient to Wenshu Monastery and Chengdu City Sports Center.  This hotel is within close proximity of Southwest Jiaotong University and Yong Ling. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Wenshu Monastery - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chengdu City Sports Center - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Southwest Jiaotong University - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Yong Ling - 2.5 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wide and Narrow Street - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sichuan Museum of Science and Technology - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tianfu Square - 2.8 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Renmin Park - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wuhou Ci - 4.6 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Du Fu Caotang - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jinsha Museum - 5.4 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sichuan University - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chengdu United States Consulate - 6.5 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chengdu University of Technology - 6.6 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Giant Panda Breeding Research Base - 9.2 km / 5.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for For Star Hotel-Renmin North Road is Chengdu (CTU-Shuangliu Intl.) - 15.7 km / 9.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>CoffeeTeaMaker</Code><Text>Tea and Coffee maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>