<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11898691</Id><Name>Ibis Shanghai World Expo</Name><Region><Id>20378</Id><Name>Pudong</Name><CityId>15982</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>800 CHENGSHAN ROAD, PUDONG DISTRICT</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>PUDONG</City><State /><Zip>200125</Zip><Country>CHINA</Country><Tel>00862161561177</Tel><Fax>00862160756116</Fax><Email>h7505@accor.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>31.170743</Latitude><Longitude>121.495729</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Shanghai (Exhibition Area), ibis Shanghai Chengshan Road is close to China Art Palace and Shanghai Children's Medical Center. This hotel is within close proximity of Shanghai Oriental Sports Center and Fabric Market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 165 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare, and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 12:00 PM  Check-out time is 12:00 PM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare, and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 165 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Shanghai (Exhibition Area), ibis Shanghai Chengshan Road is close to China Art Palace and Shanghai Children's Medical Center. This hotel is within close proximity of Shanghai Oriental Sports Center and Fabric Market. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;China Art Palace - 2.5 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shanghai Children's Medical Center - 3.7 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shanghai Oriental Sports Center - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fabric Market - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dongjiadu Road Ferry Wharf - 4.6 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Century Park - 5.2 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shanghai Science and Technology Museum - 5.4 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shanghai Confucian Temple - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shanghai New International Expo Centre - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Taikang Road - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shanghai Old Street - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Xintiandi - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;City God Temple - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Old Chinese City - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Yuyuan Bazaar - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for ibis Shanghai Chengshan Road is Shanghai (SHA-Hongqiao Intl.) - 16.5 km / 10.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WLANAccessPoint</Code><Text>WLAN Access Point</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>