<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11893862</Id><Name>Roma - Porretta Terme</Name><Region><Id>20898</Id><Name>Bologna</Name><CityId>17061</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>PIAZZA VITTORIO VENETO  4</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>PORRETTA TERME (50Km from Bologna)</City><State /><Zip>40046</Zip><Country>ITALY</Country><Tel>39053421535</Tel><Fax>390812142329</Fax><Email>hotelroma@hotelmanagement.biz</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>44.15505</Latitude><Longitude>10.97645</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>This hotel is set in the historical centre of Porretta Terme, just a short distance (200 m) from the spa baths and the spa centre. It is located in the upper valley of the River Reno, surrounded by green hills, luxuriant vegetation and some of the loveliest scenery of the Tosco-Emiliano Apennines. It is equi-distant from 2 major cities: Bologna and Florence. Both are easy to reach in about 50 minutes, either by railway from Porretta station (50 m) or along the Porrettana road. Bologna's exhibition grounds are just 45 km from the hotel and Bologna Airport is 50 km away.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>All rooms come with a private bathroom with a WC, a bidet and a shower as well as a direct dial telephone (charges apply), a TV and a minibar (charges apply). They are also equipped with a coffee table, an ironing set, central heating and a 220 V power supply.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DiningFacilities</Type><Text>This family friendly city hotel was built in 1930 and features Art Nouveau style design and a total of 44 rooms. The comfortable style and friendly atmosphere of this property offers guests a completely relaxing stay in a charming environment. This establishment has been designed with the needs of those guests in mind who believe that comfort, style and efficiency are the basic features of an ideal stay. The accommodation and the location of this property make it especially suitable for business trips or leisure breaks. Facilities on offer to guests include a lobby area with a 24-hour reception, a lift, a bar, a TV lounge and a breakfast room. Guests may also take advantage of the Internet access and the room and laundry services (both for an additional fee). There is parking available for those arriving by car.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVRoom</Code><Text>TV Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MobilePhoneNetwork</Code><Text>Mobile Phone Network</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WLANAccessPoint</Code><Text>WLAN Access Point</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>