<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11893111</Id><Name>Seegarten Hotel</Name><Region><Id>20659</Id><Name>Hamburg Airport</Name><CityId>16573</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>HARKSCHEIDER WEG 258</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>QUICKBORN</City><State /><Zip>25451</Zip><Country>GERMANY</Country><Tel>0049410663670</Tel><Fax>004904106636710</Fax><Email>info@hotel-restauraunt-seegarten.de</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>53.72426</Latitude><Longitude>9.93564</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Restaurant Seegarten Quickborn in Quickborn, you'll be on a lake and close to Stadtmuseum Norderstedt and Tribuhne Norderstedt. This hotel is within the vicinity of ARRIBA Erlebnisbad and Nordex Energy GmbH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 27 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have bathtubs or showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, and both cribs/infant beds (complimentary) and rollaway/extra beds are available on request.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the recreation opportunities such as a sauna or make use of other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves lunch and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, multilingual staff, and luggage storage. This hotel has 3 meeting rooms available for events. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 1 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves lunch and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy the recreation opportunities such as a sauna or make use of other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 27 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have bathtubs or showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, and both cribs/infant beds (complimentary) and rollaway/extra beds are available on request.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Restaurant Seegarten Quickborn in Quickborn, you'll be on a lake and close to Stadtmuseum Norderstedt and Tribuhne Norderstedt. This hotel is within the vicinity of ARRIBA Erlebnisbad and Nordex Energy GmbH. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Stadtmuseum Norderstedt - 3.8 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tribuhne Norderstedt - 4.3 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;ARRIBA Erlebnisbad - 5.8 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Nordex Energy GmbH - 7 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Casio Europe GmbH - 7.3 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Messehalle Hamburg-Schnelsen - 9.8 km / 6.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Niendorfer Gehege - 12 km / 7.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lufthansa Technik AG - 12.2 km / 7.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Am Markt - 12.6 km / 7.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of Kaltenkirchen - 12.8 km / 8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Poppenbuettel Memorial - 12.9 km / 8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ehrenhain Park - 13.2 km / 8.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hagenbeck Zoo - 14.3 km / 8.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Planetarium Hamburg - 14.8 km / 9.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Forum Schenefeld - 14.9 km / 9.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Restaurant Seegarten Quickborn is Hamburg (HAM) - 11.3 km / 7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MoneyExchange</Code><Text>Money exchange</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WLANAccessPoint</Code><Text>WLAN Access Point</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Freenewspaper</Code><Text>Free Newspaper</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>