<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11898967</Id><Name>The Pavilion Hotel Longgang</Name><Region><Id>15990</Id><Name>Shenzhen</Name><CityId>15990</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>NO 168, DA YUN ROAD .</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>SHENZHEN</City><State /><Zip>159656</Zip><Country>CHINA</Country><Tel>008675529918888</Tel><Fax>008675528293617</Fax><Email>allce_zhou@pavilionhotel-longgang.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>22.703239</Latitude><Longitude>114.214492</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1136/29/23/96/292396_14032110180018801266.jpg</Url><Width>312</Width><Height>235</Height><Bytes>12182</Bytes><Caption>Superior</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1136/29/23/96/292396_14032110180018801266thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>92</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2456</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1136/29/23/96/292396_14042811120019222788.jpg</Url><Width>312</Width><Height>235</Height><Bytes>14933</Bytes><Caption>Guest Room</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1136/29/23/96/292396_14042811120019222788thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>92</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2653</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1136/29/23/96/292396_14082219000021498785.jpg</Url><Width>312</Width><Height>235</Height><Bytes>13267</Bytes><Caption>Guest Room</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1136/29/23/96/292396_14082219000021498785thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>92</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2544</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1136/29/23/96/292396_14082219000021498788.jpg</Url><Width>312</Width><Height>235</Height><Bytes>15195</Bytes><Caption>Guest Room</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1136/29/23/96/292396_14082219000021498788thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>92</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2733</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1136/29/23/96/292396_14082219010021498800.jpg</Url><Width>312</Width><Height>235</Height><Bytes>11910</Bytes><Caption>292396_14082219010021498800</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1136/29/23/96/292396_14082219010021498800thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>92</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2040</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Shenzhen (Longgang), The Coli Hotel Shenzhen is convenient to Longgang Dragon Park and Universiade Sports Center.  This 5-star hotel is within close proximity of Bao an Stadium and Longgang Public Golf Course.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 419 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature deep soaking bathtubs and rainfall showerheads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as a fitness center or take in the view from a garden. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite at one of the hotel's 3 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Breakfast is available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, a 24-hour front desk, and an elevator (lift). Planning an event in Shenzhen? This hotel has facilities measuring 27223 square feet (2530 square meters), including conference space.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite at one of the hotel's 3 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Breakfast is available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as a fitness center or take in the view from a garden. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, wedding services, and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 419 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature deep soaking bathtubs and rainfall showerheads.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Shenzhen (Longgang), The Coli Hotel Shenzhen is convenient to Longgang Dragon Park and Universiade Sports Center.  This 5-star hotel is within close proximity of Bao an Stadium and Longgang Public Golf Course. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Longgang Dragon Park - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Universiade Sports Center - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bao an Stadium - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Longgang Public Golf Course - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Crane Lake Fortified Hakka Village and Hakka Culture Museum - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dafen Oil-Painting Village - 13.6 km / 8.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;OCT East - 14.8 km / 9.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hongfa Temple - 15 km / 9.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fairy Lake Botanical Gardens - 16.4 km / 10.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shenzhen Art Museum - 16.9 km / 10.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Minsk World - 17.9 km / 11.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Zhongying Street - 18.6 km / 11.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Yinhu International Conference Center - 19.8 km / 12.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shenzhen People's Park - 20.2 km / 12.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dongmen Pedestrian Street - 20.6 km / 12.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Coli Hotel Shenzhen is Shenzhen (SZX-Shenzhen Intl.) - 41.2 km / 25.6 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>