<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11893730</Id><Name>Airport GR International Business</Name><Region><Id>20368</Id><Name>Tianzhu - Capital Airport</Name><CityId>15862</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>6 TIANZHUFU QIAN NO.2 STREET, CAPITAL AIRPORT</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>BEIJING</City><State /><Zip /><Country>CHINA</Country><Tel>861058102333</Tel><Fax>861058102300</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>40.065461</Latitude><Longitude>116.581063</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Beijing Airport Gold Route International Business Hotel in Beijing (Tianzhu - Capital International Airport), you'll be convenient to China International Exhibition Center. This hotel is within the region of 798 Space and Lady Street.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of 150 guestrooms featuring LCD televisions. Computers are provided along with complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access. Conveniences include phones, as well as coffee/tea makers and irons/ironing boards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Dip into one of the 2 spa tubs or enjoy other recreational amenities, which include a sauna. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, an arcade/game room, and a hair salon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner. Dining is also available at a coffee shop/café, and room service (during limited hours) is provided. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, express check-out, and dry cleaning/laundry services. Planning an event in Beijing? This hotel has facilities measuring 1076 square feet (100 square meters), including a meeting room. A roundtrip airport shuttle is complimentary (available 24 hours).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 8 AM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner. Dining is also available at a coffee shop/café, and room service (during limited hours) is provided. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Dip into one of the 2 spa tubs or enjoy other recreational amenities, which include a sauna. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, an arcade/game room, and a hair salon. &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of 150 guestrooms featuring LCD televisions. Computers are provided along with complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access. Conveniences include phones, as well as coffee/tea makers and irons/ironing boards.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Beijing Airport Gold Route International Business Hotel in Beijing (Tianzhu - Capital International Airport), you'll be convenient to China International Exhibition Center. This hotel is within the region of 798 Space and Lady Street. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;China International Exhibition Center - 2.5 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;798 Space - 11.3 km / 7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lady Street - 14.8 km / 9.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shunyi Olympic Water Park - 15.3 km / 9.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Qiaobo Snow World - 16.4 km / 10.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;North Star Shopping Mall - 16.5 km / 10.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chaoyang Park - 16.6 km / 10.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Olympic Forest Park - 16.8 km / 10.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Agricultural Exhibition Center - 16.9 km / 10.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Beijing International Convention Center - 17.1 km / 10.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Xin'ao Shopping Center - 17.2 km / 10.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Nali Patio - 17.3 km / 10.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Xinglong Park - 17.3 km / 10.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Stadium - 17.4 km / 10.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;China National Convention Center - 17.5 km / 10.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Beijing Airport Gold Route International Business Hotel is Beijing (PEK-Capital Intl.) - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>