<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11898695</Id><Name>Huachen Kenzo Hotel Hangzhou</Name><Region><Id>15904</Id><Name>Hangzhou</Name><CityId>15904</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>342 XINTANG ROAD</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>HANGZHOU</City><State /><Zip>310021</Zip><Country>CHINA</Country><Tel>008657186478698</Tel><Fax>008657186963868</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>30.2755</Latitude><Longitude>120.2076</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;In the heart of Hangzhou, Huachen Kenzo Hotel is close to Zhejiang University Huajiachi Campus and Chongyi Church.  This hotel is within close proximity of Hangzhou China Silk Town and Hangzhou Grand Theatre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 185 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include safes and complimentary newspapers, and you can also request rollaway/extra beds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss out on recreational opportunities including a spa tub and a sauna. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, an arcade/game room, and a hair salon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite at one of the hotel's 2 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Planning an event in Hangzhou? This hotel features 247 square feet (23 square meters) of event facilities.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at noon  Check-out time is 2 PM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite at one of the hotel's 2 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Don’t miss out on recreational opportunities including a spa tub and a sauna. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, an arcade/game room, and a hair salon. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 185 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars. Complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Conveniences include safes and complimentary newspapers, and you can also request rollaway/extra beds.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>In the heart of Hangzhou, Huachen Kenzo Hotel is close to Zhejiang University Huajiachi Campus and Chongyi Church.  This hotel is within close proximity of Hangzhou China Silk Town and Hangzhou Grand Theatre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Zhejiang University Huajiachi Campus - 1.2 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chongyi Church - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hangzhou China Silk Town - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hangzhou Grand Theatre - 3.5 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Westlake Culture Plaza - 4.1 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Qianjiang New Town Forest Park - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Zhejiang Museum of Natural History - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Si Cheng Church - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Zhejiang University First Affiliated Hospital - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wulin Square - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hangzhou Opera - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wushan Night Market - 4.6 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Former Residence of Sha Menghai - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;West Lake - 5.2 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hu Xueyan Former Residence - 5.4 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Huachen Kenzo Hotel is Hangzhou (HGH-Xiaoshan Intl.) - 22.5 km / 14 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>