<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11898938</Id><Name>Hotel ZZZ (Xiang Mi Hu)</Name><Region><Id>15990</Id><Name>Shenzhen</Name><CityId>15990</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>No.1014 Shennan Zhonglu,</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Shenzhen</City><State /><Zip>518000</Zip><Country>China</Country><Tel>+86 755 8209 3088</Tel><Fax>008675522669880</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>22.541014</Latitude><Longitude>114.018811</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Zzz, you'll be centrally located in Shenzhen, steps from Shenzhen Museum and minutes from Lizhi Park. This hotel is within close proximity of Shenzhen Grand Theater and Shun Hing Square.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 89 air-conditioned rooms featuring LCD televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and complimentary newspapers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, gift shops/newsstands, and a hair salon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Hotel Zzz, or find a snack in a coffee shop/café. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a business center, and express check-in. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at noon  Check-out time is 2 PM &lt;br/&gt; You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Hotel Zzz, or find a snack in a coffee shop/café. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, gift shops/newsstands, and a hair salon. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 89 air-conditioned rooms featuring LCD televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and complimentary newspapers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Zzz, you'll be centrally located in Shenzhen, steps from Shenzhen Museum and minutes from Lizhi Park. This hotel is within close proximity of Shenzhen Grand Theater and Shun Hing Square. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Shenzhen Museum - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lizhi Park - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shenzhen Grand Theater - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shun Hing Square - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shenzhen Huaqiang North Commercial Circle - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shenzhen Stadium - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;International Foreign Trade Center - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Luohu Commercial City - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dongmen Pedestrian Street - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shenzhen People's Park - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Luohu Port - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Huanggang Port - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Huanggang Border Crossing - 3.7 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shenzhen City Hall - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Guan Shanyue Art Museum - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Zzz is Shenzhen (SZX-Shenzhen Intl.) - 30.9 km / 19.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>