<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11898297</Id><Name>Leonessa Hotel</Name><Region><Id>21002</Id><Name>Naples</Name><CityId>17120</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>VIA RAFFAELLO SANZIO</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>VOLLA-NAPOLI</City><State /><Zip>80040</Zip><Country>ITALY</Country><Tel>00390817748915</Tel><Fax>00390817748903</Fax><Email>info@hotelleonessa.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>40.8742575</Latitude><Longitude>14.3450367</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Leonessa in Volla, you'll be near the airport and close to Auchan Mall. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of Pietrarsa Railway Museum and Bourbon Hospice for the Poor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 45 air-conditioned rooms featuring LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include safes and complimentary newspapers, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (complimentary).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Mingle with other guests at a complimentary reception, held daily. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, express check-in, and dry cleaning/laundry services. Planning an event in Volla? This hotel has facilities measuring 2367 square feet (220 square meters), including conference space. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Mingle with other guests at a complimentary reception, held daily. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 45 air-conditioned rooms featuring LCD televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include safes and complimentary newspapers, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (complimentary).</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Leonessa in Volla, you'll be near the airport and close to Auchan Mall. This 4-star hotel is within the vicinity of Pietrarsa Railway Museum and Bourbon Hospice for the Poor. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Auchan Mall - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pietrarsa Railway Museum - 6.2 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bourbon Hospice for the Poor - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza Giuseppe Garibaldi - 7.1 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Porta Capuana - 7.1 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Castel Capuano - 7.2 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Botanical Garden of Naples - 7.3 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Santa Maria del Carmine - 7.3 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museo Archeologico Virtuale - 7.5 km / 4.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pio Monte della Misericordia - 7.6 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazza Sisto Riario Sforza - 7.7 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Spire of San Gennaro - 7.7 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ercolano Ruins - 7.7 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museum Madre - 7.7 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Museo Civico Filangeri - 7.7 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Leonessa is Naples (NAP-Naples Intl.) - 5.4 km / 3.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HandicapAccessible</Code><Text>Handicap accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CloakRoom</Code><Text>Cloak Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVRoom</Code><Text>TV Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DiningRoom</Code><Text>Dining Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantAirconditioned</Code><Text>Restaurant Air-Conditioned</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Garage</Code><Text>Garage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SunBathingTerrace</Code><Text>Sun Bathing Terrace</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccessible</Code><Text>Wheelchair Accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Cafe(s)</Code><Text>Cafe(s)</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>