<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11898363</Id><Name>Citta Del Mare Hotel Village</Name><Region><Id>21009</Id><Name>Palermo</Name><CityId>17128</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>S.S.113 KM301.100</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>TERRASINI</City><State /><Zip>90049</Zip><Country>ITALY</Country><Tel>00390918687111</Tel><Fax>00390918687555</Fax><Email>reservation@cittadelmare.it</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>38.1129116</Latitude><Longitude>13.0792301</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Città del Mare Hotel Village in Terrasini (Palermo Coast), you'll be within the vicinity of Regional Museum of Palazzo D'Aumale and Fontana degli Otto Cannoli.  This family-friendly hotel is within the vicinity of Casa Memoria Felicia e Peppino Impastato and Sanctuary of Madonna del Ponte.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 800 air-conditioned guestrooms. Rooms have private furnished balconies. Satellite television is provided for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature rainfall showerheads and complimentary toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. You're sure to appreciate the recreational amenities, which include 4 outdoor swimming pools, 3 spa tubs, and a nightclub. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and supervised childcare/activities. Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the area shuttle (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite from a snack bar/deli serving guests of Città del Mare Hotel Village. Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a swim-up bar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a 24-hour front desk, and multilingual staff. Planning an event in Terrasini? This hotel has 624 square feet (58 square meters) of space consisting of a conference center and a meeting room. For a surcharge, guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle (available on request) and a ferry terminal shuttle.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite from a snack bar/deli serving guests of Città del Mare Hotel Village. Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a swim-up bar. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. You're sure to appreciate the recreational amenities, which include 4 outdoor swimming pools, 3 spa tubs, and a nightclub. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and supervised childcare/activities. Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the area shuttle (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 800 air-conditioned guestrooms. Rooms have private furnished balconies. Satellite television is provided for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature rainfall showerheads and complimentary toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Città del Mare Hotel Village in Terrasini (Palermo Coast), you'll be within the vicinity of Regional Museum of Palazzo D'Aumale and Fontana degli Otto Cannoli.  This family-friendly hotel is within the vicinity of Casa Memoria Felicia e Peppino Impastato and Sanctuary of Madonna del Ponte. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Regional Museum of Palazzo D'Aumale - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fontana degli Otto Cannoli - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Casa Memoria Felicia e Peppino Impastato - 7.1 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sanctuary of Madonna del Ponte - 7.6 km / 4.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Centro Kolbe - 9.9 km / 6.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Carini Castle - 9.9 km / 6.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Carburangeli Cave - 10.6 km / 6.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bioparco di Sicilia - 11.7 km / 7.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Portobello - Le Gallerie del Risparmio - 14.1 km / 8.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Alcamo Castle - 16.4 km / 10.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;AcquaPark Monreale - 17 km / 10.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Castellammare del Golfo Beach - 18 km / 11.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Monte Jato Archaeological Area - 18.2 km / 11.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Parco Avventura Bosco Alcamo - Vivilbosco - 18.7 km / 11.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ethno-Anthropological Museum Annalisa Buccellato - 18.7 km / 11.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Città del Mare Hotel Village is Palermo (PMO-Punta Raisi) - 10 km / 6.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MoneyExchange</Code><Text>Money exchange</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Hairdresser</Code><Text>Hairdresser</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DiscoClub</Code><Text>Disco / Club</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVRoom</Code><Text>TV Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DiningRoom</Code><Text>Dining Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantAirconditioned</Code><Text>Restaurant Air-Conditioned</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniClub</Code><Text>Mini Club</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Playground</Code><Text>Playground</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>NumberOfPool</Code><Text>Number Of Pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ChildrenPool</Code><Text>Children's pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SunLounge</Code><Text>SunLounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parasol</Code><Text>Parasol</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniFridge</Code><Text>MiniFridge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Balcony</Code><Text>Balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomTerraceBalcony</Code><Text>Terrace or balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shops</Code><Text>Shops</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>