<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11893865</Id><Name>MONT BLANC HOTEL VILLAGE</Name><Region><Id>17052</Id><Name>Aosta</Name><CityId>17053</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>LOCALITA LA CROISETTE 36</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>LA SALLE - COURMAYEUR</City><State /><Zip>11015</Zip><Country>ITALY</Country><Tel>00390165864111</Tel><Fax>00390165864119</Fax><Email>info@hotelmontblanc.it</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>45.7969221</Latitude><Longitude>6.9689626</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Mont Blanc Hotel Village in La Salle, you'll be convenient to Marais Natural Reserve. This 5-star hotel is within the vicinity of Arpy Lake and Pre-Saint-Didier Spa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 40 guestrooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have designer toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Treat yourself with massages, body treatments, and facials. You can take advantage of recreational amenities such as a health club, an outdoor pool, and an indoor pool. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and ski storage. The complimentary ski shuttle makes getting to the slopes a breeze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and dry cleaning/laundry services. Planning an event in La Salle? This hotel has 2884 square feet (268 square meters) of space consisting of conference space and meeting rooms. For a surcharge, guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle (available on request) and a train station pick-up service.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Treat yourself with massages, body treatments, and facials. You can take advantage of recreational amenities such as a health club, an outdoor pool, and an indoor pool. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and ski storage. The complimentary ski shuttle makes getting to the slopes a breeze. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 40 guestrooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms have designer toiletries and bidets. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Mont Blanc Hotel Village in La Salle, you'll be convenient to Marais Natural Reserve. This 5-star hotel is within the vicinity of Arpy Lake and Pre-Saint-Didier Spa. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Marais Natural Reserve - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Arpy Lake - 6.3 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pre-Saint-Didier Spa - 7.1 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;San Nicolas Church - 8.5 km / 5.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;La Mothe Castle - 8.8 km / 5.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Courmayeur Cable Car - 9.1 km / 5.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Abbe Henry Park - 9.1 km / 5.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Duke of Abruzzi Alpine Museum - 9.3 km / 5.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fun Park Dolonne - 9.8 km / 6.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Saint Rhemy-Crevacol Ski Resort - 10 km / 6.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dolonne Cable Car - 10 km / 6.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Courmayeur Forum Sport Center - 10 km / 6.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Introd Animal Park - 10 km / 6.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Les Suches Cable Car - 10.5 km / 6.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bosco Express Ski Lift - 10.6 km / 6.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Mont Blanc Hotel Village is Geneva International Airport (GVA) - 92 km / 57.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HandicapAccessible</Code><Text>Handicap accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lounge</Code><Text>Lounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Balcony</Code><Text>Balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomTerraceBalcony</Code><Text>Terrace or balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>