<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11893700</Id><Name>Bellavista</Name><Region><Id>20888</Id><Name>Capri Island</Name><CityId>17050</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>VIA G. ORLANDI 10</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>ANACAPRI</City><State /><Zip>80071</Zip><Country>ITALY</Country><Tel>00390818371463</Tel><Fax>00390818382719</Fax><Email>info@bellavistacapri.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>40.55633044</Latitude><Longitude>14.22152281</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Bellavista, you'll be centrally located in Anacapri, steps from Piazza Vittoria and Monte Solaro Chairlift. This hotel is within close proximity of Villa San Michele and Casa Rossa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 15 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Rooms have private furnished balconies or patios. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as outdoor tennis courts or take in the view from a rooftop terrace and a garden. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite from a snack bar/deli, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a computer station, express check-in, and express check-out. For a surcharge, guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle (available on request) and a train station pick-up service.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite from a snack bar/deli, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as outdoor tennis courts or take in the view from a rooftop terrace and a garden. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 15 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Rooms have private furnished balconies or patios. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature complimentary toiletries and bidets.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Bellavista, you'll be centrally located in Anacapri, steps from Piazza Vittoria and Monte Solaro Chairlift. This hotel is within close proximity of Villa San Michele and Casa Rossa. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Piazza Vittoria - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Monte Solaro Chairlift - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Villa San Michele - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Casa Rossa - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chiesa di San Michele - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chiesa di Santa Sofia - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bagni of Tiberio Beach - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mount Solaro - 1.4 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Blue Grotto - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marina Grande - 1.5 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marina Piccola - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Villa Imperiale di Damecuta - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Torre Saracena - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Piazzetta Capri - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gardens of Augustus - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Bellavista is Naples (NAP-Naples Intl.) - 36.1 km / 22.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Balcony</Code><Text>Balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomTerraceBalcony</Code><Text>Terrace or balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>