<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11905128</Id><Name>South China Laguna</Name><Region><Id>15990</Id><Name>Shenzhen</Name><CityId>15990</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>1428, QIAN HAI ROAD, NANSHAN DISTRICT</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>SHENZHEN</City><State /><Zip /><Country>CHINA</Country><Tel>008675586253888</Tel><Fax>008675586253833</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>22.527366</Latitude><Longitude>113.915576</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;In the heart of Shenzhen, South China Laguna Hotel Shenzhen Nan Shan is close to Xin'an Nantou Ancient City and Shenzhen University.  This hotel is within the vicinity of Zhongshan Park and Shekou Ferry Terminal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 116 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring refrigerators and minibars. Your room comes with a memory foam bed. Rooms have private balconies. Flat-screen televisions with digital programming provide entertainment, while complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access keeps you connected. Partially open bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature deep soaking bathtubs and rainfall showerheads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a nightclub, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and gift shops/newsstands. Additional amenities at this Art Deco hotel include wedding services and tour/ticket assistance. Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the area shuttle (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Breakfast is available for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour business center, limo/town car service, and express check-in. Event facilities at this hotel consist of a conference center, conference space, and meeting rooms. A train station pick-up service is provided at no charge (available 24 hours), and extended parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 11:30 AM  Check-out time is 12:30 PM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. Breakfast is available for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 14 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a nightclub, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and gift shops/newsstands. Additional amenities at this Art Deco hotel include wedding services and tour/ticket assistance. Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the area shuttle (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 116 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring refrigerators and minibars. Your room comes with a memory foam bed. Rooms have private balconies. Flat-screen televisions with digital programming provide entertainment, while complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access keeps you connected. Partially open bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature deep soaking bathtubs and rainfall showerheads.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>In the heart of Shenzhen, South China Laguna Hotel Shenzhen Nan Shan is close to Xin'an Nantou Ancient City and Shenzhen University.  This hotel is within the vicinity of Zhongshan Park and Shekou Ferry Terminal. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Xin'an Nantou Ancient City - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shenzhen University - 2.2 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Zhongshan Park - 2.5 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shekou Ferry Terminal - 5.7 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chiwan Tin Hau Temple - 5.9 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tomb of the Young Song Emperor - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Window of the World - 6.2 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;He Xiangning Art Museum - 6.8 km / 4.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Happy Valley - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chinese Overseas City - 7.4 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Splendid China Folk Village - 7.4 km / 4.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shenzhen Polytechnic - 7.7 km / 4.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mangrove Seashore Ecological Park - 8.1 km / 5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shenzhen Safari Park - 9 km / 5.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Shenzhen International Garden and Flower Expo Park - 9.2 km / 5.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Shenzhen (SZX-Shenzhen Intl.) - 16.1 km / 10 mi&lt;br /&gt;Shenyang (SHE-Taoxian Intl.) - 2,304.3 km / 1,431.9 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for South China Laguna Hotel Shenzhen Nan Shan is Shenyang (SHE-Taoxian Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 14 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>