<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11907744</Id><Name>The Golden Tree Hotel</Name><Region><Id>64765</Id><Name>Brugge (Bruges)</Name><CityId>64765</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>HOEFIJZERLAAN 21</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>BRUGES</City><State /><Zip>8000</Zip><Country>BELGIUM</Country><Tel>003250338731</Tel><Fax>003250342109</Fax><Email>info@goldentreehotel.be</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>51.2080664</Latitude><Longitude>3.21547508</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Golden Tree Hotel places you in the heart of Bruges, walking distance from 't Zand Square and Concert Hall.  This family-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Smedenpoort and St. Salvators Church.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 20 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms with shower/tub combinations are provided. Conveniences include phones and desks, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and babysitting/childcare (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A complimentary hot/cold buffet breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include luggage storage and an elevator (lift). Self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; A complimentary hot/cold buffet breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; Special cancellation policies or charges may apply for group reservations (more than 8 rooms for the same hotel / stay dates). &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 20 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms with shower/tub combinations are provided. Conveniences include phones and desks, and you can also request cribs/infant beds (surcharge).</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Golden Tree Hotel places you in the heart of Bruges, walking distance from 't Zand Square and Concert Hall.  This family-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Smedenpoort and St. Salvators Church. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;'t Zand Square - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Concert Hall - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Smedenpoort - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Salvators Church - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sint-Salvador Cathedral - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chocolate Line - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. James's Church - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cinema Lumiere - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bruges Market Square - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Archeological Museum - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rail City Bruges - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dali Xpo Gallery - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bladelin Court - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bruges Belfry - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of Our Lady - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Golden Tree Hotel is Brussels (BRU) - 95.1 km / 59.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Golden Tree Hotel is Brussels (BRU-Brussels Airport) - 95.1 km / 59.1 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; Special cancellation policies or charges may apply for group reservations (more than 8 rooms for the same hotel / stay dates).</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WLANAccessPoint</Code><Text>WLAN Access Point</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>