<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11909275</Id><Name>Pao Jin Poon Beach Front Villa</Name><Region><Id>18749</Id><Name>Koh Samui</Name><CityId>18749</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>MOO4 MARET, LAMAI BEACH, KOH SAMUI 146/38</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>SURATTHANI</City><State /><Zip>84320</Zip><Country>THAILAND</Country><Tel>006677424030</Tel><Fax>006677424029</Fax><Email>info@pavilionsamui.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>9.47185</Latitude><Longitude>100.0413</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Pao Jin Poon Beach Front Villa in Koh Samui (Maret), you'll be close to Silver Beach and Hin Ta and Hin Yai. This 4-star villa is within close proximity of Coco Splash Waterpark and Wat Lamai.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 3 air-conditioned rooms featuring private pools and plasma televisions. Kitchenettes are outfitted with refrigerators and microwaves. Satellite programming and MP3 docking stations are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature deep soaking bathtubs and rainfall showerheads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a garden. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, a 24-hour front desk, and luggage storage. Limited parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 18 years old. &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a garden. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 3 air-conditioned rooms featuring private pools and plasma televisions. Kitchenettes are outfitted with refrigerators and microwaves. Satellite programming and MP3 docking stations are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature deep soaking bathtubs and rainfall showerheads.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Pao Jin Poon Beach Front Villa in Koh Samui (Maret), you'll be close to Silver Beach and Hin Ta and Hin Yai. This 4-star villa is within close proximity of Coco Splash Waterpark and Wat Lamai. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Silver Beach - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Coco Splash Waterpark - 1.5 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wat Lamai - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lamai Night Market - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hin Ta and Hin Yai - 3.1 km / 1.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wat Sila Ngu - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bangkok Hospital - 4.8 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Phetch Buncha Thai Boxing Stadium - 5.5 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chaweng Thai Boxing Stadium - 6 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wat Samret - 6.2 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Samui Aquarium - 6.5 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Central Festival Samui - 6.6 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Khunaram Temple - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mummified Monk - 6.9 km / 4.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tesco Lotus Koh Samui - 7.1 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Pao Jin Poon Beach Front Villa is Ko Samui (USM) - 8.8 km / 5.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 18 years old. &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndoorPool</Code><Text>Indoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniFridge</Code><Text>MiniFridge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomTerraceBalcony</Code><Text>Terrace or balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>