<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11907798</Id><Name>Hotel Het Gheestelic Hof</Name><Region><Id>64765</Id><Name>Brugge (Bruges)</Name><CityId>64765</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>HEILIGE GEESTSTRAAT 2</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>BRUGES</City><State /><Zip>8000</Zip><Country>BELGIUM</Country><Tel>003250342594</Tel><Fax>003250339475</Fax><Email>gheestelic.hof@scarlet.be</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>51.2050129</Latitude><Longitude>3.2230223</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Gheestelic Hof, you'll be centrally located in Bruges, steps from Sint-Salvador Cathedral and St. Salvators Church. This family-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Archeological Museum and Rail City Bruges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 11 guestrooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have bathtubs or showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hotel Gheestelic Hof. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, luggage storage, and laundry facilities. Event facilities at this hotel consist of conference space and meeting rooms. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hotel Gheestelic Hof. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;Special cancellation policies or charges may apply for group reservations (more than 8 rooms for the same hotel / stay dates). &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 11 guestrooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have bathtubs or showers and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Gheestelic Hof, you'll be centrally located in Bruges, steps from Sint-Salvador Cathedral and St. Salvators Church. This family-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Archeological Museum and Rail City Bruges. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Sint-Salvador Cathedral - 0.1 km / 0 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Salvators Church - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Archeological Museum - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rail City Bruges - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chocolate Line - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Church of Our Lady - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gruuthuse Museum - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Arentshuis - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Jans Hospitaal - Hans Memling Museum - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Concert Hall - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Groeningemuseum - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;'t Zand Square - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;De Halve Maan Brewery - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Absolute Art Gallery - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Diamond Museum - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Gheestelic Hof is Brussels (BRU) - 94.6 km / 58.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Hotel Gheestelic Hof is Brussels (BRU-Brussels Airport) - 94.6 km / 58.8 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;Special cancellation policies or charges may apply for group reservations (more than 8 rooms for the same hotel / stay dates). &lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>CoffeeTeaMaker</Code><Text>Tea and Coffee maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WLANAccessPoint</Code><Text>WLAN Access Point</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>