<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>119044</Id><Name>Plough &amp; Harrow Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52391</Id><Name>Birmingham (and vicinity)</Name><CityId>52391</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>135 Hagley Road,</Address1><Address2>Edgbaston</Address2><Address3 /><City>Birmingham</City><State /><Zip>B16 8LS</Zip><Country>England</Country><Tel>0121 454 4111</Tel><Fax>01214541868</Fax><Email>reception@ploughandharrowhotel.co.uk</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>52.4720894</Latitude><Longitude>-1.9272819</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1136/44/72/6/44726_16012823420039476686.jpg</Url><Width>312</Width><Height>233</Height><Bytes>16388</Bytes><Caption>Recreational Facilities</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1136/44/72/6/44726_16012823420039476686thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2809</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1136/44/72/6/44726_16012823420039476687.jpg</Url><Width>312</Width><Height>233</Height><Bytes>18164</Bytes><Caption>Garden</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1136/44/72/6/44726_16012823420039476687thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2641</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1136/44/72/6/44726_16012823420039476688.jpg</Url><Width>312</Width><Height>235</Height><Bytes>19977</Bytes><Caption>Restaurant</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1136/44/72/6/44726_16012823420039476688thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>92</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2880</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1136/44/72/6/44726_16012823420039476689.jpg</Url><Width>312</Width><Height>235</Height><Bytes>15564</Bytes><Caption>Front of Hotel</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1136/44/72/6/44726_16012823420039476689thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>92</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2375</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1136/44/72/6/44726_16020820090039724273.jpg</Url><Width>312</Width><Height>235</Height><Bytes>10666</Bytes><Caption>44726_16020820090039724273</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1136/44/72/6/44726_16020820090039724273thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>92</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2105</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The Plough and Harrow is in the heart of Birmingham, walking distance from Perrott's Folly and Birmingham Botanical Gardens. This hotel is close to International Convention Centre and Bullring Shopping Centre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of 44 guestrooms featuring LCD televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. Additional features include concierge services, wedding services, and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar and a garden view. You can also stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. English breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, a 24-hour front desk, and luggage storage. Planning an event in Birmingham? This hotel has 2153 square feet (200 square meters) of space consisting of a conference center and meeting rooms. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar and a garden view. You can also stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. English breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. Additional features include concierge services, wedding services, and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of 44 guestrooms featuring LCD televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include desks and coffee/tea makers, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The Plough and Harrow is in the heart of Birmingham, walking distance from Perrott's Folly and Birmingham Botanical Gardens. This hotel is close to International Convention Centre and Bullring Shopping Centre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Perrott's Folly - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Birmingham Botanical Gardens - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Five Ways Clock - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Birmingham Peace Pagoda - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Edgbaston Reservoir - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brindleyplace - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Sea Life Centre - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ikon Gallery - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Barclaycard Arena - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;CBSO Centre - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Symphony Hall - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;St Thomas' Church - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;International Convention Centre - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Birmingham Repertory Theatre - 1.5 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Library of Birmingham - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Plough and Harrow is Birmingham (BHX) - 13.4 km / 8.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for The Plough and Harrow is Birmingham (BHX) - 13.3 km / 8.3 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>