<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11906330</Id><Name>Asia Cha Am Hotel</Name><Region><Id>18726</Id><Name>Cha-Am</Name><CityId>18726</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>RUAMJIT ROAD, CHA AM BEACH 251</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>PETCHABURI</City><State /><Zip>76120</Zip><Country>THAILAND</Country><Tel>006629926999</Tel><Fax>00665323193</Fax><Email>aahsale@asiahotel.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>12.80116598</Latitude><Longitude>99.98480791</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Asia Cha Am Hotel in Cha-am, you'll be near the beach and minutes from Cha-am Beach, and close to Cha Am Hospital. This hotel is within the region of Santorini Park and Mrigadayavan Palace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 214 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and minibars. Rooms have private balconies. LCD televisions are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include safes and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including an outdoor pool, a sauna, and a fitness center. This hotel also features babysitting/childcare and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a bite to eat at a coffee shop/café, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services and luggage storage. This hotel has 8 meeting rooms available for events.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a bite to eat at a coffee shop/café, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including an outdoor pool, a sauna, and a fitness center. This hotel also features babysitting/childcare and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 214 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and minibars. Rooms have private balconies. LCD televisions are provided for your entertainment. Conveniences include safes and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Asia Cha Am Hotel in Cha-am, you'll be near the beach and minutes from Cha-am Beach, and close to Cha Am Hospital. This hotel is within the region of Santorini Park and Mrigadayavan Palace. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Cha-am Beach - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cha Am Hospital - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Santorini Park - 6.4 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mrigadayavan Palace - 11.7 km / 7.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Imperial Lake View Golf Club - 14.8 km / 9.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;FN Factory Outlet - 15.5 km / 9.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Puek Tian Beach - 15.8 km / 9.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Springfield Village Golf Club - 16.4 km / 10.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wat Bo Fai - 20.5 km / 12.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Black Mountain Golf Club - 23.1 km / 14.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Plearnwan Market - 23.3 km / 14.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wang Klai Kangwon Vocational College - 23.4 km / 14.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Klai Kangwon Palace - 23.8 km / 14.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Black Mountain Water Park - 24.2 km / 15 mi &lt;br /&gt;Elephant Village - 24.3 km / 15.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Asia Cha Am Hotel is Bangkok (BKK-Suvarnabhumi Intl.) - 128.8 km / 80 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>