<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11917920</Id><Name>CLASSIC KAMEO RAYONG HOTEL</Name><Region><Id>64797</Id><Name>Rayong</Name><CityId>64797</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>RAJBAMRUNG ROAD, SOI 6, NEONPHRA, 11</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>RAYONG</City><State /><Zip>21000</Zip><Country>THAILAND</Country><Tel>006638614340-9</Tel><Fax>006638614780</Fax><Email>bkkreservations@kasemkij.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>12.68178374</Latitude><Longitude>101.2601643</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Classic Kameo Hotel&amp;Serviced Apartments, Rayong places you in the heart of Rayong, convenient to Wat Pa Pradu. This hotel is within the region of Mae Rumphung Beach and Sopha Arboretum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in of the guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and microwaves. Rooms have private balconies. Flat-screen televisions with cable programming are available for your entertainment, and DVD players are also provided. Conveniences include safes, housekeeping is provided daily, and cribs/infant beds can be requested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities, including an indoor pool, a sauna, and a steam room. Additional features include babysitting/childcare and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a bite to eat at a coffee shop/café, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include limo/town car service, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a safe deposit box at the front desk. Event facilities at this hotel consist of a conference center and meeting rooms.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a bite to eat at a coffee shop/café, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities, including an indoor pool, a sauna, and a steam room. Additional features include babysitting/childcare and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in of the guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and microwaves. Rooms have private balconies. Flat-screen televisions with cable programming are available for your entertainment, and DVD players are also provided. Conveniences include safes, housekeeping is provided daily, and cribs/infant beds can be requested.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Classic Kameo Hotel&amp;Serviced Apartments, Rayong places you in the heart of Rayong, convenient to Wat Pa Pradu. This hotel is within the region of Mae Rumphung Beach and Sopha Arboretum. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Wat Pa Pradu - 1.9 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mae Rumphung Beach - 15.1 km / 9.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sopha Arboretum - 17.7 km / 11 mi &lt;br /&gt;Rayong Aquarium - 19.4 km / 12 mi &lt;br /&gt;Emerald Golf Resort - 21.5 km / 13.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Suan Son Beach - 22.7 km / 14.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ko Samed Beach - 23.7 km / 14.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ao Prao Beach - 23.9 km / 14.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Eastern Star Golf Course - 24 km / 14.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ban Chang Hospital - 24.2 km / 15 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ao Wong Duan Beach - 24.9 km / 15.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;International Clinic Koh Samet - 25 km / 15.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ao Phai Beach - 25 km / 15.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ao Cho Beach - 25 km / 15.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ao Thian Beach - 25.1 km / 15.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Classic Kameo Hotel&amp;Serviced Apartments, Rayong is Bangkok (BKK-Suvarnabhumi Intl.) - 124.8 km / 77.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>