<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11916413</Id><Name>Bay Shore Huts</Name><Region><Id>16971</Id><Name>Lembongan Island</Name><CityId>16971</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>TAMARIND BEACH LEMBONGAN</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>LEMBONGAN</City><State /><Zip>80011</Zip><Country>INDONESIA</Country><Tel>+62 813-3851-6779</Tel><Fax>00623618833166</Fax><Email>omegasan1@yahoo.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>-8.681328816</Latitude><Longitude>115.4361141</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Lembongan Bay Shore Huts in Lembongan Island, you'll be on the beach and minutes from Nusa Lembongan Beach. This beach resort is within the region of Watu Klotok Temple and Keramas Beach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 11 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Rooms have private balconies or patios. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. You can take advantage of recreational amenities such as an outdoor pool and bicycles to rent. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the area shuttle (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the resort's beachfront restaurant, where you can enjoy drinks at a bar, take in a garden view, and even dine alfresco (weather permitting). You can also stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Thirsty? Quench your thirst at a bar/lounge, a beach bar, or a poolside bar. A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, laundry facilities, and a safe deposit box at the front desk. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 6 AM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the resort's beachfront restaurant, where you can enjoy drinks at a bar, take in a garden view, and even dine alfresco (weather permitting). You can also stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Thirsty? Quench your thirst at a bar/lounge, a beach bar, or a poolside bar. A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages, body treatments, and facials. You can take advantage of recreational amenities such as an outdoor pool and bicycles to rent. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the area shuttle (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 11 air-conditioned rooms featuring kitchens. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Rooms have private balconies or patios. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Lembongan Bay Shore Huts in Lembongan Island, you'll be on the beach and minutes from Nusa Lembongan Beach. This beach resort is within the region of Watu Klotok Temple and Keramas Beach. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Nusa Lembongan Beach - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Watu Klotok Temple - 12.4 km / 7.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Keramas Beach - 14.5 km / 9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bali Marine and Safari Park - 14.7 km / 9.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Goa Lawah Beach - 14.7 km / 9.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Goa Lawah Temple - 14.8 km / 9.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Saba Beach - 15.8 km / 9.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Taman Kertha Gosa - 16.7 km / 10.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Padangbai Pier - 18.2 km / 11.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Padang Bay Beach - 18.4 km / 11.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Honorary Consulate of Germany - 19.1 km / 11.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sanur Beach - 19.3 km / 12 mi &lt;br /&gt;Le Mayeur Museum - 19.3 km / 12 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pura Segara Temple - 19.3 km / 12 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maha Art Gallery - 19.4 km / 12 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Lembongan Bay Shore Huts is Denpasar (DPS-Ngurah Rai Intl.) - 31.1 km / 19.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>CoffeeTeaMaker</Code><Text>Tea and Coffee maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DiningRoom</Code><Text>Dining Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantAirconditioned</Code><Text>Restaurant Air-Conditioned</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MedicalService</Code><Text>Medical Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BicycleRental</Code><Text>Bicycle Rental</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Playground</Code><Text>Playground</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>NumberOfPool</Code><Text>Number Of Pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreshWaterPool</Code><Text>Fresh Water Pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SunLounge</Code><Text>SunLounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SunBathingTerrace</Code><Text>Sun Bathing Terrace</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Massage</Code><Text>Massage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Balcony</Code><Text>Balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Fridge</Code><Text>Fridge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomTerraceBalcony</Code><Text>Terrace or balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Cafe(s)</Code><Text>Cafe(s)</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>