<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11917119</Id><Name>The Tryall Club &amp; Resort Villas</Name><Region><Id>17182</Id><Name>Montego Bay</Name><CityId>17182</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>.</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>MONTEGO BAY</City><State /><Zip>1206</Zip><Country>JAMAICA</Country><Tel>8769565660</Tel><Fax>8769565673</Fax><Email>DIVINE.RES@CWJAMAICA.COM</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>18.450247</Latitude><Longitude>-78.057926</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The resort is located on the island's north coast just a few kilometres west of the modern Montego Bay Airport.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>The 1-bedroom villas are split-level and feature an entrance foyer, a bedroom, an en suite bathroom and a small patio on the upper level. The bedrooms are equipped with queen-size or king-size beds, and there are pull-out sofa beds in the living room. The lower level is equipped with a full kitchen, with a dining and living area on the ground floor. There is a comfortably sized porch on the lower level. The 2-bedroom Great House Villas have a large living and dining area, a powder room and a kitchen. At one end there is a master bedroom with a queen-size or king-size bed and spa bath, and at the other end is a room with twin beds and an en suite bathroom. A large terrace extends the entire length of the villa, with views of the golf course and the glittering Caribbean Sea.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DiningFacilities</Type><Text>This club resort is a unique collection of villas nestled in a private club setting that starts at the turquoise Caribbean and continues into the panoramic hills. Each villa comes complete with attentive staff offering excellent service and classic Jamaican hospitality. It is the perfect holiday resort and exclusive escape for families with children of all ages, weddings, honeymooners, golfers, and keen tennis players, but equally a romantic hideaway for couples. The physical beauty of the setting, its facilities, and overall ambience are hard to match in any other resort or club elsewhere in the Caribbean. Facilities on offer to guests include, for example, a kids' club, a bar and a restaurant.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Kitchen</Code><Text>Kitchen</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniClub</Code><Text>Mini Club</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>