<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11924974</Id><Name>Mon Choisy Beach Resort</Name><Region><Id>264141</Id><Name>Mauritius</Name><CityId>264141</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Coastal Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Choisy</City><State /><Zip /><Country>MAURITIUS ISLAND</Country><Tel> 230-265-8500</Tel><Fax>2302655798</Fax><Email>BRIGITTE.GBTT@INTNET.MU</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>-20.022093</Latitude><Longitude>57.553715</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Mon Choisy Beach Resort in Mont Choisy, you'll be on the beach and convenient to Mont Choisy Beach and Trou aux Biches Beach.  This beach apartment is within close proximity of Blue Water Diving Center and Canonnier Beach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 35 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and microwaves. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while 32-inch LCD televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 35 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and microwaves. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while 32-inch LCD televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Mon Choisy Beach Resort in Mont Choisy, you'll be on the beach and convenient to Mont Choisy Beach and Trou aux Biches Beach.  This beach apartment is within close proximity of Blue Water Diving Center and Canonnier Beach. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Mont Choisy Beach - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Trou aux Biches Beach - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Blue Water Diving Center - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Canonnier Beach - 2.3 km / 1.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maheswarnath - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;La Croisette - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Grand Bay Beach - 3.3 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Grand Bay Shopping Center - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Merville Beach - 3.8 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pereybere Beach - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mauritius Aquarium - 5.1 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bain Boeuf Beach - 6.4 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Turtle Bay Marine Park - 7.9 km / 4.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cap Malheureux Beach - 8 km / 5 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Red Roof Chapel - 8.1 km / 5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Mon Choisy Beach Resort is Mahebourg (MRU-Sir Seewoosagur Ramgoolam Intl.) - 47.4 km / 29.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Kitchen</Code><Text>Kitchen</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WLANAccessPoint</Code><Text>WLAN Access Point</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MedicalService</Code><Text>Medical Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parasol</Code><Text>Parasol</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>