<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11924958</Id><Name>Ermitage na Pokrovke</Name><Region><Id>18146</Id><Name>Moscow</Name><CityId>18146</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Durasovsky pereulok 7</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>MOSCOW</City><State /><Zip>109028</Zip><Country>RUSSIA</Country><Tel>74959171919</Tel><Fax>74959171617</Fax><Email>5064545@mail.ru</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>55.75455584</Latitude><Longitude>37.65025901</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Ermitage, you'll be centrally located in Moscow, convenient to Atrium Mall and St. Basil's Cathedral.  This 4-star hotel is close to Red Square and Moscow Kremlin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 96 air-conditioned guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones and desks, and you can also request rollaway/extra beds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. Additional features include a hair salon and tour/ticket assistance. Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the area shuttle (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Hotel Ermitage, or find a snack in a coffee shop/café. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a computer station, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and dry cleaning/laundry services. Planning an event in Moscow? This hotel has 2152 square feet (200 square meters) of space consisting of conference space and meeting rooms. For a surcharge, guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle (available on request) and a train station pick-up service.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 1 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Hotel Ermitage, or find a snack in a coffee shop/café. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. Additional features include a hair salon and tour/ticket assistance. Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the area shuttle (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 96 air-conditioned guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Private bathrooms with showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones and desks, and you can also request rollaway/extra beds.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Ermitage, you'll be centrally located in Moscow, convenient to Atrium Mall and St. Basil's Cathedral.  This 4-star hotel is close to Red Square and Moscow Kremlin. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Atrium Mall - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Moscow Choral Synagogue - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Moscow Sovremennik Theatre - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Galina Ulanova Museum - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Abai Kunanbaev Monument - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Monument to Cyril and Methodius - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Theater of Russian Drama - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Embassy of Latvia - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Menshikov Tower - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Taganka Theatre - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palace of the Romanov Boyars - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Griboyedov Monument - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Andrei Rublev Museum of Early Russian Art - 1.4 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Polytechnical Museum - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bunker-42 on Taganka - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Ermitage is Moscow (SVO-Sheremetyevo) - 27.8 km / 17.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>CoffeeTeaMaker</Code><Text>Tea and Coffee maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Hairdresser</Code><Text>Hairdresser</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CloakRoom</Code><Text>Cloak Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WLANAccessPoint</Code><Text>WLAN Access Point</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Carpeted</Code><Text>Carpeted</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>