<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11925854</Id><Name>Riad Villa La Wenge</Name><Region><Id>17562</Id><Name>Marrakech</Name><CityId>17562</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>DERB MESSFIOUI NR 4 RAHBA</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>MARRAKECH</City><State /><Zip>40000</Zip><Country>MOROCCO</Country><Tel>00212661063886</Tel><Fax>00212524392300</Fax><Email>riadvillawenge@gmail.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>31.628537</Latitude><Longitude>-7.986252</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Riad Villa Wengé, you'll be centrally located in Marrakech, steps from Rahba Kedima and minutes from Jamaa el Fna.  This 4-star riad is within close proximity of Souk Laghzel and Criee Berbere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 7 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Partially open bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and complimentary bottled water, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as a spa tub or take in the view from a rooftop terrace. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Riad Villa Wengé, or stop in at a snack bar/deli. A complimentary full breakfast is included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, limo/town car service, and dry cleaning/laundry services. For a surcharge, guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle (available 24 hours) and a train station pick-up service.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 1 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Riad Villa Wengé, or stop in at a snack bar/deli. A complimentary full breakfast is included. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as a spa tub or take in the view from a rooftop terrace. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and babysitting/childcare (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 7 air-conditioned rooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and cable programming is available for your entertainment. Partially open bathrooms have complimentary toiletries and hair dryers. Conveniences include safes and complimentary bottled water, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Riad Villa Wengé, you'll be centrally located in Marrakech, steps from Rahba Kedima and minutes from Jamaa el Fna.  This 4-star riad is within close proximity of Souk Laghzel and Criee Berbere. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Rahba Kedima - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Souk Laghzel - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Criee Berbere - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Souk Zrabi - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Souk Smarine - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Souk El Bahja - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jamaa el Fna - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mouassine Mosque - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marrakesh Museum - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ben Youssef Madrasa - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Almoravid Koubba - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ben Youssef Mosque - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maison de la Photographie - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dar Tiskiwin Museum - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dar Si Said Museum - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Riad Villa Wengé is Marrakech (RAK-Menara) - 4.6 km / 2.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Whirlpool</Code><Text>Whirlpool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVRoom</Code><Text>TV Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DiningRoom</Code><Text>Dining Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Garage</Code><Text>Garage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SunLounge</Code><Text>SunLounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parasol</Code><Text>Parasol</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SunBathingTerrace</Code><Text>Sun Bathing Terrace</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Massage</Code><Text>Massage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>