<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>119275</Id><Name>Stronlossit Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52871</Id><Name>Fort William</Name><CityId>52569</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>ROYBRIDGE</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>ROY BRIDGE</City><State /><Zip>PH31 4AG</Zip><Country>UNITED KINGDOM</Country><Tel>00441397712253</Tel><Fax>00441397712641</Fax><Email>STAY@STRONLOSSIT.CO.UK</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Roybridge, The Stronlossit Inn is in a rural location and within the vicinity of Commando Memorial and Grey Corries. This hotel is within the region of Loch Lochy and Leanachan Forest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 12 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Bathrooms have showers and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers, and irons/ironing boards can be requested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The front desk is staffed during limited hours. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 12 guestrooms. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Bathrooms have showers and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include coffee/tea makers, and irons/ironing boards can be requested.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Roybridge, The Stronlossit Inn is in a rural location and within the vicinity of Commando Memorial and Grey Corries. This hotel is within the region of Loch Lochy and Leanachan Forest. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Commando Memorial - 6.6 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Grey Corries - 8.6 km / 5.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Loch Lochy - 10.6 km / 6.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Leanachan Forest - 10.6 km / 6.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aonach Mor Ski Resort - 14 km / 8.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ben Nevis - 14.8 km / 9.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ben Nevis Distillery - 15.7 km / 9.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Neptune's Staircase - 16.4 km / 10.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;West Highland Museum - 18.5 km / 11.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Ice Factor - 21 km / 13.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Atlas Brewery - 21.1 km / 13.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Glen Coe Mountain Resort - 26.5 km / 16.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Buchaille Etive Mor - 27.4 km / 17 mi &lt;br /&gt;Glen Coe Visitor Centre - 28.6 km / 17.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Benedictine Abbey - 29.9 km / 18.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Stronlossit Inn is Inverness (INV) - 86.1 km / 53.5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MoneyExchange</Code><Text>Money exchange</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Pub</Code><Text>Pub</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MobilePhoneNetwork</Code><Text>Mobile Phone Network</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>