<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11923986</Id><Name>EBM Executive Apartments KL</Name><Region><Id>3145125</Id><Name>Central</Name><CityId>17382</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>SOUTHERN BISTARI CONDO, JLN 1/64D, OFF JLN PUTRA</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>KUALA LUMPUR</City><State /><Zip>50350</Zip><Country>MALAYSIA</Country><Tel>0060340436090</Tel><Fax>0060340436005</Fax><Email>info@rentnow.my</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>3.16797</Latitude><Longitude>101.693631</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at EBM Apartments Kuala Lumpur, you'll be centrally located in Kuala Lumpur, steps from Putra World Trade Centre and minutes from Chow Kit Night Market. This family-friendly apartment is close to Merdeka Square and Petronas Twin Towers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and microwaves. Your pillowtop bed comes with Egyptian cotton sheets. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while 32-inch LCD televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with onsite body treatments and facials. If you're looking for recreational opportunities, you'll find a health club, an outdoor pool, and a sauna. This apartment also features complimentary wireless Internet access, gift shops/newsstands, and a hair salon. Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the area shuttle (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite at one of the apartment's 2 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Breakfast is available for a fee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a business center, and limo/town car service. Planning an event in Kuala Lumpur? This apartment has facilities measuring 2000 square feet (186 square meters), including meeting rooms. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge at scheduled times, and self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11:30 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite at one of the apartment's 2 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Breakfast is available for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 18 years old. &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with onsite body treatments and facials. If you're looking for recreational opportunities, you'll find a health club, an outdoor pool, and a sauna. This apartment also features complimentary wireless Internet access, gift shops/newsstands, and a hair salon. Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the area shuttle (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchens with full-sized refrigerators/freezers and microwaves. Your pillowtop bed comes with Egyptian cotton sheets. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while 32-inch LCD televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at EBM Apartments Kuala Lumpur, you'll be centrally located in Kuala Lumpur, steps from Putra World Trade Centre and minutes from Chow Kit Night Market. This family-friendly apartment is close to Merdeka Square and Petronas Twin Towers. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Putra World Trade Centre - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chow Kit Night Market - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Open University of Malaysia - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maju Junction Mall - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Masjid Jamek Kampung Bahru Mosque - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palace of Culture - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Art Gallery - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Capital Square - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bank Negara Money Museum - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Titiwangsa Lake Garden - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;DBKL City Theatre - 2 km / 1.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kuala Lumpur Tower - 2 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Merdeka Square - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. John's Cathedral - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bukit Nanas Forest Reserve - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nearest airports are:&lt;br /&gt;Subang (SZB-Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah) - 14.8 km / 9.2 mi&lt;br /&gt;Kuala Lumpur (KUL-Kuala Lumpur Intl.) - 45.5 km / 28.3 mi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for EBM Apartments Kuala Lumpur is Kuala Lumpur (KUL-Kuala Lumpur Intl.). &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 18 years old. &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Sauna</Code><Text>Sauna</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Kitchen</Code><Text>Kitchen</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Playground</Code><Text>Playground</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ChildrenPool</Code><Text>Children's pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shops</Code><Text>Shops</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>