<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11924272</Id><Name>Grand Lexis Port Dickson</Name><Region><Id>17397</Id><Name>Port Dickson</Name><CityId>17397</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>BATU 3, JALAN SEREMBAN, PORT DICKSON</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>NEGERI SEMBILAN</City><State /><Zip>71000</Zip><Country>MALAYSIA</Country><Tel>6066532000</Tel><Fax>6066515330</Fax><Email>reservations@lexispd.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>2.52635816</Latitude><Longitude>101.8085191</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/POXZ-91hotel_Exterior_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>270</Height><Bytes>29169</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/POXZ-91hotel_Exterior_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>4697</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/POXZ-91hotel_Exterior_2.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>270</Height><Bytes>26529</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/POXZ-91hotel_Exterior_2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>4511</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;When you stay at Grand Lexis Port Dickson in Port Dickson, you'll be close to Fort Lukut. This 4.5-star resort is within the vicinity of Port Dickson Army Museum and Sri Anjeneayar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 317 air-conditioned rooms featuring private plunge pools. Kitchenettes are outfitted with refrigerators and microwaves. Premium TV channels and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and complimentary newspapers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including a health club, an outdoor pool, and a sauna. Additional features include concierge services, an arcade/game room, and gift shops/newsstands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite at one of the resort's 2 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Relax with a refreshing drink at a bar/lounge, a poolside bar, or one of 2 bars/lounges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, a 24-hour front desk, and laundry facilities. Planning an event in Port Dickson? This resort has 10095 square feet (909 square meters) of space consisting of conference space and meeting rooms.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 4 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite at one of the resort's 2 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Relax with a refreshing drink at a bar/lounge, a poolside bar, or one of 2 bars/lounges. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Don’t miss out on the many recreational opportunities, including a health club, an outdoor pool, and a sauna. Additional features include concierge services, an arcade/game room, and gift shops/newsstands. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 317 air-conditioned rooms featuring private plunge pools. Kitchenettes are outfitted with refrigerators and microwaves. Premium TV channels and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and complimentary newspapers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>When you stay at Grand Lexis Port Dickson in Port Dickson, you'll be close to Fort Lukut. This 4.5-star resort is within the vicinity of Port Dickson Army Museum and Sri Anjeneayar. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Fort Lukut - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Port Dickson Army Museum - 8.2 km / 5.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sri Anjeneayar - 9 km / 5.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Admiral Cove Marina - 9.9 km / 6.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Port Dickson Ostrich Farm - 13.8 km / 8.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Port Dickson Mini Zoo - 15.1 km / 9.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cape Rachado Lighthouse - 17.1 km / 10.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Grand Lexis Port Dickson is Kuala Lumpur (KUL-Kuala Lumpur Intl.) - 25.4 km / 15.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Sauna</Code><Text>Sauna</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CoffeeTeaMaker</Code><Text>Tea and Coffee maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lift</Code><Text>Lift</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantAirconditioned</Code><Text>Restaurant Air-Conditioned</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WLANAccessPoint</Code><Text>WLAN Access Point</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>