<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11937194</Id><Name>Riad Marrakiss</Name><Region><Id>17562</Id><Name>Marrakech</Name><CityId>17562</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>DABACHI DERB MOULAY ABDELKADER 103</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>MARRAKECH</City><State /><Zip>40000</Zip><Country>MOROCCO</Country><Tel>00212650501172</Tel><Fax>00212524381886</Fax><Email>reservations.riad@marrakiss.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>31.628208</Latitude><Longitude>-7.985712</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Riad Marrakiss in Marrakech (Medina), you'll be minutes from Rahba Kedima and Jamaa el Fna. This riad is within close proximity of Souk Laghzel and Criee Berbere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 7 individually decorated guestrooms. Rooms have private patios. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Riad Marrakiss. Meet other guests and eat at a complimentary reception. A complimentary full breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, express check-out, and multilingual staff. Planning an event in Marrakech? This riad features 400 square feet (37 square meters) of event facilities. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed    Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Riad Marrakiss. Meet other guests and eat at a complimentary reception. A complimentary full breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 7 individually decorated guestrooms. Rooms have private patios. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected. Bathrooms have showers and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Riad Marrakiss in Marrakech (Medina), you'll be minutes from Rahba Kedima and Jamaa el Fna. This riad is within close proximity of Souk Laghzel and Criee Berbere. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Rahba Kedima - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Souk Laghzel - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Criee Berbere - 0.2 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Souk Zrabi - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Souk El Bahja - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Souk Smarine - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jamaa el Fna - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marrakesh Museum - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ben Youssef Madrasa - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Almoravid Koubba - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mouassine Mosque - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ben Youssef Mosque - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maison de la Photographie - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dar Tiskiwin Museum - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dar Si Said Museum - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Riad Marrakiss is Marrakech (RAK-Menara) - 4.6 km / 2.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MobilePhoneNetwork</Code><Text>Mobile Phone Network</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SunLounge</Code><Text>SunLounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parasol</Code><Text>Parasol</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SunBathingTerrace</Code><Text>Sun Bathing Terrace</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>