<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11937548</Id><Name>Riad Ailen</Name><Region><Id>17562</Id><Name>Marrakech</Name><CityId>17562</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>170 DERB EL MEJJAT HILANA BAB AILEN</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>MARRAKECH</City><State /><Zip>40000</Zip><Country>MOROCCO</Country><Tel>0660766563</Tel><Fax /><Email>info@riadailen.fr</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>31.61349</Latitude><Longitude>-7.97546</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The riad is very well situated in one of the last authentic districts of the Medina of Marrakesh. It is easily accessible with a guarded car park 100 m away. The parks surrounding the gate to the riad are just 5 minutes away by car and the inescapable Jeema El Fna square can be reached in 15 minutes by foot through the souks. Menara Airport is approximately 15 km away from the establishment.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>This small riad consists of 4 rooms and was recently renewed with simplicity and taste. The property offers guests accommodation with all modern comforts. Rooms come with a private shower room and are equipped with reversible air conditioning units and a safe. A self-service Internet point and wireless Internet access, as well as satellite television are also provided. Further standard features include tea and coffee making facilities and a double bed.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DiningFacilities</Type><Text>In this riad everything is made so that the intimacy of the customers is protected. The atmosphere is restful and there are so many places to meet to end the day, such as various small lounges, deckchairs on the terrace and the sofas under the Berber tent. The omnipresent but discreet members of staff are on hand to guarantee guests an even more pleasant stay. Further facilities available to guests include 24-hour reception and check-out services and a TV lounge, as well as a restaurant and Internet access in public areas. A laundry service is also provided.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>CoffeeTeaMaker</Code><Text>Tea and Coffee maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndoorPool</Code><Text>Indoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVRoom</Code><Text>TV Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MobilePhoneNetwork</Code><Text>Mobile Phone Network</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomTerraceBalcony</Code><Text>Terrace or balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>