<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11938436</Id><Name>Karam Palace</Name><Region><Id>17564</Id><Name>Ouarzazate</Name><CityId>17564</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>ZONE HOTELIERE AVENUE MY RACHID</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>OUARZAZATE</City><State /><Zip>45000</Zip><Country>MOROCCO</Country><Tel>00212524882522</Tel><Fax>00212524882522</Fax><Email>com.hng@gmail.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>30.920096</Latitude><Longitude>-6.904972</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Overview
Hotel Karam Palace -a four stars establishment- was built in the traditional southern Moroccan architectural style. You will enjoy its green spaces and refreshing swimming pool. Its terrace, overlooking Ourzazate`s valley, offers amazing views of the picturesque surrounding landscape. A true oasis, offering all the comfort of a four stars hotels in the middle of the desert.

Location
The hotel is located in downtown Ouarzazate, in the tourist area and next to many hotels. Nearby areas of interest can be reached easily and include Kasbat Taourirte (10-minute walk), Kasbat Tifoultout (15-minute drive) and Kasbat Ait Ben Haddou (30-minute drive). The Ouarzazate Airport is a 15-minute drive from the hotel.

Rooms
Each room is fitted with bathroom, air conditioning and heating, telephone, satellite TV, and mini bar.

Food &amp; Drink
Hotel Karam Palace has two restaurants: La Kasbah international restaurant, which has various specialities on offer, either as part of a self-service buffet or chosen from an a la carte menu and The Douria – a Moroccan restaurant. La Taourirte is a poolside snack bar open in summer, offering refreshments and a choice of light meals a la carte.

Tourist Information
Kasbat Taourirte - 10 min walk
Kasbat Tifoultout - 15 minute drive
Ouarzazate Airport - 15 min drive</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>