<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11945806</Id><Name>Madikwe Safari Lodge</Name><Region><Id>18263</Id><Name>Madikwe Game Reserve</Name><CityId>18263</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>MADIKWE GAME RESERVE</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>SUN CITY MADIKWE</City><State /><Zip /><Country>SOUTH AFRICA</Country><Tel>0027118809992</Tel><Fax>0027118809992</Fax><Email>res@madikwesafarilodge.co.za</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>-24.7604347</Latitude><Longitude>26.2777073</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You'll be in a national park with a stay at Madikwe Safari Lodge in Madikwe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Treat yourself to a stay in one of the 20 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring fireplaces and private plunge pools. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and minibars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You can experience a safari adventure. This lodge also features complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and gift shops/newsstands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;This lodge is all inclusive. Rates include meals and beverages at onsite dining establishments. Charges may be applied for dining at some restaurants, special dinners and dishes, some beverages, and other amenities. &lt;p&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Madikwe Safari Lodge. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary full breakfast is served daily. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include multilingual staff, luggage storage, and laundry facilities. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; This lodge is all inclusive. Rates include meals and beverages at onsite dining establishments. Charges may be applied for dining at some restaurants, special dinners and dishes, some beverages, and other amenities. &lt;p&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Madikwe Safari Lodge. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. A complimentary full breakfast is served daily. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; You can experience a safari adventure. This lodge also features complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and gift shops/newsstands. &lt;br /&gt; Treat yourself to a stay in one of the 20 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring fireplaces and private plunge pools. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and minibars.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>You'll be in a national park with a stay at Madikwe Safari Lodge in Madikwe. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Pilanesberg National Park - 90.5 km / 56.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Lost City - 96 km / 59.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wondergat - 134.7 km / 83.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kgaswane Mountain Reserve - 135.3 km / 84.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mafikeng Game Reserve - 144.5 km / 89.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mega City Shopping Mall - 145.2 km / 90.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Madikwe Safari Lodge is Johannesburg (JNB-O.R. Tambo Intl.) - 239.6 km / 148.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>