<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11944602</Id><Name>Nadmorski</Name><Region><Id>17962</Id><Name>Gdansk</Name><CityId>17962</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>EJSMONDA 2</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>GDYNIA</City><State /><Zip>81409</Zip><Country>POLAND</Country><Tel>0048586677777</Tel><Fax>0048586677700</Fax><Email>HOTEL@NADMORSKI.PL</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>54.505657</Latitude><Longitude>18.554519</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Hotel Nadmorski places you in the heart of Gdynia, convenient to Gdynia Planetarium and Danuta Baduszkowa Music Theatre.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Pomeranian Science and Technology Park and Gdynia Marina.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 90 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and minibars. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, and LCD televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment. Bathrooms feature bathtubs or showers, complimentary toiletries, and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with onsite massages, body treatments, and facials. If you're looking for recreational opportunities, you'll find a nightclub, outdoor tennis courts, and indoor tennis courts. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and gift shops/newsstands. Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the area shuttle (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite at one of the hotel's 3 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, a computer station, and express check-out. Event facilities at this hotel consist of a conference center and meeting rooms. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and self parking (subject to charges) is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite at one of the hotel's 3 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with onsite massages, body treatments, and facials. If you're looking for recreational opportunities, you'll find a nightclub, outdoor tennis courts, and indoor tennis courts. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and gift shops/newsstands. Guests can catch a ride to nearby destinations on the area shuttle (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 90 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and minibars. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, and LCD televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment. Bathrooms feature bathtubs or showers, complimentary toiletries, and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Hotel Nadmorski places you in the heart of Gdynia, convenient to Gdynia Planetarium and Danuta Baduszkowa Music Theatre.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Pomeranian Science and Technology Park and Gdynia Marina. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Gdynia Planetarium - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Danuta Baduszkowa Music Theatre - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Pomeranian Science and Technology Park - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gdynia Marina - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gdynia Aquarium - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Blyskawica Museum Ship - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kosciuszki Square - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Experyment Science Centre - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;GOSiR Stadium - 2.1 km / 1.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Orlowo Beach - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Zeromski House - 2.7 km / 1.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Orlowo Pier - 2.8 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kolibki Adventure Park - 4.6 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aquapark Sopot - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tricity Landscape Park - 5.4 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Nadmorski is Gdansk (GDN-Lech Walesa) - 14.9 km / 9.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CloakRoom</Code><Text>Cloak Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WLANAccessPoint</Code><Text>WLAN Access Point</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccessible</Code><Text>Wheelchair Accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>