<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11945815</Id><Name>Kubu Safari Lodge</Name><Region><Id>18259</Id><Name>Kruger National Park</Name><CityId>18259</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>ARGYLE ROAD</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>HOEDSPRUIT</City><State /><Zip /><Country>SOUTH AFRICA</Country><Tel>157933813</Tel><Fax>157933813</Fax><Email>fintail@iafrica.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>-24.3816219</Latitude><Longitude>31.08324495</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The hotel is situated near Hoedspruit, Limpopo province, equally distant to the world renowned Kruger National Park and the Drakensberg mountains. Famous holiday destinations, such as the Blyde River Canyon and the panorama route are in close vicinity. The new corridor and border gate to Mozambique via Kruger Park and Massingir Dam offer great opportunities for bush and beach combinations. At roughly 6 km, there is direct access to Hoedspruit Airport with two flights per day from OR Tambo International Airport (approximately 450 km away). Nelspruit Airport is around 180 km from the hotel.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>All rooms are uniquely designed in a warm African style and colour enhanced by German craftsmanship and the extensive use of natural materials such as thatch, reed and wood. They are equipped with modern en suite facilities offering every comfort. The unique set-up of the entire lodge, with a star shaped distribution of the chalets around the main entertainment area, allows the visitors to experience a true 'back to nature' feeling. Secluded verandas with each room overlooking the Bushveld or the majestic escarpment offer peace and tranquillity to observe frequently roaming game or the abundance of birdlife. All rooms come equipped with a shower, hairdryer, safe, tea and coffee making facilities, an ironing set and a terrace.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DiningFacilities</Type><Text>Set amidst indigenous Bushveld and vegetation adjacent to the Kruger National Park, the hotel offers warm hospitality, exceptional close wildlife encounters, dedicated service and superb cuisine. It is a privately owned hotel, where emphasis is placed on detail and personal attention. Renovated in 2010, the lodge features 35 spacious twin rooms and 5 family suites. Facilities on offer to guests include a lobby, hotel safe, currency exchange facilities, a TV lounge, bar, dining room and conference facilities. Guests may also take advantage of the Internet access, laundry service and car park.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>CoffeeTeaMaker</Code><Text>Tea and Coffee maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HandicapAccessible</Code><Text>Handicap accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MoneyExchange</Code><Text>Money exchange</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVRoom</Code><Text>TV Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DiningRoom</Code><Text>Dining Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SunLounge</Code><Text>SunLounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parasol</Code><Text>Parasol</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SunBathingTerrace</Code><Text>Sun Bathing Terrace</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomTerraceBalcony</Code><Text>Terrace or balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccessible</Code><Text>Wheelchair Accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>