<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11948953</Id><Name>Domaine de Chateauvieux</Name><Region><Id>18612</Id><Name>Geneva</Name><CityId>18612</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>PENEY DESSUS</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>SATIGNY</City><State /><Zip>1242</Zip><Country>SWITZERLAND</Country><Tel>0041227531511</Tel><Fax>0041227531924</Fax><Email>reservation@chateauvieux.ch</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>46.2015489</Latitude><Longitude>6.0386384</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Satigny (Peney-Dessus), Domaine De Chateauvieux is close to Microcosm and CERN.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Serves Golf Club and Vivarium de Meyrin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 13 guestrooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Cable television is provided for your entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. This hotel also features gift shops/newsstands and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves lunch and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets allowed    Check-in time starts at 4 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves lunch and dinner, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. This hotel also features gift shops/newsstands and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 13 guestrooms featuring minibars and flat-screen televisions. Cable television is provided for your entertainment.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Satigny (Peney-Dessus), Domaine De Chateauvieux is close to Microcosm and CERN.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Serves Golf Club and Vivarium de Meyrin. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Microcosm - 3.6 km / 2.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;CERN - 3.7 km / 2.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Serves Golf Club - 4.1 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vivarium de Meyrin - 4.3 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Adventure Park Evaux - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Alpine Garden - 4.4 km / 2.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Forum Meyrin Theatre - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Meyrin Commercial Centre - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Franchises Park - 6.1 km / 3.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Golf Club de Domaine de Gonville - 6.2 km / 3.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;La Parfumerie Theatre - 7.1 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palexpo - 7.1 km / 4.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Trembley Park - 7.2 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vernets Sports Centre - 7.2 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stade de Geneve - 7.3 km / 4.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Domaine De Chateauvieux is Geneva International Airport (GVA) - 6.2 km / 3.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>