<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11945801</Id><Name>The Executive Hotel - Midrand</Name><Region><Id>18255</Id><Name>Johannesburg</Name><CityId>18255</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>GALLAGHER AVENUE, MIDRAND 31</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>JOHANNESBURG</City><State /><Zip>6085</Zip><Country>SOUTH AFRICA</Country><Tel>0027110219115</Tel><Fax>0027865910790</Fax><Email>reservations@midrandexecutivehotel.co.za</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>-26.001373</Latitude><Longitude>28.126883</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You'll be centrally located in Johannesburg with a stay at Executive Hotel Midrand, minutes from Gallagher Convention Centre. This hotel is within the region of South African Lippizaner Centre and Modderfontein Golf Club.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 108 air-conditioned rooms featuring LCD televisions. Your Select Comfort bed comes with down comforters. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and complimentary toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Executive Hotel Midrand, or find a snack in a coffee shop/café. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a business center, and a computer station. Planning an event in Johannesburg? This hotel has 344 square feet (32 square meters) of space consisting of a conference center and a meeting room. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; You can enjoy a meal at a restaurant serving the guests of Executive Hotel Midrand, or find a snack in a coffee shop/café. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities, which include complimentary wireless Internet access and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 108 air-conditioned rooms featuring LCD televisions. Your Select Comfort bed comes with down comforters. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have showers and complimentary toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>You'll be centrally located in Johannesburg with a stay at Executive Hotel Midrand, minutes from Gallagher Convention Centre. This hotel is within the region of South African Lippizaner Centre and Modderfontein Golf Club. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Gallagher Convention Centre - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;South African Lippizaner Centre - 8.2 km / 5.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Modderfontein Golf Club - 11.5 km / 7.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Madame Zingara Theatre of Dreams - 11.6 km / 7.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Montecasino - 11.8 km / 7.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Morningside Mediclinic - 12.3 km / 7.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Greenstone Shopping Centre - 13 km / 8.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Johannesburg Stock Exchange - 13 km / 8.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sandton Convention Centre - 13.6 km / 8.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Nelson Mandela Square - 13.6 km / 8.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sandton City - 13.9 km / 8.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mediclinic Sandton - 14.2 km / 8.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Festival Mall - 14.6 km / 9.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kempton Park Golf Club - 14.9 km / 9.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Melrose Arch Shopping Centre - 15.4 km / 9.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Executive Hotel Midrand is Johannesburg (JNB-O.R. Tambo Intl.) - 17.6 km / 10.9 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>