<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11945153</Id><Name>Boulevard 44 Boutique Hotel</Name><Region><Id>18238</Id><Name>Ballito</Name><CityId>18238</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>LEE BARNS BOULEVARD, UMHLALIi, BALITO</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Umhlali</City><State /><Zip>4418</Zip><Country>SOUTH AFRICA</Country><Tel>032 947 1660</Tel><Fax>0867438771</Fax><Email>gm@boulevard44.co.za</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>-29.50745477</Latitude><Longitude>31.20066374</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Boulevard 44 Boutique Hotel in Umhlali, you'll be connected to the airport and close to Thompson's Bay Beach.  This family-friendly aparthotel is within the region of Ballito Beach and Casuarina Beach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 38 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring espresso makers and LCD televisions. Your Select Comfort bed comes with down comforters and Frette Italian sheets. Rooms have private patios. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Partially open bathrooms with showers feature designer toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a garden. Additional features at this Edwardian aparthotel include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare, and wedding services. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the aparthotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner. Dining is also available at a coffee shop/café, and room service (during limited hours) is provided. Meet other guests and eat at a complimentary reception. Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, express check-in, and express check-out. Planning an event in Umhlali? This aparthotel has 1615 square feet (150 square meters) of space consisting of conference space, meeting rooms, and a meeting room. For a surcharge, guests may use a roundtrip airport shuttle (available 24 hours) and a cruise ship terminal shuttle.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2:30 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the aparthotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner. Dining is also available at a coffee shop/café, and room service (during limited hours) is provided. Meet other guests and eat at a complimentary reception. Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a poolside bar. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy recreation amenities such as an outdoor pool or take in the view from a garden. Additional features at this Edwardian aparthotel include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare, and wedding services. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the area shuttle (surcharge). &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 38 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring espresso makers and LCD televisions. Your Select Comfort bed comes with down comforters and Frette Italian sheets. Rooms have private patios. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Partially open bathrooms with showers feature designer toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Boulevard 44 Boutique Hotel in Umhlali, you'll be connected to the airport and close to Thompson's Bay Beach.  This family-friendly aparthotel is within the region of Ballito Beach and Casuarina Beach. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Thompson's Bay Beach - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ballito Beach - 7.6 km / 4.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Casuarina Beach - 13 km / 8.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;King Shaka Memorial - 17 km / 10.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Umdloti Beach - 23.7 km / 14.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Umhlanga Lagoon Nature Trail - 28.9 km / 18 mi &lt;br /&gt;Umhlanga Rocks Beach - 29.4 km / 18.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Umhlanga Lighthouse - 30.6 km / 19 mi &lt;br /&gt;Zinkwazi Beach - 30.7 km / 19.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gateway Shopping Centre - 31.3 km / 19.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Umhlanga Hospital - 31.4 km / 19.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Harold Johnson Nature Reserve - 35.8 km / 22.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Beachwood Mangroves Nature Reserve - 40.6 km / 25.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Umgeni River Bird Park - 41.5 km / 25.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Windsor Park Golf Course - 41.8 km / 26 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Boulevard 44 Boutique Hotel is Hluhluwe (HLW) - 192 km / 119.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>CoffeeTeaMaker</Code><Text>Tea and Coffee maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CloakRoom</Code><Text>Cloak Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Pub</Code><Text>Pub</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DiningRoom</Code><Text>Dining Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantAirconditioned</Code><Text>Restaurant Air-Conditioned</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant Smoking Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MobilePhoneNetwork</Code><Text>Mobile Phone Network</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WLANAccessPoint</Code><Text>WLAN Access Point</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BicycleStorage</Code><Text>Bicycle Storage</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Playground</Code><Text>Playground</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>NumberOfPool</Code><Text>Number Of Pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HeatedPool</Code><Text>Heated Pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SunLounge</Code><Text>SunLounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SatelliteTV</Code><Text>Satellite TV</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndividualAirCondition</Code><Text>IndividualAirCondition</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomTerraceBalcony</Code><Text>Terrace or balcony</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Freenewspaper</Code><Text>Free Newspaper</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BreakfastRoom</Code><Text>Breakfast room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>