<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>119534</Id><Name>Ceilidh-Donia Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52867</Id><Name>Edinburgh City</Name><CityId>52507</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>MARCHHALL CRESCENT</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>EDINBURGH</City><State /><Zip>EH16 5HL</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>0131 6672743</Tel><Fax>0131 6682181</Fax><Email>RESERVATIONS@HOTELCEILIDH-DONIA.CO.UK</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>13</CountRooms><CountFloors>3</CountFloors></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1001/24824hotel1.jpg</Url><Width>320</Width><Height>313</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1001/24824hotel1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>71</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1678</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1001/24824room1.jpg</Url><Width>318</Width><Height>320</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1001/24824room1.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>69</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1668</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Hotel Ceilidh-Donia - Townhouse Hotel in Edinburgh (Newington), you'll be convenient to Royal Commonwealth Pool and Arthur's Seat. This hotel is close to Greyfriars Kirk and Palace of Holyroodhouse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 17 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring MP3 docking stations and flat-screen televisions. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while DVD players and digital programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature designer toiletries and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and complimentary newspapers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hotel Ceilidh-Donia - Townhouse Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;The front desk is staffed during limited hours. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 10 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Hotel Ceilidh-Donia - Townhouse Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a rooftop terrace and a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 17 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring MP3 docking stations and flat-screen televisions. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while DVD players and digital programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature designer toiletries and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and complimentary newspapers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Hotel Ceilidh-Donia - Townhouse Hotel in Edinburgh (Newington), you'll be convenient to Royal Commonwealth Pool and Arthur's Seat. This hotel is close to Greyfriars Kirk and Palace of Holyroodhouse. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Royal Commonwealth Pool - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;National Library of Scotland - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Holyrood Park - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Queen's Hall - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Carlton Cricket Club - 1.4 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;George Square - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Surgeon's Hall - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Meadows - 1.5 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;University of Edinburgh - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Potterrow Student Centre - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Festival Theatre - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Arthur's Seat - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Our Dynamic Earth - 1.7 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Talbot Rice Gallery - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Scottish Parliament - 1.8 km / 1.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Hotel Ceilidh-Donia - Townhouse Hotel is Edinburgh (EDI) - 12.3 km / 7.6 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>PublicInternetAccess</Code><Text>Public internet access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestuarantHighChair</Code><Text>Restuarant High Chair</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MobilePhoneNetwork</Code><Text>Mobile Phone Network</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomPrivateBathroom</Code><Text>Private bathrooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>DoubleBeds</Code><Text>Double Beds</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>KingSizeBeds</Code><Text>KingSizeBeds</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomCentralHeating</Code><Text>Central heating in room</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>