<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11971140</Id><Name>Oriental Siam Resort</Name><Region><Id>18727</Id><Name>Chiang Mai</Name><CityId>18727</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>40/1 Moo2.    Tambon Tasala,</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Chiang Mai</City><State /><Zip>50000</Zip><Country>Thailand</Country><Tel>66-53-851-189</Tel><Fax>66-53-851-022</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>18.7685</Latitude><Longitude>99.0426</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at The Oriental Siam Resort in Chiang Mai (Tha Sala), you'll be convenient to Chiang Mai Promenada and Bangkok Hospital. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Chiengmai Gymkhana Club and Nong Hoi Market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 14 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and DVD players. Rooms have private balconies. LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities including an outdoor pool and a fitness center. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and a hair salon. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the complimentary area shuttle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite at one of the hotel's 2 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a computer station, express check-in, and dry cleaning/laundry services. A roundtrip airport shuttle is complimentary (available on request).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite at one of the hotel's 2 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Be sure to enjoy recreational amenities including an outdoor pool and a fitness center. Additional amenities include complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare (surcharge), and a hair salon. Getting to nearby attractions is a breeze with the complimentary area shuttle. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 14 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and DVD players. Rooms have private balconies. LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with separate bathtubs and showers feature complimentary toiletries and hair dryers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at The Oriental Siam Resort in Chiang Mai (Tha Sala), you'll be convenient to Chiang Mai Promenada and Bangkok Hospital. This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Chiengmai Gymkhana Club and Nong Hoi Market. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Chiang Mai Promenada - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bangkok Hospital - 2.9 km / 1.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chiengmai Gymkhana Club - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Nong Hoi Market - 3.8 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Meng Memorial Bridge - 4.1 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bo Sang - 4.1 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wiang Kum Kam - 4.6 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Central Chiang Mai Memorial Hospital - 4.6 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chiang Mai Night Bazaar - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Elephant Parade House - 4.9 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Wat Gatekaram - 4.9 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Warorot Market - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tha Phae Gate - 5.6 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Thepanya Hospital - 5.7 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Chiang Mai Gate - 5.8 km / 3.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for The Oriental Siam Resort is Chiang Mai (CNX-Chiang Mai Intl.) - 7.8 km / 4.8 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BeautyShop</Code><Text>Beauty Shop</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>