<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>119757</Id><Name>Carnoustie Hotel</Name><Region><Id>52354</Id><Name>Angus</Name><CityId>52354</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>THE LINKS</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>CARNOUSTIE</City><State /><Zip>DD7 7JE</Zip><Country>UNITED KINGDOM</Country><Tel>0843 178 7109</Tel><Fax>00441241411998</Fax><Email>reservations.carnoustie@ohiml.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>56.4988</Latitude><Longitude>-2.7136</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/CARN-CARhotel_Exterior_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>239</Height><Bytes>12556</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/CARN-CARhotel_Exterior_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1744</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/CARN-CARhotel_Suite_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>239</Height><Bytes>15311</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/CARN-CARhotel_Suite_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1997</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/CARN-CARhotel_Restaurant_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>241</Height><Bytes>20152</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/CARN-CARhotel_Restaurant_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2298</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/CARN-CARhotel_Swimming_Pool_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>249</Height><Bytes>19638</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/CARN-CARhotel_Swimming_Pool_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2329</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>SwimmingPool</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/CARN-CARhotel_Meeting_Room_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>239</Height><Bytes>19934</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/CARN-CARhotel_Meeting_Room_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2412</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Carnoustie Golf Hotel in Carnoustie, you'll be next to a golf course and minutes from Carnoustie Golf Links. This 4-star hotel is within the region of Tentsmuir Forest and Claypotts Castle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Stay in one of 85 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have shower/tub combinations and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages and body treatments. You're sure to appreciate the recreational amenities, including an indoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Carnoustie Golf Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services, a 24-hour front desk, and laundry facilities. Planning an event in Carnoustie? This hotel has 11330 square feet (1053 square meters) of space consisting of conference space and meeting rooms. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a satisfying meal at a restaurant serving guests of Carnoustie Golf Hotel. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages and body treatments. You're sure to appreciate the recreational amenities, including an indoor pool, a spa tub, and a sauna. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Stay in one of 85 guestrooms featuring flat-screen televisions. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and digital programming is available for your entertainment. Bathrooms have shower/tub combinations and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as desks and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Carnoustie Golf Hotel in Carnoustie, you'll be next to a golf course and minutes from Carnoustie Golf Links. This 4-star hotel is within the region of Tentsmuir Forest and Claypotts Castle. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Carnoustie Golf Links - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tentsmuir Forest - 10.8 km / 6.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Claypotts Castle - 10.9 km / 6.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Arbroath Abbey - 10.9 km / 6.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Vigean's Church - 11.7 km / 7.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;HMS Unicorn - 15.4 km / 9.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tannadice Park - 15.7 km / 9.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dens Park - 16 km / 9.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;City Square - 16.1 km / 10 mi &lt;br /&gt;Minnie the Minx Statue - 16.1 km / 10 mi &lt;br /&gt;Desperate Dan Statue - 16.1 km / 10 mi &lt;br /&gt;McManus Galleries and Museum - 16.1 km / 10 mi &lt;br /&gt;Discovery Point - 16.2 km / 10 mi &lt;br /&gt;Howff Burial Ground - 16.3 km / 10.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Paul's Episcopal Cathedral - 16.3 km / 10.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Carnoustie Golf Hotel is Dundee (DND) - 19.9 km / 12.3 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DrivingDirections</Type><Text>The preferred airport for Carnoustie Golf Hotel is Dundee (DND) - 19.8 km / 12.3 mi. &lt;p&gt;Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or airport and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometre. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Sauna</Code><Text>Sauna</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarRentDesk</Code><Text>Car rental desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarPark</Code><Text>Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TrouserPress</Code><Text>Trouser press</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shops</Code><Text>Shops</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>