<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>119796</Id><Name>Skene House Rosemount</Name><Region><Id>52841</Id><Name>Aberdeen City</Name><CityId>52342</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>ROSEMOUNT VIADUCT</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>ABERDEEN</City><State /><Zip>AB251NX</Zip><Country>United Kingdom</Country><Tel>00441224645971</Tel><Fax>00441224626866</Fax><Email>rosemount@skene-house.co.uk</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>61</CountRooms><CountFloors>3</CountFloors><CountSuites>61</CountSuites></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1033/10/84/78/8/GsWqzyXu_cc9d95d47dadc26b499d9fe1ab9b9995.jpg</Url><Width>800</Width><Height>583</Height><Bytes>73164</Bytes><Caption>GsWqzyXu_cc9d95d47dadc26b499d9fe1ab9b9995</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1033/10/84/78/8/GsWqzyXu_cc9d95d47dadc26b499d9fe1ab9b9995thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>96</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2116</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1033/10/84/78/8/pSkhhoQS_7671ffe5d780efa03af60bb3d993d304.jpg</Url><Width>722</Width><Height>576</Height><Bytes>45264</Bytes><Caption>pSkhhoQS_7671ffe5d780efa03af60bb3d993d304</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1033/10/84/78/8/pSkhhoQS_7671ffe5d780efa03af60bb3d993d304thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>87</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2196</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Skene House HotelSuites-Rosemount, you'll be centrally located in Aberdeen, steps from His Majesty's Theatre and minutes from St. Mary's Roman Catholic Cathedral. This 4-star apartment is within close proximity of Union Terrace Gardens and Robert Gordon University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 98 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and microwaves. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access is available. Conveniences include phones, as well as separate sitting areas and coffee/tea makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare, and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at one of the apartment's 1 restaurants. A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a business center, a computer station, and complimentary newspapers in the lobby. Event facilities at this apartment consist of a conference center and meeting rooms. Free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at one of the apartment's 1 restaurants. A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Make use of convenient amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare, and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 98 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and microwaves. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access is available. Conveniences include phones, as well as separate sitting areas and coffee/tea makers.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Skene House HotelSuites-Rosemount, you'll be centrally located in Aberdeen, steps from His Majesty's Theatre and minutes from St. Mary's Roman Catholic Cathedral. This 4-star apartment is within close proximity of Union Terrace Gardens and Robert Gordon University. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;His Majesty's Theatre - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Mary's Roman Catholic Cathedral - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Union Terrace Gardens - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Robert Gordon University - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Belmont Picturehouse - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aberdeen Music Hall - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Academy - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bon-Accord Centre - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mall Trinity - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aberdeen Art Gallery - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Nicholas Centre - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Provost Skene's House - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aberdeen College - 0.7 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Marischal Museum - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Victoria Park - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Skene House HotelSuites-Rosemount is Aberdeen (ABZ) - 8.1 km / 5 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>