<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>119768</Id><Name>Argyll</Name><Region><Id>52356</Id><Name>Argyll &amp; Bute</Name><CityId>52356</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>FRONT STREET</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>INVERARAY</City><State /><Zip>PA32 8XB</Zip><Country>UNITED KINGDOM</Country><Tel>00441499302466</Tel><Fax>00441499302389</Fax><Email>reservations.argyll@ohiml.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>56.2317</Latitude><Longitude>-5.074</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/INVE-ARGhotel_Exterior_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/INVE-ARGhotel_Exterior_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/INVE-ARGhotel_Guest_Room_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>239</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/INVE-ARGhotel_Guest_Room_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/INVE-ARGhotel_Restaurant_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>240</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/INVE-ARGhotel_Restaurant_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/INVE-ARGhotel_Bar_Lounge_1.jpg</Url><Width>239</Width><Height>360</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/INVE-ARGhotel_Bar_Lounge_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>60</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>80</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Designed in 1750 by the famous Scottish builder John Adam, the Argyll Hotel was originally built to accommodate guests to Inveraray Castle. The hotel is an ideal base from which to explore the Western Highlands and Islands, with many attractions such as the historic Inveraray Castle, Inverarary Jail and Courthouse and the Arctic Penguin Maritime Museum all nearby.  (GW 09/2008)</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The hotel is very centrally located overlooking the Loch. The hotel is the ideal base for touring the beautiful countryside of the Western Highlands and Islands. There are many local attractions to choose from, including the historic Inveraray Castle, or simply marvel at the incredible scenery. The hotel is located just an hours drive from Oban and bout 90 minutes from Glasgow City and Airport which are to the South.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>All 36 bedrooms are en-suite and many offer guests stunning views over Loch Fyne. Each of the hotel's well appointed en-suite bedrooms has colour television, direct dial telephone, hair dryer and tea and coffee making facilities. Rooms are traditionally decorated to a good standard - Providing a cosy Scottish stay.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PropertyInformation</Type><Text>Traditional white building, originally designed and built in the 18th Century. The main house is set over 3 floors and provides car parking for guests.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DiningFacilities</Type><Text>The Argyll Restaurant offers an a la carte menu with an excellent selection of quality local produce whilst representing value for money combined with thoughtful presentation and great care with textures and flavours.The Argyll Bar has a huge selection of draught and bottled beers, malt whiskies and wine, normally accompanied with some local "craik!" .  The Lounge bar  - with its traditional Bar menu &amp; daily specials board - still maintains the high standards set in presentation and flavour. Both bars have wonderful leather sofas to melt into with the added comfort of a real coal fire!</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>Short</Type><Text>Medium sized reception area with seating for guests.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>