<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11983451</Id><Name>Phuphaya Seaview Resort</Name><Region><Id>18776</Id><Name>Phi Phi Island</Name><CityId>18776</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>9/1 Moo 7, T. Ao-Nang, Muang</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Phi Phi Island</City><State /><Zip>81000</Zip><Country>Thailand</Country><Tel>66 075 601 145</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>8.1673</Latitude><Longitude>98.8804</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Phuphaya Seaview Resort in Ko Phi Phi, you'll be convenient to Ko Phi Phi Viewpoint and Loh Bagao Beach. This hotel is within close proximity of Ao Ton Sai Beach and Ko Phi Phi Pier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 25 guestrooms. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of room service (during limited hours). Continental breakfasts are available daily for a fee. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 25 guestrooms. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access is available to keep you connected.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Phuphaya Seaview Resort in Ko Phi Phi, you'll be convenient to Ko Phi Phi Viewpoint and Loh Bagao Beach. This hotel is within close proximity of Ao Ton Sai Beach and Ko Phi Phi Pier. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Ko Phi Phi Viewpoint - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Loh Bagao Beach - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ao Ton Sai Beach - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ko Phi Phi Pier - 1.4 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Long Beach - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Laem Tong Beach - 3.3 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Viking Cave - 6.5 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Maya Beach - 7.9 km / 4.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Miracle Beach - 23.4 km / 14.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ko Jum Beach - 23.5 km / 14.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tup Island - 23.7 km / 14.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Phra Nang Cave - 29.2 km / 18.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Phra Nang Beach - 29.3 km / 18.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;East Railay Beach - 29.3 km / 18.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Princess Lagoon - 29.3 km / 18.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Phuphaya Seaview Resort is Phuket (HKT-Phuket Intl.) - 65 km / 40.4 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>