<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>119910</Id><Name>The Crescent Townhouse</Name><Region><Id>52383</Id><Name>Belfast (and vicinity)</Name><CityId>52383</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>LOWER CRESCENT 13</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>BELFAST</City><State /><Zip>BT7 1NR</Zip><Country>UNITED KINGDOM</Country><Tel>00442890323349</Tel><Fax>00442890320646</Fax><Email>info@crescenttownhouse.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/BEL-BEShotel_Exterior_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>285</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/BEL-BEShotel_Exterior_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>This Belfast hotel is within walking distance of major historical landmarks, popular visitor attractions which include the Botanical Gardens and Titanic building, featuring galleries and exhibitions narrating the story of the world-famous ship. Guests can enjoy a variety of cultural attractions like the Ulster Museum, nightclubs, bars, and pubs within five minutes' walk. The Empire, one of the finest live music bars of the city, is only 100 yards away. The Odyssey is less than two miles from the hotel.

Business travelers with software companies and Callor Gas, as well as academics visiting Queens University, enjoy the easy blend of business and leisure. 

Reserve a room at the BEST WESTERN Crescent Townhouse for your next trip to Ireland!</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>The hotel is located opposite the Botanic Railway Station, offering convenient transport from the crossing between Lower Crescent and Botanic, connecting to the Central Station of Belfast and near the airport. The city airport lies only five miles away and the Ulster rugby ground is not far away. A recipient of the TripAdvisor Award for Excellence in 2013, this boutique hotel is renowned for the friendliness of staff.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>The hotel features traditionally decorated rooms with comfortable, modern amenities including a flat-screen TV and free Wi-Fi. The suites are decorated in traditional Victorian style fitted with dark Mahogany canopy beds, floral drapes, antique wing armchairs and a roll top bath and walk-in shower. A wide range of food is served at the hotel's restaurant, the AA Rosette award-winning Metro Kitchen, with specialties made with locally sourced ingredients. The Metro Bar offers a sample of the local nightlife with weekly live entertainment including musicians and comedians.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DiningFacilities</Type><Text>Fine dining on premises
 Metro Brasserie, on premises, full service, continental, open for: breakfast, dinner, seven days, European.
 Metro Bar, on premises, bar/lounge, continental, open for: lunch, seven days, European</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>CoffeeTeaMaker</Code><Text>Tea and Coffee maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TVInRoom</Code><Text>TV in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ReceptionArea</Code><Text>Reception Area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CheckIn24hr</Code><Text>24hr. CheckIn</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Reception24hr</Code><Text>24hr. Reception</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RestaurantNonSmokingArea</Code><Text>Restaurant - non-smoking area</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shower</Code><Text>Shower</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Carpeted</Code><Text>Carpeted</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Lounge</Code><Text>Lounge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bath</Code><Text>Bath</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TelephoneInRoom</Code><Text>Direct Dial Telephone</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RadioInRoom</Code><Text>Radio in room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccessible</Code><Text>Wheelchair Accessible</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BathRoom</Code><Text>Bath Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Heating</Code><Text>Heating</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurants</Code><Text>Restaurants</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>