<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>11990491</Id><Name>Purple Lotus Boutique Suites</Name><Region><Id>16839</Id><Name>Bengaluru (Bangalore)</Name><CityId>16839</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>46, 6th Cross, Lavelle Road</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Bengaluru</City><State /><Zip>560 001</Zip><Country>India</Country><Tel>91-80-4005-6300</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>12.9726</Latitude><Longitude>77.5992</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Purple Lotus places you in the heart of Bengaluru, walking distance from UB City and Visvesvaraya Industrial and Technological Museum.  This family-friendly hotel is within close proximity of St. Mark's Cathedral and Government Museum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 20 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Your Select Comfort bed comes with down comforters. Rooms have private balconies. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while 32-inch flat-screen televisions with cable programming provide entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Treat yourself with massages and body treatments. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare, and a television in the lobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner. Dining is also available at a coffee shop/café, and room service (during limited hours) is provided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a 24-hour business center, and limo/town car service. A train station pick-up service is provided at no charge (available 24 hours), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Satisfy your appetite at the hotel's restaurant, which serves breakfast, lunch, and dinner. Dining is also available at a coffee shop/café, and room service (during limited hours) is provided. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 15 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Treat yourself with massages and body treatments. This hotel also features complimentary wireless Internet access, babysitting/childcare, and a television in the lobby. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 20 individually decorated guestrooms, featuring kitchens with refrigerators and stovetops. Your Select Comfort bed comes with down comforters. Rooms have private balconies. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while 32-inch flat-screen televisions with cable programming provide entertainment.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Purple Lotus places you in the heart of Bengaluru, walking distance from UB City and Visvesvaraya Industrial and Technological Museum.  This family-friendly hotel is within close proximity of St. Mark's Cathedral and Government Museum. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;UB City - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Visvesvaraya Industrial and Technological Museum - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;St. Mark's Cathedral - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Government Museum - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sree Kanteerava Stadium - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;M. Chinnaswamy Stadium - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cubbon Park - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Brigade Road - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hindustan Aeronautics Ltd. Corporate Offices - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Garuda Mall - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cisco Systems Bengaluru - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Thomson Reuters Offices - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vikasa Soudha - 1.2 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Vidhana Soudha - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Commercial Street - 1.5 km / 0.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Purple Lotus is Bengaluru (BLR-Kempegowda Intl.) - 27.6 km / 17.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 15 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CurrencyExchangeService</Code><Text>Currency Exchange Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>