<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>12008596</Id><Name>Country Inn &amp; Suites By Carlson Mussoorie</Name><Region><Id>16908</Id><Name>Mussoorie</Name><CityId>16908</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Convent Rd, Near Library Chowk; Mussoorie, Uttaranchal</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Mussoorie</City><State /><Zip>248179</Zip><Country>India</Country><Tel>+91 (135) 263-5601</Tel><Fax>+91 (135) 263-2726</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>30.27</Latitude><Longitude>78.06</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Mussoorie, Country Inn &amp; Suites By Carlson Mussoorie is in the mountains and convenient to Gun Hill and Bhata Falls.  This family-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Municipal Garden and Jharipani Falls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 50 guestrooms featuring refrigerators and minibars. 32-inch LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature rainfall showerheads and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages and facials. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. For your convenience, a complimentary breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include a 24-hour business center, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and a 24-hour front desk. Planning an event in Mussoorie? This hotel has 2600 square feet (234 square meters) of space consisting of a conference center and conference space. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is Noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, which features a bar, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. For your convenience, a complimentary breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pamper yourself with a visit to the spa, which offers massages and facials. Additional features include complimentary wireless Internet access and wedding services. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 50 guestrooms featuring refrigerators and minibars. 32-inch LCD televisions with cable programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature rainfall showerheads and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Mussoorie, Country Inn &amp; Suites By Carlson Mussoorie is in the mountains and convenient to Gun Hill and Bhata Falls.  This family-friendly hotel is within close proximity of Municipal Garden and Jharipani Falls. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Gun Hill - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Bhata Falls - 1.6 km / 1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Municipal Garden - 3.2 km / 2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Jharipani Falls - 3.4 km / 2.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kempty Falls - 6 km / 3.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sahastradhara - 8.4 km / 5.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Forest Research Institute - 14.3 km / 8.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Clock Tower - 14.5 km / 9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Surkanda Devi Temple - 20.3 km / 12.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Country Inn &amp; Suites By Carlson Mussoorie is Dehradun (DED-Jolly Grant) - 30.8 km / 19.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ValetParking</Code><Text>Valet parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Sauna</Code><Text>Sauna</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Security24Hour</Code><Text>24-hour security</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ClothingIron</Code><Text>Clothing iron</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WakeUpService</Code><Text>Wake up service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CarRentDesk</Code><Text>Car rental desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CoffeeShop</Code><Text>Coffee shop</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Freenewspaper</Code><Text>Free Newspaper</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairAccess</Code><Text>Wheelchair access</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Shops</Code><Text>Shops</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CurrencyExchangeService</Code><Text>Currency Exchange Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ChildrensClub</Code><Text>Childrens Club</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>24HourFrontDesk</Code><Text>24 Hour Front Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MultilingualStaff</Code><Text>Multilingual Staff</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>