<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>120309</Id><Name>Burnside</Name><Region><Id>52929</Id><Name>Windermere</Name><CityId>52596</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>BOWNESS ON WINDERMERE</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>WINDERMERE</City><State /><Zip>LA23 3EP</Zip><Country>UNITED KINGDOM</Country><Tel>+44 1539442211</Tel><Fax>+44 1539443824</Fax><Email>reservations@burnsidehotel.com</Email><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><CountRooms>57</CountRooms><CountFloors>4</CountFloors><Latitude>54.359871</Latitude><Longitude>-2.92044</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CA/F5/34/90/0/CAF534900_0.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>17960</Bytes><Caption>Exterior view</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CA/F5/34/90/0/CAF534900_0thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>1845</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ExternalViewOfTheHotel</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CA/F5/34/90/0/CAF534900_1.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>27506</Bytes><Caption>Bar</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CA/F5/34/90/0/CAF534900_1thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2585</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/1030/CA/F5/34/90/0/CAF534900_2.jpg</Url><Width>400</Width><Height>300</Height><Bytes>22445</Bytes><Caption>Outdoor pool</Caption><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/1030/CA/F5/34/90/0/CAF534900_2thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>93</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>70</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>2280</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>ViewOfAGuestRoom</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>The 3-star Burnside Hotel offers excellent quality accommodation and facilities within a luscious landscape. Overlooking Lake Windermere the hotel is set within landscaped gardens within the Lake District National Park, designated an area of outstanding natural beauty. The surrounding area offers sailing and boat trips, walking and hiking paths and good quality golf courses. The hotel is furnished in a traditional country style with open fireplaces and homely wallpaper. Silhouettes restaurant offers a table d'hote menu featuring dishes made from seasonal produce. Chef's speciality dishes, finely crafted deserts and an excellent selection of fine wines make the restaurant a dining experience above the norm. For a more casual meal experience guests can grab a drink in Harleys Bar and try a Bistro meal at the adjoining eatery, The Bistro. The Parklands Country Club, part of the hotel, offers exemplary facilities conveniently within the hotel grounds. Guests are given complimentary access to the club and athletic types won't be disappointed by the range of sports facilities which include a fitness studio where guests can work out using the range of up to date gym equipment take a yoga or aerobics class, squash court and badminton hall or simply have a game of table tennis. The club also has a swimming pool, spa, sauna and steam room and a beauty salon offering a wide variety of treatments using Dermalogica products, including massages and a solarium. The club's lounge bar has two snooker tables, a pool table. With a viewing gallery overlooking the swimming pool, it serves snacks and drinks from 4pm to 9pm weekdays and 12pm to 9pm on weekends. The club also provides a soft play area for children. Standard rooms are well appointed with a comfortable bed and elegant furniture including a writing desk, armchair and wardrobe. Amenities include a television, telephone and security safe.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>RoomToiletries</Code><Text>Room Toiletries</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>