<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>120482779</Id><Name>Comfort Hotel LT - Rock 'N' Roll Vilnius</Name><Region><Id>17363</Id><Name>Vilnius</Name><CityId>17363</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Kauno Street.14</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Vilnius</City><State /><Zip /><Country>Lithuania</Country><Tel>01137052505111</Tel><Fax>01137068598920</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><CheckInTime>15</CheckInTime><CheckOutTime>12</CheckOutTime></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Comfort Hotel LT - Rock 'n' Roll Vilnius is a modern, music-themed hotel with its own rock radio. It offers free access to a 24-hour gym and free Wi-Fi. The Vilnius Old Town can be reached within a 10-minute walk.
All air-conditioned rooms at Comfort Hotel LT - Rock 'n' Roll Vilnius are decorated in a modern, urban style and feature a 32-inch flat-screen TV, an armchair and a table. The bathroom is fitted with heated floors and a hairdryer.
A healthy breakfast buffet is available every morning and the restaurant offers European cuisine by a famous Lithuanian chef. There is a lobby shop offering fresh snacks and beverages, such as free coffee and tea.
Guests can relax with a drink at the hotel’s bar and the hotel staff can arrange bicycle, tours and car rental. Hotel also offers underground parking. There are Apple computers available for the guests to use.
Comfort Hotel LT - Rock 'n' Roll Vilnius is situated 700 m from the Vilnius Train Station and Vilnius International Airport is only 4 km away. IKI Supermarket is located on the opposite side of the street, just 50 m away. 
Naujamiestis is a great choice for travelers interested in shopping, walking and ambiance.
This is our guests' favorite part of Vilnius, according to independent reviews.
This property is also rated for the best value in Vilnius! Guests are getting more for their money when compared to other properties in this city.</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>