<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>12056597</Id><Name>Hotel Zel</Name><Region><Id>18828</Id><Name>Antalya</Name><CityId>18828</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Liman Mah.baris Manco Cad. No:11 Konyaalti</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Antalya</City><State /><Zip>07070</Zip><Country>Turkey</Country><Tel>+90 242 3242257</Tel><Fax>-</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Zel Hotel in Antalya (Konyaalti Beach), you'll be close to Antalya Trade Port and Antalya Aquarium. This hotel is within close proximity of Minicity and Arapsu Bridge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 45 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy the recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool or make use of other amenities including babysitting/childcare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include dry cleaning/laundry services and a safe deposit box at the front desk.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt;  &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant, or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Quench your thirst with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy the recreation opportunities such as an outdoor pool or make use of other amenities including babysitting/childcare. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 45 air-conditioned rooms featuring minibars and LCD televisions. Rooms have private balconies. Complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming is available for your entertainment.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Zel Hotel in Antalya (Konyaalti Beach), you'll be close to Antalya Trade Port and Antalya Aquarium. This hotel is within close proximity of Minicity and Arapsu Bridge. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Antalya Trade Port - 2.6 km / 1.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Minicity - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Antalya Aquarium - 4.7 km / 2.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;Arapsu Bridge - 4.8 km / 3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Migros Shopping Center - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dolphin Park - 5 km / 3.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Aktur Lunapark - 5.1 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Konyaalti Beach Park - 5.2 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Konyaalti Open Air Theatre - 5.4 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cam Piramit - 5.5 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Glass Pyramid Congress and Exhibition Centre - 5.5 km / 3.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Akdeniz University - 5.7 km / 3.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Antalya Museum - 6.5 km / 4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Antalya Archeological Museum - 6.6 km / 4.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Yavuz Ozcan Park - 7.9 km / 4.9 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Zel Hotel is Antalya (AYT-Antalya Intl.) - 17.1 km / 10.6 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>InternetAccess</Code><Text>InternetAccess</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>