<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>120577428</Id><Name>Hotel Le Recif</Name><Region><Id>64801</Id><Name>Saint Gilles</Name><CityId>64801</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>50 Avenue de Bourbon</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Saint-Gilles</City><State /><Zip>97434</Zip><Country>Reunion</Country><Tel>+262 2 62 40 55 55</Tel><Fax>011262262212147</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><CheckInTime>14</CheckInTime><CheckOutTime>11</CheckOutTime></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Location
Situated right by the beach at Saint Gilles Les Bains, this family-friendly conference hotel is spread over a few hectares of land. Its location, just 1.5 km from the centre of St. Gilles, makes it easy to access facilities like public transportation, shops and restaurants, pubs and discos. The bus station is just 50 metres away and other nearby places of interest include the Piton de la Fournaise volcano (80 km away), Le Maido viewpoint (30 km away), the Cirque de Salazie volcanic cal
Facilities
The hotel was built in 2005. Guests are welcomed at the accommodation, which has a total of 146 rooms. In the air-conditioned establishment, travellers are welcomed at the reception area with 24-hour reception and a 24-hour check-in/check-out service. Amenities include a cloakroom and a safe. Wireless internet access in public areas allows guests to stay connected. Among the culinary options available at the hotel are a restaurant, a dining area, a breakfast room and a bar. Various shops are available, including a souvenir shop. There is also a garden. Those arriving in their own vehicles can leave them in the car park of the accommodation. Additional services include multilingual staff, a babysitting service and a laundry service. Active guests can make use of the bicycle hire service to explore the surrounding area.
Rooms
Rooms feature air conditioning, a living room and a bathroom. Most rooms feature a balcony with a view for guests' enjoyment. Many rooms feature a sea view, which further enhances the ambience. The rooms have a double bed and a sofa bed. A safe and a minibar are also available. Additional features include a fridge and a tea/coffee station. An ironing set is also available for travellers' convenience. Little extras, including internet access, a telephone, a TV, a radio and WiFi, contribute to a great stay. Slippers are laid out in each of the rooms. Some of the rooms are adapted for wheelchair users. The bathrooms are fitted with a shower and a bathtub. A hairdryer and bathrobes are provided for everyday use. Bathrooms with wheelchair access can also be booked. Special family rooms are available for families with children.
Sports/Entertainment
The establishment offers an outdoor pool and a children's pool. A terrace, a sun terrace, sun loungers and parasols are available. There is also a poolside snack bar. A variety of sporting activities are available at the hotel, for example tennis, bocce and beach volleyball, or for a fee, biking/mountain biking and golf. Water sports enthusiasts can enjoy snorkelling, diving and aquafit. Guests can take advantage of a wide range of indoor sports at the accommodation, including a gym, table tennis, badminton and aerobics. A wellness area with a hammam, massage treatments and a solarium is available at the establishment. Travellers of all ages have the opportunity to enjoy an interesting entertainment programme.
Meals
Catering options available at the hotel include bed and breakfast, half board and full board. Available meals include breakfast, lunch and dinner. Staff are also happy to provide special dietary cuisine. In addition, special catering options and snacks are available. Alcohol-free drinks and alcoholic beverages are offered.
Payment
The following credit cards are accepted at the accommodation: American Express, VISA and MasterCard.
Please note of Bed tax compulsory for each night spent at the hotel and payable by guests directly at the hotel.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Situated right by the beach at Saint Gilles Les Bains, this family-friendly conference hotel is spread over a few hectares of land. Its location, just 1.5 km from the centre of St. Gilles, makes it easy to access facilities like public transportation, shops and restaurants, pubs and discos. The bus station is just 50 metres away and other nearby places of interest include the Piton de la Fournaise volcano (80 km away), Le Maido viewpoint (30 km away), the Cirque de Salazie volcanic cal</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>Rooms feature air conditioning, a living room and a bathroom. Most rooms feature a balcony with a view for guests' enjoyment. Many rooms feature a sea view, which further enhances the ambience. The rooms have a double bed and a sofa bed. A safe and a minibar are also available. Additional features include a fridge and a tea/coffee station. An ironing set is also available for travellers' convenience. Little extras, including internet access, a telephone, a TV, a radio and WiFi, contribute to a great stay. Slippers are laid out in each of the rooms. Some of the rooms are adapted for wheelchair users. The bathrooms are fitted with a shower and a bathtub. A hairdryer and bathrobes are provided for everyday use. Bathrooms with wheelchair access can also be booked. Special family rooms are available for families with children.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PropertyInformation</Type><Text>The hotel was built in 2005. Guests are welcomed at the accommodation, which has a total of 146 rooms. In the air-conditioned establishment, travellers are welcomed at the reception area with 24-hour reception and a 24-hour check-in/check-out service. Amenities include a cloakroom and a safe. Wireless internet access in public areas allows guests to stay connected. Among the culinary options available at the hotel are a restaurant, a dining area, a breakfast room and a bar. Various shops are available, including a souvenir shop. There is also a garden. Those arriving in their own vehicles can leave them in the car park of the accommodation. Additional services include multilingual staff, a babysitting service and a laundry service. Active guests can make use of the bicycle hire service to explore the surrounding area.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>AreaActivities</Type><Text>The establishment offers an outdoor pool and a children's pool. A terrace, a sun terrace, sun loungers and parasols are available. There is also a poolside snack bar. A variety of sporting activities are available at the hotel, for example tennis, bocce and beach volleyball, or for a fee, biking/mountain biking and golf. Water sports enthusiasts can enjoy snorkelling, diving and aquafit. Guests can take advantage of a wide range of indoor sports at the accommodation, including a gym, table tennis, badminton and aerobics. A wellness area with a hammam, massage treatments and a solarium is available at the establishment. Travellers of all ages have the opportunity to enjoy an interesting entertainment programme.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DiningFacilities</Type><Text>Catering options available at the hotel include bed and breakfast, half board and full board. Available meals include breakfast, lunch and dinner. Staff are also happy to provide special dietary cuisine. In addition, special catering options and snacks are available. Alcohol-free drinks and alcoholic beverages are offered.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>The following credit cards are accepted at the accommodation: American Express, VISA and MasterCard.
Please note of Bed tax compulsory for each night spent at the hotel and payable by guests directly at the hotel.


*Please note of Bed tax compulsory for each night spent at the hotel and payable by guests directly at the hotel.*

***Special Note: Third adult in Junior Suite or Superior is on a sofa bed or rollaway***


*For Honeymoon rooms, a copy of the Wedding/Civil Partnership certificate must be sent to the Reservation department as part of the booking procedure.
Wedding/Civil Partnership certificate must not exceed 9 months from date of issue at time of travel and will be required at check-in.*


***Special Note: 3rd adult on a sleeper sofa in Superior room and Junior Suite room types***</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>