<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>120521516</Id><Name>W Punta de Mita</Name><Region><Id>17513</Id><Name>Puerto Vallarta</Name><CityId>17513</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Kilometro 8.5 Carretera a Punta de Mita</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Puerto Vallarta</City><State /><Zip>63734</Zip><Country>Mexico</Country><Tel>011523292268333</Tel><Fax>011523292268333</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo><CheckInTime>15</CheckInTime><CheckOutTime>11</CheckOutTime></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>null</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>W Punta de Mita is nestled in a captivating setting on one of the world's most alluring beaches, along Banderas Bay on Mexico's Pacific coast. Surrounded by white sands, pristine waters and lush tropical flora, the resort's ambience is as extraordinary as it is comfortable</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PropertyInformation</Type><Text>null</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DiningFacilities</Type><Text>Spice Market Beach - Bask in Spice Market Beach's casually exotic setting that reflects our tropical region. Influenced by the street food that Chef Jean-Georges Vongerichten enjoyed in Southeast Asia, light shareable dishes are complemented by handcrafted cocktails. mesa1 - Privately situated as an island in a water feature, mesa1 is exclusively available via reservation for up to 18 of your nearest and dearest. Indulge in a seven-course tasting menu by a personal chef who will design the perfect epicurean journey. Living Room - Meet, greet, flirt and play in the Living Room. Sip a great variety of authentic signature cocktails as you lose yourself in chill vibes and hot beats, from progressive house to scintillating live DJ mix. Venazu - Feast on Venazu's authentic, delectable Mexican cuisine inspired by street food. Our all-day dining restaurant fosters a convivial, unpretentious atmosphere with a colorful ambience and sweeping ocean views from the outdoor terrace. WET  Deck - Relax poolside at our Huichol-esque WET Deck with ceviche, a signature mojito or another curated cocktail prepared by an extraordinary mixologist. Bask under the sun amid a DJ's beats, or live large in a cabana with Whatever/Whenever  Service. Chevicheria - At Chevicheria, signature ceviche and craft beers are served from a converted 1950s Chevrolet 3800 truck. Vibrant Latin American recipes blend citrus and raw fish or seafood seasoned together.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>Short</Type><Text>null</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>