<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>120570150</Id><Name>Riad El Bacha</Name><Region><Id>17560</Id><Name>Fez</Name><CityId>17560</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>N 11 Rue Sidi Abderrahmane Lamlili</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Fes</City><State /><Zip>30200</Zip><Country>Morocco</Country><Tel>+212 535 762 554</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><CheckInTime>15</CheckInTime><CheckOutTime>11</CheckOutTime></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Guesthouse Riad El Bacha Fes
The riad has a total of 8 bedrooms (each one with a private bathroom) and it is only 2 minutes walk to the main square (taxi, bus, cars...)!
The communal areas include a living room, the patio and the roof terrace (2) whit amazing view of the old city, the borjs…


Trade with travelers
Visiting us will bring you in contact with a relaxed and peaceful lifestyle which western societies have lost long time ago. 
You first day in my place, you'll get a city map and all the information to visit the city,
You'll have an idea about all the service in the place and also the idea about our culture and food.
Calm and quiet, safe and it's near to the most important monument, restaurants, souks….(you don't need car to visit the old Medina or to see the monuments).
We will be alwyse in your front in case you need any help or assistant, to answer any question you may have or to book a hammam, a trip to the desert or a dinner in our main Riad.
You can also enjoy the large roof terrace which can be served lunch or dinner. 
Breakfast included 
Meal (lunch or dinner) available on request.
Airport pick up service (20€ for 3pax) 
Train/bus station pick up service (10€ for 3 pax), is available on request.
We will be very happy about your visit, our goal is to make you feel at home, for have an unforgettable holiday in Morocco!
The neighborhood
Riad El Bacha is surrounded by the greatest monuments ( to within 3 min walk): the Zaouia of Moulay Idriss II , Karaouiyine mosque ( in the ninth century , the mosque became the first university in the world , before Oxford or Sorbonne) , the Madrasa el Attarine , the traditional tanneries ( Chouara ) , the Andalusian quarter of the medina , the place Seffarine , the Dar Batha museum, henna souk and shopping souk.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>***Please kindly note that there is a city tax payable by guests directly to the hotel.***</Text></Description><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>