<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>12053401</Id><Name>Sheraton Oran Hotel and Towers</Name><Region><Id>5233712</Id><Name>Oran</Name><CityId>5233712</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Boulevard 19 Mars</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Oran</City><State /><Zip>31025</Zip><Country>Algeria</Country><Tel>213 - 41 - 590100</Tel><Fax>+213 (41) 590101</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>5</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>35.7154</Latitude><Longitude>-0.609</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Centrally located in Oran, Sheraton Oran Hotel is convenient to Cathedrale de Sacre Coeur and Dar el-Bahia.  This 5-star hotel is within close proximity of Le Theatre and Place du 1er Novembre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 321 air-conditioned rooms featuring fireplaces. Satellite programming and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, with wired and wireless Internet access available for a surcharge. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature jetted bathtubs and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take time to pamper yourself with a visit to the full-service spa. You're sure to appreciate the recreational amenities, including a nightclub, a health club, and an outdoor pool. Additional features at this Art Deco hotel include wireless Internet access (surcharge), gift shops/newsstands, and a hair salon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite at one of the hotel's 5 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Thirsty? Quench your thirst at a bar/lounge, a poolside bar, or a swim-up bar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include high-speed (wired) Internet access (surcharge), a business center, and complimentary newspapers in the lobby. Planning an event in Oran? This hotel has 20860 square feet (1938 square meters) of space consisting of conference space and meeting rooms. A roundtrip airport shuttle is complimentary at scheduled times.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 3 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite at one of the hotel's 5 restaurants, or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. Thirsty? Quench your thirst at a bar/lounge, a poolside bar, or a swim-up bar. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take time to pamper yourself with a visit to the full-service spa. You're sure to appreciate the recreational amenities, including a nightclub, a health club, and an outdoor pool. Additional features at this Art Deco hotel include wireless Internet access (surcharge), gift shops/newsstands, and a hair salon. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 321 air-conditioned rooms featuring fireplaces. Satellite programming and DVD players are provided for your entertainment, with wired and wireless Internet access available for a surcharge. Private bathrooms with shower/tub combinations feature jetted bathtubs and complimentary toiletries. Conveniences include safes and desks, and housekeeping is provided daily.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Centrally located in Oran, Sheraton Oran Hotel is convenient to Cathedrale de Sacre Coeur and Dar el-Bahia.  This 5-star hotel is within close proximity of Le Theatre and Place du 1er Novembre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Cathedrale de Sacre Coeur - 3.9 km / 2.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dar el-Bahia - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Le Theatre - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place du 1er Novembre - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palais de la Culture - 4 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Demaeght Museum - 4.1 km / 2.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Great Synagogue of Oran - 4.2 km / 2.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stade Ahmed Zabana - 4.5 km / 2.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Santa Cruz Fort - 5.1 km / 3.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Sheraton Oran Hotel is Oran (ORN-Es Senia) - 10.7 km / 6.6 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TennisCourt</Code><Text>Tennis court</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>IndoorPool</Code><Text>Indoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>OutdoorPool</Code><Text>Outdoor swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Gym</Code><Text>Fitness room / Gym</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Spa</Code><Text>Spa</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SwimmingPool</Code><Text>Swimming pool</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WheelchairService</Code><Text>Wheelchair Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CurrencyExchangeService</Code><Text>Currency Exchange Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>FreeOnSiteCarparking</Code><Text>Free On - Site Car parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Doctoroncall</Code><Text>Doctor on call</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>NightClub</Code><Text>Night Club</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>50</Score><Description>Five star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>