<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>12053395</Id><Name>BEST WESTERN Hotel Colombe</Name><Region><Id>5233712</Id><Name>Oran</Name><CityId>5233712</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>06 Bd Zabour Larbi Hai Khaldia Ex Delmonte</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Oran</City><State /><Zip>31000</Zip><Country>Algeria</Country><Tel>+213 +213 41 46 61 62</Tel><Fax>+213 213 41 45 34 79</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo><Latitude>35.691</Latitude><Longitude>-0.6421</Longitude></GeneralInfo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Located in Oran, Best Western Hotel Colombe is in the historical district and convenient to Cathedrale de Sacre Coeur and Palais de la Culture.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Dar el-Bahia and Le Theatre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 23 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and free minibar items. Rooms have private furnished balconies. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while 55-cm flat-screen televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms have deep soaking bathtubs and designer toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Don’t miss out on recreational opportunities including a 24-hour health club and a 24-hour fitness center. Additional features at this Art Deco hotel include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a television in the lobby. Spending a day of fun is easy with the complimentary theme park shuttle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at a restaurant or in one of the 2 coffee shops/cafés. Or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Relax with a refreshing drink at one of the 2 bars/lounges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a business center, and limo/town car service. Planning an event in Oran? This hotel has facilities measuring 538 square feet (50 square meters), including meeting rooms. A cruise ship terminal shuttle is provided at no charge (available on request), and free valet parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed    Check-out time is 12:30 PM &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at a restaurant or in one of the 2 coffee shops/cafés. Or stay in and take advantage of the hotel's 24-hour room service. Relax with a refreshing drink at one of the 2 bars/lounges. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 18 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Don’t miss out on recreational opportunities including a 24-hour health club and a 24-hour fitness center. Additional features at this Art Deco hotel include complimentary wireless Internet access, concierge services, and a television in the lobby. Spending a day of fun is easy with the complimentary theme park shuttle. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 23 air-conditioned rooms featuring refrigerators and free minibar items. Rooms have private furnished balconies. Wired and wireless Internet access is complimentary, while 55-cm flat-screen televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment. Private bathrooms have deep soaking bathtubs and designer toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Located in Oran, Best Western Hotel Colombe is in the historical district and convenient to Cathedrale de Sacre Coeur and Palais de la Culture.  This 4-star hotel is within close proximity of Dar el-Bahia and Le Theatre. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Cathedrale de Sacre Coeur - 1 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;Palais de la Culture - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dar el-Bahia - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Le Theatre - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Place du 1er Novembre - 1.1 km / 0.7 mi &lt;br /&gt;Demaeght Museum - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Great Synagogue of Oran - 1.3 km / 0.8 mi &lt;br /&gt;Stade Ahmed Zabana - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Santa Cruz Fort - 2.4 km / 1.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Best Western Hotel Colombe is Oran (ORN-Es Senia) - 9.9 km / 6.1 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Spring Break check-in age is 18 years old. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirConditioning</Code><Text>Air conditioning</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MiniBarInRoom</Code><Text>Mini-bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HairDryer</Code><Text>Hair dryer</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>ConferenceRoom</Code><Text>Conference Room</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Playground</Code><Text>Playground</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Freenewspaper</Code><Text>Free Newspaper</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CurrencyExchangeService</Code><Text>Currency Exchange Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>24HourFrontDesk</Code><Text>24 Hour Front Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MultilingualStaff</Code><Text>Multilingual Staff</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Porters</Code><Text>Porters</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Doctoroncall</Code><Text>Doctor on call</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TeaCoffeeMaker</Code><Text>Tea / Coffee Maker</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>VIPSecurity</Code><Text>VIP Security</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>