<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>12057801</Id><Name>Dedeman Palandoken Ski lodge</Name><Region><Id>4942256</Id><Name>Erzurum</Name><CityId>4942256</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Palandoken Kayak Merkezi</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Erzurum</City><State /><Zip>25100</Zip><Country>Turkey</Country><Tel>442 317 05 00</Tel><Fax>442 317 05 04</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>3</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/ERZ-DEDhotel_Lobby_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>270</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/ERZ-DEDhotel_Lobby_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/ERZ-DEDhotel_Restaurant_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>270</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/ERZ-DEDhotel_Restaurant_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>LobbyRestaurantAndBar</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/ERZ-DEDhotel_Recreational_Facilities_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>270</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/ERZ-DEDhotel_Recreational_Facilities_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/ERZ-DEDhotel_Meeting_Room_1.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>270</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/ERZ-DEDhotel_Meeting_Room_1_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Photo><Url>/RXLImages/7/ERZ-DEDhotel_Recreational_Facilities_2.jpg</Url><Width>360</Width><Height>270</Height><Bytes>0</Bytes><Caption /><ThumbnailUrl>/RXLImages/7/ERZ-DEDhotel_Recreational_Facilities_2_thumb.jpg</ThumbnailUrl><ThumbnailWidth>80</ThumbnailWidth><ThumbnailHeight>60</ThumbnailHeight><ThumbnailBytes>0</ThumbnailBytes><PhotoType>OtherPhotos</PhotoType></Photo><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>Mount Palandoken is a wonder of nature rising next to the authentic charm of Erzurum, one of the biggest cities in Eastern Anatolia. Favored by snow-enthusiasts as well as lovers of winter scenery from all walks of life, the region is number one in Turkey when it comes to skiing. Palandoken is also becoming prominent around the world for its ideal snow quality. Turkey's longest ski runs, with varying degrees of difficulty, are also to be found at Palandoken. The Palandoken Ski Lodge is the idyllic place for an unforgettable winter holiday with a magnificent view of the mountains. Our hotel offers the best of Dedeman hospitality in a sophisticated environment in close proximity to the center of Erzurum and other points of natural beauty.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>Providing all the comforts of a fine ski-resort hotel, the Dedeman Palandoken Ski Lodge has 66 rooms available. The hotel is located 15 km from Erzurum Airport, 7 km's from the coach bus station and 6 km from the city center. The Dedeman Palandoken ski hotel in Turkey is the ideal accommodation in Palandoken for Erzurum holidays.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>RoomTypes</Type><Text>All rooms feature services and amenities including direct-dial telephone, mini-bar, electronic safety deposit box, electronic door-lock system, room service, kettle, free of charge wireless internet, LCD TV, satellite TV, hair dryer and smoke-fire detector. 
Superior Room - The Dedeman Palandoken Ski Lodge has 48 superior rooms with mountain-view; All of the superior 27 m2 rooms also have wall-to-wall carpets, bathrooms with bath-tubs.
Corner Room - The Dedeman Palandoken Ski Lodge has 4 Corner rooms with mountain-view; All of the Corner rooms also have wall-to-wall carpets, bathrooms with bath-tubs with 27m2 living space.
Deluxe Room - The Dedeman Palandoken Ski Hotel has 2 Deluxe rooms with a generous 42 m2 of living space and mountain-view; All of the Corner rooms also have wall-to-wall carpets, bathrooms with bath-tubs.
Junior Suite - Our hotel has 12 Junior suites with a stunning mountain-view, each composed of two separate rooms over a total 40 m2 space. One of these is designed as a lounge for your relaxation; the other is a luxurious bed-room with a large bed. These suites have work desks in addition to a sofa group.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>DiningFacilities</Type><Text>Somine Restaurant - Our A la carte restaurant with a rich menu of Turkish and world cuisine as well as special dishes, the Somine Restaurant accommodates 60 guests in a comfortable setting with live music on weekdays.
Gondol Cafe Restaurant - Meals are usually served in delightful open buffets at the Gondol Cafe Restaurant. Open every day between 08.00-22.00, the restaurant can accommodate 200 guests. 
Lobby - A cozy milieu with cafe and bar concepts at your service 24-hours a day.
Gondol Bar - This is the unrivaled watering-hole where our guests relax with live music after a day full of activity. Open for service between 20.00-00.00.</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>MeetingBanquetFacilities</Code><Text>Meeting / Banquet Facilities</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CurrencyExchangeService</Code><Text>Currency Exchange Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Doctoroncall</Code><Text>Doctor on call</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>30</Score><Description>Three star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>