<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>12062207</Id><Name>The Millennium Suites</Name><Region><Id>21303</Id><Name>Old City</Name><CityId>18846</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Akbiyik Street No:42 Sultanahmet</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Istanbul</City><State /><Zip>34122</Zip><Country>Turkey</Country><Tel>90 212 638 00 16</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Millennium Suites, you'll be centrally located in Istanbul, minutes from Mosaic Museum and Hagia Sophia. This 4-star hotel is close to Blue Mosque and Basilica Cistern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 7 air-conditioned rooms featuring free minibar items and LCD televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature rainfall showerheads and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and minibars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and babysitting/childcare. Additional features include tour/ticket assistance and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, where you can take in a garden view and dine alfresco (weather permitting). Or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include limo/town car service, a 24-hour front desk, and coffee/tea in the lobby. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available on request).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Pets not allowed  Check-in time starts at 1 PM  Check-out time is 11 AM &lt;br/&gt; Grab a bite to eat at the hotel's restaurant, where you can take in a garden view and dine alfresco (weather permitting). Or stay in and take advantage of 24-hour room service. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and babysitting/childcare. Additional features include tour/ticket assistance and discounted use of a nearby fitness facility. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 7 air-conditioned rooms featuring free minibar items and LCD televisions. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with showers feature rainfall showerheads and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as laptop-compatible safes and minibars.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Millennium Suites, you'll be centrally located in Istanbul, minutes from Mosaic Museum and Hagia Sophia. This 4-star hotel is close to Blue Mosque and Basilica Cistern. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Mosaic Museum - 0.2 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sultanahmet Square - 0.2 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hagia Sophia - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Fountain of Sultan Ahmed III - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Blue Mosque - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;The Million Stone - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Basilica Cistern - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Arasta Bazaar - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;German Fountain - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tomb of Sultan Ahmet I - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Le Arts Turcs - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Gulhane Park - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Sogukcesme Sokagi - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hagia Irene - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Serpentine Column - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Millennium Suites is Istanbul (IST-Ataturk Intl.) - 13.8 km / 8.6 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The name on the credit card used at check-in to pay for incidentals must be the primary name on the guestroom reservation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CurrencyExchangeService</Code><Text>Currency Exchange Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Doctoroncall</Code><Text>Doctor on call</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>