<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>12061987</Id><Name>Rose Garden Suites</Name><Region><Id>21303</Id><Name>Old City</Name><CityId>18846</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Kucuk Ayosofya Mahallesi Sehit Mehmet Pasa No. 11/13</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Istanbul</City><State /><Zip>34122</Zip><Country>Turkey</Country><Tel>+90 (212) 517 91 11</Tel><Fax>-</Fax><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;With a stay at Rose Garden Suites, you'll be centrally located in Istanbul, steps from Sokollu Mehmet Pasha Mosque and Little Hagia Sophia Bath. This 4-star hotel is close to Hippodrome and Blue Mosque.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 13 guestrooms featuring minibars. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature rainfall showerheads and designer toiletries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. This Art Deco hotel also features shopping on site, wedding services, and a television in the lobby. Guests can catch a ride on the shuttle (surcharge), which operates within 5 km.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Enjoy a meal at one of the hotel's dining establishments, which include 2 restaurants and a coffee shop/café. From your room, you can also access 24-hour room service. Mingle with other guests at a complimentary reception, held on select days. Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a beach bar. A complimentary buffet breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include complimentary high-speed (wired) Internet access, a 24-hour business center, and limo/town car service. A train station pick-up service is provided at no charge (available 24 hours), and free self parking is available onsite.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 1 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; Enjoy a meal at one of the hotel's dining establishments, which include 2 restaurants and a coffee shop/café. From your room, you can also access 24-hour room service. Mingle with other guests at a complimentary reception, held on select days. Relax with your favorite drink at a bar/lounge or a beach bar. A complimentary buffet breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take in the views from a garden and make use of amenities such as complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. This Art Deco hotel also features shopping on site, wedding services, and a television in the lobby. Guests can catch a ride on the shuttle (surcharge), which operates within 5 km. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 13 guestrooms featuring minibars. Your room comes with a pillowtop bed. Complimentary wired and wireless Internet access keeps you connected, and satellite programming provides entertainment. Private bathrooms with bathtubs or showers feature rainfall showerheads and designer toiletries.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>With a stay at Rose Garden Suites, you'll be centrally located in Istanbul, steps from Sokollu Mehmet Pasha Mosque and Little Hagia Sophia Bath. This 4-star hotel is close to Hippodrome and Blue Mosque. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Sokollu Mehmet Pasha Mosque - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Little Hagia Sophia Bath - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cardakli Bath - 0.1 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Little Hagia Sophia - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Hippodrome - 0.2 km / 0.1 mi &lt;br /&gt;Serpentine Column - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Turkish and Islamic Art Museum - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Esma Sultan Fountain - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Blue Mosque - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Arasta Bazaar - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Tomb of Sultan Ahmet I - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cemberlitas Bath - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Mosaic Museum - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Column of Constantine - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;German Fountain - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Rose Garden Suites is Istanbul (IST-Ataturk Intl.) - 13.1 km / 8.2 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed. &lt;br /&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>BusinessCenter</Code><Text>Business center</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>