<?xml version="1.0"?><HotelElement><Id>12063987</Id><Name>Taxim Suites Hotel</Name><Region><Id>21304</Id><Name>Taksim</Name><CityId>18846</CityId></Region><Type>Hotel</Type><Address><Address1>Cumhuriyet Caddesi No:31 Taksim</Address1><Address2 /><Address3 /><City>Istanbul</City><State /><Zip>34437</Zip><Country>Turkey</Country><Tel>90 212 254 7777</Tel><Fax /><Email /><Url /></Address><Stars>4</Stars><GeneralInfo /><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>General</Type><Text>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Property Location&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A stay at Taxim Suites places you in the heart of Istanbul, walking distance from Taksim Gezi Park and Taksim Square. This 4-star apartment is close to Topkapi Palace and Suleymaniye Mosque.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rooms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Make yourself at home in one of the 18 guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and stovetops. 26-inch LCD televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms have deep soaking bathtubs and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rec, Spa, Premium Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a 24-hour fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. Additional amenities include babysitting/childcare and tour/ticket assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Business, Other Amenities&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;Featured amenities include express check-in, express check-out, and dry cleaning/laundry services. A roundtrip airport shuttle is provided for a surcharge (available 24 hours).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Check-in time starts at 2 PM  Check-out time is noon &lt;br/&gt; A complimentary continental breakfast is served daily. &lt;br/&gt; Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt; Take advantage of recreation opportunities such as a 24-hour fitness center, or other amenities including complimentary wireless Internet access and concierge services. Additional amenities include babysitting/childcare and tour/ticket assistance. &lt;br /&gt; Make yourself at home in one of the 18 guestrooms, featuring kitchenettes with refrigerators and stovetops. 26-inch LCD televisions with satellite programming provide entertainment, while complimentary wireless Internet access keeps you connected. Private bathrooms have deep soaking bathtubs and hair dryers. Conveniences include phones, as well as safes and desks.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>SurroundingArea</Type><Text>A stay at Taxim Suites places you in the heart of Istanbul, walking distance from Taksim Gezi Park and Taksim Square. This 4-star apartment is close to Topkapi Palace and Suleymaniye Mosque. &lt;br/&gt; Distances are calculated in a straight line from the property's location to the point of interest or attraction, and may not reflect actual travel distance. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Distances are displayed to the nearest 0.1 mile and kilometer. &lt;p&gt;Taksim Gezi Park - 0.3 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Taksim Square - 0.4 km / 0.2 mi &lt;br /&gt;Taksim Republic Art Gallery - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Ataturk Cultural Center - 0.4 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Istiklal Avenue - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Akbank Culture and Arts Centre - 0.5 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Istanbul Technical University - 0.6 km / 0.3 mi &lt;br /&gt;Macka Park - 0.6 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;BJK Inonu Stadium - 0.7 km / 0.4 mi &lt;br /&gt;Cicek Pasaji - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Dogancay Museum - 0.8 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Military Museum - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Istanbul Lutfi Kirdar Convention and Exhibition Centre - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Istanbul Military Museum - 0.9 km / 0.5 mi &lt;br /&gt;Kabatas Pier - 0.9 km / 0.6 mi &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preferred airport for Taxim Suites is Istanbul (IST-Ataturk Intl.) - 15.6 km / 9.7 mi. &lt;/p&gt;</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>PoliciesDisclaimers</Type><Text>You must present a photo ID when checking in. Your credit card is charged at the time you book. Bed type and smoking preferences are not guaranteed.Your reservation is prepaid and is guaranteed for late arrival. The total charge includes all room charges and taxes, as well as fees for access and booking. Any incidental charges such as parking, phone calls, and room service will be handled directly between you and the property.</Text></Description><Description><Language>en</Language><Type>EssentialInfo</Type><Text>Extra-person charges may apply and vary depending on hotel policy. &lt;br /&gt;Government-issued photo identification and a credit card or cash deposit are required at check-in for incidental charges. &lt;br /&gt;Special requests are subject to availability upon check-in and may incur additional charges. Special requests cannot be guaranteed.  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No onsite parking is available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</Text></Description><Amenity><Code>NonSmokingRoom</Code><Text>Non smoking rooms</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Parking</Code><Text>Parking</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Safe</Code><Text>Safe</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>AirportTransportation</Code><Text>Airport transportation</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>RoomService</Code><Text>Room service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Bar</Code><Text>Bar</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Restaurant</Code><Text>Restaurant</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>LaundryService</Code><Text>Laundry service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Concierge</Code><Text>Concierge</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>SpecialSpaPackages</Code><Text>Special Spa Packages</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Babysitter</Code><Text>Babysitter</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>CurrencyExchangeService</Code><Text>Currency Exchange Service</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>WiFi</Code><Text>Wi-Fi</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>TourDesk</Code><Text>Tour Desk</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Elevators</Code><Text>Elevators</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>HighSpeedInternet</Code><Text>High Speed Internet</Text></Amenity><Amenity><Code>Doctoroncall</Code><Text>Doctor on call</Text></Amenity><Rating><System>Stars</System><Score>40</Score><Description>Four star</Description></Rating><Rank>1</Rank></HotelElement>